Watch any video online with Open-SUBTITLES
Free Browser extension: osdb.link/ext
Yumi's Cells 2
Episode 39: Laptop
First place is mine! Mine!
Oh yeah! First place! First place!
The unique sweetness is gone. It's no fun!
Writer Kim Yumi, are you going through a hard
time? This is like a funeral march dragging on.
Why did you make a sequel? Just
end it if you don't have anything to say.
I can't read this anymore. I'm leaving now.
What?
Oh yeah! First place!
The unique sweetness has disappeared.
Everything is malicious comments.
It's because it's so popular. There are
no malicious comments if it's not popular.
But still, there are too many malicious comments these days.
It's because the ending is almost near. They
must be worried that it won't be a happy ending.
Don't worry too much about it, Writer.
You're going to give them a good ending.
A good ending?
Our company's employees are all looking forward to it, too.
Since you're not giving them any hints, they're
all in suspense wondering what the ending will be.
What will the ending be? I'm curious about that,
too! Won't you let me know what the ending will be?!
Cooking cell told me to bring this to you so you can gain some strength.
Bye!
The ending is coming.
God Yumi! Let's have a legendary ending!!
Although you get the full support of everyone once you
become the top priority, it's not necessarily a good thing.
Oh, no. What should she do?
She has to end it well.
What should she do if it doesn't go well?
- What if Yumi can't give a good ending?
- Stop it!
They said they're looking forward to a good ending.
If it's not a good ending, won't Yumi be ostracized?
I said stop it, please!
This cell is always clinging on to the Prime Cell. Anxiety.
If this doesn't go well, it's all over! We
used all the down payment to buy the house.
We got a huge loan!
If things go badly, how will we pay back the loan?
What to do? What will we do? What will we do?!
I said stop it!
I'm so anxious that I can't write!
You'll send me the manuscript tomorrow
morning before the wedding, right?
Ah, I should.
Miss Writer, fighting! I'll see you at the ceremonial hall.
Yes, fighting!
Yumi was already pretty stressed because
she had to finish the manuscript for the sequel.
But the real incident occured the night before Yi Da's wedding.
Reason! Emergency, emergency!
- What is it?
- I don't see the laptop!
Look for it. It must be somewhere.
It's not there!
It's not in the place where she usually charges it?
No, it's not.
Then what about the table?
What about under the bed?
It's not there!
Maybe she put it in another bag before she left?
No!
Did it get mixed in with the recyclables?
I'm telling you it didn't!
It's not here. It's gone.
How much of the manuscript is in the laptop?
Including the episode that I'm going to
upload tomorrow, it's 60 chapters in 6 episodes.
That much?! You didn't make a backup?
She definitely left it somewhere outside before she came home.
What places did she visit today?
It's because the ending is almost near. They
must be worried that it won't be a happy ending.
There! She had the laptop up until then.
Yes, Miss Writer?
- Your laptop?
- Yes.
We were looking at my laptop together
this morning and talking about the comments.
That was my laptop, though.
You didn't take your laptop out.
Did you lose it? How?
Yes, well...
I should look for it. I'll find it.
You backed it up, right? As long as the manuscript is alright...
Oh, of course!
Yes.
She must have really lost it.
Let's not despair!
For now, she can just go buy a new laptop tomorrow and rewrite it all!
Rewrite it all? 60 pages?!
Don't you have the outline in your head?
In the end, Yumi couldn't find the
laptop up to the morning of the wedding.
What will she do now? Everyone from the
publishing company is going to the wedding.
What will she do? What to do? Come up with an excuse.
There's no manuscript to upload today,
and there's no manuscript to upload next week
either. Even if she writes, there are malicious comments.
What do we do? They won't leave—
I'm not being the prime cell anymore.
Bye, guys.
Don't look for me ever again!
Goodbye!
- Writer!
- Oh, no!
Writer abandoned her prime cell position and ran away.
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you.
Aigo, Writer Yumi! You made it?
Editor-in-Chief. Congratulations.
Thank you.
- Where's Yi Da?
- She's in the waiting room right now.
You finished by the deadline before you came, right?
- Yes.
- I'll read it after the ceremony.
I'm looking forward to the last chapter.
Yes.
Oh, yes. Excuse me.
- Congratulations.
- Oh, thank you.
The groom's side
Kim Yumi
Wow, Miss Yumi!
Oh, Bon Hui! Hello!
- It's been a long time. It's been so long!
- I know!
It's good to see you.
Wait, I heard that you're the one who set up the bride and groom.
They said that the groom is your editor-in-chief.
I didn't set them up.
Really? He was a loser this time, too?
Yeah. He was the worst of the worst.
It's not like I'm betting on who's worse.
- Hey, I really got angry and—
- Miss Writer.
Oh, Editor-in-Chief?
I saw you on my way to the publishing company.
Oh, I had plans with my friend, so...
I was just about to get up and leave anyway.
Yi Da, say hello. This is my
Editor-in-Chief. I talked about him a lot, right?
This is my former co-worker, Yi Da.
Hello, I'm Kang Yi Da.
Hello. I'm Ahn Dae Yong.
- You're the best!
- Pardon?
You're the person that chose our Yumi's work.
I always told Yumi that you've got a great eye..
You've really got an amazing eye for writers.
That's because Miss Writer's writing is—
You're the best! Really the best!
What is this? Who is that cute creature?
She said she's Kang Yi Da.
Let's save that. Kang Yi Da.
[Kang Yi Da]
Her name is Kang Yi Da.
Cute Best (Jjang) Yi Da.
The line is perfect, too!
- Hello!
- Hello.
Hello, I'm Ahn Dae Yong who greeted
you last time. You remember me, right?
Oh, this ahjusshi?
Yes, of course. Hello, how have you been?
I have a meeting nearby today.
If it's okay with you, shall we have lunch together?
Julie Literature Editor-in-Chief Ahn Dae Yong
Yes, that sounds good.
What's with this ahjusshi? It doesn't suit him to leave an emoticon.
He's cute.
I only introduced them to each other. I found out later
that they were dating each other without me knowing.
What's with that? Oh, you also set Ruby up with her boyfriend.
I also only introduced Ruby to him,
and they started dating on their own.
Then I should stick by you from now on if I'm going to get married.
Oh right! We're catching up and forgot we
haven't even given our congratulatory money yet.
I'm in charge of giving them the envelopes from the marketing team.
Yu Ba Bi
Team Leader Yu can't come, so he put me in charge of it.
Ah...
Do you know that he's going to an overseas branch?
- An overseas branch?
- Yes, he was assigned to Singapore.
He said he couldn't come because he's leaving
today. So he asked me to bring the envelopes.
What's this? This is ridiculous.
Writer Cell ran away, and Love isn't here.
Is there a cell village without a prime cell?
- Reason.
- Huh?
Is our Yumi really living well right now?
The wedding was broken off, and she's missing the deadline.
Hey, you can't be like that. Today is Yi Da's
wedding ceremony. Let's not ruin the mood.
I'm saying that I'm sad. Everyone else gets married so easily.
- Is there anything else?
- No, that's everything.
I just left. I'll call you when I get to the airport.
Okay.
Hello?
- This is the café at the Baekseok-dong intersection.
- Oh, yes.
Hello.
I'm calling the number that was left on the coupon.
Ah, yes. What is it?
She's a writer. I thought she would be looking for it.
Yes, that's right. She would be looking for it.
I'm glad that I had your phone number.
Yes, thank you.
She must be at the wedding right now.
Is it okay to head to the airport now?
Oh, yes.
No, wait! One moment. I've got to stop somewhere.
This is my first request.
More than anything else, please be considerate of each other.
In the passion absorbed by each other's charms, the other's strengths
make you happy...
Are they going to give us steak?
Or galbitang?
I want to eat steak.
- Oppa.
- Hm?
By the way, isn't that woman in the pink
dress pretty? The one on the bride's side?
- You're way prettier, Ruby.
- What are you saying? That's obvious.
Did I say something too obvious?
Hey.
Shh.
Let's listen courteously to the good words.
- Yes, sir.
- The husband has to love his wife
and the wife has to love her husband in order to become a true family.
Alright, everyone. Listen up!
Writer has run away.
We are in a bind. There is no place to retreat to.
Yumi couldn't meet the deadline today, and
she lost the manuscript for the next three weeks.
She doesn't even have any idea about her story's ending.
- Oh, no.
- What should she do?
All that she has left is a missed deadline, malicious comments,
and the interest on her loan.
So today's strategy...
the thirty-six strategy!
(Thirty-Six Strategems: "If all else fails, retreat.")
- Is that a strategy?
- Thirty-six?
As soon as the ceremony ends, Yumi will leave the ceremony hall,
turn her phone off, and go to Mom's house.
- What?
And she'll disappear!
Until when? Until Writer comes back and she comes up with a plan!
That's the only way that Writer Kim Yumi will live today!
What makes love complete isn't passion...
Oh, wait! It's Ba Bi. It's Ba Bi!
Love is...
Yumi. How are you?
You're probably attending the wedding right now.
I was contacted because you left your laptop at the cafe.
I came to get it so I could bring it to the wedding,
but I don't think I can make it because traffic is so backed up.
What time did you say your flight was?
I'm leaving for Singapore today, you see.
♫ Did you doze off last night again? ♫
♫ Are you standing at the end of your path? ♫
♫ Close your eyes and come into my arms ♫
♫ Everything is all right ♫
♫ I can't even express it in words ♫
So I'm sorry, Yumi,
but I left your laptop in the airport locker.
I was trying to help you, but I ended up inconveniencing you. I'm sorry.
♫ One day I'll hold you tightly in my arms ♫
You know that I'm always supporting Writer Kim Yumi, right?
Even if we've broken up, that won't change.
I hope you write good stories. Goodbye.
♫ I will become the moon just for you ♫
♫ So that you can breathe within me ♫
♫ Darkness and loneliness entirely ♫
♫ will cease to exist ♫
♫ Cause you're my star ♫
♫ No matter what kind of night falls, I will shine on you ♫
♫ so that you can fall asleep in the warmth of the moonlight ♫
♫ Cause you are my star ♫
♫ Cause you are my life ♫
♫ I'm just shining on your night ♫
♫ When I met you like a miracle ♫
♫ I got to know love ♫
♫ When you cry, everything ends for me ♫
♫ I'll give you all my light ♫
♫ I will become the moon just for you ♫
♫ So that you can breathe within me ♫
♫ Darkness and loneliness entirely ♫
♫ will cease to exist ♫
♫ Cause you're my star ♫
Yumi!
- Oh, Wung!
- My meeting ended late. The ceremony isn't over, right?
The ceremony is over. Everyone's eating. Go on and head inside.
Wait, where are you going?
To go find something.
- What?
- My laptop. I lost my laptop. Today's my deadline.
- See you later.
- Yumi. Yumi!
♫ Cause you are my life ♫
♫ I'm just shining on your night ♫
You can take my car...
Terminal 1
♫ I'm just shining on your night ♫
It's locker number 14. You know the passcode, right?
Will you end your locker usage and remove your items?
Yes. No.
Please wait a moment
Just a moment, please.
Thank you for your use. Please close the
door completely after removing your items.
Too much time has gone by. He's probably already on the plane.
Let's at least leave him a text message
so he can see it when he gets there.
Departures
I found the laptop. Things must have been hectic and busy.
Thank you for going out of your way.
Huindol Village Bus Stop
Ba Bi.
I...
All this time,
I've been thinking a lot.
I think I know what you're going to say.
I had a feeling.
I'm sorry.
By the time you see this, you'll be in Singapore, right?
I hope only good things happen for you there, too.
I'll also sincerely be rooting for you.
Oh?
What's this?
Yumi.
Oh.
I thought you got on the plane.
It was delayed. There was no announcement.
I think it happened so I can see you before I go.
Really?
I'm glad that I could see you and say goodbye in person before I left.
You saved me.
My entire manuscript was in here. Thank you.
When will you finish the book?
The end of the year? If it goes well, around Christmas.
Oh, I see.
Finish it well.
I want to, but I'm not skilled enough.
You'll do well.
What about a boyfriend?
Did you get a boyfriend?
- No. I don't have time to.
- Really?
Whats this?
Why is he smiling? What does that mean?
Ba Bi really
makes my heart flutter!
Hey, hey! Are you guys starting up again?
Is this the first or second time? Knock it off!
Ba Bi always speak sweetly.
We know, we know.
You?
- Me?
- Do you have a girlfriend?
I am seeing someone.
- What's this?
- Look at that. You heard him, right?
- Get a hold of yourself.
- I know. I said I know!
Did I say anything?
I see. I hope it goes well.
Team Leader Ba Bi.
We have to go in now.
Oh, really?
I'll head in.
Okay. Have a good trip.
Bye.
By the way, is that woman from earlier your girlfriend?
Oh, no.
For some reason, the mood seemed to be a bit...
She's my ex-girlfriend.
What about now?
It's been a while since we broke up.
Then why was she at the airport?
Things ended up that way coincidentally.
It was as if she was a girlfriend coming to see me off, right?
But, Team Leader. Why won't you go on any blind dates?
I've recommended several women, but you said you weren't going on any.
- Because I don't want to.
- Why?
Why are you smiling?
Why aren't you going on any?
I'm not sure.
I don't really know why, either.
Episode 40
The Return
Love disappeared one year ago on Christmas Eve.
♫ I didn't hear anything
The small light went out ♫
Dating, damn you!
This damned love affair! I'm telling you it's exasperating!
Love changed into the incarnation of rage.
Love.
Give the prime cell position to Writer.
♫ Ling Ling don't try to be understanding ♫
♫ Aside from minor quirks I am usually such a person ♫
The day that she got kicked out of her position as prime cell,
Love was banished to another dimension.
Even when we met Wung as if it were fate,
and when we got back together with Ba Bi,
she didn't come back.
Yumi, should we...
get married?
Let's get married.
Even when she was proposed to...
All that time...
I've been thinking about it a lot...
I think I know what you're going to say.
Even when we were breaking up, Love didn't come back.
- I'm better at that.
- Wait, why?
Of course, it's not like there was never
a time when her heart fluttered after that.
Writer Kim!
Ah, Oppa!
Mr. Yeon Il?
Oh, my friend said he wanted to greet you
before he left. Say hello, Yeon Il. This is Writer Yumi.
Hello.
Ah, hello.
I'm really enjoying My Love Muse.
Thank you.
- It's Love! Love is here!
- She said Love is here!
So she's finally back!
She sometimes wonders, "Is this possibly a romantic feeling?" But...
Me? I'm not Love, I'm Curiosity.
There are a lot of cases where it's not.
It's Curiosity. It's Curiousity!
What is it? Why are you acting like that?
- You guys were all fooled.
- So annoying.
Romance
Customer,
here is the book you were looking for.
- Yes.
- Wow, he's handsome!
It must be real this time!
Love has really come back!
Handsome men are not guilty.
Where's Love?
It's not her.
It's not her!
It was Sensitivity.
- What the heck?
- Man, I'm pissed off.
Excuse me.
I think you dropped this.
Ah. Thank you.
Really, really, my heart just dropped.
Is it real this time? This time it's love!
Guys, that guy, isn't he so sexy?
I want to touch his arms just once.
Clean him up.
At first I could fool my feelings.
But these days Yumi can't be fooled.
Eonni. You were piercing a hole with your eyes at Z's friends.
Are you falling in love?
It's not like that.
That's suspicious.
- I told you that's not what it is.
Okay.
Will Love return this Christmas?
No.
This Christmas, these guys returned.
Fat
Fat Cells.
We have finally arrived on a new land.
This is the land we will be living from now on.
Leader!
Then where do we settle down at?
Let's go to the heart!
Heart! Heart!
No, let's go to the love handles!
Huh?
- The love handles?
- The love handles are safe.
If we go there then there is lesser chances to get kicked out.
On top of that, a lot of our Fat siblings already live there.
- Yay!
- Let's go!
Let's go!
To the paradise of happiness, the love handles!
- To the love handles!
- The love handles!
- Yay!
- Woo!
No, not that way guys. Come here.
It's not?
Why can't I figure this out?
Yumi is now trying to meet her deadline before the end of her novel.
♫ I also wouldn't know ♫
♫ my heart ♫
I just have to write five chapters.
Just five chapters.
♫ There's a me ♫
Why does it have to be five chapters?
♫ I don't know ♫
♫ Even if I walk slowly ♫
♫ My heart is running far away there ♫
Why is it so messy?
Reason, how about we clean the room before we write?
Wait, are you crazy?!
Why are you trying to do things you
don't normally do during her deadline?
Reason, I suddenly want to find out
which resorts Hollywood celebs go to.
I really want to know where.
Let's try looking it up.
Curiosity, why are you acting like this too?
♫ my heart is far away there ♫
♫ Even at night when everyone is asleep ♫
♫ It's racing wide awake ♫
When you get deadline syndrome,
everything except the deadline becomes interesting.
Where is this?
♫ There is a world I don't know ♫
♫ Even if I spend a day when nothing happens ♫
These hairs.
♫ Even I still don't know ♫
♫ It's running there far away ♫
♫ It shouldn't run so fast ♫
♫ Even if I knew I can't do anything with my heart ♫
This is so fun!
Shall I wash the blankets in the village, too?
Stop it!
I'm going crazy.
Why are the last five chapters so hard?
I'm even sleepy.
Hello?
Eonni, when are you done?
I don't know. I don't have a plan.
I think I'm going to be cancelled.
What do you mean, cancelled?
We all got a party together and are waiting for you!
A party?
We're waiting to congratulate you for finishing your novel.
First thing in the morning?
We're going to start now. It's planned for the fifth.
Hurry up and come.
Miss Writer, the side dishes and beer
here are seriously killer! Hurry up and come!
Eonni Yi Da said she's coming right after her honeymoon trip, too.
Are you going to sit in the corner of
your room writing alone on Christmas Eve?
Eonni, do you really want to live like that?
No.
So get dressed and hurry up.
A party?
That sounds good.
What?
I just thought of something.
If I make the ending happen at a year-end party...
Eonni, I can't hear you very well.
Ah, that's right! That's it!
They meet each other for the first time there.
Coincidentally, at the year-end party.
They can't talk to each other at all because the music is so loud.
What? What are you talking about?
Okay, I'm hanging up!
That's right.
♫ Are you paying attention to me? ♫
They met there for the first time.
♫ Or is it meaningless? ♫
♫ Do our eyes keep meeting? ♫
♫ Or were you just looking at something behind me? ♫
That day was Christmas Eve.
Yeon Jae ends up going to the year-end party thrown by her company,
and ends up meeting him as if it's fated.
♫ I'm going to continue to hide it ♫
♫ so you won't know how I feel ♫
But because the music is too loud,
she can't hear him when he tells her his name.
But he remembered Yeon Jae's name.
Like a miracle.
When her writer's block suddenly clears,
it's extremely thrilling.
It's none other than Endorphin Time.
Yeah!!!
Endorphin
Everyone, we're here!
- Yay!
- Woo!
Everybody shout!
Who are we?
En-dor-phin!
- Yay!
- Woo!
"I remember."
♫ Oh, I want to hear your heart ♫
The End
Enter
The end.
Send
Your mail has been sent successfully.
[I've submitted the manuscript ^^]
It's over!
It's done!!!
It's been a year since she became a writer. During
that time, Yumi wrote two novels, My Love Muse
and it's sequel.
It's so refreshing.
Kim Yumi, you worked hard.
- Good job, Yumi.
- You worked hard, Yumi.
You worked hard, Yumi!
You worked hard, Yumi.
The cell village is also busy at the end of the year.
After the Endorphin concert, there's a year-end awards ceremony.
It's a beautiful night.
Yumi Awards
All right, then. I'll announce this year's award winners.
End of the year closing.
The Most Improved Cell Award for Yumi's
cells that showed the most growth this year.
It can't be any other cell but me. Why are you acting
as if you don't know when you do? So embarrassing.
The Best Cell Award!
The winner is... The winner is...
Let's go to commercials.
Here?!
My Love Muse 2! Currently a best-seller!
Yumi Awards
Best Cell Award
Sensitivity - Writer - Flowy
The winner is...
Ba Bi's cells!
Yumi Awards-The Best Cell Award
Babi's cells
- Huh?
- What?
I can't believe this, seriously!
As Babi's cells are currently employed overseas,
they can't attend the award ceremony,
so I will accept in their—
- Hey!
I'm the one who made Yumi a writer!
And I made the first and second books a success!
You should be giving that award to me!
What kind of bulls**t is this!
Let me go!
Writer, calm down.
You are the one who wrote the books,
but Ba Bi was the one who saved you.
What? Ba Bi saved me?
That's why I'm asking. Do you want to write for us?
I think you'll do a good job.
The first one to recognize our talent was Ba Bi.
The one who always supported us was also Ba Bi.
♫ My dear, ♫
The one who even found our laptop in the end was Ba Bi, too.
Writer Cell
If Ba Bi hadn't believed in you, you
probably would have already been buried here.
Do you admit it?
I admit it.
♫ I will take it to you ♫
♫ and open your door ♫
Thanks to you, I was able to finish the novel safely.
Thank you.
Merry Christmas.
♫ I won't let you go ♫
♫ Both the next time and ♫
♫ the day after tomorrow, us ♫
Notebook
Recipient: Kim Yumi
Oh, right.
Once she finished the book, there was something she had to do first.
What is this?
Laptop
Hello.
Wung. Why did you send a laptop?
Oh! You saw?
I heard you lost yours. I thought you would need one right away.
It's your equipment.
No... Wung, I'm grateful...
But I found my laptop.
Oh, really? That's great.
So I will send this back.
That's okay. Just use it.
That's the newest model so it has the best specs.
No. Why would you buy me a laptop?
Why? I could give it as a gift.
So that you would write nice things.
No, this is really not right. I will send it back.
If you send it back then I will send you another one.
What?
And if you send it again then I will send one again and again.
Come on, what kind of stubbornness is that?
I have a call coming in.
Talk to you later.
Hello? Wung?
So she went to return it personally.
Hey, Yumi!
Aren't you Yumi?
Louis, it's been a long time.
Totally a long time.
What brings you here?
Come in.
I can wait in the lobby though.
What are you saying.
If ever I let you wait in the lobby
then Wung, that punk
no, I mean CEO Gu would kill me.
It's about time for the meeting to be
over so if you could just wait for a moment.
Yes.
Please be comfortable.
That... can I ask for your signature later?
Signature?
Yes. My girlfriend is a fan of your piece My Love Muse.
Yes.
Then I will bring you a paper later on.
- Please be comfortable.
- Yes.
How cool.
Gu Wung has really succeeded.
CEO Gu WUng.
Wait. I think I have seen this name a lot.
Storm Man. UlaUla.
My love muse
Walwal*
(To be quick.)
So much fun! Most fun in the world!
I keep on waiting for Monday!
The writer is so great! Hope she succeeds!
She keeps playing with her readers! Daebak!
- Kim Yumi is the best!
- Julie Publishing, give the writer a big payment for the manuscript!
My love muse is the best!
Writer Kim Yumi is the best!
That's right.
The nicknames that kept on posting praises every morning.
All this time, Wung was the one who posted those?
♫ Even if I don't extend my hand the feeling of warmth ♫
He didn't even miss once, for a year.
How could this be? I got so much strength from all those comments.
This is really so Wung.
Gu Wung! Gu Wung! Gu Wung!
Gu Wung! Gu Wung!
I have an emergent suggestion.
Let's add one more cell award for this year.
As a co-Yumi award!
♫ Like a star ♫
♫ while looking at me smile brightly ♫
♫ You who are so precious to me ♫
Hello, sir.
♫ Always by my side ♫
♫ Remain by my side ♫
Yumi!
Sir!
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Are you really okay?
I'm fine so you can go do your work.
Your slippers.
Thank you!
Are you really okay?
- I am totally fine.
Even if you have become the CEO, you haven't changed.
But what brings you here? I was so surprised to hear you came.
I came to bring the laptop.
I told you I won't take it back.
I also earn money well these days.
Also, I'm very thankful
so I can't accept this. I also have a conscience.
What are you so thankful for?
There's this thing.
I am really moved, Wung.
Let's eat lunch together. I will be done in thirty minutes.
I need to go.
Where?
- I just dropped by because it was on my way.
I will get going.
Can't I go too?
It's a gathering for the publisher.
I know Control Z too.
Later. Let's eat together.
It's my treat.
Why?
- Because I'm thankful.
Merry Christmas, Wung.
Merry Christmas.
♫ Always by your side ♫
♫ Stay by my side ♫
Good news.
I'm having a tropical Christmas. Merry Christmas.
Even though a breakup is the end for love
I realized these days that a breakup does
not mean the end to a connection to someone.
Yumi!
What?
♫ I only wanna be with you everyday ♫
Congrats on completing your manuscript! Hope "My Love
Muse" Season 2 is a big success. Wish you great success.
I'm so touched!
Congratulations!
♫ I wonder if you felt my pounding heart ♫
♫ Your exciting image ♫
Fill your glasses! Your glasses!
♫ makes me dream again ♫
Fill your glasses. All right!
Our publishing company worked so hard
this year! Especially our Writer Kim Yumi!
Thank you all so much.
To Writer Kim Yumi,
Cheers!
- Cheers!
This year's Christmas is okay.
Even though the dating cell died.
But still, Merry Christmas!
♫ I want my feelings to be wholly delivered to you ♫
♫ Awesome day if it becomes your day ♫
♫ so you can always smile ♫
♫ and clear your clouds away ♫
Eonni, sleep well tonight.
♫ Everyday ♫
Get home safe!
Merry Christmas, Writer-nim.
Merry Christmas!
♫ My heart which is racing uncontrollably ♫
♫ keeps rushing my footsteps ♫
♫ going toward you ♫
So pretty.
♫ I think of them all day if I was wrong ♫
Is it because of the alcohol?
Strangely it's a sleepless night.
Reason.
Who is it? Is it hunger?
It's me, sensitivity.
Suddenly I want to sing a song.
In the middle of the night?
Sleep, sleep --
Why do you want to sing all of a sudden?
I don't know. I just feel like it.
Why?
It's Christmas Eve.
I want to sing then sleep.
Here.
♪ The day starts as if being shoved ♪
♪ I spend the day constantly acting fearless and before I know it
♪ the night arrives ♪
♪ The dark night ♪
♪ The sadness which I've endured all day ♪
Who's there?
Who are you?!
It's me.
Who is "me"?
(Also means "Who am I?"
You are Reason.
I am asking them, not me.
It's me, Love.
Hi, guys.
Love!
When did you come back?
A few days ago.
A few days ago?
I don't exactly know whether it was a few days or today?
Because I was suddenly sucked in.
Where am I?
When I opened my eyes, I was back.
I'm late because I had to walk back from the desert.
I couldn't fly because I'm not the prime cell.
Anyway, it's good to see you, even though I don't know how you got back.
I missed you.
Love!
I missed you guys too!
Love came back on Christmas Eve.
She came back after a year.
I don't how she was able to come back.
Was it because of Ba Bi?
Merry Christmas!
Or was it because of Wung?
Let's go!
Merry is celebrating Christmas!
Hurry, come in.
Come in. It's fine, it's fine.
Come here.
Writer, these are the people who will
be working at our publishing company.
I brought them to introduce you.
Hello!
Nice to meet you! Nice to meet you!
When Miss Mi Yeon goes on maternity leave,
you will be working with this guy right here starting next year.
Sorry?
- I said he is the one who will be responsible for you starting next year.
- Yes? Oh!
Hello!
Let's do our best, fighting!
Let's do it!
Or was there another reason?
♫ The day starts ♫
Love is here?
Love?
♫ as if being shoved ♫
- Hey!
- Love!
Love!
You guys!
♫ I spend the day constantly ♫
Whatever the reason, it's good.
♫ Acting fearless ♫
Love returned and Yumi was ready to be
happier.
♫ The dark night ♫
♫ The sadness ♫
♫ which I've endured all day ♫
♫ arrives like a routine ♫
- Wow.
- Yes!
Here, grab my hand.
Love, sit here.
♫ I hide in the middle of nowhere ♫
Thanks.
♫ Pathetically with a thud landing on the floor ♫
It's nice.
♫ I am crying ♫
Wow, it looks like cotton candy.
Would that taste good, too? ♫ Today, too ♫
We can't miss
a moment like this.
Yumi! Aren't you happy?
♫ Dark feelings will be passed tonight ♫
- It's pretty.
- It's really pretty.
I want to
have a snowball fight.
It's even better looking at it from up high.
Look at that!
♫ ♫
♫ I'm going tonight to the shining place ♫
♫ We are going to the shining place ♫
My stomach hurts.
Did I drink too much?
Unknown: Writer, did you get home safely yesterday?
Unknown?
Who is it?
Unknown: Writer, did you get home safely yesterday?
Who could it be?
Oh, it must the publishing house employee.
I don't have his number.
Yes, I got home all right.
But I'm sorry because I drank a lot yesterday, I don't really remember
who you are.
I see. I introduced myself to you yesterday.
I will be working with you starting next year when
Team Leader Mi Hyeon takes her maternity leave.
Oh, that's right.
He did introduce himself.
What was his name?
My name is Sin Sun Rok.
Yumi Film End Scene
Kim Go Eun as Kim Yumi
♫ In so many thoughts we ♫
Park Jin Young as Yu Ba Bi
♫ Let's put behind us our weary hearts ♫
♫ and think about someone ♫
Ahn Bo Hyun as Gu Wung
♫ I uselessly took an interest ♫
♫ In the times ♫
♫ which I always spent the same way crying ♫
♫ ♫
♫ will we hang on? ♫
♫ Although I am a little scared ♫
♫ of this approaching day ♫
♫ If it happens will you say to me ♫
♫ "you did well" and "good job"? ♫
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today