ENJOY ALL VOD IN HIGH QUALITY @ 4KVOD.TV
GET LIVE TV,MOVIES,SHOWS IN ONE PACKAGE
FAMILY MOTTO
A HARMONIOUS FAMILY WITH LOVE
EUN-HEE
Eun-hee.
I was curious about so many things.
I'm sorry.
I'm not really sure what family is.
Can I see that too, please?
Excuse me.
Can I…
get three of these, please?
So would that be one ring
and three necklaces?
Yes.
I'm sorry I couldn't tell you
about the biggest decision
in the 26 years of my life.
I think my family
will stop me if I tell them,
so I'm running away now.
I've been planning this for a long time,
but I'm not all that happy.
I thought it'd be freeing
to leave my family,
but if you explain it to my sisters
and comfort them,
I'm sure they will make
Mom and Dad understand.
I'm sorry,
Chan-hyuk.
Was I…
nothing to Ji-woo?
Am I just a family
he wants to escape from?
What's going to happen to my family?
We seriously knew…
nothing about each other.
Ji-woo is a grown-up.
He can leave anywhere if he wants.
Even if it's family,
if he wants to leave, then he can.
There's no use now.
I'm going to tell Eun-joo.
I won't…
keep secrets anymore.
We'll solve everything together now.
LOGIN
Eun-joo.
I guess he didn't want to
explain it to us.
I'm sure he couldn't even if he wanted to.
We had so many incidents recently.
He probably thought
we would be against it.
He's old enough to get married now.
We can't help but wait.
But…
something's bothering me.
How can he meet her
after sending her money first?
Stop thinking already.
Must you beat a person
who is having surgery tomorrow?
I'm old now.
I can't think of anything.
I can see it.
It's hard to see your path
but easy to see someone else's path.
Yes.
We are someone else.
No, that's not what I mean.
Right.
I didn't hide the fruit
so I could only give it to the kids.
The fruit that wasn't in the refrigerator
was for the elders at the nursing home
I volunteer at.
I always left them there
so they won't be mixed up with ours.
It must've been so ridiculous for you.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry too.
I knew that you got the wrong idea
and got angry because of the fruit.
But…
I didn't explain it on purpose.
When you got the wrong idea,
I felt great.
Yes.
"I hope you misunderstand that
I think it's a waste to give you fruit
and hate me."
I just let it be.
That's how we've been living our lives.
We didn't try to clear up
the misunderstandings.
After hearing you,
I now…
know why.
Why I collected sleeping pills.
It's because of those damn fruits?
That's not why.
I thought you'd see
the sleeping pills I collected someday.
"I'm always thinking of killing myself."
I wanted you to see them
and be filled with regret,
so I collected them,
without a desire to kill myself.
To break your heart.
Mr. Kim Sang-sik, it's time
to move you to a different room.
Why all of a sudden?
No way.
He's so strict about money.
I'm sure he won't be conned.
I don't think he's strict about money.
It seemed like he treats
his friends quite a lot.
Was he a cheapskate only to us?
Did you know about this?
How should I know?
I'm sure I don't know Ji-woo
as much as you do, Chan-hyuk.
The problems in our family
are like forgotten boxes
piled up in storage.
Then the door was opened,
and the baggage started
falling out all at once.
Is there…
another problem?
TAE-HYUNG
Hey.
Tae-hyung.
What brings you here?
Isn't fasting hard?
Skipping a meal or two isn't a big deal.
Are you the one who moved me to this room?
I'm okay with sharing a room
with the others in a big, crowded room.
I thought it'd be hard for your wife.
That's true.
The son-in-law truly cares
for his mother-in-law.
You must be happy.
How did you know?
It seems like my mother
saw you at the hospital.
So she knew,
but she acted like she didn't.
Why didn't you tell Eun-joo?
None of your business.
I was going to tell her after the surgery.
They will all be here soon.
If Eun-joo finds out about this,
she will suffer even more.
You used to love your son-in-law.
Your mother-in-law is not herself
these days because I'm sick.
Why do you think
Mom and Dad didn't tell us?
When Mom heard about my divorce,
she blamed herself, saying
the graduation from marriage
caused the divorce.
Nonsense.
Then will they not tell us
if something happens
because it may burden us?
We would eventually find out,
so what's the point of making it harder?
We have to tell them
to tell us everything.
The location of the tumor is bad,
so there's a high chance
of having an after-effect.
He can lose his memories again too.
His vision may decrease,
or he may suffer from paralysis.
I'm sure they heard the explanation.
We have to go see them,
so don't cry too much.
Does my face look okay?
Mom, Dad, what is this?
That scared me, seriously.
It's okay.
You should've told us if you were sick.
Where's Ji-woo?
The mood will lighten up
when Ji-woo is here.
Is he busy?
He wasn't home yesterday,
so I called him but didn't answer
He calls back right away
when he misses a call.
Ji-woo
went on a business trip.
When?
He left urgently. Urgently.
To where?
Well…
Where was it again?
He went overseas.
He went on a business trip overseas?
He's all grown-up now.
Then don't tell him.
He'll find out if he comes back,
so let him do his work.
He has a soft heart
and he loves his family too much,
so he'll rush home right away
without working.
Don't tell him.
Okay.
Don't worry.
Ms. Sook.
I'm afraid that I might
lose my memories again after the surgery,
and I'm afraid that I might not be able to
return this time.
You don't need to be scared.
Just forget about all the bad things
and fill yourself with good memories.
We'll go into the operating room.
DEPARTMENT: NEUROSURGERY
PATIENT'S NAME: KIM SANG-SIK
DURATION: 8 HOURS AND 41 MINUTES
OPERATING CENTER
The surgery went well.
The location of the tumor was unideal,
so it took a long time.
We tried the best we can.
Let's keep an eye on his recovery.
Now everything depends on the patient.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
It went well.
It went well. That's a relief, right?
Mr. Sang-sik.
-Dad.
-Mr. Sang-sik.
Mr. Sang-sik!
-Code Blue for Mr. Kim Sang-sik.
-Mr. Sang-sik!
-Dad!
Dad!
Mr. Kim's family,
-please step out.
-Mom.
Mom.
You're like a rock.
You can't lose to something like this.
When I was wandering
without a place to settle,
my first child gave me
my first family photo
and called me father.
My second child is as heartwarming
as the spring sun and smiles brightly.
My youngest child makes
my heart mellow every time I see him.
And the strongest
and loneliest person in the world.
My wife.
Mr. Sang-sik.
Are you okay?
Can you see us?
Dad must be awake, right?
Don't worry, Mom.
Yes.
They're my family…
whom I love.
He regained his consciousness,
so he needs to rest.
Please come again later.
-Let's go.
-Okay.
No particular aftereffect was found.
We have to wait
for the checkup results to see
if the tumor is malignant or benign.
Don't worry too much and get some rest.
Is he okay?
Yes.
He recognized all of us,
and that Ji-woo was missing.
Ji-woo…
hasn't called yet, right?
No.
I came because I was worried.
You should go now.
Stay with me…
for a moment.
I feel relaxed.
I hide my facial expressions
and I'm careful with my words
even to my family,
but with you…
I don't feel like that at all.
It feels like I'm resting.
I was worried if I came,
I would just be another nuisance,
but I'm glad I came.
Dad…
came to see me
after I miscarried.
Dad.
Don't you have work today?
I have to go to work now.
You should've come home
for a short moment at least.
Why are you here?
No, it's okay.
I've been working for days,
couldn't wash up,
and went hiking from time
to time, so I'm filthy.
-How's your condition?
-I'm fine.
Get some rest.
It'd be better to just quit working
and take time off.
I have work for the second half.
I'll take care of it.
These are…
wild pine mushrooms found
by a true wild ginseng digger
who climbs the mountains
a few times a day.
These are really good for you.
And you eat them all by yourself.
Can you smell them?
-Dad…
-Go inside.
I have to go.
Go inside.
If it was Eun-hee,
she would've thanked him,
hugged him right away,
and taken him home
to make him see her eating it.
But I didn't say anything.
When Dad couldn't wake up…
that was the first thing I thought of.
THIS ACCOUNT IS PRIVATE
CEO.
Ji-woo's first love disappeared.
She changed her account.
This is a fraud.
INTERNATIONAL CALL
Hi.
I'm sure you won't have an opening party.
I came in to see if you need anything,
but it's empty.
I'm about to start.
It seems small, doesn't it?
At first, I thought so too.
But when the desk and the items came in,
it was actually pretty big.
Are you sure you don't need anything?
A gift from a colleague
and a fellow tenant.
Hey.
Really? Okay.
-Chief Yoo.
-Yes, Chief Kim.
I don't think I can wait for the shipment
because of my family matter,
so please open the door
when the furniture comes.
Yes, of course.
I have tons of work these days,
so I can wait for 24 hours too.
Don't worry.
Who was it that made you
answer the phone outside?
A friend.
Ji-woo's father had surgery.
-Surgery?
-Ji-woo, who's out of reach
is on a fake business trip
when his father had surgery.
How long do you think this lie will last?
He has no money for a return ticket.
And he said he's too sorry to call you.
Let's send him money first.
Don't tell him about the surgery.
Tell him to come back right away.
-Can you lift your arm, please?
-Your father
won't even know that the one
taking care of him isn't his son-in-law,
but an enemy who's even worse
than a stranger, right?
Mom.
You must be relieved now.
Your language is violent.
I'll tell him when he gets better.
No.
I'll tell him later.
Later.
Do we have to know everything
because we're family?
Sick people don't need
to know some things,
and only those who need to know
have to know.
That's coming from experience.
By the way, about Ji-woo…
He still hasn't called back?
He's coming.
I didn't tell him about Dad's surgery.
I'm going to tell him when he arrives.
That's coming from experience.
If he finds out that
his father had surgery while he was gone,
Ji-woo, who loves his family so much,
will be heartbroken.
Go inside and rest. Don't overdo it.
Why? What about the kids?
Let's go.
Mom, Dad.
Wait for me.
Please understand my mom.
Of course.
I understand.
By the way, why isn't Ji-woo coming?
Is something going on with him?
It's a family matter.
You need to stop.
Okay.
I'm leaving tomorrow.
Yes.
He said he ran into her in a game,
and I think he was tricked.
And he has no money
to book a return ticket,
so I think he got ripped off too.
I've been searching on social media
and checked it with the story
I heard from Ji-woo,
and it looks like he fell
for her suggestion to live quietly
by the lake while running
a kayak rental shop.
Kayak?
Did he like things like that?
I'm sorry. I should've taken
better care of him.
Why would a CEO take care of
a grown-up employee's privacy?
If you feel bad,
we feel even worse for doing this.
Still…
I'm sure he's having the hardest time.
And he must be disappointed in himself
for falling for it so easily, like a fool.
When he gets back to his senses
he would regret losing all the money,
and it might last for a long time.
Go home now, Seo-young.
I'll get going now.
I'll meet him first.
You stand behind me and buy time,
so Eun-joo can't see him.
If not, she'll crush Ji-woo
into pieces with her words,
and blow him away.
You seriously know less
about your family than I do.
I'll pretend to smash Ji-woo
as soon as I see his face.
Never mind. Damn it.
I might do that for real.
You bastard.
Hey, you…
I…
Why do you…
look like this?
Didn't you have any money?
Did you eat something?
I ate on the airplane.
Ji-woo, let's unpack your things first.
Mom.
Dad shouldn’t know
just yet, right?
We said you went on a business trip,
so tell them later
when you can actually laugh
when you recall today.
I'm so sorry.
Are you okay?
Yes.
-Much better than before.
-Okay.
Much better.
-And this side…
-This side too.
I can lift it quite high.
Hi.
Ji-woo.
Was the business trip hard?
You got so skinny.
No.
Dad, are you okay?
Are you allowed to stand up?
Yes.
Did you miss your youngest son?
Of course, I missed you so much.
Which country did you go to?
Canada.
It's quite far away.
That's awesome.
Canada is…
He packed all of his stuff
for a business trip?
How meticulous.
He makes himself up so much.
Who does he take after?
He looks at the mirror
longer than his sisters do.
Eun-hee.
I would've left by the time
you read this letter.
I didn't want to live like Dad.
I want to live freely
without being tied down by my family.
Mom, you must've been tired.
You must be tired. Go home and rest.
It's okay.
Mom, I'll stay here now. Go home and rest.
Yes.
You should go home and rest.
No, thanks.
I have to stay next to your dad.
Eun-hee,
by the time you’re reading this letter,
I'll have started a new life
in an unfamiliar country.
I'm not confident to live like Dad.
I want to live a life in which
I don't have to achieve anything.
I want to just live my life
floating on a kayak
here and there, without doing anything.
I believe you'll explain
my feelings to Mom and Eun-joo
and be on my side.
I want the three of you
to wear the same necklace.
When I settle down,
I'll invite all of you.
Let's meet again
with a smile on our faces.
Ji-woo…
His world must've crumbled.
-Are you okay?
-Yes, I'm okay.
Dad, why don't you walk back once more?
I think I can move well.
Dad, do it five seconds each. One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Five.
Now, the left foot again.
Left foot. Slowly.
-Slowly.
-I have to try and stay like this.
Right foot again.
Lower it.
Left foot.
Remember when my workload got reduced
and got injured working
at a construction site?
You looked after me day and night
during my long hospitalization.
Eun-joo was busy making
money instead of me,
and Eun-hee was busy looking
after Ji-woo and going to school.
The kids suffered a lot because of me.
At that time, we didn't say a word
to each other at the hospital.
But now, you listen to me
and the kids take turns to come to see me.
I feel so great.
What are you trying to say?
Look.
You're keen too.
I'm…
moving into a studio apartment
when I'm discharged.
Have you heard of a studio apartment?
It has a television, a refrigerator,
and a washing machine in it.
I just need to move in.
They deliver breakfast
and do the laundry too.
There are lots of idiots
in the world who are like me.
Good grief.
At that time…
I didn't look after you with all my heart.
You were a truck driver,
but you suddenly worked
at a construction site and made a mess.
The insurance couldn't cover it either,
so our two daughters
were suffering so much,
trying to make money.
I cursed you a lot in my mind.
I'm sorry.
I didn't bring it out
to make you feel sorry.
I'm just saying that this is the happiest.
I know that
at the time…
when you were not well,
you lived like a sinner.
I know.
I'm a sinner.
I was a sinner.
I'm so sorry to Eun-joo and Eun-hee
and my heart breaks.
That's the right thing.
Both of us now
should stop being scared of our kids
and stop thinking about them.
Let's decide
after you get discharged
and recover at home.
We only have…
each other now.
You're saying such romantic words,
so you should smile.
Why did you come all the way here?
You said you have no time for me.
Then I should try hard
to make time for you.
How's Ji-woo?
He doesn't talk.
I'm angry too,
but I'm holding it back
since he feels worse.
He said I'm like his brother,
and he just left like that?
Once he recovers,
that little brat is dead.
Let's teach him a lesson together.
Let him be for now.
He's having a hard time.
I can hardly remember the last time
he smiled so innocently.
I wanted Ji-woo
to live his life with optimism
without getting heartbroken,
and I thought
I can make him live like that, at least.
This is what's disgusting about family.
Who do you think you are to keep him
from being heartbroken or whatever?
Yes, you're right, you jerk.
But…
Seriously.
I saw
his heartbroken face for the first time
and my heart broke.
Just what's the deal about being a family?
Isn't it obvious?
You hurt each other more than anyone else,
and when you get hurt from somewhere else,
they comfort you. That's what family is.
Don't let your parents know for now.
I'm so disappointed by the thought of me
being nothing to Ji-woo.
So if your parents find out,
they'll be super disappointed.
We need to
see each other every day now.
Okay.
Wow, look at the menu.
Don’t you think this is a betrayal?
Then did you think
I'd be drinking wine and eating ramen
with the trauma of divorce?
I heard you have malnutrition and anemia,
so I bought these.
They are a matching set.
Ji-woo, who ran away
after giving us one heck of a time,
gave us a matching set of necklaces.
It's not my style.
Both you and I don't
want any popping hearts.
There's one for Mom too.
So the three of us got popping hearts.
What about the letter?
I'm sure he didn't just give us necklaces.
It didn't say much.
Stop keeping it quiet
and covering things up.
Tell me. So we can find out
what he was thinking.
Eun-hee.
The necklace.
First love or kayak or whatever.
Let's not mention those
in front of Ji-woo,
even as a joke.
You think I'm some kind of a…
I have enough sense to know that much.
He only looks sparkly on the outside.
I think he was mentally exhausted
at his age.
That's how I was at that time.
At least we must teach him a lesson
that the dream of doing nothing
is utterly ridiculous.
Yes, crush him into pieces.
Oh.
Tae-hyung said to take the medicine.
Here.
Are you going to keep
calling him Tae-hyung?
Then should I suddenly call him
Mr. Tae-hyung,
Dr. Yoon,
Mr. Yoon, and so on?
It's a trace of being a family.
I'll try and change it slowly.
Here.
I made up my mind.
I'm going to meet
my biological father.
Are you going to the office?
Your desk and furniture all came.
You didn't bring your car, did you?
You know…
A call from Mom.
MOM
Gosh.
I got a call.
-Mom, you're on speaker.
-Min.
Do you know how to see
males and females in chicks?
Mom, I'm a patent attorney.
I think you need a gender attorney.
Right. A patent attorney, yes.
Hey, because you're so busy,
I thought you knew how to do this too.
Mom, you're on speaker right now,
-so I'll call…
-Right, Min.
Your stir-fried red pepper paste
was awful.
It's too sweet. I told you I'd do it.
Mom, that's blackberry jam.
Hey, is that true?
Hey, oh, I need to try it again.
Mom, you're on speaker,
-so I'll call you back…
-Honey, this is…
Not yet! Don’t mix it with the rice!
It's not red pepper paste.
It's blackberry jam.
Anyway, it's something sweet.
Anyway, I'm hanging up, okay.
My mother doesn't know
what a patent attorney does just yet.
Well, but…
She doesn't need to know, right?
She loves me the most in the entire world.
How do you like the desk placement?
Yes, it'd be fine like that.
You saw it well.
You see…
It's the East and West,
and do you see
the tall buildings back there?
It's a small difference,
but it affects the lighting.
The size of the window is a bit off, but…
So what I mean is,
putting the desk here
would be the most stable.
That's what I mean.
Okay. I won't move it.
By the way…
These flower pots are…
They're my office opening gifts.
These plants are NASA-approved
to purify the air.
This guy is a banyan tree. Ivy. Dracaena.
Don't they have lovely names?
When you get new furniture
and paper the walls,
you need to ventilate well.
You know, there's this thing
called sick house syndrome…
Why are you laughing?
You can only think of
my mom's laughter when I talk, right?
I told Mom that she was on speaker but…
Patent Attorney Yoo Min-woo.
Congratulations. Cheer up. Be successful.
Hello.
Are you preparing
for independent publishing?
Yes, I am.
Hi.
LEARNING ABOUT INDEPENDENT PUBLISHING
Hi, everyone. This is Mr. Im Geon-joo,
who will give us a lecture
on independent publishing.
Give him a round of applause.
Hello.
What do you think
was the most disappointing
when I started working this job?
Low payment.
Low income!
That's right.
"Those who overcame
such a low income write books
and translate them too."
"I didn’t know that, and I've been
reading books too easily."
I had to repent.
I'm sure all of you have thought of this.
You might've thought of quitting
but never ended up doing so.
And then your thoughts
reached independent publishing.
I wish you the best in your work.
-Thank you.
-Okay.
Thank you.
Eun-hee, I uncovered your plan.
So your dream is independent publishing?
No.
This is…
a long-term plan.
I'm going to think about it
after I learn a lot more.
I still have a long way to go.
Then do you want to go to the US?
CHAN-PAL
The look on your face is saying,
"You're so disgustingly persistent."
Right?
Jeez, come on.
I'm just suggesting it
because you can apply
for an education program
before you quit work.
I'm going to stay here.
Did you think
I was asking you to go with me?
Are you going to stay here?
I planned to do so from the beginning.
Eun-hee.
I think I can tell you
about the week I spent with Ha-ra.
Breaking up wasn't just
about me wrapping things up.
Things we've been ignoring for years.
Things we couldn't say for a while.
We did all of them.
I packed her things
so she could go back to the US
and helped her clean up.
You don't need to be that specific.
I'm saying this
so you don't blame yourself
thinking that you met someone horrible.
I would never blame myself.
Good.
I think I'll do better
when I meet my new love.
I'm sure you will too.
I guess so.
I'll get going then.
MISSED CALL
CHAN-PAL
Hey.
The lecture ended just now.
Really? I'm on my way there.
Really?
Wait for a bit.
You're here.
-Was the lecture good?
-Yes.
-Get in.
-Okay.
Seriously.
I think I'm a natural-born driver.
Are you scared?
No. You're doing great.
Go slowly and step on
the brake little by little.
Okay.
I knew it.
Stopping isn't easy in any form.
Hey, don't say cool things
for making a mistake.
Slowly.
Chan-hyuk.
Yes?
When I was dating Jong-pal,
I told small lies.
Why?
That bastard is narrow-minded.
My life was busy
with part-time jobs at the time.
So whenever I had free time,
he would say I'm doing something
without seeing him,
So when I went to see a show
or a movie I wanted to see,
I told him I was working.
Yes.
Whenever he went to take photos with me,
you always said you were working.
I promised myself…
that I would never lie
if I date anyone ever again.
So Mr. Playboy wasn't the one.
The whole beginning is a lie.
I think not telling a lie
sounds like a lie too.
Isn't that too overwhelming?
Just tell me sweet lies
and heartwarming lies at least.
I was at the lecture today,
and the lecturer was the vice CEO.
I'm going to the lectures
for three months.
Yes.
When I ignored your call earlier,
we had a private conversation too.
I'm not going to…
lie to you.
Are you sure about that?
"I will never lie when I date someone."
So you won't lie to me?
Yes. Think a bit more.
We have plenty of time.
Let's go.
I was worried that…
it may be super awkward…
and that…
I may feel nothing, but…
Let's…
give it a shot.
Yes.
Mr. Kim Sang-sik.
A rock can crack and break
as it rolls down,
so be a tree instead.
Our time of lush green leaves has passed,
so let's be two beautiful autumn trees
with falling leaves.
Ms. Sook…
wrote a poem.
Read the poems Ms. Sook wrote.
Send Ms. Sook on a trip to the U.S.
Buy a house with a yard.
Go to a theme park with the grandkids.
Take a family photo.
Go on a family trip.
Put 100 million won in my bank account.
Exercise.
Learn to play the harmonica.
Go to a Siberian chrysanthemum festival
with Ms. Sook.
Go trekking to the Himalayas.
Go camping with Ms. Sook.
Thank you.
Hello, ma'am.
I'm Chan-hyuk.
Yes.
You recognized me right away.
I recognize you too.
You haven't changed.
You're still wonderful.
That way, please.
Okay.
It's been so long, right?
Yes, this is my first time seeing you
since Eun-joo's wedding.
You gave Eun-joo's wedding photo
to me separately, right?
The one you gave Ji-woo.
I love that photo.
Thank you.
What am I saying
with someone busy like you?
I wanted to thank you
because you are the CEO
of Ji-woo's workplace,
but it was too difficult, so I couldn’t.
I've been seeing you
since I was in college.
It makes me sad if you say I'm difficult.
Please think of me as Eun-hee's friend
before Ji-woo's boss.
I thought it was rude
to set up this occasion.
I thank you for saying that.
I…
I want to be careful here,
so I asked you to see me.
Yes. Please feel free to ask me anything.
Did Ji-woo
really go on a business trip recently?
Aren't we supposed to
eat dinner with our kids?
Our kids are supposed to
come for my discharge.
You have to take medicine too.
You go ahead and eat first.
I told the kids to eat dinner
before they come.
Divorce?
Our eldest daughter has been…
so miserable.
Are you okay?
I was heartbroken.
Like you right now…
We can't do anything about it.
I trust our eldest daughter's choice.
We're always heartbroken
because of them,
but at the same time, we trust them.
Do you think…
our kids are the same?
Do you know
what Ji-woo did to us?
He wasn't on a business trip.
He…
he just left because he hated us.
He just left without a word.
Mom. How's Dad?
I'm here.
How's Dad?
Mom, I'm here.
Mom.
It's a gift.
It's the same one I gave my sisters.
Mom, I'll put it on for you.
No, thanks.
Follow me.
Mom, light the candles on the cake.
For Dad's return home.
Don't do that.
What is family?
What is family…
to you?
I'm asking because I really don't know.
You guys don't know either?
Or…
have you never thought about it?
When you…
cut ties with Eun-joo,
I was wondering, "What happened?"
"Is her heart filled with hard feelings?'
I was worried sick alone for years.
Did you know?
When you…
announced your divorce
without consulting me
about it,
I just accepted it.
And it's still breaking my heart.
Did you know?
You…
Do you…
Do you even know…
what you have done?
Mom…
Get out.
Your mom…
will have nothing to do with you anymore.
I'm going to make her.
What is…
family?
I…
We…
still…
don't know.
BUCKET LIST
Do you think the kids know?
Mom, I need to meet my biological father.
And your girl might be watching too.
I've always been on your side
since we were trainees.
I can smell romance from CEO.
I've never thought this
but today, I disliked my kids.
I…
want to leave.
Subtitle translation by: Hae-lim Lee
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/ah22r
Help other users to choose the best subtitles