Nick!
Look at me.
I'm gonna get our son back.
Don't move.
Come on.
It's okay.
This ain't over.
Noah's back.
He got special leave and decided
to surprise me for a few days.
I knew
that you were married.
Have you noticed anything
different about...
Julia and Baz lately?
Like what?
They've been hanging out
a lot...
without you.
I don't want you
to feel left out.
♪♪
Excuse me.
A-Are you Pope?
I'm Taylor's mom.
Thanks for coming.
You look good.
So do you.
I owe you an apology.
I judged you.
When what I should have done
was forgiven you.
♪♪
♪ She stares deeply ♪
♪ Locked inside me ♪
♪ Burnin' brightly ♪
♪ One they know
that I cannot take ♪
♪ Waitin' for it all to begin ♪
♪ Every night now, they'll win ♪
♪ Come and meet my black hole ♪
♪ Got a big black hole ♪
♪ I've got a big black hole ♪
♪ I've got a big black,
big black hole ♪
♪ Got a big black hole
inside of me ♪
♪ Got a ♪
♪♪
Yeah, it's that
fiber-optic shit. So?
So the county's going to
announce next week
that they're putting these
in every one of their buildings.
Schools, courthouses...
I work for the county. I ain't
heard nothing about that.
That's gonna be
a lot of cable.
Truckloads.
I don't know.
Hard to keep track
of it all.
You know how close
they watch that?
I know exactly
how close they watch it.
I'd give 'em a B-minus.
Come on.
Couple spools for every delivery
winds up on one of my trucks...
that's not a problem.
But then
you got to move it.
Oh, gosh. Where am I gonna find
contractors looking for a deal?
Push it.
Come on, Pope,
you got one more in you.
Baz, help him.
Are you gonna let it crush you,
or are you gonna crush it?
- Yeah! Whoo-hoo!
- Whoo-hoo!
Never a doubt.
See that, Deran?
That's how
winners are made.
Told you he had it.
♪♪
Hey,
what do you think, Pope?
Should we get Julia
on the bench next?
She's a girl.
Girls do aerobics.
You're a Neanderthal.
You know
what that means?
It's a subspecies of humans
that went extinct...
40,000 years ago.
Alright, smartass.
Hey,
you know you can't get
that Discovery Channel shit
past my boy.
♪♪
Come on.
You do this for two months,
you could build a garage
for your Firebird.
Loading dock 6.
Come in the south gate.
Will do.
Thanks, Reggie.
♪♪
What do you think?
What do you wanna do now?
Here?
♪♪
You get any sleep
last night?
No, I didn't.
Were you up all night staring
out the window, Mr. Night Watch?
How's Renn doing?
She alright?
She's handling it.
Alright.
Why don't you get out of here?
Go get some sleep.
Alright?
Yeah.
ENJOY ALL VOD IN HIGH QUALITY @ 4KVOD.TV
GET LIVE TV,MOVIES,SHOWS IN ONE PACKAGE
Everything okay?
Yeah.
Cool.
Uh, so you know how I had
something to run by you?
And you said
wait till tomorrow?
No, not really.
Well, I do.
I got a job.
Yeah?
Doing what?
No, man. A job.
For you.
With me.
It's a dentist's office.
Kind of a low-rent dentist,
but he just got in a box
of Dutch Lions.
What the hell
is a Dutch Lion?
Coins, silver.
Each one's worth
a couple hundred bucks.
Yeah, what is a dentist doing
with a bunch of silver coins?
He's a collector
or some shit,
but he keeps them in his office
in a filing cabinet.
Doesn't even have a safe.
And you know this how?
'Cause my cousin
Shawna's roommate
is his dental hygienist.
Your cousin Shawna's
roommate?
Dude,
I already scoped it.
It's a shitty little
cinder-block building
with cheap-ass security.
Child's play
for you, man.
Each coin's worth
a couple hundred bucks.
We're talking 30 or 40 grand
for 15 minutes' work.
What do you plan on doing
with the, uh, dentist?
What, are you gonna
knock him over the head
with his own drill?
Dude, he's on vacation
till tomorrow.
There's no one there.
We hit it today,
get back before happy hour.
Come on, man.
You know I work hard here.
You know
I'm a good worker.
But I can do more.
Let me do more.
Yeah,
you want to do more?
How about you finish
prepping the kitchen?
♪♪
Well?
I got nothing.
Sergeant Noah Dean,
right?
Does his job,
no complaints.
Any personal beefs?
Doesn't seem like
anybody thinks about him
one way or the other.
He's just there.
He's got a wife
named...Penny.
Works at
a lawyer's office.
Pretty vanilla.
Are there any problems
with the wife?
Is he cheating
on her or...
No sign of it.
Why you got such a hard-on
for this guy?
Let me know
if you want more info.
Should be easy to track.
He just got his PCS orders.
PCS orders?
Permanent Change of Station.
His unit's rotating out.
Dude's coming home.
♪♪
Okay.
We're gonna go and...
No.
Hey.
Hey, bud.
I thought you were
going to the gym.
Yeah, I was, but I, uh...
changed my mind.
I wanted to come hang out
with you two.
Oh, that's sweet.
You should put some ice
on that bruising.
Yeah, my abuela
gave me worse.
God damn it.
Hey, hey, let me...
let me... let me do it.
Alright.
Get these pants up.
Wow.
Hey.
Hmm?
We're gonna be fine.
Yeah, I know.
Want to go for a walk
or something later?
Yeah, I was gonna take, uh,
Nick to the zoo.
Oh, okay.
Well, he loves
the merry-go-round.
Don't you, bud?
Yeah.
Here you go.
♪♪
You can come with us,
if you'd like.
Yeah, I'd like that.
The ice maker
broke again.
I'll go grab some bags of ice
from the grocery store.
Here's last night's
receipts.
Where is it?
Dentist's office,
where is it?
El Centro.
Street to street?
Is there an alleyway?
Yep, alley.
Neighbors?
Uh, laundromat and a Goodwill
across the street.
What exactly would you
need me to do?
Just let me ride
with you.
Show me how to do it.
Yeah, alright.
That's fine.
Seriously?
Yeah.
Alright, thanks.
I got a piece out in my car.
No, you're not
gonna need it.
You get the wrong info,
we get caught, you know,
carrying a gun makes
the charges a lot worse.
Right.
Got it.
We're gonna need a third,
so I'm gonna call J.
Alright.
Okay.
♪♪
Hey.
How's your arm?
It's okay.
Been back to my house?
No. No, I wouldn't go
when you're not there.
I met your mom
yesterday.
My mom?
Yes, nice lady,
dark hair.
She looks like you.
If she's in town,
she's probably having
boyfriend troubles again.
Yeah, she was worried.
She's looking for you.
Yeah.
She's like that.
What's she do for a living,
your mom?
She runs a...
a dog-grooming business.
Aah!
Who is she?!
I don't know!
Aah! Aah!
She's a cop!
A cop!
I mean, okay, she...
I don't know.
She's a cop?!
I'm on probation!
She just...
She can violate me!
What department is she with?
I don't know, I swear.
It's... It's not Oceanside
is all I know!
What does she want?
Info.
What kind of info?
On you!
What kind of info?!
S-She wanted to know
how to get inside your house!
Aah!
And you helped her?!
I swear, please!
Please!
I can't get rid of this bitch!
I can't!
Okay, she doesn't do shit
the normal cop way!
Is she dirty?
I don't... I don't know.
She's just scary.
If she doesn't live in
Oceanside, where's she staying?
I don't know, I don't know.
I'm sorry, man.
Please, please.
You call her, you tell her
you want to meet.
What's up?
- Hey, thanks for coming.
- No problem.
I wanted to talk to you
about something, actually.
Uh, it's one of your buildings,
the eight-unit.
I think we should take it
off the market.
What? I thought you said
we needed to sell them all?
Yeah, but if we have too many
multi-family properties
on the market at one time,
it's gonna drive
all the prices down.
Okay. Yeah, fine.
That's fine.
Good. Um...
So, what'd you want
to talk about?
Tommy's got a job for us.
It's got to happen today.
Mark's out of town.
We need a third.
You just walked out of a mansion
with $300,000 in diamonds,
and now you want to roll
with your barback?
What the hell
is wrong with you?
It's gonna be the easiest job
we've ever pulled,
and... and we need to start
developing people, okay?
We need to have a network.
Smurf had a network, right?
How much are you
telling this guy?
Nothing he can't handle.
Look,
if we do this for him,
he's grateful,
which means he's loyal.
That's what we need.
We need loyal people.
It's like minor-league
smash-and-grab shit.
It's fun.
I kind of feel like having
some fun, don't you?
♪♪
Reverse.
Oh, what?
That's impossible.
Look at the card,
Barry.
Oh.
You did not
just call me Barry.
You didn't draw four,
so...
hop to it.
Oh, you two are
ganging up on me.
I'm gonna report this
to the Uno police.
Hey, baby,
I need your help.
Me? Why?
'Cause you got
a steady hand.
And attention to detail.
Come on.
Yeah. Go.
It's good what
she's teaching you.
And when you're done, we'll,
uh... we'll all catch a movie.
Okay.
Here we go, man,
back home.
Had a good time at
the monkey house, didn't we?
Alright, I'm gonna put him down
for his nap.
Right, buddy?
♪♪
Hey.
You alright?
Relax, you're home.
Alright?
♪♪
Come on.
Why can't you
just buy bullets?
These ones
are different.
They crumble on impact,
so they're not traceable.
You have to protect yourself,
Andrew, protect your family.
Not too much.
How many grains?
I don't know.
You just gotta know,
you know?
You should have a scale,
a digital one.
This is all guesswork.
Put it on the press.
How many of these
do we have to do?
About a hundred.
That'll take forever.
Yeah, it will if you
don't stop complaining.
Alright. 50.
I want to go
to the movies.
Alright. Go.
♪♪
Oh, shit.
Oh! I-I thought...
I thought you were with Smurf.
Hey, so it's okay.
Andrew, it's okay.
He'll be fine.
Julia.
Andrew, wait, wait, wait!
Please, wait!
Wait!
What happened?
Wait. Just take a deep breath.
What's wrong with him?
Smurf, shut up!
Andrew, I'm sorry!
No, Andrew, wait!
Stop!
Oh, shit.
♪♪
Shit, shit, shit.
Just give him some time.
He'll be okay.
It's not that simple.
You don't know him.
I know him just fine.
If you stop treating him
like a baby,
he'll stop acting
like a baby.
Shit.
He's gonna walk around
and come back home,
and then
we'll talk to him.
Okay, fine.
Hey, I'll come with you.
No! God, he's my brother,
not yours!
♪♪
Make sure it's on.
What's up, Pope?
I'm in the middle
of a rebuild.
Christ sakes.
How can I help you
today?
You can't take
my truck, dude.
I'm not taking it.
It's my livelihood.
I want to hire you.
Not sure I want
to be hired.
What do you want?
I want your help getting
some info on someone.
Get one of your brothers
to do it.
I want you to do it.
Okay.
Great.
I'm gonna need
that wrench.
Well, God damn.
It's been a while.
Mm.
Forget what it was like?
No.
No, I didn't.
Sleep.
♪♪
Just needed
to clear my head.
♪♪
Give me some.
Are you sure?
Mm-hmm.
Pack it up.
♪♪
Definitely looks empty.
You ready?
Yeah.
You plan on leaving fingerprints
everywhere?
Oh, shit.
I'm throwing some gloves
under the seat.
- Sorry.
- No, it's alright.
Okay to be
a little nervous.
Alright.
Let's do it.
10 minutes,
in and out.
♪♪
We could bust out
the lock cylinder.
No, just use the window.
- Yeah, okay.
- Go check it out.
Me?
Yeah, you.
Go check it out.
There any, uh, motion sensors
or window detectors?
Uh, yeah, yeah,
I see one.
What's the brand?
Uh, TrigShield.
Okay, good.
They suck.
Window first,
then the wires.
♪♪
Check this shit out.
For "Distinguished
Service."
This is just, like,
medical records.
There ain't shit in here.
Let's try the lobby.
♪♪
Hey.
Now, this is what
I'm talking about, baby.
Oh, sweet.
Nice. Oh.
Guess this is what
Dutch Lions are.
Guess Tommy's cousin's roommate
wasn't lying.
Hm.
Yo, I found them.
We got 'em right here.
No, I'm looking at it right
here. Give me that hammer.
Dude, this is them.
Well, maybe he has
another box,
'cause I'm looking at it
right here.
No, we got what we need.
Let's go.
Hey!
What the hell?!
Oh, shit!
Son of a bitch!
Ah!
Let's go!
Hey, my sword!
Come on,
come on, come on!
Benjamin
on baby daddy.
Yeah.
Don't take your hands
off the counter, baby.
Harder. Again.
Double or nothing.
♪♪
Don't let go!
Hey!
You okay?
You're not gonna let him
come in our house like that
and disrespect you.
You got this.
4 grand in the pot, baby.
Come on, knock him down.
Mm.
♪♪
Yeah!
Shit!
That's my rent money!
Yes!
Don't bet it
if you can't afford it.
I'll grab the baby.
We need more beer.
Vamos!
Let's go!
You're so late.
Yeah, I had to make sure
I wasn't being followed.
You think
he's following you?
I didn't see him, but I want
to go inside to be sure.
You're fine.
Just get in.
No, I want to go inside.
I don't have time for that.
Look, I'm hungry.
Could you just...
buy me some food,
please?
No, just get inside
and say what you have to say.
♪♪
You called me.
What do you want?
I need money.
Oh. Really?
Yeah, you put me
in a dangerous situation.
Oh, no, you got yourself
in this goddamn situation, kid.
Look, you... I mean,
you got me snitching on
a scary dude here, okay?
It's hazardous as shit.
And money's
gonna make it safer?
No, it would make it
worth my time.
Why do you even want this dude?
Don't worry about it.
I sh... I should get
to know what you're doing.
What I'm doing
is keeping you out of jail.
You're welcome.
What if I talk
to your boss?
Really?
Listen, you little shithead,
you were already on probation,
and then you were dumb enough
to go selling Vicodins...
♪♪
Stay here.
I mean, just like
a hundred a week.
You can afford that.
You want to stay
out of jail?
So do what I tell you
until I'm done with you.
And you're not getting
any goddamn money.
Shit.
Ohh. Jesus Christ,
that guy could hit.
Yeah, well, it's a good thing
you've never been arrested,
'cause you left quite a bit
of blood back there.
Get up on the table.
What if I get arrested later?
Can they match me to it?
Don't get arrested.
Pull up your pants leg.
Wait.
Let me see the box I grabbed.
There's no way that guy
would've fought so hard
if it's not
something valuable, right?
Let's see.
What?
The return address
is a dental lab.
I mean, they are
pretty expensive.
Yeah, not every box
is full of treasure, Tommy.
That's a big one.
Oh, shit.
Remember, when people
who know what they're doing
tell you what to do,
you listen.
This shit won't happen.
You remember this?
Here, you can, uh,
bite down on that.
Wait, wait.
Let me get some of that nitrous.
Nah, you won't need that.
Yeah, you want
to remember the pain.
Stops you from doing
something stupid again.
Alright.
Do it.
Aah! Aah! Aah!
Ohh.
I don't want to hear it.
She's your sister.
No, Smurf, she's not.
You can call it
whatever you want,
but in this house,
we're all family.
Family doesn't
screw family.
Well, then I'll leave.
Where you gonna go?
Oh, baby.
You know you're too old
for the orphanage, right?
♪♪
God damn it.
Hey.
Geez.
Trouble?
Yeah, it just started making
this grinding noise
and... and
jerking around.
You mind?
Please.
Alright.
Let's see.
Oil's okay, but there's
no transmission fluid.
Tranny's probably shot.
I can take it to my shop,
check it out.
Or you can call
another truck.
No, let's go.
You live around here?
I can have one of my guys
at the shop run you home
after we do paperwork.
No, I'm staying at a motel
down the street.
Okay.
Did you see him
go down?
It was like someone
knocked over a fridge.
Yeah, I'm pretty sure
he fell on her.
Oh, yeah, Misty?
Yeah.
She probably liked it.
Mm.
What do you want?
Uh...
get me a Jack and Coke.
Uh-huh.
Oh, and will you grab me
some beef jerky?
Uh-huh.
Okay.
Heya, bud.
You get some whiplash
from Mom's driving?
Hey!
Get... Get back here!
Start the car!
Get back here!
Let's go! Let's go,
let's go, let's go!
Lottery tickets?
Get back here!
♪♪
Sit down.
So, how'd you get in?
I asked the lady at
the front desk to let me in.
Family friend.
How's your transmission?
Trashed.
You gotta check
those fluids.
Huh?
Why'd you bother
with a tow truck?
Wanted to know where I'm
staying, could just follow me.
Oh, I was pretty sure you could
pick up a tail, you know?
Considering you're a cop.
♪♪
You pretended
to be Taylor's mom.
Yeah.
Why?
Doing my job.
And you were
in my house.
Yeah.
My house!
So, how much?
What?
How much do you want?
♪♪
Nothing.
Bullshit.
You're leaning on a snitch,
you're creeping
without a warrant.
You were looking
for a payoff.
Parasites.
That's what
cops like you are.
But I don't
feed parasites,
because you give them
a little blood,
and they just
keep on sucking.
No, no, no, the only way
to deal with parasites,
you squeeze the life
out of them!
You just squeeze it.
You know what I mean?
Who killed
Catherine Belen?
You?
Baz?
Your mother?
You want to kill me?
I've already
uploaded my notes.
They'll come
right after you.
You want to kill me, Andrew?
Go ahead.
Go kill another woman.
Why not?
They can only
fry you once.
♪♪
Any luck?
No.
Where'd you look?
Park, the strand,
every alley off of Mission.
Andrew's asleep
in his bed.
That's what Baz said
he would do.
Hmm.
I wonder
if he'll come back.
What's that mean?
Baz took off.
Why?
Boys...
Such an asshole.
He's had it a lot harder
than you.
Do you even remember
living in the motel?
You remember
living in the trailer?
Yes.
Do you know
how hard I've worked
for us to have
a decent home?
To create this family?
For you to just ruin it.
What the hell
did you just say?
Andrew told me
about you and Baz.
It's... It's...
It's... It's not
even like that.
It's not just sex.
Baz, he... he actually loves me.
So now you think
you're a woman?
'Cause you know how to make
a teenage boy hard?
Baby, it is not
rocket science.
He'd stick it
in a snotty Kleenex
if he thought
it was still wet.
That's just reality,
little girl.
You better
get used to it.
♪♪
Where... Where am I?
My apartment.
And who are you?
Ginger.
Ginger, okay.
Well, Ginger,
where's Renn?
Your girlfriend?
She went out to score.
God damn it.
You seen my phone?
Ginger, my phone,
have you seen it?
Hey, do you mind?
Oh, God damn it.
Change your baby.
Alright, buddy, I'm coming.
Hold on a sec.
Seen his, um... his diaper bag?
You know, his dia... diaper bag
anywhere, phone, something?
Look, can you just...
You have
any paper towels or...
anything I can use?
Please?
Alright, buddy,
let's get you out of here.
Come here.
I got you.
Sorry.
There you go.
There you are.
Hey.
You okay?
I know.
Ahhh.
It's alright.
Silver coins,
you got a little sword.
It's like we're a bunch
of goddamn pirates.
Mm. Mm.
Pirates with dentures.
Yeah.
Hit it.
Oh, you should be giving Tommy
some of that.
No.
He's gotta learn that there are
repercussions for his actions.
Yeah. I mean, his ego's
gonna take a while.
Got his ass kicked
by a goddamn dentist.
That's why you don't start
on old people, huh, Pope?
They'll beat the shit
out of you.
You alright?
♪♪
A cop
has been tailing me.
Since when?
I don't know.
And?
Oh. Shit.
She knows.
She knows what?
I killed Cath.
♪♪
I did it for Smurf.
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/ah2f7
Help other users to choose the best subtitles