api.OpenSubtitles.org is deprecated, please
implement REST API from OpenSubtitles.com
Travel is useful, it exercises the imagination.
All the rest is disappointment and fatigue.
Our journey is entirely imaginary.
That is its strength.
It goes from life to death. People, animals,
cities, things, all are imagined.
It's a novel, just a fictitious narrative.
Littré says so, and he's never wrong.
And besides, in the first place,
anyone can do as much.
You just have to close your eyes.
It's on the other side of life.
- Louis-Ferdinand Céline,
"Journey to the End of the Night"
Fire!
You're a real pain in the ass!
Hey, one of my Asians just croaked!
Enough!
They even have cocktails with cherries.
Remember?
Hey, jerks!
I'll screw you!
Have you seen Ermanno?
- I'll screw you! Now!
- Get lost!
What the hell?
My phone's been stolen!
What are your doggies called?
I have a pet too... a codfish.
Did you call me by my first name?
Did you?
How dare you!
So you're an asshole!
I'm starring in two TV dramas...
I'm playing a Pope in one,
and a junkie on the road to recovery
in the other.
Impressive!
No theatre work?
I'm supposed to do
Shakespeare with Pietro, but...
it has to be at least
three hours long,
be an ambitious project,
and no more small cities!
I'm trying to write a piece
for theatre, and the concept is...
- What about you?
- I might give up acting.
In this shitty country there are never
any good female roles.
I'll write my first novel,
a Proust-style piece.
Really?
Proust is my favourite writer!
Along with Ammaniti...
What a coincidence.
Who is that woman?
Don't you recognise her?
It's Lorena.
Who?
An ex TV showgirl, now in
full physical and mental decline.
Never seen her! But then
I've never had a television.
Viola, I know you don't have one.
You tell me all the time.
- What does she do now?
- Nothing, of course.
Happy birthday, Jep!
Happy birthday, Rome!
La Colita!
To this question, as kids,
my friends always gave
the same answer...
"pussy."
Whereas I answered...
"the smell of old people's houses."
The question was:
"What do you like most, really,
in life?"
I was destined for sensibility.
I was destined to become a writer.
I was destined to become
Jep Gambardella.
THE GREAT BEAUTY
You paid no attention to me
tonight!
Romano, don't start moaning,
we're not an item.
- You liked that guy?
- I like everyone and no one.
But it's always me you're with
when you like no one.
- Will you take me to the airport?
- Sure. What time are you leaving?
- In three hours.
- Three hours?
Then I should crash on your sofa...
Go home, I need to pack
and I don't want anyone around.
- But I live miles away.
- See you at 8:00.
Goodnight.
Guys?
Children!
Run along!
Catellani?
The best, of course.
Did Catellani the tailor
make your suit?
There was no doubt
about Malagna's shady intentions.
The girl should be rescued
at any cost, without loss of time.
- Sir, you drank!
- Just enough to forget my birthday.
- You want infusion?
- Heavens, no!
- I got you a present.
- How sweet!
This is a lucky charm from my country.
Good thing it's lucky,
because it's pretty ugly.
Keep it on your bedside
and stop complaining!
I will! And thanks.
Wake me up at 15:00, you rascal.
You're funny when you call me that!
I don't love you!
Brilliant!
Did you enjoy the performance?
Parts of it.
That violent head-butt
made me understand many things.
- Let's start from the beginning.
- Or the end?
You know, Talia Concept
loves to provoke.
Don't bother, there are more
important things than provoking me.
And this habit of speaking
in the third person is unbearable.
What are you reading?
I don't need to read, I live on
vibrations, extra-sensory ones.
Extrasensoriality aside,
what do you mean by vibrations?
The poetry of vibrations cannot be
described with the vulgarity of words.
Well, try at least.
I'm an artist,
I don't need to explain jack shit.
So I'll write: "Lives on vibrations,
but doesn't know what they are."
Hold on, for fuck's sake,
I never said I don't know what they are.
All right, then what is a vibration?
I'm starting to dislike this interview,
I sense conflictuality in you.
- Conflictuality as a vibration?
- As a pain in the ass.
Try to calm down
and tune into my poetic frequency.
- You're right.
- Good.
Thanks.
Let's talk about my mum's
abusive boyfriend.
No! I want to know
what a vibration is.
It's my radar to intercept the world.
Your radar... meaning?
You're a pain in the ass, a provoker.
A provoker who can't stand a provoker,
that's fascism.
I'm a fascist? Fuck off!
We got off to a bad start...
Talia Concept wants to be interviewed
by your paper, it has many readers.
But you're biased.
Write about how she has sex
with her fiancé 11 times a day,
he's a talented conceptual artist,
he covers basketballs with confetti!
He's sensational!
Talia Concept is talking about things
that are meaningless to me.
All I've heard
is unpublishable fluff.
You can't charm me
with things like:
"I'm an artist,
I don't need to explain."
Our paper has a core
of cultured readers
that don't want to be taken for fools.
I work for that core.
So let me talk about my eventful,
difficult but necessary
journey as an artist!
Necessary for who?
For heaven's sake, madam,
what is a vibration?
- I don't know.
- You don't know.
You're an obsessed jerk!
I'll tell your editor to send me
a journalist of a higher stature.
A piece of advice:
when you speak to my editor,
go easy on the stature business.
She's a dwarf, you know.
This trait of hers
caused her much suffering.
Jep, this interview is a hoot!
Maybe, but don't send me to interview
someone who head-butts walls again.
- You know what the trick is?
- Foam rubber.
Amateur dramatics isn't dead.
Did you get offended
about the stature comment?
Don't be silly!
That's the funniest bit!
I'm a dwarf, it's no secret.
It's the first and last thing
everyone says about me.
You're a spectacular woman, Dadina.
You've had the career you deserve.
But you haven't had the career
you deserve.
Maybe I don't have much to say...
Bullshit, you're lazy.
You never leave Rome.
Why don't you go to Giglio
to do that report on the Concordia
I've asked you to do 50 times?
Re-heated rice is always tastier
than freshly cooked rice.
The old is better than the new.
Plans tonight, chérie?
As the great De Blasi,
my predecessor, said:
"Tonight I'll do two things,
eat soup and have a shag."
Two things that contradict each other.
That's what I'd say too,
and she'd reply, in a serious tone:
"No, Dadina, they don't,
because they're both hot."
You're a hypocrite, Mariella!
You hurt me.
And everyone knows.
You're a hypocrite!
You hurt me!
And everyone knows
the only virtue is hypocrisy.
Like that.
Good.
Great.
There's a publishing house
in Ancona, it's not that small,
they want an interview book about you.
Another interview book?
We're obsessed with interviews!
Can't you hear them?
"As I always say"... to who?
Forget it!
And honestly,
who'll buy a book called:
"Visions and revisions.
Jep Gambardella's Galaxy"?
It's a serious title!
Unfortunately in this country,
in order to be taken seriously,
you have to take yourself seriously.
I only wrote one novel, 40 years ago.
Impossible to find too...
Bullshit, "The Human Apparatus"
was a masterpiece!
It even won the... what was it?
- The Bancarella prize.
- Shit, the Bancarella prize!
You're very kind, but forget it...
it'd be too pompous.
I can't, you'll put me
in an awkward position.
I've agreed and I've even accepted
an advance...
- How much?
- 1,500 euros.
Give it back, I'll give you 1,500 euros.
By the way,
I spoke to the theatre people.
They'll give you three nights
but you pay for the lights.
Who cares about that!
Jep, this is great news.
It's really great news.
Thank you!
What's wrong?
I was talking...
Are you still up?
It's time to go to bed.
That's Viola Bartoli, Bartoli's widow.
The guy who was killed,
the actual Bartoli.
Viola has a 50 metre yacht
that belonged to Himmler, the Nazi.
You know what I call Viola?
- No, what?
- "Too-good-to-poo".
- I don't understand.
- Because she's pernickety.
Usually pernickety people don't poo.
When I introduced Trumeau
to my family, my father said:
"Miss, before marrying my son,
have you ever seen him poo?"
- How gross!
- It's not as bad as you think.
Actually, my wife and I are the only
couple in Italy who are in love.
Orietta, watch out for Lello.
Yes, I know.
He's the world's greatest salesman,
he cons everyone.
In no time he'll get you to spend
every cent on whatever he's selling.
You always flatter me.
Just because I express myself well
doesn't mean I'm always working!
- What do you do?
- I sell toys.
Not just in a shop,
he's a wholesaler on a global scale,
he even sells to the Chinese!
What about him?
Don't you know him? Sebastiano Paf,
perhaps Italy's greatest poet.
He wrote: "Upwards and onwards
with life, down with reminiscence."
He's on the Dukan Diet,
so Dadina won't leave him.
- Is he with her?
- He is, but she...
Like at high school.
Why doesn't he ever talk?
Because he listens.
- Stop sniffing up with your nose?
- Bugger off.
Jep's found a theatre for me.
- Ronconi will feel threatened...
- Come on, that joke's old.
Do you want the lead role?
I'm no longer an actress,
I'm a writer now.
Maybe...
Maybe I'll make a film.
We were talking...
- Viola, darling!
- Help me, I'm worried about my son.
- What can I do?
- Why don't you talk to him?
You always say you're good
with strangers...
That's the problem, I'm too good.
- Is he seeing a therapist?
- Yes, but he wants to stop going.
Take him to a psychiatrist, they're
pragmatic: Ativan, Prozac and so on.
That stuff makes him feel worse.
Relax, he's always been odd,
he is what he is.
By the way, have you tried
Ahè's endive quiche?
It's the first time she's made it
and it's better than my mum's,
please, you must try some!
You changed your hair colour.
I feel Pirandello-esque recently...
- Great jazz, no?
- Not really.
The Ethiopian jazz scene is the only
interesting one today.
I'm from Milan, to be honest...
I find Romans...
unbearable!
The best people in Rome
are the tourists.
Take Italy...
What are we famous for overseas?
Fashion and pizza.
A country of designers and cooks!
How can someone who sells toys,
bringing joy to the world,
be such a pessimist and a defeatist?
You're dark.
- Dark?
- Yes.
I heard Gisella Montanelli
went to loans sharks
to pay her hairdressing debts.
Jep says I'm dark!
Gisella's really sunk that low?
Rome is the only city in the world
where Marxism has truly existed.
You can't excel over others
for more than a week,
you're immediately brought back
to mediocrity.
Rome is pure collectivism.
Pure collectivism.
Stefania, what utter nonsense!
Do you know that Flaubert wanted to
write a book about Nothing?
If he'd met you, we'd have had
a great book, what a shame!
You're a misogynist.
It's not all about you, I'm not
a misogynist, I'm a misanthropist.
When hate's involved,
one must aim high.
You're a dark man.
I'm a transparent person,
without a doubt!
I don't understand...
Lello!
Aren't you stopping tonight?
Mum!
When I see you I blush!
Andrea...
- You're crazy.
- No, Mum, I'm not crazy!
I've got problems.
"As the light flashed,
love sat down in the corner."
"Shy and distracted as it was."
"This is why
we could tolerate life no longer."
Gosh,
no one's quoted me for years!
I read your book as a teenager,
I've never forgotten the end.
Stop right there, you're stroking
my ego in a dangerous way.
You must've been deeply in love
when you wrote it.
Moravia made the same comment,
more or less.
Even though he worded it
a bit better.
I once saw Piazza Navona
covered in snow.
Really? What was it like?
White!
When I come to Rome I live there.
Deep in the outskirts...
What job do you do?
Me? I'm rich.
Great job.
You didn't enjoy it.
I know I'm not very good.
Why do you say that?
Plus it's so sad being good,
you risk becoming deft.
It didn't seem like you cared much.
You're very beautiful, Orietta,
very, very beautiful.
I take photos, you know.
Of myself.
At all times of the day,
to get to know myself.
- With the self-timer, with my phone...
- Interesting.
My Facebook friends say
I take great photos.
I bet there are some of you naked...
- A few.
- I knew it!
Do you want to see them?
- Of course.
- I'll get my computer.
The most important thing I discovered
a few days after turning 65
is that I can't waste any more time
doing things I don't want to do.
When I arrived in Rome,
at the age of 26,
I took a plunge, rather quickly,
almost without realising it,
into what might be defined
as the whirlpool of the high life.
But I didn't just want
to live the high life.
Sacconi should be in charge.
Antonini's a fucking pain in the ass!
I wanted to be
the king of the high life.
And I succeeded.
I didn't just want
to go to parties.
I wanted to have the power
to make them a failure.
- Gambardella?
- That's me.
Sorry for showing up like this,
without warning...
I'm Alfredo Marti.
Nice to meet you, I'm Jep,
but my house is this one.
I don't want to bother you.
How can I help you?
I'm Elisa De Santis' husband.
Did you have children?
No.
I couldn't.
But I could.
I could.
I'm sorry.
Forgive me.
She could too.
Elisa died.
Yesterday.
- Come in, I'll make some coffee.
- No.
It would hurt too much to see
what Elisa always desired.
Alfredo, if you need anything,
you know where I live.
Don't leave me alone, please.
Don't leave me.
Love, sitting in the corner,
was shy.
But not distracted.
She always loved you.
With immense focus.
We were married for 35 years...
but Elisa always loved you.
What are you saying?
Elisa and I went out together
when we were kids.
She left me, I think,
it was so long ago I don't remember.
Yes, she left you.
On September 8th, 1970.
Exactly...
Alfredo, you're distraught now,
that's normal.
I'm not distraught.
Elisa only ever loved one man.
- You.
- How can you say that?
I never saw Elisa again,
you were together for a lifetime!
I found a diary of hers, with a lock.
And I broke the lock off.
I write for a living, believe me...
when you write, you give life
to fantasies, imagination, lies...
I was only a good companion.
That's all she wrote about me.
35 years together...
and I'm mentioned in two lines
as a good companion.
Here, Alfredo.
What'll you do now?
What I've always done.
I'll live in adoration of her.
What's he doing?
Stop!
Jep!
Well done!
He made it!
- Have you seen my daughter?
- Your daughter? No.
Francesca!
Who are you?
Who am I?
- I am...
- No, you're nobody.
Nobody?
But I...
Francesca, where on earth were you?
I've been looking for you
for an hour!
- Are you sad, sir?
- No.
Sir is strange.
I don't like that,
I prefer you to be sad.
Are you going to bed?
You won't believe it, but last night
I went to bed at 22:30.
Now I don't know what to do.
Morning is an unknown object to me.
Unknown.
Sir can help me clean the house then.
- Sir can't, sir feels strange.
- Sir is a rascal.
"But what signified this turbid
seething of servile passions"
"seen through that silence
which surrounds Rome"
"with its nine circles
like a river of Tartarus?"
"Is there a new nation struggling
within the walls of the city?"
"From the crevices of that soil
a feverish vapour ascends like smoke"
"and works like a magic philtre
in the blood of some men"
"producing a form of heroic madness
unlike any other."
What do you think?
Shit, it's powerful, don't you think?
Why the hell do an adaptation
of D'Annunzio for the stage?
D'Annunzio has always been
paradigmatic...
You think that certain
intellectual feats give you dignity,
and that others are better than you,
but you're wrong!
Try and write something of your own,
like...
a feeling, or sorrow...
I've known you ages
but you've never been here.
Don't get big-headed, you've got
a room in a student flat...
Are you going out with
that gloomy girl you're always with?
I wish!
I've tried it on 7,000 times.
I've never gotten a kiss, not one!
- She's a bitch.
- No, she's not.
- She's complicated.
- She's a bitch.
Trust me, you're too kind.
I can tell her type from a mile off,
I don't even need to meet them.
- What are you doing with that hat?
- My morning exercise.
- That's exercise?
- Yes!
Do you know how many women
you've been with?
No, I'm rubbish at maths.
I've always been good at maths.
It's six, I introduced you to them.
Seven.
- Seven?
- Seven.
- When did number seven happen?
- Last summer.
A friend of my sister's back home
when I went to see my folks.
She runs a shop...
- She's nice.
- That means she's a dog.
What about you and Orietta?
- Who's Orietta?
- Don't you know?
She was at your house...
A real beauty.
At my age, a beauty isn't enough.
I might take up writing again.
That's great news!
Has something happened?
Why?
You want to write again after all
these years, something's happened.
Something always happens in Rome.
Nothing's happened.
What are you looking at?
Come here.
They met at university
10 days ago.
They haven't stopped kissing
for 10 days.
This generation of youths
horrifies me.
Supported by this State for years,
when they realise they're smart,
they go study or work in America or
London, forgetting about the support.
They have no civil vocation.
As a young girl, in the occupied arts
department, I oozed civil vocation.
- Is that so?
- Yes, why?
- Come off it...
- What do you know?
In those years you were in Naples
being a loafer with posh girls
and writing your only novelette.
I didn't notice that history
was being made.
Novelette? It was a masterpiece
of Italian literature!
I confirm that Jep and civil vocation
never got along,
he was lazy and the other hyperactive.
Romano, stop sucking up to your idol,
you're pathetic!
"The Human Apparatus"
was a narrow-minded, frivolous book
and pretentious too, like its title.
Jep knows that.
- That's why he stopped there.
- Sorry, what about you then?
I tried changing things
with literature.
I wrote 11 novels, and a book about
the Party's official history.
You're forgetting your contribution
to that reality show...
"Girl Farm."
Television can be
a very formative experience!
I always go when I'm invited.
I get my hands dirty, I try things...
I don't spend my life being a snob.
Are you saying that a socially
committed writer is advantaged,
and safeguarded,
compared to a novelist
who deals with, how can I say...
with feelings?
Of course she is!
The cause someone commits
their life to isn't secondary.
Like creating a family,
dedicating oneself with sacrifice to
raising and educating one's children.
Eusebio and I have four children,
we plan the future together.
I work hard
to be both a mother and a woman,
but at the end of the day, I feel
I've done something important.
So if we don't have children we should
contemplate the idea of suicide?
- I don't mean you, of course.
- She means me.
Dadina, I admire you greatly.
You're a badass.
Do you use "badass"
in any of your 11 novels?
Yes, I do, I try to be modern.
- Modernity is badass.
- De gustibus.
What great conviction!
Should I envy you or be repelled?
Yes, I have convictions.
I'm 53...
- You'd never know.
- Never.
I'm 53, I've suffered,
I bounced back,
and learned lots about life.
Well, I can see you have nothing
to say, at last.
I was drinking...
As we care about you,
we don't want to embarrass you.
You know, all this boastful talk,
all this serious ostentatiousness,
all this ego...
These harsh damning judgements
of yours
hide a certain fragility,
a feeling of inadequacy
and above all a series of untruths.
We care about you, we know you.
We also know our untruths
and for this, unlike you,
we end up talking about nonsense,
about trivial matters,
because we don't want
to revel in our pettiness.
What untruths are you talking about?
Everything I said is true,
it's what I am, what I believe in.
Please, I'm a gentleman.
Don't destroy my only certainty.
Tell me exactly what my lies are
and what my fragility is!
I'm a woman with balls, tell me!
"Woman with balls" would be too much
for any gentleman.
All right, Stefania, you asked for it.
In random order:
Your civil vocation during
your student days went unnoticed.
But another vocation of yours
is remembered by many,
the one practiced by you then,
in the university toilets.
You wrote about the Party because
you were its leader's mistress.
And your 11 novels,
published by a small publishing house
subsidised by the Party,
reviewed by minor Party-affiliated
newspapers,
are insignificant,
everyone says so.
I'm not saying my novelette
was any better,
I agree with you there.
Your relationship with Eusebio...
What relationship? Eusebio
loves Giordano, everyone knows.
He has for years.
They lunch every day
at the Pantheon, under the coat rack,
like sweethearts under an oak tree.
You all know but turn a blind eye.
Your dedication to your children,
with all the sacrifices entailed...
You work all week in TV,
go out every night,
even on Mondays, when popper
dealers don't even venture out.
You're never with your children,
not even on the long holidays you take.
And plus you have a butler, a waiter,
a cook, a chauffeur
who drives the kids to school,
three babysitters, so...
how and when exactly
do you make any sacrifices?
These are the untruths and fragility
I'm talking about.
Stefania, mother and woman.
You're 53, with a life in tatters,
like the rest of us.
Instead of acting superior
and treating us with contempt,
you should look at us
with affection.
We're all on the brink of despair,
all we can do
is look each other in the face,
keep each other company,
joke a little, don't you agree?
Son of a bitch!
Egidio!
Bastard!
I haven't seen you in 30 years!
- I need to talk to you.
- Later! I'm busy, can't you see?
- Is this still your place?
- Luckily not, I sold it.
I'm still the manager though.
You're famous! You're always
in the gossip rags.
You're at all the VIP parties,
always with a girl!
You never come here...
Get lost, will you?
We're having a serious talk!
- Are you married?
- Married, divorced.
- I've got a daughter, Ramona.
- Did you have to call her Ramona?
You artists are all the same!
I tell you I have a daughter
and you complain about her name!
What's wrong with "Ramona"?
Nothing, it's a name that implies
ambitions...
There's my daughter, you see?
She makes me so mad,
I've told her a million times!
You're too old for this!
Now these hot young Polish girls
rule the scene.
They're experts at turning tricks.
She's 42 and she wants to be
a sophisticated stripper.
But the world's no longer
sophisticated. Right, Jep?
I know, only you and I are.
That's right, goddammit!
But she wants to keep doing
this job, for the money.
I don't know why she always
needs fucking money.
- For drugs?
- I wish, we'd have a common interest.
She doesn't even drink beer.
I don't know what she spends
her money on, she's always broke.
- Do I seem like a loser?
- No, why?
Because I can hear myself talk,
I sound like a loser.
I'm nearly 70 and I have to work
till 6 in the morning every day.
I swapped cocaine for heroin
15 years ago.
What an asshole!
A heroin junkie at 50!
Could I be more of a loser?
But I'm not important,
it's her I worry about, I love her.
And I'm no loser there,
I'm a father.
And like all fathers, I'm worried.
What'll she do in a few years?
She can't be a stripper at 50!
- Why don't you help her?
- Me?
Don't you know any rich guys
who want a beautiful wife?
We could change her name,
that's no problem.
You'd do me a big favour.
I'm a writer, not a pimp.
Sorry, I was a bit vulgar.
Daddy's little girl, this is
my good friend, Jep Gambardella.
I'll leave you to it,
I need the toilet.
Be right back!
- Hi, I'm Jep.
- Ramona.
If you want a girl, get a Pole.
Are you kidding?
Who wants a girl?
Not me.
I really am an old friend
of your father.
- Dad has no friends.
- He used to.
When I came to Rome,
I loved coming here.
Your father was a nice guy.
He taught me loads of things,
such as: vodka is uncouth.
How useful!
He asked me to find you a husband.
He's obsessed.
I'm not looking for a husband.
Well, you should be.
- A family's a beautiful thing.
- I know.
But I'm not cut out
for beautiful things.
What's wrong?
I feel old.
You're no spring chicken.
Madame Ardant!
Excuse me.
You're excused.
May I...
say something...
a bit cheeky?
Please do.
When I saw you...
in "The Woman Next Door"...
I fell in love with you.
May I say something cheeky too?
Certainly.
I would've liked to have been
the woman next door.
Why?
To die of love.
- Goodnight.
De Oliveira is older than me
and he still makes films.
I want to make another film too.
What would this new film be about?
Well, after...
32 films which, all in all,
had nothing important to say...
I'd like to leave behind
a very simple concept.
Maestro, nothing important?
You forever influenced
the imagination of millions of people.
What would
this very simple concept be?
I'd like to tell my viewers:
Respect your curiosity.
Indulge it.
Many restrain it.
Why?
Because they're lazy
apathetic moralists,
they're sceptics.
And... ignorant as well.
What was cinema for you?
Cinema...
is a chance to survive...
the disappointments
that reality hands us every day.
In truth...
time, in defining reality,
renders it disappointing.
But if reality is disjointed,
broken apart...
re-examined...
re-elaborated...
it can become a wonderful sight.
Does real life not offer
this same wonderful sight?
There's only one circumstance
in which reality measures up to cinema.
When?
When love bursts in.
In that moment, time no longer beats
with the same rhythm of reality.
Want to know what my next film
will be about?
I'd be honoured.
It's about a girl.
Whose eyes change colour
every single time
she opens and closes them.
She becomes famous,
people adore her though
they've never heard her say a word.
Just silence...
and these eyes.
Blue...
green...
black.
Then blue again.
Fascinating.
Know where this idea came from?
From my first fascination
which wasn't for a girl, no...
It was for...
the first traffic light
installed in Milan
at the intersection
of Piazza del Duomo and Via Torino.
I believe it was on April 12, 1925.
My father put me on his shoulders
because there was a crowd...
Can you imagine? A crowd...
gathered to see a traffic light.
What a beauty...
what a great beauty.
- This is going to be a great interview.
- Tell me...
is Dadina still the editor
of your paper?
Yes.
Dadina and I had a tempestuous affair.
But it happened ages ago.
Dadina...
was an amazing and mysterious lover.
Her mysteriousness made me crazy
with jealousy, of course.
I can assure you that Dadina was...
was a woman who kept her lovers
awake at night.
- Don't include that please.
- I'm a gentleman.
That's my only certainty.
- Gambardella?
- Yes?
- Do you have a cigarette?
- Of course.
- Spying on me?
- No, I was going to knock.
- When?
- When you were more relaxed.
- What brings you here?
- Nothing, I'm just curious.
- I told you what I think.
- I've no hidden agenda.
Do you think every guy
who comes near you wants sex?
Perhaps they just want to talk,
driven by simple and harmless
curiosity.
- That's never happened to me.
- It has now.
Wouldn't armbands be more
comfortable?
Yes, but they irritate my armpits.
Any plans for lunch?
I'm going to my mum's with my dad.
So where's the dog?
What dog?
People buy houses like this
so they can have dogs.
I had a Labrador, but 9 years ago
he got fed up and left me.
Labradors are dumb.
And Cocker Spaniels are dumb too.
Good morning.
This is what you call rhythm.
Hi, Jep.
Hi, Antonello.
- You know Venditti?
- I know everyone.
It must be very satisfying
knowing so many people!
You're guaranteed to be unhappy.
Have people let you down?
I've let them down.
Andrea! Are you with your mum?
- She's parking.
- How are you?
Not well.
Proust says that death
may come to us this afternoon.
Proust is scary.
Not tomorrow, not in a year,
but this afternoon.
But it's evening already
so it'd be tomorrow afternoon.
Turgenev said:
"Death looked at me, noticing me."
Don't take these writers
so seriously!
Who should I take seriously then?
Nothing, apart from the menu,
of course.
Things are too complicated to be
understood by one individual.
Just because you don't understand
doesn't mean nobody can.
- Your reply?
- My reply?
- Jep!
- Hello, Viola.
- Good evening.
- Viola.
Darling, why don't you
get a table for us?
How does he seem?
- He's better.
- Good, very good.
He's much better, I'm so happy!
- Dinner on Thursday?
- Of course!
On Thursday I'm inexplicably free.
Did you hear about Valentina Lemme?
She's dating her personal trainer.
Really? It doesn't show.
- I invited her anyway.
- Are you sure?
She's nasty, you know.
She's like the devil!
Really? You think so?
I see her at yoga twice a week.
- You'll come?
- Of course.
- See you Thursday.
- Okay.
Goodbye.
Watch that table carefully,
but don't let them notice you looking.
Waiter? Champagne, please.
Cristal.
You can't imagine how much one learns
by living alongside
a cluster of religious institutes.
So that was your first time?
Yes, he didn't think he'd been good,
too quick, he said.
So, out of anger or to let off steam,
I'm not sure which,
he got a football
and played with it furiously!
And you?
I didn't enjoy making love with him,
but seeing him with a football
was an unforgettable thing!
He became really good,
he played on the national team.
Your dad said you spend everything
you earn.
What on? You can tell me.
Maybe one day. But why didn't you
write another book?
Because I went out too much
at night.
Rome makes you waste a lot of time.
It's distracting.
Writing requires focus and peace.
That's not much of an answer.
You have plenty of peace here,
it's like being in the country.
I wrote in short spurts.
I was a sprint-style writer.
I told you about my first time...
but you've told me nothing.
It's your turn now.
On an island...
one summer.
I was...
18, she was 20.
At the lighthouse, at night.
I went to kiss her,
she turned away.
I was disappointed.
But then she turned to look at me.
She brushed me with her lips...
she smelled of flowers.
I didn't move,
I wasn't able to move.
Then she took a step back...
and said...
She took a step back.
And said...
I'm going home, it's late.
Want to come to a party
tomorrow night?
Outstanding!
Did you want us to die
of fright tonight?
You won't believe it,
but I love knife throwers.
A true likeness,
especially the hips.
A masterpiece, Geronimo.
It'll look great on the mantelpiece.
Geronimo, you've moved me.
In the depths of my intimacy,
you moved me.
God bless you, Jep!
This is Ramona.
What a unique and marvellous creature.
- Is he taking the piss?
- It's hard to know.
I was being honest.
I'm just sorry you missed
Geronimo D.
- What a tragedy!
- Come in, make yourselves at home.
- Who is that asshole?
- Lillo De Gregorio.
The greatest modern art collector
in this debauched country.
What's Jep's floozy friend wearing?
I don't know.
Jep's proving to be a disappointment.
- Good evening, countess.
- Hello, you're looking well.
I wish I could say that same
about the count. Hello, ladies!
Trying to kill me, you troglodyte?
You dickhead! What have you done?
You served 8 euro sparkling wine!
You think this is
your cousin's birthday party?
You piece of shit!
Bring out the Cristal now
to make good!
Go!
You piece of shit!
Where's the butler?
This love that's blasphemous.
Corrupt.
Inert, haughty,
polyphonic, elegiac, diaconal,
postulatory.
In essence, an ineligible love.
She blushes and says:
"Forgive me, I didn't know
you loved me so much."
"My ignorance is obscene."
He looks at her, reassuringly,
and says:
"Let me defend our love."
How's that for the start
of the second act?
You've written a pile of shit.
Are you stupid?
You're distracting my artist.
Dad, we're having fun.
- Alfio fell down.
- Alfio, I'll deal with you later.
Carmelina, come and do some work.
Mum, I want to play here.
- Has this human being gone mad?
- We'll sort it out.
- I'm not coming, I'm staying here.
- You don't mean that.
Europe's greatest gallery owners
are outside.
If you show them what you can do
then ours will be a happy family.
But I'm already happy,
I want to be a vet one day.
Get to bed, you two!
My kids are going to bed,
it's late for them.
- Come.
- I'll go to bed too.
I'm a kid too.
That girl was crying.
Nonsense!
That girl earns millions!
Excuse me a moment.
Hi, Stefano.
Hi.
- The catering's gone downhill.
- Rome's gone downhill.
Steeply downhill!
Do you have the case with you?
- I always do.
- You up for it?
Anything's better than staying here.
See that?
Stefano has the keys to Rome's
most beautiful buildings.
Is he a porter?
No, he's not a porter.
He's friends with princesses.
Are you ready?
Come with me.
I don't have it.
I told you I don't have it,
so why keep insisting?
Stefano...
Good evening, Princesses.
Good evening.
You look like an old child.
How come you have all these keys?
Because...
I'm a trustworthy person.
You see? It looked huge,
but it's tiny.
Stay still, I'll take a photo of you.
Don't move.
That's no good.
Laugh.
Got it?
Yes, that's good.
Many people think that a funeral
is a fortuitous event,
without any rules.
That's not true.
A funeral is a high-society event
par excellence.
You must never forget
that at a funeral
you are appearing on stage.
Nice.
Nice, but try the other one.
You must patiently wait
for the relatives to disperse.
Once you are sure
that all the guests are seated...
only at that point, may you
offer your condolences to the family.
In this way, everyone will see you.
You take the mourner's hands,
and rest yours on their arms.
You whisper something to them,
a comforting phrase,
said with authority.
For example:
"In the days to come,
when you feel the void,"
"I want you to know
that you can always count on me."
The public will ask...
"What's Jep Gambardella saying?"
This is definitely the right dress.
You're allowed to retire
to a corner by yourself,
as if contemplating your sorrow.
However, another matter
must be approached with shrewdness.
The chosen place needs to be isolated
but clearly visible to the public.
Besides, a performance is good
when it is devoid of any superfluity.
So, the fundamental rule:
one must never cry at a funeral.
You must never steal the show
from the family's sorrow.
That is forbidden.
Because it is immoral.
Viola.
In the days to come,
when you feel the void,
you can always count on me.
Now I ask Andrea's friends
to come forward,
so that the coffin
may be carried outside.
Your back!
It was nice not making love.
It was nice loving each other.
I'd forgotten what loving someone
was about, I'd forgotten that.
I spend all my money to cure myself.
Your breakfast.
Come on, get up, today I'm taking you
to see a sea monster.
Your breakfast.
Five more minutes.
Can you see the sea?
Where?
On the ceiling.
Yes, I can see it.
Who's going to look after you now?
I'm sorry about your daughter.
My condolences.
I spent all my summers
making plans for September.
Not any longer.
Now I spend my summers
remembering the good intentions
which vanished.
In part because of laziness,
in part because of carelessness.
What's wrong with feeling nostalgic?
It's the only distraction left for
those who've no faith in the future!
Without rain...
August is coming to an end
and September isn't arriving.
And I'm so ordinary!
But there's no need to worry.
It's all right, it's okay.
Bravo!
Thank you.
Did you like the show?
People clapped, aren't you happy?
No, I'm not happy.
Why'd you stop?
Take me home.
Get out, I'm not taking you.
You're a shithead like all the others.
Actually, you're worse
because you're good.
Romano...
come here.
Sit down.
Touch me.
In between my legs...
Goodness, look at all the seagulls!
Okay, shall we go?
What are you doing here?
Arturo!
Why are you here?
Don't you see?
I'm rehearsing my magic show.
This is tomorrow's special number:
the vanishing giraffe.
You can make this giraffe vanish?
Of course I can make
the giraffe vanish!
Then make me vanish too.
Jep, do you think that if I could
really make people vanish
I'd still be here at my age
playing these silly games?
It's just a trick.
It's just a trick!
Romano, how did it go?
Well, they clapped.
I'm glad.
- So why are you so sad?
- I'm not sad.
What's with the giraffe?
For a magic show.
I'll come and see you tomorrow.
I'm not doing the show tomorrow.
Why not? You said it went well.
I'm leaving, I'm going back
to my hometown, for good.
I won't even pack up my things,
I'll leave it all.
I've lived in this city
for 40 years.
And in the end I thought...
the only person
who deserved a goodbye
was you.
So you're leaving?
Romano... why are you leaving?
Rome has really disappointed me.
Bye, Jep.
See?
- Want some coffee?
- No, thanks. I know you're busy.
I need to ask you something.
Go ahead.
Why did Elisa leave me?
I don't know.
Didn't she say anything about it
in her diary?
No, I don't think so.
Would you be offended
if I asked to read it?
No, I wouldn't.
In fact, I'd understand.
But I'm afraid I can't let you read it.
Why not?
Because a few days after the funeral,
I threw it away.
May I introduce you to my girlfriend?
Hello, my name's Polina.
Like Polina in "The Gambler"
by Dostoyevsky.
What are you doing tonight?
Nothing.
Polina's going to finish ironing...
then we'll drink a glass of red wine.
We'll watch some television
and go to bed.
What about you?
I'll have a lot of drinks, but not
so many as to become unruly.
And then...
when you'll be getting up
I'll be going to bed.
What lovely people you are!
I love doing the train!
I'll screw you.
"Who am I?"
That's how
one of Breton's novels began.
And of course in the book
there's no reply.
- Did you hear about Viola?
- What?
She donated everything
to the church.
She works in the parish
and is going to volunteer in Africa.
The trains at our parties
are the best ones in Rome!
- You think so?
- I do.
They're the best because
they go nowhere.
- Well?
- It's wonderful, thank you.
Come on, it's all gone.
Tell me why you left me, please.
I want an explanation, please!
Go away!
Get out! Get out!
You see all these people?
They can't do anything.
But I know how to do something.
We know how to do something.
How sweet!
- Who's that, your mother?
- Who?
Yes... that's my mother...
So...
- So...
They've been asking me for years
why I don't write another novel.
But look at these people.
This wildlife!
This is my life
and it's nothing.
Flaubert wanted to write a book
about nothing but he failed,
so how could I?
It's good.
Thanks, rascal.
- Ron Sweet.
- Hello, I'm Gambardella.
Sorry I'm late.
We've been finalising the details
for tonight's opening.
- It's a pleasure.
- The pleasure's mine.
- Come in.
- Thanks.
What inspired this exhibition?
It wasn't my idea
to do this photo exhibition.
It was my father's idea.
When I was born, he starting taking
photos of me, every day.
One photo per day.
He never forgot, not even once.
From the age of 14 upwards,
I continued.
I photographed myself every day.
Go ahead.
I love hot-air balloons.
Good God,
did we really have to invite her?
Mum, she's my mother-in-law.
She resembles
a wonderful primitive animal.
A primitive animal
with infinite patrimonial assets.
Where are the meatballs?
Stop, don't!
That mozzarella's blue.
You're an asshole.
Such a fool...
Tell me something,
who is that cardinal?
- That's Bellucci.
- Bellucci?
- The one in line to be...
- Exactly. The papal throne awaits him.
I met him
at Giada Ricci's carnival party.
Rumour has it that he used to be
Europe's best exorcist.
- Pulling my leg again?
- No.
I never joke about the devil.
Do you know I'm very, very bored?
We're having a great, great time.
Cardinal,
when will The Saint arrive in Rome?
On Thursday,
but please don't call her The Saint.
She is a Saint but not technically.
She'll become one.
There's no doubt about it.
The Congregation will decide.
First soak the mushrooms
in warm water.
Then you cut up the duck.
Remove the skin
and put it in a pan
with one spoon of oil.
Cook it on a high flame
for 15 minutes.
At that point...
Cardinal, do you remember me?
Lello Cava.
We met at Giada Ricci's party.
I was dressed as an escort.
Come, they're starting to serve lunch.
I'd like you meet my writer friend,
Jep Gambardella.
A writer!
This country needs writers.
I thought it needed more priests.
That too...
The two are not dissimilar...
they both require a vocation.
Help.
- May I ask you a question?
- Of course, my dear man.
Well, for some time now...
from a spiritual point of view...
Skunk hunt?
Of course, I'll lead the way!
I know the Tebaldi grounds well.
Jep Gambardella, the king
of socialites! You're losing it.
I've been losing it for 40 years.
It's a steady decline.
This is it, we're here!
Come this way!
This way, come!
Here!
Skunk hunting, what a shitty idea.
Lello, do skunks really stink?
How should I know?
- How much prosecco did you drink?
- 117 glasses.
Dickhead,
what would you do without me?
We're here, come!
There are tons of skunks here.
Hic sunt puteolae.
Come, come see the skunks.
Won't you come see the skunks?
I will steal you...
From everyone who keeps you far
From me
I will take you
With my boat toward lands unknown
To you
You will get to know
The freedom to love
that you were never given
I will steal you
You'll see, I will manage
My love
If you so desire
Tell me something, Stefania.
Have we ever slept with each other?
Of course not!
That's an awfully big mistake!
We must make amends, immediately.
Idiot.
Thank goodness.
We still have something nice
to do together.
The future is marvellous, Stefania.
To be honest, Catellani hasn't had
many brushed fabrics in recent years.
In my opinion, Rebecchi's still
the best tailor in Rome.
- Who are you?
- A hard-working man.
One who, while you play the artist
and have fun with your friends,
keeps this country going.
I keep this country going,
but many people
haven't understood that yet.
Imagine that, Dadina,
Giulio Moneta was my neighbour.
One of the world's 10 most wanted men
and I didn't know.
Heard from Romano?
He vanished, understandably so.
He cut off ties with everyone.
You've changed,
you're always thinking.
But not about the usual bullshit
that we laugh over.
Maybe I should do what Romano did.
I'm not fit for this life or this city.
Nobody's fit for anything, dammit.
Take it from the queen of misfits.
Everything around me is dying.
People who are younger than me,
things...
All before my eyes and I...
And you're suffering.
And you don't understand.
How's the soup, Little Jep?
The soup's good.
Why did you call me Little Jep?
No one's called me that for centuries.
Because a friend,
every now and again,
needs to make their friend
feel like they did as a child.
How can I make you feel
like a little girl?
You don't need to,
I feel like a little girl every day!
I've seen the world from
that viewpoint for 60 years.
As soon as you finish your soup
I'll give you some killer news.
Tell me, I'm dying to know.
You know Sister Maria, the missionary,
the one they call The Saint?
Yes, she's coming to Rome
to receive some honour.
Exactly. In all her life,
she's only given three interviews.
- Yours will be memorable.
- Yeah sure, think of Giulio Moneta!
This is different.
She studied in Italy
and speaks Italian.
She read your book and loved it.
She wants to meet you so I organised
a dinner party at your house tomorrow.
- Did I do well?
- You did very well.
Get your interview with
that big-headed Bracco done today
and tomorrow
we'll focus on The Saint.
Well well, Pappardella!
It's Gambardella...
As I always say to my clients:
Beautiful bodies don't last,
they're apparitions.
- Big words, Bracco.
- Truthful words.
I have a certain knowhow
that makes the human circus go round.
Which is?
Access to beauty.
One.
- How are you?
- Fine.
Just got back from India,
I had amazing dysentery.
Come to my divorce party, I'll have
burlesque dancers on elephants.
Of course.
What present would you like?
One thing, peace in the Middle East.
- I'll try.
- Two.
700 euros.
Here you go.
Yes, darling.
Perhaps...
I was thinking, my mouth...
I'm scared, I've never done it before,
professor.
Don't call me professor.
Call me "my friend" or "my love."
We all need love.
What star sign are you,
deeply intense lady?
- Aquarius.
- I knew it.
Want to go back 30 years
to when it rained in August?
Done.
- 700.
- Three.
Baby doll.
- Hi.
- My baby doll.
My boyfriend says
I don't really need it...
We all need it.
Your boyfriend is blinded by love
and he can't see things as they are,
that's why.
That's 700.
- How's your mum?
- Fine.
- Five.
- That's 700.
You're plumper, darling.
You're always in my heart.
- That's 700.
- Eight.
Hello, honey.
As handsome as ever.
- You're my pride and joy.
- Thanks.
Eleven.
- You've been to see Casagrande.
- I don't know who that is!
You betrayed me.
We're undertaking a journey,
and you've interrupted it.
This is the last time.
Go, go.
Bye then.
Full price.
- Twelve.
- That's 1,200 euros.
Professor,
I'm here for my hyperhidrosis.
Where's this undesired perspiration?
On my hands.
- Pray for me, sister.
- You don't need my prayers.
You don't know how much of my income
I must surrender to the tax man.
Go on, sister.
That'll be 700, sister.
Tomorrow I'll have the honour
of dining with her.
- At the Holy Father's?
- No.
No, at Jep Gambardella's.
You see, the Pope even invited
the enclosed nuns.
Sisters...
Hold on...
Oh God!
Sisters, sisters, sisters!
Sisters, sisters...
Yes, perfect!
Thanks... great.
Ah, Red Cross nurses!
So fit!
Okay, great...
What handsome young men!
Great!
Let's go!
What'll we eat?
- Carbonara and veal roulade.
- A light meal...
The Saint weighs 11 kilos.
If she's vegetarian?
There's always Ahè's endive quiche.
That's vegetarian.
Hello? Yes.
Now you tell me?
How'll I fucking find the Odescalchis?
- What's wrong?
- The Saint's assistant called me.
The Saint would like
Count Odescalchi to come too,
he treated her like family
when she was here.
- Do you know him?
- Of course, but he's not in Rome.
All the nobles are in London,
at Philip's great-niece's wedding.
Hold on...
Let's call the Colonnas from Reggio.
The nobles for hire? They're dead.
- Nonsense, they're immortal.
- But they're not the Odescalchis.
The Saint won't even notice,
70 years have gone by!
The Colonnas are true aristocrats,
and aristocrats all look the same.
True...
This piece of furniture
looks great..
I'd never have thought
of putting it in the bathroom.
It looks great,
like a new bathroom!
Well done, Andrea!
Count Colonna speaking.
Yes, we are available.
For tonight...
Short notice would entail
a small surcharge.
Our rate is 250 euros per person
for the evening.
Plus the cost of the car hire.
No, I'm not sure...
This would be somewhat
humiliating for us...
We are willing to be hired...
as the Colonnas from Reggio.
But as for pretending to be
the Odescalchis...
I don't know...
We were at war for two centuries.
I feel it's immoral.
Let me talk it over with my wife
Elisabetta.
All right, ma'am.
For this time, we'll go along with it.
But we would appreciate it
if you would supplement
the contribution.
Cut at least twelve pieces of rabbit!
Set aside the kidneys, liver, head...
Gently brown it.
Don't forget thyme,
laurel leaves, rosemary...
Then red wine, Ligurian olives...
pine nuts.
And after an hour,
you have Ligurian-style rabbit!
Sister Maria, what convent
are you staying at?
Actually, we're at the Hassler Hotel
at the Spanish Steps.
To be honest, Sister Maria
finds it uncomfortable.
Never heard the Hassler
described as uncomfortable!
It's very comfortable but Sister Maria
isn't used to sleeping in a bed.
She sleeps on the floor,
in a cardboard bed.
Do you have any visits planned?
Sister Maria will climb St John's
Basilica's Scala Sancta on her knees.
- Have you?
- I'd have liked to, but...
I have a bad knee...
Orthopaedic problems
are unimportant,
compared to the plenary indulgence
granted by the Scala Sancta.
That's true!
Another speciality
of mine is lamb with...
Does Sister Maria still help
the sick?
22 hours a day, every day.
She washes them, feeds them...
You ought to see her.
Despite her age,
she doesn't walk, she runs.
She's inexhaustible!
Now she's tired, but that's because
she's not with her patients.
How old is she?
She'll be 104 in October.
- That's impressive.
- I thought she was older!
Longevity too, like all things,
is not accidental.
About Sister Maria's interview
with Jep...
Her interview?
There must be a mix-up...
Sister Maria hasn't given
any interviews since 1971,
after the reason
for her mission in Chad,
was misunderstood by some.
Of course, but considering
her admiration for Jep's work...
You told me she enjoyed
"The Human Apparatus."
She found it beautiful and fierce.
Like the world of men.
Great! There would be no risk
of any misunderstanding,
Sister Maria can review the text...
- No, I'm sorry.
- Don't insist.
I don't wish to raise any false hopes,
there's absolutely
no question of any interview.
Sorry, but why do you always answer?
Why not let Sister Maria talk?
Madam...
I took a vow of poverty.
And you can't talk about poverty...
you have to live it.
Such true and real words!
Powerful words!
Do you need anything, madam?
- She needs the bathroom.
- It's on the left.
The change of diet
isn't good for her.
Sister Maria, in Mali, only eats
40 grams of plant roots a day.
Me too sometimes, in the evening,
as a light meal,
I have some splendid
roots with lemon.
You clean the roots
by scraping them with a knife
and you cut them into small chunks...
Cardinal, remember when we met
at that wedding?
You were there too...
I felt the need to ask you
about matters close to my heart.
Matters regarding faith...
regarding the strength
of spirituality...
But then you got distracted.
You can ask me now.
- No, I don't see the point.
- Why?
I'd be very disappointed to discover
that you have no answers.
I'm only saying it's a possibility...
I think that...
Never mind...
I apologise for earlier.
I'm afraid I was somewhat offensive.
There is one question
I really want to ask you.
Are the rumours about you true?
That you were a truly great...
exorcist?
See you at the office.
Sister Maria...
Sister Maria!
Where's Sister Maria?
I thought she was with you.
- She was with you.
- Yes, but then she went to you.
We're going, thank you and goodbye.
Sister Maria!
- Sister Maria!
- Have you seen her?
- She's not there.
Saint...
Sister Maria!
Saint!
She's called Sister Maria.
Sister Maria...
Where has that bitch got to?
These 550 euros
have come at just the right time.
It was a lovely evening too.
Lovely evenings are others, Alceste.
Sister Maria!
My goodness!
Come, Elisabetta, let's go to bed.
You go ahead, I'm going upstairs
for a moment.
Don't be late.
Countess,
we must put a stop to this.
I'll lose my job
if I let you in every night.
This isn't your home anymore.
- It's a museum now.
- This will always be my home.
In this room, in 1930,
Princess Antonietta gave birth
to her only daughter,
Elisabetta Colonna of Reggio.
The princess died
after giving birth.
Young Elisabetta,
in these opulent rooms,
had a happy and carefree childhood.
But shortly after, the financial
hardship endured by Prince Erminio
forced him to sell the property.
They're migrating west...
but now they are resting.
Did you know
that I know the Christian names...
of all of these birds?
Why...
did you never write another book?
I was looking for the great beauty,
but...
I didn't find it.
Do you know...
why...
I only eat roots?
No, why?
Because roots are important.
Now there's something
I want to show you.
This is how it always ends.
With death.
But first there was life.
Hidden beneath the blah, blah, blah.
It is all settled beneath
the chitter chatter and the noise.
Silence and sentiment.
Emotion and fear.
The haggard, inconstant
splashes of beauty.
And then the wretched squalor
and miserable humanity.
All buried under the cover of the
embarrassment of being in the world.
Elsewhere,
there is what lies beyond.
I don't deal
with what lies beyond.
Therefore...
let this novel begin.
After all...
it's just a trick.
Yes,
THE GREAT BEAUTY
to Peppe and Maurizio
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/agwyk
Help other users to choose the best subtitles