ENJOY ALL VOD IN HIGH QUALITY @ 4KVOD.TV
GET LIVE TV,MOVIES,SHOWS IN ONE PACKAGE
Why did you get her Suhagan fixed first with government money and then got her scraped?
Saw the government was already bad and
He did no harm to the department
We will decide whether the damage is done or not.
After all, what did you understand yourself?
now
My family has always been Vedanta's mean and speculators.
The head of such a department is a thief, what a tremendous headline for the media.
network is not available
We have enough evidence to set up an inquiry against you.
where did you hide that volkswagen
Wife doesn't eat kisses
on his leaves
Sorry, this matter has increased a lot, otherwise the map of sorry
Couldn't solve this question properly and I promise it won't happen in future
Ok
Will cover up the matter on your request
Permanent Malda
you don't fit into the government system
I know you go to my place Naina
write what you write
last year's
Everything will be okay
didn't understand you
You are so much function in your work that you are just afraid of you.
so much time my commitment
all gone in vain
everything
Yes
but you'll find the way forward
Isn't it
furniture needs rest
Alone that you don't care at all
I have finished it doesn't matter, everything will be fine
floor function
Do you love your wife the same way?
leave it
Yes
yes got it
OK then
i have to go to a meeting
right now
In the evening
may take a while
will take hours
Jaggu Dada
you fall asleep
Ok
will come soon
What's the matter, let's come late Latif is looking at you
Major diagram you are late sorry
What is all this, someone told us about the border operation, why didn't I come and walk?
Works Meets Wanted To Be
China will be the border and should be kept on all contact
Model Central Free Mill should call the police there your old friends will talk soon
alone abroad speaks russian and hindi
He will definitely get help, we don't know how big a problem he can become.
When we transfer him we will get hold of someone in the rakshana residency ok ok let's start work
what to eat
thanks for the food range
came again and made a ruckus
what wants to do
stays outside the house keeps making threats
started drinking and everything is running through his mind
I can not come
we have to end this thing
this thing is your baby today ya know me not to talk about it
green devotion
That's why tomorrow keeps threatening me
Short
go son
who play
see the food your responsibility is over
I'm scared what should I do
If Rani Chandrakar was cast then call the police
I told you that because of that I have lost my job
you talk to him
I have to go
will do nothing i have to go
Ok change the world, it's the same situation here too
Should we keep an eye on the border now or not in the city?
keeping an eye on the border
He knows what happens at the border
how we caught him in business from ko sevaram
was nervous but did corporate
Good
What do you have to do corporate life in this business after taking care
come on your guy
hold on hold on
Google you don't have the door this time you locked the door before coming inside
very big talk what is there to talk about
I sincerely hope that some topic will come out, what do you want winter, I can't lie to you
We both know that you come every time my answer remains the same every time I know nothing
never even started asking easy tell me how are you talking about that
it's just fine
What's the matter what's your food and drink range for us
yes everything is for you
you are living a life of sannyasis
just trying
Now imagine what you are going to tell us
tell you about what
My I have heard something and brother I have seen something, I don't know anything
something happened yesterday
and we know
something different happened
what happened baby
Looks like someone was taking the elephant across the border
Well understand something sir, we are not joking
man what are you guys doing
are doing a lot
I don't understand things with love what to do that little girl in the back room
What did narcotics send or all the fun will go away, what do I know how those people came here, I just came here like this
do you think i live here
The engagement
sorry
take this as a chance for yourself
get out of the mud
carefully
does it all look ok
Don't know what's right
teacher
Let the madman who is standing outside stay outside, I will tell you everything
hey small why
worship scripture
Tattoo count of a bloodthirsty and strange man
think you got this painting
But it doesn't seem like that
Yes, at such a time, this is what I am seeing
Where can you find such wonderful Estonian art?
and can be found in taxi or art gallery in this but not here
78 has a lot of information
do you also collect
I have some very good painting I have very good 10 interesting
Well this hobby of yours is very expensive
within my power
Why don't we just sit down and talk about today and its collection
sorry we
I have to go somewhere near that so much again
don't make excuses we both have a very old identity
Suman Public I don't want to talk to us about this
x friend
Chill out
It would end us here, it is a very old thing, I do not want to talk, everything is going well in your life.
so is everything as you want
Is there happiness in the heart and peace in the mind what do you mean
You have sworn answer Harshad I was underage I was goofy I was in trouble and updating
Were talking old, where is the country this time, the country is different but
What has been done for you, only misunderstanding and humor problem, it was known that
their child is nothing we are giving you a chance sir babu
You yourself are Major General in HD
Sujata Favorite I do not have time for these things, at that time a young man was stuck in the office
You kept coming to me, I could not do anything till then the country will change
And your life will be yours according to our papers
SSB Major Hotel Pet your payment will start immediately then preferred
i am unemployed i am not of any use i am fired myself
Everyone knows what it takes to lose you money will come
God will get you threats, you have nothing to be with
then what will happen after that you go ahead with us
Hi!
am i talking to my friend
Yes
western union security services speaking
i voice contact
where are you
Com I heard that you broke your ties with the police
Wasn't enjoying what happened
Were you in the department of the set?
as far as i think
yes i thought now
do something new in life
then i have a good offer for you
very special place
And an old friend is missing you
Oscar
ministry of defense
your old partner
Looks like Oscar is getting bored there
you should meet him once
man made a fool of us why do you have someone better than this
got it
we are ready too
70 I am going to become a father
Status
will do a great job
something is happening
Whats up
Hello hello hello
Champak says you like it now
Havana Club
you all ahead
Hello Hello
are your darling
how many years have it been
Is
Hi!
i go to the kitchen
Haircutting is a little work left
is white
Making us in Havana
leave it all
ministry of defense
Director in the Office of Information and Analysis of Defense Policy Survey
and whenever you wake up
The work is a bit boring but the place is good
I want my own people everywhere
Well I don't know why they made me capital I have nothing to do
Also tell me, the work of the ministry is a bit strange, are we doing this or
But can you tell me what will be my work there?
I'll explain everything when we get there
not necessary yet
it is necessary
We have to cheer up the old people
we have to be united
These young people will block your way with their umbrella smiles
i first
want to think about it
what is there to think about
We're both going professional together again
don't know for sure
to correct
are you doing something else
No no no no no till now so i didn't think of anything like that
i didn't say modi
when you helped me in trouble
so i want you a little
you
We will not get the same salary as Mirchi Ritu in the police, our work in the head of department there
boring lot
Ministry of Defense will be fine
a boy
wind you go ahead
I don't know if I remember the time when we went to that training.
I don't remember that story mp girl Swati or soviet drank a lot and hit her
then not Alfred
One person had gone to my wedding uninvited, there was a pool party going on
had great fun
made us dance till morning
I even did a split on the stage, today's party was them in the morning
Found out that we are cops, think they were partying with cops all night
The days of youth are different
You can show us by searching for
Would have shown but 4:00 may not be spoiled
covering
ruling
to control it
There is no problem with reaching
i never forget these things
A big shipper like you doesn't forget things
At least I have done you a favor, just do it, you have also done a lot for me.
What was that
Why did you leave the job in Australia
office politics
Aashiq was fit to become director general but
they trapped
how stupid i am
Offering
happens to everyone
i have also learned
but i was 5
i'm so tired
Will Mulayam be given a car by an MP?
don't know see me
nothing happened nothing happened
Hi!
nice to meet you
Me too
First something has changed, you have become old and wise
african teacher
Cocaine
how is the definition
Tumhari Wife Aur Bachcha Absolutely Salamat Hai Song List
MP3 has reached Holika, they will be sent to death as soon as possible
thank you very much don't worry good people
Hello Hello
Hello my love
Boundless
first let me show you the room
or some rules
his cabinet
direct
Jira Perfume Office IT Room is the secret document and
Mustafa if you want to drink coffee
so you have to go with me
Ajay see this
This is our lockers, want to keep mobile inside it, you could not go inside the office with mobile
ulcer
come to my cabin
have a meeting
you can give me the rest of your stuff too
keep it safe
Pakistan
Train
what happened then
what is this going on
thinker
tap of the world
we had good news
we made a mistake
In Mantu, you carried out an independent police operation in front of the limits of the Defense Force.
want to be court martial
want to send fruit on the road
you want our department to close
sit down
a man gave me
Eighty-four delegation came
Is it good
yes i celebrate your first day
Really
and understand
very nice
Park
You even know how irresponsible it was
We were sure to take off all the clothes
itchy ear
Yogi himself pressed the ticket
why didn't you inform the police
I was afraid of losing Ali, I don't trust him but I don't trust him.
Hey you know that only after death, there is no turning back, it is called sir, I just got a slight scratch but
If there was 1 inch here and there then it would have been the same nature.
Say we were criminal, we were not in vain
I know how much I'm listening because we messed up their operation
i agree with you
My fault
Ok
We wouldn't have to tell a story to the media as if we were training and got these travelers
ok go to work said the train is still in this world
Tarak
choir photo download
dream video downloading
is it me
mail me
press this
Thank you
i don't know how i
It's Brothers Group Emergency Meeting
Near Defense Ministry in your office
any passenger
Bamboo 296 2003 Protocol signed in Brussels by 7 new member states of NATO
jaipur train today sonia
Dhulia
Litti Vihar Romania Slovakia and Slovenia Recognized by all 19 member countries
Use Department Office to store new member-in-approved contracts on March 19, 2004
Will hand it over to the bench and from that time all these countries will become permanent members of NATO, that's all.
Now it is confirmed which world will become a member of NATO
good luck to you all
It will change a lot
The security of classified for intelligence will have to go on a separate head, I have received a briefing for this from all the departments.
all the regulations will change everything
May Begum will be checked again
On one hand, we have to change the whole system, we will not have a large number of people who can control the security of the State Secret.
I understand it will be extra work for you but they need extra resources us corporation
Narcotics Operation
Listen, use your resources in a better way, you will get all the resources you need
think maybe
We've got what we needed Abu, you wouldn't have shown us yours
I will listen to everyone's department brother
where is the paper
Undertaker sayings
tomorrow you
There has been a huge increase in
NATO's Cigarettes Our Department Will Be Incorporated These People A New State Cigarettes And Classified Foreign Intelligence
remain admin and i will be its director
adjacent
Women will be the head of the department from the army
Means your responsibility to keep the classified foreign intelligence
is a big responsibility
You will have no idea how much paper we will have to do with you
Everything will go through us for the network
what can you understand
that why you need a deputy for you
Yes
get it right
everything else is far
Nothing else
it's all nothing
In this way, consider the sale step of Make Ice Bagh.
And I promised you rest work
don't worry you know how much i love working
alfred
Let's have some relaxation man
Briefing like this makes his head heavy for him
go gold
look i can't come
i know if you want
I've asked you to put drugs on me
to spy
lion photo
good evening good evening son
Nice place, can rest here for a few days
have everything to eat
have everything you need
Fireplace
keep beer in the fridge
you can over there
don't go anywhere yourself
i will come to pick you up
I have fever, if I am not feeling well then I will give you medicine too.
It's just a matter of few days, the model is about to open
Till then you can rest here
all is well isn't it
I was told that everything will be fine, I will just stay, nothing will happen to me but here it is
this some son
If where you are, then nothing will happen to you, everything will be fine
daily
do you understand me
say yes now
so that it is known
i have to go i have some urgent work i will come soon
go take care of yourself
ok i am ready very good what should i do
I will tell you later
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/ah2fn
Help other users to choose the best subtitles