THE NAMES OF PEOPLE, INCIDENTS, AND
BACKGROUNDS OF THIS DRAMA ARE FICTIONAL
How much do you know
about your husband, Gu Jingi?
What do you mean?
What will you do
if your husband, Gu Jingi, killed
Prosecutor Geum Seokyeong's brother,
took out his heart, and used it
to do an illegal heart transplant?
What?
I told you to stay away from nonsense.
My father wouldn't do that.
He's right. That's impossible.
It's true.
Chief Cho Junghyun told us everything.
She said the chairman took out the heart
from Geum Seokju.
And he also gave me an order
to fabricate the autopsy report.
Yoonjung.
I'm sorry. I should have told you sooner.
Are you saying he really killed a patient?
Mother, are you all right?
I'm fine.
I'm fine,
so tell me.
Why are you suddenly here
telling me all this?
Help us find Mr. Cheon.
Then we'll keep Banseok University
Medical Center safe from Jayden.
How can you?
Before I tell you how,
please let those two
leave the room.
Make Ms. Pyo leave? Why?
She blackmailed Park Kitae,
fabricated Gil Soyeon's medical record,
and instigated
Nam Hyukchul's false witness.
It was all done by her
under Gu Jingi's order.
Do you have evidence?
Ma'am, it's not true.
I just did my best for the hospital…
Leave the room.
Ma'am.
I told you to leave.
I understand.
ENJOY ALL VOD IN HIGH QUALITY @ 4KVOD.TV
GET LIVE TV,MOVIES,SHOWS IN ONE PACKAGE
EPISODE 16
What are they going to say?
I'm going to take Honours Hand
from Jayden.
Every piece of power he has
comes from Honours Hand.
Take it away? How?
I'll expose that Jayden received
an illegal organ transplant.
Illegal organ harvesting is
a serious crime
that can result in capital punishment.
If Jayden conspired with Gu Jingi
and killed a patient
to take out his heart,
Honours Hand won't condone it.
If that's exposed, my father…
Make your choice.
Will you protect your husband
or save Banseok University Medical Center?
If you pursue both, you'll lose both.
It's me, Pyo Eunsil.
Han Yihan and Geum Seokyeong are
at Chairman Gu Jingi's home.
They said they came to tell his wife
that thing from five years ago.
Did you take care of Cho Junghyun?
Don't let the police find
even a piece of her hair.
We have no time to lose.
It'll be too late if Mr. Cheon runs off
after killing Cho Junghyun.
What do you mean?
Why would he kill Cho Junghyun?
Cho Junghyun
went missing at her place yesterday.
Her son, Nam Junhwan,
was left behind unconscious.
Mr. Cheon abducted her.
You already knew
that he had been carrying out
all kinds of dirty deeds
your father asked him to.
If you don't trust us,
you can hear it yourself.
Hear it myself? From whom?
Come on in.
I got home with my mom.
As soon as we entered the room,
he covered my mouth
and put a syringe on my neck.
I heard it clearly.
My mom begged him to let me go,
but the guy who had me said,
"The chairman doesn't want
any loose ends."
Please make sure you keep him safe.
We never know.
Yes, he'll be safe with me.
Let's go.
We must locate Mr. Cheon
as soon as possible.
If we let this go on,
Cho Junghyun will also…
Do you want Gu Jingi
to kill Cho Junghyun too?
If you're his family,
stop him before this becomes more serious.
But how?
Let's call the secretaries
and the Security Team.
They both report to Mr. Cheon,
so they might know something.
We can use
even the smallest lead right now.
Keep a close eye on Pyo Eunsil
from now on.
If Mr. Cheon wants
to reach out to Gu Jingi,
he must get through Pyo Eunsil.
Did you have to do it like this?
You could've told me.
-You knew my mother would be shocked.
-You already knew too.
You were at the penthouse too.
Back then…
Back then, I was out of it.
Sure.
It must've come as a big shock.
You probably never imagined
your father illegally transplanted
somebody else's organ.
If you wish to do him good,
then find where Mr. Cheon is
before Cho Junghyun dies.
No one is truly trustworthy.
Did you betray us too?
Why? Since she betrayed you,
will you kill her too?
Never mind.
You'll abduct her,
confine her, assault her,
then blackmail her.
You've committed all kinds of crimes,
so you can't back out.
But if you won't back out,
you'll go down with Gu Jingi.
You must be anxious.
I just did my job as an attorney.
Sure.
I hope you do your job
during the trial tomorrow.
It wasn't too fun
when you admitted too quickly.
I want to put an end
to Gu Jingi in court.
NEW-HOPE LAW OFFICE
THE DAY OF GU JINGI'S TRIAL
CLOSED TEMPORARILY
DUE TO A PERSONAL MATTER
You're Han Yihan?
I heard about you.
You played a decisive role
in bringing down Banseok with Jayden.
Let me introduce myself.
I'm the Chief Director
of Honours Hand headquarters, Susie Yoon.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Lawyer Han Yihan.
Please excuse me. This is important.
Please have a seat.
Speak.
I found Mr. Cheon.
He'll turn in the burner phone
to the Security Team at 2:30 p.m.
and turn himself in to the police.
At 2:30 p.m.?
That's half an hour from now.
What should I do?
Let me know where they're meeting.
If he runs away,
keep a moderate distance and tail him.
Don't catch him.
Don't catch him? Why not?
We should make him talk.
Even if he gets caught,
will he spill everything that easily?
We must save him instead of catching him.
That way, he'll trust us.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
It seems urgent. You should go.
I'll hear the rest from them.
Thank you.
Over there!
Get in. I don't think
you have any time to think.
Don't look at me like that.
I'm here to save you.
You? Save me?
-Why?
-I want to quit seeing these people.
People who get blamed
for other people's crimes
when they have enough on their hands.
What?
Gu Jingi put every charge on you.
Do you get it now?
If you gave them the phone
and turned yourself in,
you would've become a murderer.
Cho Junghyun better be alive.
That's how you'll save yourself.
Where is
Cho Junghyun?
COUNSEL, DEFENDANT
Counsel. What is this?
What is this noise?
Suddenly…
Counsel.
Is this phone you have in your hand yours?
Your Honor. Prosecution has confirmed
circumstances that suggest this cellphone
possessed by the defendant's counsel
is important evidence in this case.
Please consent to check it.
What are you doing? Let go.
Prosecution. What do you mean?
How is it evidence?
DEFENDANT
Who is it?
It's Cheon Hyungu.
Where are you?
I'm at the courthouse.
Mr. Cheon Hyungu?
Yes, that's right.
Prosecution, what is going on?
Cho Junghyun, Cheon Hyungu.
Were you planning on killing them both?
Did you say you were sick of this?
I'm sick of it too,
so I'll reveal everything
right here, right now.
Your Honor,
I am sorry to interrupt the trial.
I am Attorney Han Yihan,
representing Cheon Hyungu, the accomplice
and the witness, Cho Junghyun.
My client wanted
to turn himself in to the police today,
but the Security Team
of Banseok attacked him
and made an attempt
to destroy the evidence.
Evidence? What evidence?
This phone has the record
of every single crime
which the defendant has ordered
my client for years.
Your Honor, I would like to call
Cheon Hyungu to the stand.
Impossible. We did not agree
on having Mr. Cheon Hyungu.
He's a wanted criminal at the moment.
We must send him to the police
and have him questioned.
I couldn't make a request beforehand
because he was wanted by the police.
The attorney has previously stated that
Cheon Hyungu is the real culprit
who killed Lee Dohyung,
so we must confirm the truth
with Cheon Hyungu himself.
We must reach an agreement.
We'll adjourn for 20 minutes,
then decide if Mr. Cheon will be
allowed to witness without summons.
All rise.
"Attorney Han appeared in court
during the trial
and stated there's evidence that supports
Gu Jingi's charges
in the phone used by Mr. Cheon,
Gu Jingi's accomplice."
Isn't this dangerous?
You said we had to go somewhere together.
Is this it?
Yes.
Five years ago, I got into an accident
because Gu Jingi deceived me.
What are you doing? That was dangerous.
It has been a while, Boss.
No, you aren't my boss any more. Jayden.
You told Han Yihan about me.
What can I do? I needed to save myself.
So should we meet right now?
My new boss wants to talk to you.
Fine. Come to my penthouse right now.
Witness.
Around 10 a.m. on March 23rd, 2022,
you met Assistant Director Lee Dohyung
with Gu Jingi, the defendant.
-Yes.
-In the video of the said day,
the defendant gave you an order
to take care of the victim, Lee Dohyung,
within Banseokwon.
Let me ask.
Witness, did you kill the victim?
I said…
we should let him live.
It was a hospital, so he could have lived
if we moved him and treated him.
However,
Chairman Gu stopped me.
Do you know what I regret the most?
Five years ago in the detention center,
letting Han Yihan go alive.
-What's he saying?
-Han Yihan? That lawyer?
-Letting him live?
-What did he do?
"Five years ago in the detention center,
letting Han Yihan go alive."
What does this mean?
Your Honor, what happened
five years ago is unrelated to this--
No, it's a part of the evidence,
so we'll hear from him.
Five years ago,
Chairman Gu gave me an order
to instigate Gong Gukkwang and assault
Lawyer Han Yihan in the detention center.
And on the night of the assault,
he visited Mr. Han Yihan
and told him that he'd die there
unless he admitted to the malpractice
he had committed against Geum Seokju.
Did he make you abduct Cho Junghyun too?
Yes, he told me to abduct her, kill her,
then hide her body.
Why didn't you do as he said?
Because I knew I've been betrayed
thanks to Mr. Han Yihan.
Do you have evidence
to back up your statements?
On the phone we just spoke,
you'll find every single order
I got from him for the last five years.
I'll confirm the contents of his phone
and turn it in as evidence for this trial.
That's all.
Counsel, would you like to question him?
No, I will not.
Your Honor, I'd like to call
Cho Junghyun to the stand.
Ms. Cho.
-Yes.
-Can you bear witness?
I can.
I understand. Please get ready.
Not bad.
I guess Banseok adored you
without knowing you'll betray them.
Are you complaining about bringing
the biggest benefit to Honours Hand?
Also,
I think you're the one
who came to stab me in the back.
Stab you in the back?
As the Chief Director of the headquarters,
I came to inspect you,
the head of the Asian branch.
I came to verify the report
that you received
illegal heart transplant surgery
in return for our investment.
You heard such nonsense and came this far?
I guess the chief director
doesn't have much to do.
We'll find out soon
if this was nonsense or not.
Han Yihan said
he'll reveal everything
between you and Gu Jingi on trial today.
If it is true, I can just go back,
but what about you?
That'll be the end of you.
Witness, in the morning
of November 21st, 2016,
did you take part
in the heart transplant surgery
along with the defendant,
Gu Jingi, at Banseokwon?
Yes, I did.
The heart he used
during the transplant surgery.
Who did it belong to?
It was the heart of Geum Seokju.
Who…
Who took out…
the heart?
Chairman Gu Jingi did.
And I helped him.
You're going to put him on ECMO?
He's recovering well. Why?
Just do as I say.
Don't ask questions.
But this is just…
Don't you want
Junhwan to live?
-Sorry?
-There's this new drug.
It treats hypertrophic cardiomyopathy
by internal treatment.
Of course, it's approved by the FDA.
It's rarely used locally.
It costs millions of won per injection.
And it's not covered by insurance.
I'll give it to Junhwan.
And I'll pay for everything.
Although it's on the premise
that you'll help me.
I knew his order wasn't normal,
but I couldn't turn it down.
Back then, I thought
the new drug was going to save my son.
Did Gu Jingi
take out the heart
from the patient himself?
Yes.
Yes, he took the heart out
from Geum Seokju,
put it into the VIP patient's chest,
then sutured him.
After that, Chairman Gu
called Dr. Han Yihan
and had him transplant
Geum Seokju's heart
into the VIP patient's chest.
And the next morning,
the chairman destroyed
the ECMO Geum Seokju was on
and finished his life.
Witness.
You just confessed to your criminal case.
Are you aware of this?
Yes.
I'm going to confess
to all the crimes I committed
and face the punishment.
I see.
Prosecution.
Do you have anything more to add?
Prosecution. Are you okay?
I'm all right.
I'm okay.
Prosecutor Geum.
Seokyeong.
Call an ambulance. Hurry!
Can you hear me?
Seokyeong.
Yes. It just ended.
Gosh. Things got a bit complicated.
Cheon Hyungu and Cho Junghyun testified,
so we were close.
But Prosecutor Geum collapsed,
so the trial was halted.
She collapsed?
I guess things didn't go well?
Okay.
The prosecutor collapsed,
so the trial was halted.
You're lucky.
But it won't change anything.
Things just got delayed. That's all.
We will stop questioning
the witnesses here.
And we will set a date
for the next hearing.
As soon as I hear from the prosecutor,
we'll set a date to continue.
Yes, Your Honor.
All rise.
Chairman Gu.
Good work.
Father.
-Hyunseong.
-Why…
Why did you do it?
I'm sorry.
All I can say to you is…
My son.
All right. Let's go.
Dilated cardiomyopathy.
I understand that
it's a hereditary disease.
How could she have
the same condition as Seokju?
This is awful.
If something bad were to happen to her,
Yihan would…
The price went down
as soon as the market opened.
Gu Jingi's trial yesterday
must have shocked a lot of people.
There were a lot of articles
about you and Honours Hand.
It says how a foreign company was about
to take over Korea's leading bio-company
and how there was a suspicion
of illegal organ harvesting
during the process.
I don't care.
A suspicion is just a suspicion.
I'm going to leave the country as soon
as I redeem my investment in stocks.
You'll come with me, right?
Of course, I'm coming with you.
I need to get a medical checkup
as an outpatient at Banseokwon.
-A medical checkup?
-There's something I must find.
Tell the medical director
that I want to see him tonight.
What is it?
Han Yihan reported me
to the bar association
for threatening
Park Kitae and Nam Hyukchul
and for conspiring
to change the surgeon without consent
and to fabricate medical records.
I will soon be disbarred.
I don't think I can defend you anymore.
I'm sorry.
No, I should apologize.
I gave you too big of a burden.
Okay. Just relay my message
to the medical director.
I'll take care of the rest myself.
I'm truly sorry that
I can't represent you to the end.
Ms. Pyo.
Mr. Gu.
You have a visit from a lawyer.
His name is Han Yihan.
Will you turn him away?
-Mr. Han.
-Yes.
Mr. Gu has agreed to your request.
Come with me.
Has it been five years since it had been…
just the two of us like this?
Why was it Seokju?
If you needed a heart for your investment,
you could have figured out another way.
Why was it me?
I didn't know
when the hospital would get another heart
if not his.
And you, Han Yihan,
were standing my son's way.
I thought
I had to get rid of you for good,
so my son could
no longer be in your shadow.
I believed that I had to remove you
because he was never going to surpass you.
Because of your selfishness,
I lost everything that mattered to me.
My greed
caused everything.
I'm sorry.
I'm asking you for your forgiveness,
but I know it won't be enough.
Despite that,
I want to protect Banseok no matter what.
To stop Jayden from taking over.
I hid a video that proves
that Jayden was the recipient
of Seokju's heart.
Find that video,
stop Jayden from taking over,
and protect Banseok, please.
I'm begging you.
Why are you asking me?
Han Yihan.
You were the only one
who didn't get swallowed in greed.
I'm ashamed to ask you this.
The only person I can trust
is the person I tortured the most.
It's you,
Han Yihan.
Han Yihan came to Banseokwon?
Yes. He went to the VIP floor
with the head of the Security Team.
You'll feel dizzy and enervated.
After I inject the shot, I'll request
to transfer you to Banseokwon.
Okay.
Nights here…
are quite long.
Nights…
This contains evidence
that Jayden took the heart?
Yes.
LAWYER HAN YIHAN
I need to check.
Director Jung.
Why are you here?
Did you buy off the medical director too?
It wasn't hard.
Those who once caved into money
will cave into a bigger sum of money
next time.
This is what you used
to drug me five years ago.
But the dosage is several times higher.
So this is the end
you wanted all along.
Even if you kill me,
the truth will come out
because I gave Han Yihan the video
that proves you got
Geum Seokju's heart.
Does it look like
I'm doing this to silence you?
No. I'm getting revenge.
Revenge for taking
the most precious thing in my life.
I'll tell you my story now.
Once you hear everything, you will
understand me too.
Why do you suddenly want
to postpone the surgery to tomorrow?
I apologize.
There is someone I need to meet.
Once I get a transplant,
I will need to stay here for a month.
I must meet this person now.
Someone he had to meet?
Was it…
What is it?
I checked Jayden's car accident report
this afternoon.
There was a passenger.
A passenger?
That night,
I left Banseokwon
after taking the drug you gave me
because I got a call
that they had found the person
I wanted to meet in Korea.
You have arrived at your destination.
This is the end of the route guidance.
The passenger was Kim Junghye.
KIM JUNGHYE, FEMALE, 63
She was a 63-year-old woman.
She died.
The fellow passenger in the car died.
I took the heart out myself.
I asked him
how he got the heart that night.
This is what Gu Jingi said.
"The fellow passenger in the car died."
That's how he took out the heart.
Then the heart Jayden received
belonged to this woman, not Geum Seokju?
No. I doubt that.
Given the size and condition of the heart,
it couldn't have belonged
to a woman in her 60s.
Then who is this woman?
KIM JUNGHYE, FEMALE, 63, DEAD
I heard that you were my son's friend.
You're quite handsome.
I wonder
if Jaehyuk would've been handsome too.
Your son…
Do you want
to meet Jaehyuk?
Of course.
I even missed him in my dreams.
Then why didn't you look for him?
Jaehyuk…
really missed you.
I was scared.
I sent him away to such a faraway country
because things got tough for me.
Looking for him after all these years
scared me.
I didn't want him to see me like this.
I'm not exactly well-off.
So the possibility of becoming
a burden on him also scared me.
And when I heard
Jaehyuk was looking for me, I was afraid,
but I still thought I had to see him.
I know I can't be forgiven for what I did,
but I wanted to say this to him at least.
That…
I wanted to see him…
and missed him too.
I resented you a lot…
because you abandoned me.
But…
I still missed you.
Mom.
No way. Are you…
Jaehyuk?
What is it?
What's wrong?
What is it? What's wrong, Jaehyuk?
Jaehyuk. Oh, no.
Jaehyuk. Are you all right?
Jaehyuk!
Don't exert yourself.
You still need to rest.
Where am I?
You're in a VIP room at Banseokwon.
You were in an accident.
An accident?
But you were very lucky.
You were transported to my hospital
right away and were treated accordingly.
And your heart transplant
was successful too.
I had surgery?
What about the woman in the car?
The one in the passenger seat.
Unfortunately, she met her end.
Ten days have passed since the accident.
Our hospital held a funeral for her.
The passenger didn't have any family.
Did you know the deceased well?
You took away
the most important thing from me
at the moment I had been waiting for.
She was the only family I had left.
You took my mother from me.
Back then…
-I…
-I want you to regret and be reminded
of what you did
and die slowly
and painfully.
And that is the end
I had been planning for you…
in the past five years.
I…
Jayden didn't want
to get the heart transplant that night.
That's why
Gu Jingi caused the accident.
Jayden had to get the heart,
so Honours Hand would invest in Banseok.
It means
Jayden was deceived by Gu Jingi too.
Now, I get why
Jayden was so determined
to get revenge on Gu Jingi.
-That way. Be careful.
-Father.
Let's move him.
-One, two, three.
Get that.
What happened?
How could a healthy man
fall unconscious overnight?
What on earth did you do to him?
I'm sorry.
He told me
he wasn't feeling well last night.
But I don't know what happened.
He's conscious now.
Father. Are you all right?
-Hey. My son.
-Yes?
I'm all right.
He's conscious now.
But it's only temporary.
Shut it, you punk.
Father. Don't worry about anything. Okay?
I…
-Hyunseong.
-Yes?
I don't have
much time left.
Father.
Get Han Yihan for me.
Okay.
I hope she wakes up soon.
What's this about?
My father…
He's looking for you.
PATIENT ROOM
Stay with her at all times.
Whatever happens, don't leave her side.
Don't worry. I won't go anywhere.
Hyunseong.
Okay.
Was it Jayden?
Thank you for coming.
My Hyunseong…
Hyunseong…
April 2nd, 9:24 a.m.
Mr. Gu Jingi passed away.
No!
No.
Why did you suddenly change the time?
We were going to leave in the afternoon.
Something came up at the headquarters.
We were going to leave today anyway,
so it doesn't matter.
Why? Is something on your mind?
No.
Sir, Jayden left the penthouse.
He packed everything up.
And Director Lim Yuna checked out as well.
Han Yihan speaking.
Jayden called
Honours Hand's chartered flight.
When does it leave?
It leaves Incheon International Airport
at 10:30 a.m.
-One hour remains.
-Okay.
Seokyeong, you are awake.
Do you recognize me?
Daewoong.
Lie down. You need to take it easy.
What…
What happened?
You lost consciousness at the court
and got transferred to New-Hope.
Thank goodness you regained consciousness.
Where is Yihan?
Well,
he went to see Chairman Gu.
Gu Jingi?
GU JINGI, A FORMER MINISTER CANDIDATE
PASSES AWAY
What is it?
Mr. Jayden Lee, it's time to board.
Okay.
Shall we go?
It's Gate 12.
I checked with the captain.
Okay.
What is it?
Before I board the plane,
there is something I want to ask you.
Is our sudden departure related
to Gu Jingi's death?
Jayden!
Hyunseong.
What are you doing?
We need security at Gate 12!
-It's okay. Don't call security.
-But…
I said it's okay.
Don't interrupt us.
Why? Do you think I killed Gu Jingi?
Yes.
You killed my father.
So, are you going to take revenge?
Will you be able to do it?
Come to me when you are certain.
Even if it takes years,
I will wait for you.
Make sure you take revenge.
Shall we go?
With your life,
pay for my father's life.
Gu Hyunseong, get a grip.
Your father wouldn't want this!
-Please help him. Please.
-Over here.
Please.
Han…
Han Yihan.
Bring me the first-aid kit. Call 911.
I didn't know
how Gu Jingi
would get the heart.
Don't speak.
The blood shouldn't enter the lungs.
Please tell
Prosecutor Geum Seokyeong
that I am sorry.
I want to apologize.
Jayden, wake up.
Jayden!
PATIENT TRANSPORTATION
Daewoong, prepare for surgery.
Call Dr. Choi Yosub and Ms. Cho Junghyun.
And get me an anesthesiologist.
What? Why?
Jayden got stabbed in the heart
with a scalpel.
-We don't have much time.
-Okay.
Here.
NEW-HOPE MEDICINE CLINIC
Yosub, let's get the bypass first.
-I will go and get ready.
-Okay.
Yihan, hold on.
Seokyeong regained consciousness.
Yihan.
Seokyeong.
How about Jayden? How is he?
I heard that he got stabbed in the heart.
Tell me which condition he is in.
The blade
reached the heart.
If he doesn't get surgery now,
things will get very dangerous.
The heart…
Yihan, we are ready.
Make sure
Jayden lives.
Make sure he lives
so that he can have a trial
and get punished properly.
That's what we fought for.
Yes.
Patient name, Jayden Lee.
Let's begin the surgery.
-Scalpel.
ONE YEAR LATER
SURGERY IN PROGRESS
Don't be nervous. Breathe in and out.
I will try.
Play the music.
Give me the marker.
-Forceps.
-Scalpel.
-Scissors.
OPERATING ROOM
She will be fine.
Please make a sound.
What? My voice.
Good job.
This time, make a longer sound.
Let's close it up.
Shall we raise her up?
-Okay.
Be careful.
It looks like the surgery went well.
The two of you went through a lot.
Thank you so much.
NEW-HOPE LAW OFFICE
NEW-HOPE MEDICINE CLINIC
Thank you for your hard work.
It wasn't hard.
Thanks to you, Soyeon received surgery
and I could stop being a ghost surgeon.
Thank you so much.
What are you going to do from now on?
Well,
I made up my mind.
I am going to work here with you.
Will you be okay?
New-Hope is much smaller than Banseok.
Come on. I need to be here
so that you have time to work as a lawyer.
You are Doctor Lawyer.
Thank you.
Don't mention it.
Get going now.
CASE NUMBER 2023 RETRIAL 2836
HAN YIHAN'S RETRIAL
The judge is entering. All rise.
You may sit down.
As you know, we have a retrial today.
The prosecution gave a statement.
It's time to hear from the defendant.
Defendant, give us your statement.
Yes, Your Honor.
Your Honor,
on November 22nd, 2016,
a 19-year-old male patient
who had received a heart transplant
for dilated cardiomyopathy,
Geum Seokju passed away.
-Congratulations.
Yihan.
Did the result come out? What happened?
The verdict is not guilty.
-Hey!
Not you.
You did well.
I will go back after I drop by somewhere.
Okay. Don't come back too late.
They are preparing a party.
-Yihan, hurry back!
-Congratulations.
-Hey.
-Hurry back.
-This isn't his first birthday party.
-Okay. See you later.
It has been a while.
HOPEFUL CORRECTIONS
RESTRICTED AREA
AUTHORIZED PERSONNEL ONLY
Why didn't you tell me
about your past?
Had you told me from the start,
things wouldn't have gotten…
No.
Still,
the end
would have been the same.
I wanted to be with you guys
for a bit longer.
Those times
were fun.
I relayed a petition for Gu Hyunseong
to the court.
Since the victim
asked for a lighter sentence,
it will be taken into consideration
at the second trial.
I am glad.
Your case also has room for extenuation.
I will defend you,
so why don't you appeal?
No. I won't appeal.
I had revenge in my way.
Now, I am paying the price.
Without avoiding it,
I will carry out the sentence.
Let's say goodbye one last time.
Thank you.
KOREA CORRECTIONAL SERVICE
You…
saved me twice.
Why did you save me?
I lied to you until the end.
I am…
a doctor.
HOPEFUL CORRECTIONS
Yes. Lawyer Han Yihan speaking.
I… I really don't need this.
Just stay still, Seokyeong.
You shouldn't look haggard
on a day like this.
What do you think? Does she look better?
Yes. Her skin looks dewier.
-I…
-No. She needs more.
Let's apply more.
I am really okay.
-Put it on her body.
-Yes. Put it on your body.
Seokyeong, I have a hunch.
You might get proposed to today.
Get proposed to?
Think about it.
The bad guys are paying for their crimes.
Yihan got acquitted.
A proposal will make a happy ending.
Gosh, what are you talking about?
-Apply it.
-Yes. You never know.
Apply it.
I am sorry. You must have waited long.
What is it that you want to tell me?
Don't be surprised.
Seokyeong.
The heart transplant has been decided.
-What?
-The surgery will be performed
by Dr. Choi Yosub
at Banseok University Medical Center.
Once the surgery goes well
and you become healthy,
let's…
Lawyer Han Yihan speaking.
THANK YOU FOR WATCHING DOCTOR LAWYER
WE THANK LEE KYUNGJIN
FOR HER SPECIAL APPEARANCE
Translated by Eunsook Youn
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/agzvd
Help other users to choose the best subtitles