ENJOY ALL VOD IN HIGH QUALITY @ 4KVOD.TV
GET LIVE TV,MOVIES,SHOWS IN ONE PACKAGE
How's it going? Is it close to Ho Chi Minh City
The perfect resort for Boss Choi
Why is development slow here
It used to be a semiconductor factory
The project was approved as a tourist destination when they heard it was closed
Look at the location and the view
I'm sure a lot of tourists will come once the development starts
Who did you say I was meeting today
He's the head of a car rental agency
He said he must meet President Choi
How much did you charge
For what? - For what
Is that what you think I am
What do you take me for
He'd do anything to hang out with you
Cui presidents
Are you sober
How the hell did that drink cost so much yesterday
I had the honor to drink wine Louis XIII for the first time yesterday with the light of Cui's boss
Why did you let him do that
I should have stopped him
Don't you make a lot of money, too
I made a lot of money
But we need to spend our money wisely
Don't spend money on booze every fucking day
Come on, let's get this day over with and get a hangover
He begged me for hours to see you in person
I hear he's got a lot of money
Well, he's not just dealing with Koreans
There are many buildings in Ho Chi Minh City
you
The boss is Choi Yong-ki
Is my hello
I've heard so much about you
Please get on the bus
Well, you guys talk
Don't you hot
You're eating a cookie
Why don't you eat something good
I heard what Jonghoon said
He said you ran a pretty big car rental business
I hear you have a lot of money
what
You his mama
You son of a bitch
- Oh, it's hot. - Hey, what the fuck are you doing
What are you doing, son of a bitch
Get out of the way points
Do I look like I run a car rental agency to you
You were kidnapped
Hey, you son of a bitch put that knife down
Hey, put the knife down, boy
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. - I didn't say that
I'm the fucking shin of Yeongdeungpo
I know, I know
- Said he knew, boy. - What's he talking about
What the hell do you know
- Hey. - Leave the girl alone, boy
What the fuck?
- Don't fucking touch me. - Come on
Get over here and I'll give you a fucking knife
Why the fuck are you not answering your phone again
Oh, oh, here, here
It's this way
- There you are. - Here, here
Hello? Where? Where?
- In there. - No, I mean tin channel. Where is he
He's not answering his phone
This his mama
Get over here, get over here
I need you to put that knife down
You are here
What's the
What took you so long to get here
Oh, I went on that blind date thing
What kind of blind date goes on once a week
Well, he has to get married, too
What's wrong with him
Young Shin named Yeongdeungpo is a total lunatic
- New? - You sons of bitches
- Just escaped from a mental hospital. - Don't worry about me
The hostage?
The shopkeeper's aunt and a college girl altogether two
Hey, man, why don't we just break in
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa
It's too dangerous. Maybe we should call it suppression
Now we don't know what this maniac is capable of
Where are all of us
Hey, keep your hands down and there's a lot of people watching
You puppies
Do you know how hard it is for the yakuza
Calm down, calm down
What's wrong with your mother
Can't cook
- What are you. - Whoa, whoa, whoa
Yeah, you must be tired
Get the fuck over here
Watch out. I gave you all the knives
Where are you from
Oh, shit.
Oh, my god
hello
- Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
- What are you doing, man? - What
- Come here and talk. - Why
yeah
- Stay away. - Not you
- Stay the fuck away. - Wait, wait, wait
This is dangerous
Hey, you boy
Is it the first time you've seen me and the first time I've seen you
what
Can you believe me
I don't fucking believe that
Danger put the knife down
I told you to put the fucking knife down
- Hey, get the men out of here. - Yeah
- Hong Seok. - Get out, get out
To this to this
Hurry up
Get them in the car
- Get your hands off me. - Hey, boy
If you stab someone with a knife
You say it hurts you say it hurts
- Does it hurt? - It hurts
Smelly boy
Give me up
You fucking
What the fuck
You're not a zombie
Come here please don't take pictures
Excessive police repression hospitalized for 12 weeks
What kind of excessive repression is that
In front of some lunatic with a knife
Is the police going to make a deal and say, Sir, please calm down
I told you how good you were doing and gave you thumbs up
These guys are still writing stories like this
ok
I had my eyes covered and I didn't know it was me
Hey eee, you should cover up
You can't tell
- Tell me the truth. - What
Anyone would think you were a criminal based on your face
Boy's got a lot of nerve
No more our big brother
Kind of a Russian mob vibe
Hey, hey, if you say that
Your class leader and the others have more
He's just a terrorist
His face has been growing down since high school
- Don't you think so? - Yeah
There is a feeling of standing in the community of changsheng column
You know what I mean
It feels like yesterday's length is different than today's
- Don't you think so? - That's when I first met the squad leader
- Quiet, quiet. - Almost put the cuffs on him
Be quiet with your buttoned-up cuffs
Interesting?
Was it that much fun?
You have come
It's
You seem pretty happy to be in the news
I am hard luck!
I just should
- Ugh. - What a terrible thing to be called
I'll go and plead with the chief and come back
That's it. That's it
You should go to Vietnam
- Vietnam. - Vietnam for what
Meet Yoo Jong-hoon
- I don't know who. - Isn't that who
The same guys who robbed the gold and silver store in Garifong last year
This is the boy on the lookout
Oh, yeah, yeah, this guy got it
For he is
He turned himself in in Vietnam for stealing gold and silver
- Why? - I don't know
So you're in charge of bringing him in
Think of it as a business trip for two days and three nights
Haven't been abroad for a long time
- Who are you going with? - Dude
My dad was a Vietnam warrior
It should be me, the son, this time
Big brother my sister's brother's friend's
- Best friend lives in Vietnam. - What's wrong with this guy
- I'll try. - You son of a bitch
You had nothing to do with this
- You want to put your hands down? - Feed you guys
What do you think this is for fun
We're on our way to pick up a murderer
This is very important shit
I go with him
cut
- Wait, wait, wait. - What
How are we supposed to go with each other
- We need someone who speaks English. - English
Monitor do you speak English
- Are you talking to me about English now? - Tell me
I'd like a salad, but
- Is that all right? - You speak English so well
yeah
If you go abroad with me
Everything is ok
All right, all right, all right, I'm done talking to you
Just trust me and come with me
Wow, our monitor is really decent
Yo! Fuck
Didn't you say it was okay to go with you
They don't understand British pronunciation at all
Aye yo mama
I knew something was wrong when you said what kind of vinegar
I just wanted to see Vietnam
That what the hello
hello hello
That what I
We are the police in Korea
The police
We're too busy to leave now
Out right Out
quiet
- You don't understand a word of fucking English. - Don't call me names
I can understand Korean
sit
I sit down first
I'm sorry
thank you
Alas!
I'm running a little late
I am Park Chang-soo, police resident officer at the Korean Consulate General
-Uh-oh
Nice to see you
I am the full-time monitor of Jinchuan City
- So you're class president? - Yeah
I'm Ma Xidao in charge
- The person in charge. - Yeah, yeah, yeah
The staff I work for
He didn't speak a word of English
It's been a bit of a farce
ok
Do you want to eat before you go out
- Yeah, sure, sure. - Sure, sure
Well, you take your bag and your luggage
- Bao Bao. - But there's nothing to eat here
Here, here, here, here
Where is all that stuff
- There. - Ah
Is this only a thousand dollars a thousand
- Yeah. - Oh, my God
I don't know how I can travel without money
They all need a discount
Those guys over there are Korean gangsters
- Right? - Korean gangsters everywhere you go
There are a lot more Koreans doing business around here
The underworld has also increased
Violent crime also gives me a headache
What the fuck are you looking at
Underworld hello
- All the way to Vietnam. - Fuck you
- It's a cop. - Are you sure
- Cops. - Really? You sure
- Are you sure? - I'm sure. - Put it on
Hey, there's some weird stuff in there
And what looked like marijuana
Those guys are weird
What? Marijuana isn't.
- I'm on my way. - Oh, no
- Oh, you. - Not one of them
Can we take a break
- Look, they're leaving. Look, look. - Go, go, go
- Korean, right? - Yeah
- Hey, hey, hey. - We're having our opening
- The price is perfect right now. - What are you doing
- Service like Gangnam price like Ho Chi Minh - how so many Koreans
- All right, all right, kid. - Like Vietnam
Take away!
- Hey, hey. - Hey
Temasek,
You are the essential oil
The eldest brother
The kid
What the hell are you doing here
I have to think about life, too
Don't you get it
I can't spend my whole life in Korea like that
Whoa, whoa, then you shouldn't be doing this
I think I could do it in the morning
Our brother is very active in his work
This is who
I am cooking oil
What's cooking oil?
But I don't know what you're doing here
Are you here to arrest a prisoner
A vacation for a vacation
Be careful, brothers
Police in South Korea
It's not gonna work here
In the underworld here
There are a lot of guys who carry guns
- The gun? - Yeah
Some with guns and some with marchetti
A sword
The atmosphere here is totally different from Korea
right
It's none of our business. We're just here on vacation
- How could we get shot? - Yeah
- Then come and play. - Yeah
- Sure. - The service is like Gangnam
- Where are we going? Forget it. - Prices like Ho Chi Minh
The consulate is no different than our office
Oh, it's a bad environment
Anyway, at least we have air conditioning
Yeah, it's hot
- How could you do that? - You waited
ok
It's really hot
Yeah, it's hot
Looks like there's a lot of missing passengers around here
Yeah, over 30,000 visitors a month
There will be more cases
There are also many iron heart of their own play disappear
It's all about money
Just sign your name right here
You just take this file
Give it to immigration control
After 10:00 tomorrow morning
You can take the person away
But why so many files
- Because this case is also very rare. - What
The criminal came to the consulate to answer for it
There's no precedent
Vacate a room in a hurry
He was temporarily detained
But we also have many difficulties
But why did he turn himself in
He said it was his conscience
Feel what you feel
He said he had a bad conscience
Conscience is the task of
- Conscience. - What the hell
Ah this
Oh, shit, I made a mistake
The whole conscience
I'm sorry to trouble you
Zhong Xun!
Why did you turn yourself in
I'm really soul-searching
I'm going to Korea to be punished
You want to go to South Korea
You're eating a lot of food
It's
Monitor of the class
To the real room
Take this?
Well know
Give it to me
Well done
Well, you keep an eye on it
ok
Yeah, it's okay. It's okay.
Elder brother know
I don't know what you know
Why did you say you turned yourself in again
Because your conscience smitten you
- A guilty conscience? - Ah
Clock clock clock clock
Clock bell
Jondo tried to kill me
The clock is there
Is that Jong-du Lee with you
- He's here, too, isn't he? - No
Isn't it
HSS
I know everything, don't I
Or we could take an ear off
Ear ear ear
Vice President
You go easy
There are a lot of ears. It wouldn't hurt to take one off
I need you to start talking
- Why would Lee kill you? - Pain pain
Pain pain
I touched a woman that Chung was seeing
Take the damn thing off his ear
Hey, if Lee Jong-du is here
That gold from the white is also in the choice
Didn't the three of you work together
- No. - Oh
HSS
No, no, no, no, no
Even if you don't say
I know everything, too
It's not what you're doing here
Is that the kuang one? Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait
Why are you doing this all of a sudden
Don't move. Don't move before you get hurt
If you move, you're dead
Save me
Is it under construction
- My eardrums are bursting. - Don't do it
Pain, Don't play
Not that I really don't know
I don't know where to start
Ah, you don't know where it is, do you
That means you know where the clock is, right
I think we're just gonna go down there and arrest people
I don't think so
I was on my way to pick up a guy
You caught a couple of them so you can go back and get promoted
No, no, no.
We can't do this without jurisdiction
It's illegal for you to investigate or arrest here
Hello I said
I was just trying to convince him to turn himself in
What kind of investigation is that?
You go there and you investigate
Aren't you on a blind date
- That's research. - Get over here
- What are you talking about? - Yoo Jong-hoon
Did you say anything
I've been talking bullshit ever since
Monitor this file
I'll just hand it over to immigration
Ah well
Oh, I have a brother here that I know
- I have to go see him. - Okay
Do you know where this is, perhaps
It's not that far from us, is it
But it's kind of a rough neighborhood
That's not a problem
He is more dangerous
Is this
Hello, somebody, somebody.
Fuck locked
- Is it locked? Yes
!
opened
Hey, how did you break the lock
- Shit. - Jongdo Jonghoon already told us everything
South Korea
!
This is what
- why - fuck
Oh my god
What the fuck is going on here
This is a homicide
- Ugh. - Damn it
That's a big head
Call Consul Park
Hey, get up, boy
up
What are you lying about here, boy
What's the matter
Lee Jong-du was murdered
Tell me what you've been doing here
- You want to get beat up? - Sergeant
Not vice president that could be a problem
Squad leader, talk to him
I need you to talk some sense into him
Don't start work
Hey, why don't you stop looking like that
- LET me let you go. - What
- I think that's a good idea. - What
Hurry up to come over
- Come here. - It's not a police officer
I turned myself in
Surrender?
I will not accept surrender you get out
- Get out of here. - Didn't I fucking turn myself in
Arguing in front of who the fuck
Dare to swear in front of anyone
I'll walk you out
- Help me! - Get out of here
Save me
- Go home. - Wait, wait, wait
- What is this about? - I was wrong
- What are you doing? - I'm wrong
Let him down
I am in Vietnam
Ran into a kid named Jiang Haishang and we kidnapped a guy
Who is Jiang Hai Shang
Jianghai is he
Encouraging us to kidnap Choi Yong-ki, who runs the resort
Because Choi yong-ki's family is rich
I'm too young to be polite
Spending money like water
Give me a
It's only $50,000
Fuck not even 90 million Korean dollars
If you got the
Less than 20 million won per person
What the hell is that talking about
hello
What's the matter
Don't tell me you went through all this trouble for a little money
Tell me about it
Clock degrees
I let them in because you said they were sophisticated
I didn't realize it was a bunch of rookies
- What? - You mean a novice
Is it too innocent
What the fuck
Mama of
What are you talking about hello
If it wasn't for boss Choi's money
I would have killed it for you
Oh, look at you for getting fucked
Son of a bitch
Don't you want to make money
Enough is enough
You talk a little bit
- What the fuck. - Hey, hey
- Hey, hey, hey. - Let go
Enough is enough
- What the fuck is this guy? - Put him in fucking custody
Stop! Stop! Stop
I'll come back to it later
Get that son of a bitch
You stop the fuck right there
You fucking
We can't let him get away
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
Fuck what?
Get the fuck out of him
Hey, stand over there fucking right now
I have no choice but to come here
Get the fuck over here.
- Get the fuck over here. - You son of a bitch
Fuck your mother
Do you want to die
Hold on, hold on, hold on
I'll I'll give you 100 million each
- I'll give you $100 million each. - Fuck
- Fuck. - $100 million each
- Are you serious? - In my hotel room
It's over 200 million and a little bit of gold
Just cut me some slack, please
So what the fuck is the code
2963?
2963 that's right!
So I said
If you'd given me the money when I asked for it
- Isn't that all? - I'm sorry
I wish you had told me
It's a fucking effort.
Why don't we make a resort until the kid gets here
Your fucking mouth
You fucking lie one more time and you're dead
Mama of
Dead?
You must be a fucking lunatic
Are you crazy
What if you kill someone
You have no choice
Don't kill the money before you get it
You son of a bitch
Fucking money...
What's going on? Fuck.
It's good to lose personal money
What the fuck is this all about
You're not gonna do your job right
Hurry up, boy
It's really convenient to work abroad
The police don't mind their own business
Convenient operation
From the hotel safe
200 million and a little nugget
That's it?
I think we can get some more
again
Hello to you
First, don't move
Then it takes about two days for the money to arrive
The clock and I just ran away
That kid's eyes changed when the money came in
And then not long ago
Strange people started poking around me
This guy is Jiang Haishang
Sent his men here to kill me, too
I'm sorry
All the more reason you should have said something sooner
Is that why you turned yourself in
right
He clock degrees
Jiang Hai Shang must have killed him, too
He'd kill me if he knew I was here
please
Take me back to Korea, brother
What are we gonna do about this
Look for the bodies
You're happy, aren't you? Damn it
You write down the address here
- The address? - Yeah
The vice monitor
And then things get very complicated
I didn't say anything like that
We need to at least get this address
Ok ok
Monitor of the class
This really needs to be handled by the police
Or you will be forcibly sent home
Then please
- What? - Will you just forcibly repatriate him, please
Forget it
Sergeant, can I do this for you
Alas! The eldest brother
Interesting?
Look up the name Jiang Hae-shang
Let's see if we have a record
Then check if there have been any reports of choi yong-ki's disappearance recently
Kang Hae-sang and Choi Yong-ki
Any other details
Didn't the
Hung up the
Good good
Thank you
So did you say anything
It's the same cops who don't understand cops
It's gonna be a month before we get a warrant
When the time comes jiang Hai is still that boy
He's gone to another country
Well, it's not Korea
That's right Yesterday the whole
Is there anything we can do about him
- I said no. - No, I can't
- Shit. - Where are you going
Vice President
Squad leader deputy squad leader where are we going
I need you to talk to him
Let's go talk to him
He must have listened even less
Have you seen this man
I don't know what you're talking about
Hello tin road,
I know I can't stop you
But this is not Garibong Dong
Wait etc.
- Oh, you are. - Wait a minute
What are you doing here, Officer Ma
I just want to take this kid down
Get out of my way
Wait a minute
The police officer
You really can't
Will you be responsible if anything goes wrong here
That's illegal
I'm not saying if the laws of this country
Can't protect the people of our country
Well, at least we can protect them, right
You're right
Isn't it
Mama of
Call the police the police
Then we'll all be taken away
But are you sure there's something to it
Are you farming
Dig for me seriously faster faster
- It's an earthworm. - Shit
What thing
Hey, I got it. I got it
I fuck
There's also here
It would have been
What a mess
I'll contact the police
There were four bodies
I'm really here on vacation
- What's up, man? - Hello
Have you heard of jiang Haishang
Why are you going after this kid, too
How do you know him
There's a Korean underworld
It's quite famous around here as a ra-nine
It's been around since about three days ago
Jianghai still find
- Pull nine? - Yeah
Where is the boy now
I don't know about that
Is there something wrong with you
Text me when you find out
The eldest brother eldest brother
- What hotel? - What? What
No no no hotel
- We are. - I'm calling you
Mom let go
- We're cops, too. - Squad leader
So many people have died in our country
- How could I do nothing? - Squad leader
How do we not have the right to investigate
I pulled a gun gun gun gun
That's also the case
So let me do it here
- Why don't you go back to the hotel? - Okay, okay
Ok, I know. Sorry, sorry
- Got it. - OK, I know
This kid has to be caught
Just bring it to the Korean consulate
I think I can get a plane back to Korea
How are you gonna catch it
Any plans
Come with me
Wow, it's really hot
Are you there yet?
- Where? - Here, here, here
The boss
Let's go
I want half a million dollars in cash
- You checked with your own eyes, right? - There are a lot of tourist bags
Sure that's right
I confirmed it myself
I also saw Jiang Haishang went out this morning
Did go
good
thank you
Wow, so many
Look at this guy
At least a billion dollars
How many people did you kill? This is
Let's get the money out of here
ok
To find the
How did you get here
I came by bus
Do you think it
All of them are Korean
feed
You come over
To come over
- What? - What
Pull the nine nine call what he is to me
Who are you
All of these are Korean gangsters
Hey, everybody get over here
Are you the police
Get out of here and stop looking for trouble
Is there
Where to go
Just lie down. Lie down
Could get hurt
Just lie down
- Hey. - Lie down
The Korean police came to someone else's place of business
What the hell is wrong with you sons of bitches
Are you the police
You must be Ra-koo
Yeah, I'm a fucking asshole
You are what
- I'm the little one. - That's really bad
You are all dead
This is Vietnam
This is not Korea
fuck
That's a real gun the kid's got
So, this kid's gonna kill somebody
Come here, come here, come here
I'll shoot you in the head
- Don't fuck me. - Spare my life
Stay the fuck away from me
Don't move don't move
All don't move
Don't move or I'll shoot you
Don't move, either of you
If you don't tell the truth from now on
- All right? - All right
Make it clear to me
Why do you want Jiang Haishang
We did take the money
We were given the address details and I don't know
So I said who
All I know is it's from Korea
I know nothing but professional killers
Killer?
right
So we found Jiang Haishang
That little strip over there
hello
Who are you
- I owe you. - Don't owe you. Get over here
- I'll be right back. - Hard work
Brother, where are you?
We just got Kang Hae-sang's location and we're heading there
Did you learn anything
Jiang Haizang requested a friend of the department of information
A survey of
There is something strange about Choi's remarks
- He wasn't reported missing. - Really
What about his parents and the rest of his family
What does his father do
The name is Cui Chunbai
The owner of JOEUNCAPITAL, a private loan firm
Where does Cui Chunbai seem to have heard of this name
HSS this person
He was the head of the myeongdong loan market
The name of the loan company is actually lending money to corporations
A day's worth of cash
More than many chaebol
But the son went missing and never reported it
I'm not gonna dig into him again
Okay, look into it and I'll call you back
good
How's that
He must have been Choi yong-ki's father
Send someone to kill the man who kidnapped his son
what
Here we go
Yo, look at this guy
Give me death
Are you from Korea
Did you take my money
Who sent you
Fucking roll
Cui Chunbai
Cui Chunbai cui Chunbai
Yong-ki's father, right
Yonki's father
I am Jiang Haishang
You're not dead yet
Did you send someone to kill me
You take money and you kill people
You think you're gonna be fine
I told him to go home
But I didn't say anything about bringing him home alive
I'm gonna kill you for sure
Why did you take my money
what
Give it back to me
Otherwise I would have gone back to Korea
This helpless courtesy was eaten by the dog
Hey, wait, wait, wait
- All right. - What are you doing with that gun
I just forgot to give it back
Under such an inferior
The door was open
Mama of
You must have run away on the scent
What the fuck is that
That's a couple of dead people
I think we're a little late
Mama of
But why are there so many travel bags
Young dog
Pick on one of our own
Look at these passports.
This is what
We found Choi Yong-ki
Mama of
Get the fuck over here
You son of a bitch
Are you Jiang Haishang
Is the police
Don't move
Put the knife down
Monitor of the class
What the fuck
This thing is not called a gun shit
I have no idea
No, that's not a bad thing to say
How is this for our own people
The things that come up
If that's what we're gonna do
Of course I know there's an order to everything
Hello tin road,
We got to catch that son of a bitch
I was so angry
You know I'm gonna catch that kid
- You need to calm down. - How do I calm down
I can't even pee alone right now
Damn it, call me if you need to pee
Oh, come back
We're stuck here
How long are you staying
-Uh-huh. Hong Seok
Big brother, are you okay
How about the monitor and others
Sergeant, he's fine.
Jianghai yet?
Intelligence has been gathering information about what's going on in Southeast Asia
Documents on the kidnapping and murder of Korean tourists
Philippines Cambodia
However, the four cases are the same as Jiang Hae-sang's crime methods
After getting close, I got familiar
Threatening money for kidnapping
But no one came back alive after the transfer
How many people in all
So far we've got four
Oh, the eldest brother
Director he also said
I want you to stop getting in trouble and get back here
I got it. Let's go
How are you, Monitor
- Is everything okay? - Ouch
Ok ok
It's just an exaggerated cry of pain
So didn't I tell you to go back to the hotel
Is really of alas
You two
They've all been deported
- What? - When the person in charge comes
You need to get to the airport now
- Wait a minute. - Wait a minute
I need you to behave yourself
That boy Hae-sang Jiang I'm gonna catch him here
The police officer
Not the eldest brother
I said you were so obsessed with catching people out of town
What is the reason
What reason is there to arrest a murderer
Bad guys are what you catch
To grasp
I'm not leaving until I have that kid
I don't go
- I'm sorry. - I really can't leave
- Shit. - I'm really pissed off
- I'm not leaving. - Right
I just brought in the tall guy
what
You have no choice
hello
Jiang Haishang where is he
Eight dead people and you're gonna take them all on yourself
You'll be killed by the police here anyway
hello
If you tell me where Jiang Haishang is
I'll be in charge of requesting your return
immediately
You will be deported from Vietnam
I can't walk
- I'm not leaving. - Wait
Wait, stop, stop, stop
- Tin lane. - Move, move, move, move
Don't do this. Don't do this
To come to
- Come on, let's go. - Let's go
- Let's go. - Let's go
- Korea. - Korea for what
We were evicted, weren't we
We should be evicted
- We're being evicted? - Of course we're obeying the law
Help me out
We Korea Korea go fast
OK, let's go, let's go
- We have to go. - Are you crazy
Hey, aren't we here to catch Jiang Hai Shang
Jiang Haishang he went to Korea to see Cui Chunbai
- Come on. - Go, go, go
Oh, man, this maniac is laughing his ass off
- Oh, man. - Yeah
Hey whistle our monitor how to do this
Don't say
About a dozen guys came over with big knives like this
- If it wasn't for me. - You go home and rest
Back from the
I need to go back and talk to the authorities
- Because I'm the monitor. - Give him his luggage
- All right. - Let's get out of here, too
What the hell are you doing
I need you to help me carry it
This hand of mine is like this
Flying is so tiring
Ouch what to do
We're circling the west Sea crossing to see if there's any boats sneaking in
But the eldest brother
You're sure he's back in town
For sure
By the way, your squad leader almost died
The thought of that wicked criminal makes my blood boil
He attacked a police officer
Just let me see it again
Where are you going
- I'm going to the third floor. - Let's go
There must be no mistake about it this time
- The rest of the money - Jajangmyon takeout
I didn't send the guy who ran away at the airport
- Where do you want it? - Just put it there
The boss
Would you please slowly
I'm gonna tear this place apart for you
- You eat it. - Fuck
- And I ordered sweet and sour pork. - Then I'm out of my way
Order these for one person
How did you know I was here
Do you know navigation
Enter the navigation and it all comes out
hello
Sit down
Illegal aliens sit down
I've been legal for a long time
Ever since I came back from the knife
I'll just do what's legal
Is it legal to take money from smugglers and put them to work
- Kick your ass. - Hey, hey
I don't have time right now
I need you to tell me the boat route from China to South Korea
I told you I haven't done it in a while
What are you doing? That's rude
You can't do that
Long time no see
to
-you didn't hear me
I'm not the jang I-soo I used to be
now
I'm not gonna let you do this to me
HSS
So said
Did any ships come in yesterday or today
Know the
Hung up the
Who?
Nicknamed Captain One-eyed
He runs all the smuggling boats from China
There was a strange ship
Arrived at Gongping Port early this morning
- Hey, call Hong Seok. - Okay
Hello, Hong Seok, where are you now
Ah, not where you put the surveillance near Gongping Port
Bring it all in
- Yeah, wait. - There's more
There are
- No more. - Yeah, that's all
I'm not saying you popped in
- Bullying again. - Cut the crap
I call you and I get it
- Let's go. - Okay
What a fucking dog I am
- Did you call me? - No
Oh, god damn it. Oh, god damn it
Where is this?
This is the parking lot behind Gongping Port
There's nothing there
Look at the next
!
The eldest brother
What's the matter
There's something weird about this guy
He's blowing a tire
Is that a car key
- Uh, I think I found it. - Did you find it
Play back the
Take a look at
suspended
amplification
Wu, 26, 8251
Yeah, that's the guy
Wanted on this car
This guy finally got you
President of
I think Kang Hae-sang came to Korea
Reconnect with the killers
Bring it from the outside
The first two
Two more when you bring the guy in front of me
yes
Bring it to me, alive or dead
Okay, got it.
We'll release the explanation to the press
Get out of here
hello Temasek,
I told you to go back in peace
You're spreading the word all over the place
Are you trying to make things worse
To bore me to death
What's the big deal
I'm trying to catch a prisoner
So why are you arresting people there
They have their own police there, too
And you
You said you'd supervise him and I got you out of here
And you two got me in trouble together
Also shot
Ah, the gun didn't work so well that I didn't fire it too many times
Ah, but the chief's handing it over to external affairs
What does that mean?
It's not that we managed to gather surveillance data
How can you hand over the case to them now that we're close to solving it
You tell me there's nothing I can do
- Shit. - Why can't you always do that
It's really strange
ah
Oh, our chief is not again
You didn't read your report carefully, did you
- Oh, you didn't read it? - Yeah
I don't work
What do you mean
oh
There are now four bodies recovered in Vietnam
In the Philippines and Cambodia
In the case of the kidnapping of Koreans
The suspect is Kang Hae-sang four more cases
This guy is a nut job
So I forwarded it to foreign Affairs
If these are the only ones that should be handed over to foreign Affairs
Anything else?
The father of Choi Yong-ki, who is now dead
Because he killed his own son
He hired thugs in Korea
Tell them to kill Jiang Haishang and his crew
But Jiang Haizang killed all those thugs
Now I'm looking for Cui Chunbai
At this time if Jianghai still appear
Cui Chunbai will he endure
- Isn't that a headache? - That's a headache
Cui Chunbai hired thugs to look for them everywhere
Then Seoul is a sea of blood
Then we'll all be on TV
On TV
- Then we're all screwed. - We're all screwed
- Especially brother. You're the worst. - Worst
- Because you're in charge. - Because you're in charge
Did you write that in the report
Is it gonna get this big
So please
Just read the report, please, please, please
I told you to read it carefully
I can only block it for a week
You have a week to solve this case
A week
- Got it. - Ah
- A week. - A week
- My mother a week. - Oh, my god
alas
I brought my yonky home
You must be the detective
is
Thank you
Please make sure you have a meal before you go
good
To remarry.
No children with his dead first wife
That Choi Yong-ki is the only blood
Understand why you hired a goon
Ah really
Oh, what a bunch of bastards
Gather a lot of
yeah
Ah, what a lovely day!
Can't we reimburse you for the gas
You don't think that's possible
Mama of
Hey, you bought this in installments
- 60 months - days
There are 59 months left
You take care of it not to solve a crime
Sacrifice it, you know
You know how much I love this car
- It's not a used car. - Yeah, Dong-gyun
Well know
- Give me the car keys. - What
East are found jiang Haishan in the car
- I'm going over there. - Let's go. I'll drive
The forehead is not you
Keep a good eye on Cui Chunbai here
You stay here and check the surveillance, okay
- Okay. - Hey, give him your car keys
- My car keys? - Give me yours
I'm much more comfortable with this USB
This is called the SUV
alas
I can't convince you
Oh brother
Hey, did you find anything
Ah Jiang Hai shang this guy can be really careful
I cleaned it up before I threw it away
- Shit. - Didn't find anything
And there's no surveillance around here
Things are getting a little tricky
He waited in the underground parking lot
It's president Zhu's side of the Chinese triad
They can be trusted
If I fail this time I'll kill you first
is
The president is going downstairs. Get ready
Yeah, I'm coming down.
Know the
Let's go
, etc.
What's wrong with these guys
Tut doesn't look like anything
I am Jiang Haishang
You this guy
You this bastard
ahhh
Give me to death
I said I would come to Korea
Where's my money
Say hello to the president
All we have to do is kill someone named Jiang Hae-sang
ah
Who the fuck is this
You got to get over here
Long time no see
What the hell is wrong with the Chinese
You're gonna have to give me a little more money
!
What circumstance
Mama of
Hong Xige is on the first floor underground
Cui Chunbai was kidnapped
And so on mother's
First floor underground Equus Equus
Fucking stop! Stop! Stop! Stop
Mama of
Feed stopped
Big brother, are you okay
Hey, did you see the license plate
Look at the
Is the camera on
Open the camera
Can see!
This is where you're gonna lose your head tomorrow
This is it
$2 billion by tomorrow
Keep your phone on
this
When did you receive it
I picked it up at home last night
- Go ahead and play it. - Okay
- These two are brothers, aren't they? - Yes
Special robber of commission killing
Oh, these guys
These guys are never gonna make it back
These guys fled to the Philippines after they were wanted in Korea
Interpol is also looking for them for murder cases involving Koreans
But investigate the movement
They had the same travel schedule as Kang hae-sang in the Philippines for about six months
This looks like an abandoned factory
Were there any abandoned factories near where we found the car
We don't have any extra backup right now
You used to
Go to the police station over there and dig through it carefully
Well know
hello
Are we gonna be enough on our own
If it fails, it's us
There is no time now
Even though Yonki is with
His dad did a lot of things wrong
But they are my family
Please do something to catch him
What should I do
Yeah, so that's what it means
We can't send him money
It's hard to track him if he's moving money to offshore accounts
Nor does it guarantee your husband's safety
Yeah, that's why it needs to be done in person
I need you to lead him on
And don't get excited when you talk to him
We'll guide you when you call
I'm really sorry for asking you to do this
There's no need to be sorry
There's no other way
There's a phone call. Phone call
Hey, come on, get ready.
- Hey, be quiet. - Wait
Pick up!
hello
I am Jiang Haishang
You just do what I say and he'll be fine, okay
Do you have the money
I'll send you my bank account number now
- Are you an idiot? - Ah
Why would I give you $2 billion
- Uh-huh. - Wait
- Wait a minute. - You son of a bitch
I gave you my money and my son is still dead
I don't know if you're gonna kill my husband this time
How could I possibly send you money
You don't even try
Then your husband will die, too
Well, thank you for that
What you say
hello
You killed my son
If you kill my husband again
Then you tell me who the money goes to
You're going overseas anyway
Isn't it
I'll give you $2 million
You pay me in person and you pay me in person
I'll give it to you as soon as I know my husband is alive
You are so grand, ma 'am
good
Then you'll give me $2 million tomorrow in a suitcase
There are
If you put a tracker in there
Or some weird little stunt where I kill your husband and meet you at your house
Got it!
Until 1:00 a.m. tomorrow
It's on Central Avenue in Sun Hill and you're driving here alone
Have you got it
I can't drive.
I need a driver
- Oh, my God. - Don't you agree
Is the deal off?
There can only be one driver
good
We'll close the deal tomorrow and save your husband...
The whole family looks the same
- Can I have a glass of water? - Yes
good
call
hard
A glass of water
ha
Wow, this old lady is no ordinary person
Wow, I really want to catch that guy
Hey, back to who we're sending to drive
We can't he'll find out
Who sent that
Hey, tut, if a bad pie is found
That could be a big deal
Pretending to be married is not a bad thing
This is how you start your new life
Just close your eyes for three months
the
Did you get the money
However,
- What does a guy look like? - Ah
What do you look like?
Yeah, I'll be right back
hello
Why didn't you answer your phone
You're the one who made a busy man like me stop by
What's going on with this
Ah, what are you doing again
Business wasn't so good anyway, you know
What kind of confirmation is this
Feed you this guy you
This guy's a liar and you can go home
Well, you can't give him the money and go home
Hurry up. Hurry up
- He's an illegal stowaway, too. - Oh, yeah
You come here you come here
You're going to drive a car
Hurry up to come over
Lao zhang
What can I do for you
Hey, Cyclops, get me a boat
Which day of the
- Tomorrow. - Tomorrow
What's all this sudden?
This is a little difficult
Maybe with a little more money
Double to you
When and how many people
Three at one o 'clock
One point three people, please
good
I think he's on the right track
All access to China is now blocked
He's the only one who wants to sneak in quietly
Here we are now
Go up
Enter the city and turn around
I'll give you the signal and you'll bring him down
Let's get rid of grandma here
Just take the money and go on the boat
Why are we the only ones going
Mama of
Are you trying to be clever
You want to take it all without us
You're gonna pick up the money anyway
What are you gonna do with all this distrust
Do you believe us
And you?
Hey, we must catch Jiang Hai Shang today
That guy knows my face with the captain
So you guys just follow me
Get out of the car and look around
good
Jang Yi-soo set out
Oh, shit. That's fucking bad luck
Ha!
Get on the bus
Put the money in the back seat, please
So I can see
She's on her way with a chauffeur
No cops with you
There is no
When they get to Central Avenue follow the battle plan
You have to do what I say, okay
This guy knows how to keep his fucking mouth shut
He still thinks he's our boss
- Detective. - Yeah
Thank you for helping me
Is ah
Don't worry
Confirm mercedes-benz
good
So let's get ready
Hong Seok, take a good look at the cars around you
Hey, Hoon, now you follow me
Well know
Anyone waiting on Central Avenue should take a good look around
I did
What's going on with Mom
You stay with me.
Big brother found the abandoned factory area
But the search was too extensive
It takes a while
Hey, find Cui Chunbai as soon as possible
Good to know brother
We found the Chang brothers
White Elantra 38 horse 1775
Hello, is there jiang Hai Shang
No, there are only two brothers
Where the hell is This guy Jiang Haishang
200 meters to Central Avenue
Immediately to the
Is coming to
You rest assured
I'm an expert in this kind of thing
Chill out
hello
Right on time.
Where are you
First, turn around
what
That delivery truck over there seems to be following us
You slow down first
What's going on with Mom
What do I do
Sit well
Hey, this guy turned around
- You want to follow me? - Hey, hey, just keep walking
Why did you turn around
Sang-hoon, you're going straight
Hello to keep up with
Hey, this guy's walking us. I'll follow them first
Hello's go
Ah, these guys are starting to get smart
Hey, Hong Seok, you wait on the main road
All right, squad leader and Sang-hoon stand by
- Yeah. - Feed us and we'll be there
To quickly get on the bus
Ah, when are we gonna finish searching this place
Mama of
Are you in
This is the first time you've done this
Turn around again
Are you playing with me
Ha ha you this is don't want to get the money
Turn around when you're told to turn around
Mama of
- Turn around. - Shit
Feed the tin and we'll go straight
I want you to follow me this time
Brother the longer we wait the worse for us
We've passed this intersection four times now
This is gonna blow our car out of the water
Hey, Tin Tao why don't we grab these two first
Caught them so quickly that they did not have time to contact Jiang Haizang
Why don't you just call Cui Chunbai later
No we need to make sure Choon-bai is safe first
No, it does matter
- But what if we don't get those two? - No, hostages are more important
I'm freaking out
Whatever the fuck
Mama of
The eldest brother
We found the Hyundai that choi Was driving when we kidnapped her
Oh, yeah, Choi Chun-bai
I don't see. Let me search the building again
Call me as soon as you find it
Well know
Squad leader Dong-gyun found the Hyundai
What? I found it.
Yeah, I got it. I got it. I'll follow
To the
Feeling come
Ha!
There you go. Fuck
Cui Chunbai
It feels like it's somewhere around here
Mama of
hello Cui Chunbai
Well, I guess you're all right
Mama of
Up to the
Uh,
Let's get out of here and get up
It's ok? well
Ah, almost there. Almost there
It's almost there
Ah, these guys are so fucked up
Ah...
here
- Here. - Request backup. Request backup
- We have a suspect. - Ah
fuck
- We have Hae-sang Kang. - We have suspect requesting backup
Suspect in sight suspect in sight
Request support
Son of a bitch
Where are you going, you son of a bitch
You come over
What's going on? Isn't that Choi Chunbai
Yeah let's go get those boys
- We found Choi Chun-bai. - Did you find her
Yeah, I told you I found it
Okay, so here we go
Hey, why aren't you answering your phone
- What's wrong with you? - Ah
Hello boy Wu Dongjun
Feed your zha
- What the fuck? - Oh, captain
Oh, sorry.
- I didn't get the damn Hae-shang. - Fuck
ah
- What? - Call an ambulance
- Hey, Hey, Oh dong-gyun, wake up. - Oh, what's going on
- Hello, Wu Dong-kyun has been stabbed. - What
Jiang Hai is still this dog stabbed and ran away
Mama of
Where are you
How many times have I said this shit
That was at the intersection near LC Department Store
Let's get out of here the police are here
What the hell are you talking about
Note?
What?
- I don't see it here. - Okay
Let's start at the hotel
He threw it away when he came in with a new battle plan
You don't want to be followed
I've been hiding somewhere and now all of a sudden the cops show up
What the hell are you talking about, you son of a bitch
Zhang Jizhe
Stop talking nonsense and we could all be dead
- Huh. - Hello
Are you stubborn with me
We're gonna keep the money for ourselves
You fucking son of a bitch
ok
Hey listen up
We found Cui Chunbai
To grasp the two first
Jiang Haishang stabbed Wu Dongjun and fled
If we can't catch these boys, we can't catch Jiang Hai Shang
Mama of
Well horse Interpol
The horse Interpol
Want to die? fuck
- Put it on speaker. - Got it
- Yes. - Hello, ma 'am
I found your husband
You don't have to worry
Jang I-soo, you see the white Elantra in the back
- Mm-hmm. - From now on, those boys are the first to go
You little bitches
How do we catch them
Keep your distance until I give you the signal
Don't stop. Keep driving
good
Trust me from now on
you
Not the detective.
Clearly?
You cut off the next intersection at the first sign
What the fuck if it's a real cop
Oh, fuck all that
Stick it in front of the old lady and push the baby
...
Oh!
Mama of
- That's that way. - Where? Where
Oh shit
Hey, man, these guys right now
- They all went to the department store over here. - The department store
Hurry up and don't miss it
Mama of
Grasp the
- Get out of the car. - Ah
Quick quick quick run
Do you do?
How do we do that
Hey, what are you doing
Do you want to die
Throw it. Run. Run
Get the fucking money box
- Run, ma 'am. - Yeah
- Open the door. - Hello, no, no, no
- Uh-huh. - Uh-huh
...
ah Smelly boy
You son of a bitch pull over and force the boy
Try it on, you son of a bitch
ah
fuck
rabbit
Let's get in a little fight
Hong Xige underground seventh floor
Hey, hey, make sure you stop them
parking
Let you stop
Ah!
Well!
Fuck it
feed
hello
Where's that kid going
yi
Mama of
- Disperse the crowd. - Yeah
I am a policeman
You don't move
You son of a bitch
I told you not to fuck it
- Uh-huh. - You son of a bitch
- Son of a bitch. - Ah
Hey mom
What am I gonna do to you, you little bastard
Mama of
Who the fuck are you you little bastard
West eight o
- You're hiding from the little shit. - Feed the little shit
- Hey, grab him. - Don't let go
Let go of
Get the fuck off me
Whoa, whoa, whoa, push him over there
ahhh
fuck
- Ah, here, here. - Don't move
Mama of
Don't touch the little bastard
Be honest
- Hey, ma 'am. - We got a suspect
Wife?
- Shit. - Shit
-Aah. -Aunt
ah
Run which go to
- Get out of the way. - Shit
- Get out of my way. - Bitch
Get out of the way get out of the way
You get over here
ah
Where did the driver make the kid go
Where's my money
- Ah. - I said, where are you
Where is the
Get up, you fucking bitch
rabbit
You get out
- Are you all right? - This way
ah
Oh, uh,
...
Oh, are you going down
- Excuse me, excuse me. - This is the police. Excuse me
Please let the
ah
Hey, you guys get this guy out of here
What happened to him? Did he die
Fed up!
It's nice to be
That's so fucking nice
And who the hell is this little bastard
True his mama
Step on the gas.
Hello the
Hello Mr.
Get out of here, you little bastards
That's how you start a new life
The eldest brother
First of all, Zhang Yi Zhu threw off Jiang Hai is still
But Jiang Haishang is the fucking kid
And now he's on the run after stabbing a vigilante
The fuck
Feed the country wanted Jiang Haishang
- Yeah. - Dongyun
Ah, the monitor took him to the hospital
Eldest brother could not get in touch with Jang Yi-soo
Don't answer the phone
Looks like he took the money and ran
The gang that staged the kidnapping downtown
caught
A nationwide manhunt is underway for the stabbing of one of the vigilantes
After the escape of the main culprit Jiang mou
- The main culprit, Mr. Kang. - Ha
Police also suspected theft
On suspicion of murder.
Trade at ransom
Jang, an Ethnic Korean with 2 million dollars
Police speculated that Jang would smuggle himself into China
So they're searching the west coast
fuck
- Hello. - One-eyed
What's the matter
Please find me a ship to China
A ship to China
Ah, no boats now
Oh, fuck you to find it for me
Ha, you think a boat is a taxi
That's all of a sudden
What else was I supposed to do
- Fuck. - I told you there was no boat
I'll give you double double
If it was double that, there'd be a boat
Hiss but there's no room for this one
Mama of
I'll give you double double, you little bastard
Where are you
I'm sending my youngest son to pick you up right now
From behind the waterfront parking lot
good
Ah...
...
Are you Jang I-soo
Take the money with you
Here you count
just
From here to the middle of the sea
hello
You who ah
Haven't you seen the news
Massy said the little bastard
Hey, you little bitch
Do you know who I am
You who ah
I'm Zhang Qian from Harbin
Ha!
Give it to the little bastard
Go on, you little bastard
Hey, wait a minute, wait a minute
You stay away from me, son of a bitch
Don't you little bastard come near me
rabbit
Lucky for you, you little bastard fuck
- No, you're not. Get over here. - Why not
No, you don't
No, no, no, no, no
Don't don't don't
o
I am a policeman
In the line of duty
Please get off the bus and thank you
Well, if you could just get out of the car
What you say
Um, auntie, please get out of the car
The aunt takes this to her grandson
- Thank you. - Well, slow down
call
Oh, damn it.
I'm tired because that son of a bitch
What made you think of catching the bus
Brains are smarter than they look
Well, that's smart
Ah, why do you keep chasing me that's disgusting
You are short of money
What do I have to give you
50-50 split!
Who take 5 ah
Ha, you really can't you
Mama of
You need a good beating
If I feel like I'm going to die
It would be
Ring the bell and I'll let you off
fuck
Come here, son of a bitch
hello
Not even close get up, you son of a bitch
...
I'm gonna fucking kill you
With your family
Yo!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, this is big. This is big. Fuck
Oh I'm sorry
Let's go faster, faster, faster
Hey, are you all right
- Yeah. - Jiang haishang
The?
Hey, money, money, money
- What about it? - Oh
- Yeah, go get it. - Go get it
- Yeah. - But how did the bus get like that
well
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
Take the money
What the fuck is going on here
Hey, what's going on here
Oh, yeah. I told him to catch criminals
How did they send someone to the funeral
Fuck you, ma Sai, you boy
Alas!
It's
rabbit
- Hello. - Hello
We got Jiang Haishang
You worked your ass off, son
And they put a warrant out on me
And just say it's hard and that's it
I knew it
Son of a bitch
Hello how are you
- You're taking the money and running now? - I don't know
I almost died trying to get away from him
Why don't you stop running and go sneak
- What's not? - Call Captain One-eyed
Book a boat for China today, you hear me
smuggling
You tell the truth, you little boy
I thought you were gonna take the money and run
Hello hello hello
Hello how are you
We have a bad signal here.
hello
hello Zhang Yizhu
rabbit
Alas!
call
Kang, who killed 13 people in total, was arrested
Kang brutally murdered Korean tourists in Southeast Asia
Brutally killing South Korean tourists
Kidnapped Choi to take the money and flee overseas
He was arrested by police
Choi was rescued to avenge the death of his son
For allegedly sending contractors to Vietnam
And was transferred to the court for trial
The police used the incident as a turning point
In order to compete with the High crime rate of Koreans
Southeast Asian countries cooperate in the investigation
Countries are being discussed
A plan to dispatch the police
Oh, by the way, my rear view mirror is broken
- What about that, Captain? - Mine, too
Hey, hey, you guys worried about the car
I got knifed, kid
Alas!
- Stabbed with a knife this small. - Yeah
Hey, it was Marchetti who got stabbed
About this long
That's how I got stabbed
So deep I thought it was penetrating. I
- You thought it was pierced. - Yeah
I thought I almost lost my neck
Oh, hey, hey, don't lie. Don't lie
- I didn't lie. - And they worked hard
This is pig brittle bones or something
I think we're gonna have to eat beef
Yeah, I got it. I got it
- Oh, yeah. - Here we go
I knew you were gonna say that so today
- Got a big one. - What
Ballantine's been here for 30 years
- This is over a million won. - Hey, wait a minute
I'm on it. I'm on it
To the well
Yes, yes, yes, not now
Hey, there was supposed to be something up here
- What? What? - Thank you, loyalty, loyalty
Well, it's been drunk
Drink too
- I've had some before. - Yeah, I've had some
- Is it obvious? - Oh, really
- Obviously. - Hey, don't drink. Don't drink
-Not anymore? -Not if it's obvious
Obviously don't drink it
to So I
This time with ginseng wine 30 years old
Ginseng wine 30 years old
- It's true. - I just
Is it just me
It's true. It's true
To a cup of
To Wu Dongjun
How about a cup of
- Two drinks. - Don't drink anything weird
- Thank you. - Pour a glass
- You don't have to. - I don't have to
- It's not bad. - It's not bad
Hey, don't drink the weird stuff
Let's toast everybody for your hard work
hard
Watch any video online with Open-SUBTITLES
Free Browser extension: osdb.link/ext