Last season
on "That Girl Lay Lay"...
I was talking
to my positive affirmation app.
You got this, Sadie.
It would be so cool
if you were here.
I wish you were real.
Ah!
You can freeze time?
Mom, Dad, I was wondering
if we could be
Lay Lay's host family.
It would be like
a wish come true.
I hear everything.
No one knows you're
the avatar I wished to life.
Yeah!
What?
I can explain.
Explain that.
Okay, Marky.
We need to talk.
Now, this is how you
make a bed the right way.
And this it's how you make
a bed the Lay Lay way.
What's wrong with you?
Anyway, have you seen
Marky yet?
Not since he found out
you're an avatar
that came out of my phone.
Girl, I've never seen
someone scream so loud
and run so fast.
And I've seen your father
around a cricket.
And that's after we
explained everything to Marky.
Yeah.
Now that he knows my secret,
we got to make sure he's cool.
Otherwise, he's gonna tell
your parents.
And they'll know
we've been lying to them.
There's nothing my parents hate
more than liars.
Maybe raisins and coleslaw,
but liars are up there.
Hopefully, he's
not freaking out.
I'm still freaking out.
I can't believe I've been
around Lay Lay this long
and never noticed
anything strange about her.
Or did I notice,
and you made me forget?
Do you have mind-wipe powers?
Stop wiping my mind.
She didn't.
You just didn't notice
anything strange about her.
Because there's nothing
strange to notice.
Besides, you're a 10-year-old
who wears a sweater vest.
I wouldn't talk, little one.
Marky, this is a good thing.
When Lay Lay was
in my phone,
she was an avatar
for my positive affirmation
app.
Yes.
I'm really good
at helping people become
the best versions
of themselves.
Look at me.
Because of Lay Lay,
I'm more outgoing,
and I'm the president
of my class now.
She even gave me the confidence
to become an era-era DJ.
Some people say
I got it going in...
On?
Out?
Whatever.
People are talking.
I'm talking about how,
just 12 hours ago,
I saw you turn invisible.
Okay.
Did it scare you?
Please.
I'm done freaking out.
Okay.
- Boo!
- Ah!
I was wrong.
I'm still freaking out!
ENJOY ALL VOD IN HIGH QUALITY @ 4KVOD.TV
GET LIVE TV,MOVIES,SHOWS IN ONE PACKAGE
This is either
their happy dance,
or they stepped
in some fire ants.
Girls, we just got some
of the best news
of our careers.
Oh, let me guess, Bun B
sampled one of your songs,
and now you're rich, so we can
spend the rest of our lives
on private jets and yachts.
No, but thank you for making
our good news less exciting.
We were named Advertising
Songwriters of the Year
by the Cleveland Hall of Fame
Music Awards.
Whoa!
You won a CHoFMA?
That's how John Legend
became John Legend.
Before he won a CHoFMA,
he was just John.
There's a fancy ceremony
coming up,
and anybody who's anybody
in the biz attends.
Winning an award like this
triples your business.
So maybe there
will be a yacht.
There ain't gonna be
no yachts.
Look, can't you just
be happy for us?
Bryce, tell them who we're
asking to introduce us.
Our friend,
hip-hop superstar...
Iggy Azalea.
Really?
You stole my thunder?
Mr. A, you know Iggy Azalea?
Oh, you're not as lame
as Sadie says you are.
I never said lame.
I said... I love you, daddy.
Iggy is the perfect person
to do it.
Yeah, we co-wrote a jingle
with her before she blew up.
We're practically peers.
Yeah, just like
Mrs. A's workout buddy
is Michelle Obama.
Right.
Michelle wishes she had
this arm definition.
And every year, the CHoFMA
recipient gets to pick someone
to perform at the ceremony.
Oh, here's a crazy idea
that isn't so crazy.
What if Lay Lay and I perform?
Oh, girls, I'm sorry.
I think what the music awards
are looking for
is more of a big-name act.
What's bigger than someone
with two names?
Come on, Mom and Dad,
we want to perform
in front of Iggy Azalea,
and this is your big night.
We want to be a part of it.
Please, Mrs. A.
I won't beg you,
but I will make Sadie do it.
Okay, but you girls got
to bring your A game.
Yes.
We get to perform
in front of Iggy Azalea.
Sounds like it's gonna be
a big night for all of us.
Oh, what was that dance
you all were doing
when we walked out here?
Hmm.
♪ I'm Sadie's
affirmation app ♪
♪ And so no matter
what happens, I got her back ♪
♪ 'Cause see my homey Sadie
wished on a star ♪
♪ She said,
"I wish you were real" ♪
♪ Now I'm as real as you are ♪
♪ And now who's coming
out the app? ♪
♪ That girl Lay Lay ♪
♪ Who's avatar power
is to freeze? ♪
♪ That girl Lay Lay ♪
♪ All day, all day,
it's your girl ♪
♪ That girl, that girl,
that girl Lay Lay ♪
Okay.
I think I got all
the freaking out out.
Do you want to hear
about Lay Lay's other powers?
There's more?
Can you fly?
Shoot lasers out of your eyes?
Turn broccoli into brownies?
No.
Lay Lay's powers
are related to the phone.
When she holds her breath
and disappears,
it's like a phone
going into rest mode.
And have you ever hit
pause on a video?
Whoa.
How is that possible?
Anything's possible
when you're this fabulous.
Okay.
So I can't catch,
but I can freeze time.
And if there's anyone
I don't want to freeze,
I just have
to think about them.
Wait, have you ever frozen me
before,
and I didn't know it?
Wait.
Have you ever frozen me
before,
and I didn't know it?
Of course not, Marky.
I didn't think so.
I'm way too smart for that.
What did Mom and Dad say when
they learned about Lay Lay?
Oh!
Uh, I'll never forget
what they said.
Right?
What'd they say, Lay Lay?
Uh, they said, "Wow,"
and... and "Whoa,"
and then your mom...
She was like, "Whee!"
Hey, kids.
Hey, Dad.
How come you never
told me Lay Lay...
Marky, Mr. A doesn't want
to talk
about me being an avatar.
Yeah.
He's so over Lay Lay
and her powers.
Wait a minute.
You never told them.
I certainly don't not did.
You're doing that weird
double negative thing
when you lie.
I certainly am
not not doing that.
Sadie, this is why I
never play spades with you.
You are the only other person
besides us
who knows the secret.
Well, there's also a goat
who knows everything,
but she ain't no snitch.
Wait.
If I'm the only one that knows,
that means you two
need me to keep this secret.
And you know that means?
That we have a bond
more sacred
than a pinky promise?
No.
It means you two
work for me now,
or I tell Mom and Dad
everything.
You wouldn't dare.
Who am I talking to?
Of course he would dare.
Lay Lay,
we have to do what he says.
Ugh!
How come I never told you
Lay Lay was what, Marky?
That Lay Lay is
such a good mime.
Sadie, too.
Show them
trapped-in-the-box, girls.
Okay.
Why don't you guys stay
locked in that box,
and I'll just leave?
- Oh, that was close.
- Yeah.
Good cover, Marky.
It's nice to have you
on team Lay Lay.
Oh, no.
From now on,
this is team Marky,
and I need a fan
and foot rub stat.
Say what now?
Why would we ever do that?
Mom?
Dad?
Oh, yeah.
This is gonna work out
just fine.
Marky's been
wearing me out, Sadie.
He had me freeze time twice
just so he could get a snack
during his favorite TV show.
Just press pause, Marky.
I know.
I made the snacks.
But I snuck down here
to work on our song.
Good, because we really need
to rehearse for the CHoFMAs.
It's your parents' big night,
and Iggy Azalea
is gonna be there.
We got to bring it.
Oh, it's been brung.
Come on.
You like that?
All right.
Come on.
Break with me, girl.
And break it with me, girl.
Break it with me.
Shimmy, shimmy, shimmy.
Oh, no shimmy.
No shimmy?
I can't.
Oh, I've never heard
you hiccup before.
You okay, Lay Lay, or was
my dancing just that bad?
Marky has been nonstop
with his demands.
He had me use my powers
a million times today,
and your dancing is that bad.
If it isn't
my favorite girls.
Ugh!
I've got
a new entrepreneurial endeavor
that you two are gonna love
helping me with,
because I said so.
Marky, we've got to practice
for our performance,
and Lay Lay is tired
from all your demands.
Stop power tripping
on her powers.
I hear you, but I've got
financial independence
to achieve.
That's why I invested in a new
instant hair removal cream
called InstaShave.
What do you know
about hair removal?
The closest thing you have
to a mustache
is ketchup on your lip.
I don't need it,
but the A-listers
at the CHoFMAs will.
And if the right celebrity
gets a hold of InstaShave,
my business will boom.
Uh-uh.
I see where this is going.
You want us to use
InstaShave on our heads.
What?
I'm not doing that.
- These buns are...
- Iconic.
Calm down.
All the celebrities get
gift bags full of swag.
You think I don't know
what swag is?
Look at me.
All I need you to do is sneak
some samples of InstaShave
into the CHoFMA swag bag
so that every celebrity
leaves with it.
What if we say...
No?
I'll say...
Mom, Dad!
Fine.
Whatever you want, Marky.
Or I can take
this lovely pillow
and smack the snitch
out of him.
No, Lay Lay.
Put the pillow down.
Hey, hey, hey!
No, no.
- Hey, stop!
- You want to do this?
- Let me do this!
- No.
- No more.
- Let me go.
Hey, bad Lay Lay.
Bad Lay Lay.
Bad, bad, bad.
Honey, how are we
supposed to know what
Iggy Azalea's assistant
looks like?
They all look the same...
Computery, glasses,
pale, and weak
from too much screen time.
Hi.
I'm Jasmine,
the pale and weak assistant
you're here to meet.
You're Iggy Azalea's
assistant?
- Yeah.
- But you're so young.
Am I, or are you
just really old?
Listen, little girl...
Uh, thank you.
Thank you for taking the time
to meet with us.
So Iggy would love to give
your presentation speech.
Yes!
I celebrated too soon,
didn't I?
Little bit.
As her new assistant,
I need to make sure
that she's associating
with the right people.
Mrs. Alexander,
it's to my understanding
that you're a bit of a...
diva.
Excuse me?
Oh, no, you said the D word.
Iggy said you got
into an argument with her
the last time
you worked together.
Oh, no, she's still
hung up on that?
I wouldn't call it
an argument.
It's just she was wrong,
and I was right.
And apparently,
you told her that, a lot.
It was a jingle
for Hooper's Hot Tubs,
but it was so long ago,
who can even remember...
Okay.
She wanted
♪ Ooh, my, my, buy a hot tub ♪
But I knew it should be
♪ My, my, ooh,
buy a hot tub ♪
You heard it.
I was right.
Should I be talking to you?
I think that would be best.
The only way Iggy is willing
to introduce you two
is if I get a video
of her apologizing.
Okay.
I understand.
Come on, baby.
Say you're sorry.
Oh, that's not it.
Iggy wants Trish to do
an "I'm sorry" dance
so she can share it
with her millions of followers.
Oh, and you're gonna love
this song.
It goes
♪ Ooh, my, my, I'm sorry ♪
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry that you wasted
your breath
singing that nonsense.
Honey, honey, having
Iggy Azalea introduce us
would be a huge deal.
Just... just apologize.
Who cares now?
No.
Please, baby, baby, please.
No, baby, baby, no.
You have 24 hours
to change your mind.
I'll be here same time
tomorrow.
Oh, right.
I ordered lunch,
but now I'm not hungry.
Iggy would want you
to pay for it.
Okay, bye.
What even is InstaShave?
Sweet James Brown,
Marky is going to need
more than a celebrity
endorsement to sell this goop.
Oh, yeah.
That stuff definitely works,
because it just burned out
all my nose hairs.
Okay.
These are custom labels
with my adorable smile on them.
No one could say no
to this face.
You want us to put those
labels on every single one
of these containers?
Oh, not just these.
There's 12 more boxes.
So you girls had better
get a move on.
Toodles.
Let's get to work.
As long as we're
under Marky's thumb,
we're never gonna get a chance
to rehearse for the CHoFMAs,
and we can't let
my parents down.
You're right.
We're gonna be here all night.
Bars.
Wait, I know.
We can multitask.
Let's rehearse our performance
while we finish Marky's work.
Come on, girl.
♪ Rip and dip that hip ♪
Okay.
♪ Go, Lay Lay ♪
♪ Go, Sadie ♪
♪ Do the Say Say ♪
♪ Hey ♪
♪ Whoa, whoa ♪
- Do a hip.
- Oh!
Get into it!
Is this fun
and frolicking I see?
No, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no!
I want less "Happy Feet"
and more "Hard Knock Life."
You know what?
Forget this.
I'm going upstairs to get me
a drink and kick my feet up.
Do I need to tell
my parents your secret?
I wish you would.
Oh, I feel weird.
Something's happening.
Wow.
She's moving with super speed.
Well, that's a new one.
Whoa.
What was that?
Did I just...
Zip around the room
like Usain Bolt
strapped to a rocket ship?
Yeah.
Yeah, you did.
You just found
a new avatar power.
It's like speeding up
a video on your phone.
Which is perfect,
because we have
so many more containers
to label.
Wait, did I say we?
Because I meant y'all.
Well, I guess this
will give us more time
to rehearse, since...
I can get this done quicker.
Yeah.
Maybe you're right.
Let's go, Lay Lay,
clap, clap.
Super speed, invisibility,
freezing time?
With her avatar powers
and my business genius,
we're gonna take over
the world.
Thank you so much
for doing this.
It's just
a silly apology video,
and then tonight,
we'll be introduced
at the Cleveland Hall of Fame
Music Awards by Iggy Azalea.
Who was wrong.
Yeah.
See, I know you were right,
and you know you were right.
So what's it matter
if her millions of followers
think you were wrong?
I'm gonna need one more.
Please, baby, baby, please.
Ew, you're
somebody's parents.
Have you made your decision?
I have.
I'm doing this for you.
- For us.
- Whatever.
Hit record, little girl.
♪ Ooh, my, my, I'm sorry ♪
♪ Ooh, my, my, I was wrong ♪
♪ Ooh, my, my,
your way was better ♪
♪ This is my apology song ♪
Ooh, my, my.
We're going to break
the Internet.
And Iggy is gonna
introduce us tonight.
You know it.
'Kay, bye.
Thank you so much
for doing this for us.
I'm sorry you had to go
through all this.
Oh, you can apologize
better than that.
- What do you mean?
- Uh-huh.
- No.
- Ready?
No, serious...
Ready, five, six, seven,
eight.
♪ Ooh, my, my, I'm sorry ♪
♪ Ooh, my, my, I was wrong ♪
Yeah.
♪ Ooh, my, my,
your way was better ♪
♪ This is my apology song ♪
Babe, I forgot
to press Record.
Yeah.
One more.
Five, six, seven, eight.
♪ Ooh, my, my, I'm sorry ♪
♪ Ooh, my, my, I was wrong ♪
I moved so fast,
my brain got jiggled,
and I do not like jiggly brain.
Good job.
The first phase
of Operation Marky Gets Rich
is complete.
Whoa.
Lay Lay,
you're hiccupping again.
Are you Okay?
Oh yeah, I just...
Need a minute.
Hey, kids.
We got something to tell you.
We just booked Iggy Azalea.
Bars.
Good job, Mom.
You're not as lame
as Sadie says you are.
I never said that.
I said... I love you, Mommy.
Our 15 minutes of fame
just turned into 20.
Whoo!
Why are we running?
I'm too excited to walk.
Okay.
Your parents' night
is gonna be so amazing.
It's like a dream come true.
Speaking of dreams,
let's talk about my dreams...
Money!
Lay Lay, you're gonna use
your super speed powers
to get my samples
into every gift bag,
including Iggy's.
You're gonna
make us work more?
You're killing me, Marky.
I can't perform
after filling up
all those bags
with super speed.
I'm the queen of extra,
but that is too extra.
Oh, I don't feel good.
What are you doing?
Lay Lay Lay.
Lay Lay Lay Lay Lay Lay.
Why do you keep
saying your name?
Lay Lay Lay Lay Lay Lay.
Uh-oh.
"Lay Lay" is all she can say.
This isn't good.
Lay Lay Lay Lay.
Lay Lay.
What is wrong
with her, Sadie?
You had her doing too much.
Marky, you broke Lay Lay.
- Lay Lay Lay Lay Lay Lay.
- Oh, this is bad.
This is bad.
- Lay Lay Lay Lay.
- I know.
You're glitching.
- Lay Lay Lay Lay.
- I know.
If we don't fix this,
it'll ruin my parents' night
and our chances
of performing in front
of era-era Iggy Azalea.
Lay Lay Lay Lay.
You're right.
Then my parents will find out
you're an avatar from my phone,
and they'll know
that we lied to them.
Then, they'll hand you
over to the government,
where you'll be plugged
into a giant supercomputer
in Nevada.
Oh, and then I'll never see
you, because my mom says
the desert makes her ashy,
and we won't go there.
You understood all that?
Of course, I did.
I'm her bestie.
Lay Lay.
Well, what about
my InstaShave plans?
Lay Lay!
I understood that one.
Hey, kids we were
so excited about Iggy,
I forgot to ask
if your song was ready.
We're good.
Great.
You don't not have
anything to worry about.
Sweet James Brown,
a double negative?
What's wrong?
Trish Showtime Alexander
will get you ready.
Trish?
We have a serious situation.
Jasmine's coming over.
She wants to hear our speech.
Oh, right.
We have to make a speech.
I was so focused
on getting Iggy on board,
I kind of did not
not think about it.
A double negative?
Mom, are you okay?
I'm not not fine.
Everybody, get off my back.
When you mother has
to speak in public,
she gets, uh,
a little freaked out.
But she's
Trish Showtime Alexander.
She's great at performing.
When she has
to sing or dance.
But when she has
to give a speech,
you get Trish
deer-in-the-headlights
Alexander.
See?
Roadkill.
This is our big night.
We can't look crazy
in front of our peers.
Or in front of Iggy.
Who is also our peer.
Lay Lay.
- What is happening?
- Lay Lay.
She's just saying,
♪ Go, Trish ♪
♪ You got this ♪
Yes.
I can do this.
Whoo!
Now you're running?
Lay Lay fired me up.
We have to figure out
how to fix Lay Lay,
because this ain't okay-kay.
Lay Lay.
Oh, you're right.
That is bars.
Oh, what am I gonna do?
You know I can't speak
in front of people.
This is your fault.
How is it my fault?
When we got married,
it gave me license
to blame all
my irrational fears on you.
Listen, babe,
big daddy Bryce got you.
I learned a thing or two
about public speaking
when I was in the play
"Cat on a Hot Tin Roof."
Just get to the point, Bryce.
Okay.
Confidence is the key.
Now, pretend I'm the audience,
and confidently,
let me hear your speech.
Hi
Okay, uh, that could use
a little work.
Oh, I can't do it.
I can't speak in front
of all those people.
My mom's gonna think
I don't appreciate her.
Oh my gosh, it's Jasmine!
Relax.
I'm gonna open the door.
You're gonna do your thing,
and Jasmine's gonna love it.
I got this.
Hi.
I'm so excited
to hear your speech.
And go.
Okay, do your thing.
Hi
Should I call the paramedics?
I know.
It needs work.
Okay?
Trish performs better
when there's a beat.
So what if she did it
like a spoken word,
and I'll accompany
with some bongos?
Okay.
Make that work.
Love you both.
Air kisses.
Bye.
I know you're nervous,
but two days
before the opening night
of "Cat on a Hot Tin Roof,"
- we...
- Okay, bye.
Lay Lay.
I love it.
Thanks.
My hair looks fantastic.
Lay Lay.
Yeah, yeah, I know.
No one's hair
is as fly as yours.
Lay Lay.
I got it.
I know how to fix Lay Lay.
You do?
Lay Lay came from your phone.
Right?
So why don't we fix her
like a phone?
I called a cell phone repairman
from Nerd Knights
and told them my phone
was glitching.
They'll be right over.
Won't they be suspicious
when they see your phone
isn't broken?
That's why...
I put yours
in a pitcher of water.
Marky!
You'll thank me later.
Okay.
The Nerd Knight van
just pulled up.
You guys stay here and listen.
When he tells me
how to fix my phone,
I'll yell the instructions
to you, and you follow them.
Okay?
Sounds like a great plan.
Lay Lay.
Yep.
It's a totally stupid plan.
Hear ye, hear ye.
It is I, Sir Fix-A-Lot.
I like big ruts
and I cannot lie.
So what, pray tell, seems
to ail thee, me lord?
My good sir,
the phone keeps glitching.
Ah, the dreaded glitch.
Oh, how it lays low
the good townspeople.
Well, nary thee worry, me lord.
I can slay
this dragon of a problem.
Awesome.
What do we do?
Well, first,
we want to remove
all frivolous features
that could be slowing down
thy phone.
- Got it.
- Got it, yes.
I'll remove
everything frivolous!
Okay.
Let's get rid
of this stuff you don't need.
Lay Lay.
Got it.
Bling is not frivolous.
Well, also, sometimes,
thy phone can overheat.
Now, may I recommend
the fanning motion?
Shake the phone
to cool it down!
Lay Lay Lay Lay Lay Lay.
Lay Lay.
The final step,
the coup de grace,
would be to hold down
thy power button
to reset thy phone.
Hold down
the power button
to reset the phone!
Kid, are you okay,
or do you just like shouting?
Power button?
Where's your power button,
Lay Lay?
- Lay Lay.
- Okay.
Lay Lay.
Lay...
Once thy phone reboots,
it should function
in its normal capacity,
and verily, thou shall live
happily ever after.
Thanks, Sir Fix-A-Lot.
My pleasure, my lord.
I am off henceforth and whither
to the windows to the wall.
Exeunt with a flourish.
- It worked?
- I think so.
She's still rebooting.
We need a little more time.
Kids, time to leave
for the CHoFMAs.
Sadie, drop Lay Lay and run.
Marky, calm down.
I have an idea.
One second, Mom.
Is that the bongo
for my speech?
No.
This is the bongo for the luau
I'm going to after the show.
Let's leave
the sarcasm at home, huh?
Kids, we have to go.
We're gonna be late.
Ready for the CHoFMAs.
Oh, Bryce,
let me fix your collar.
Ready?
It's time to go.
The driver's here.
You got us a driver?
No.
It's me.
I'm the driver.
Let's go, kids.
Right behind you.
Hey, this girl's bling
is heavy.
How does she hold herself up?
I hope she reboots soon.
It's almost showtime.
Whoa.
Something's happening.
Do you think
the reboot worked?
Lay Lay?
It did not.
That Sir Fix-A-Lot
is getting one star.
Fake it till you make it.
Tonight, we own the world.
Or at least
downtown Cleveland.
Oh, hey, kids.
Hey...
Come over here for a sec.
Look at this place.
In just an hour,
it's gonna be filled
with hundreds of people.
You got your hands full,
bongo boy.
Hi, guys.
Hi, Jasmine.
Where's Iggy?
Funny story.
Not in a ha-ha way,
more like a,
"Ooh, that's completely ruined
your night" kind of way.
Jasmine, you don't want
to play with me right now.
Cut to the chase.
All right.
Iggy was dropping a puck
at a big hockey game in Calgary
and got snowed in.
She can't make it to the show.
What?
She's really sorry,
like super-duper sorry.
What are we supposed to do?
This is our parents' big night.
Lay Lay!
That's right, Lay Lay.
You're going to get
to perform, too.
If it's any consolation,
Iggy said
I should introduce you guys.
How is that consolation?
We told everyone that she
was gonna introduce us.
We're gonna look like fools.
Guys, this is not
the end of the world.
Trish, you and I are
still getting a CHoFMA,
and I know you're gonna rock
that speech.
- Am I?
- Yeah.
Of course, I am,
because I've been waiting
for this moment
my entire career,
and my mama didn't raise
no coward.
Sadie and Lay Lay,
I know you're gonna electrify
this crowd.
- Lay Lay!
- Hey!
That's the spirit!
They're gonna chant
your name.
That's right.
Lay Lay and I are ready.
I hope.
Guys, we're Alexanders.
I know this isn't exactly
how we planned it,
but it's still gonna be
a magical night.
You're right, Dad.
This is going to be
a magical night.
Don't mess it up.
I wasn't done yet.
It's gonna be a magical night
because I get
to be on stage with my family.
There's nothing
better than that.
We got this.
Alexanders on three.
You're introducing us.
Get in here, too.
Yay, I'm so excited.
One, two, three.
- Alexanders!
- Lay Lay!
Lay Lay, I wish you could
say something other than...
- Lay Lay.
- Yup.
That's the one.
Sweet James Brown,
we've struck the mother lode.
It's all the swag bags.
Lay Lay, I'm gonna need you
to use
your super speed powers
to get these samples
into those gift bags.
Whew.
She did it.
Why are Lay Lay's hands
shooting fireworks?
That's just the magic
of the scheme coming together.
Lay Lay, you're amazing.
No, girl.
You're amazing.
Lay Lay, you said
something other than "Lay Lay."
You got this.
Oh, no.
Those were Lay Lay's
default phrases
when she was in my phone.
When we reset her,
she must have went back
to factory mode.
Are you there?
Lay Lay, it's me, Sadie.
Hi. I'm Lay Lay.
- What's your name?
- What?
No.
You know me.
Nice to meet you, Nome.
I'm Lay Lay.
Oh, no.
Marky, this is not good.
She doesn't know who I am.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to break her.
Whatever you say, superstar.
She's gone.
My best friend is gone.
When life gets you down,
turn that frown upside down.
You actually paid
for an app that talks
like this?
Marky, you don't understand.
Lay Lay helped me
with my confidence.
She helped me come out
of my shell.
She's like the sister
I never had.
Get your boot-scooting booty
on down to the Boot Barn,
where we've got
the best prices in town.
Yee-haw.
Is that a commercial?
You didn't even get
the ad-free version?
It wouldn't have been
financially responsible.
Ain't nothing to it
but to do it, girl.
Welcome
to the Cleveland Hall of Fame
Music Awards.
Oh, this is bad.
We have to go on stage soon,
and everyone will find out
Lay Lay's secret.
Maybe no one will notice
something's off about Lay Lay?
Hola, amigos,
y vamos el Boots Barn.
Yee-haw.
Yeah.
Someone's gonna notice.
Lay Lay, please, hear me.
You're a real teenage girl now.
You're not the avatar
for my positive affirmation
app.
A smile goes with any outfit.
Look at her.
My best friend is broken.
Without her, I'm lost.
I'm sorry.
I feel horrible.
I didn't mean for this
to happen.
You trusted me with a secret,
and I took advantage.
I swear, I would do anything
to get Lay Lay back.
Wow, Marky, that's
really nice of you to say.
Of course, now,
it doesn't matter,
because you destroyed
my best friend, but thanks.
And now,
let's get the CHoFMAs going
with the presentation
of Jingle Writers of the Year.
Hi.
I'm Jasmine.
In just a minute,
you'll get to hear Trish
and Bryce's daughter Sadie
and her friend Lay Lay
debut a new song.
But first, give it up
for the advertising
songwriters of the year,
Bryce and Trish Alexander.
Marky, we need to figure out
what we're gonna do
with Lay Lay.
She's still broken.
Boom.
That's what I'm talking about.
Girl power.
Oh, man.
Lay Lay and I are supposed
to perform next, but if we do,
someone will figure out Lay Lay
is an avatar from my phone,
and then the men in black
will show up,
and they'll do that thing
where they just stare at you
until you start talking.
And if you don't talk, they'll
offer you a stick of gum
and stare at you
until you do talk.
And then, they'll take away
my best friend,
and all I'll have left
is a stick of gum.
And it'll be winter mint,
which everyone knows
is the worst flavor of gum,
because it burns your tongue.
I'm going to be friendless
with a burning tongue.
You've got this, babe.
Remember, confidence.
Get your Badu on.
Wow.
Dreams really do come true.
Like the sky that is blue,
pride runs from my head
to my feet.
Thank my mama
for believing in me.
Mama, I took pride in my work,
like you said I could,
and now your little girl did it
like you said I should.
Wait.
I have to thank
one more person.
Okay, then.
I'd like to think
my kindergarten teacher,
Mrs. Kreider.
Oh, and my first grade teacher,
Mrs. Weldon.
I got her through
the stage fright.
I'm that good.
Yeah.
Is she ever gonna stop?
No.
She's on one.
And to Nelly Sal win,
that girl in seventh grade,
I have some words for you.
Sorry.
Rest in peace, Nelly.
They're about
to put you guys on stage.
Lay Lay, if you
can hear me in there,
please know I loved having
you be a part of my life.
You were the best bestie
anyone could ask for.
If you don't try,
you'll always wonder why.
Ah, ever since
those stupid hiccups,
she just hasn't been Lay Lay.
That's it.
Maybe if we cure the hiccups,
it will cure the glitch.
Okay, but how?
When someone has
the hiccups,
you have to scare them,
like this.
Go big or go home.
That's not
how you scare Lay Lay.
This is how you scare Lay Lay.
Girl, your shoes
don't match your jacket.
The best way
to look good is to feel good.
Oh, no.
If hearing her outfit is wack
didn't scare her out of it,
nothing will.
No, there is another way.
Get your boot-scooting
booty on down...
Skip ad.
What are you doing
with that InstaShave?
Ah!
What happened
to your eyebrows?
Marky, your forehead so big,
now it's a five-head.
That was snark.
You're snarky again.
Lay Lay's back.
I missed you so much.
I missed you, too.
I felt so weird.
It's like I was me,
but I wasn't me.
Lay Lay, I'm sorry
I overused your powers.
I won't do it again.
I love having you around.
From now on,
your secret is safe with me.
Thanks, Marky.
That means a lot.
I'm sorry. I can't.
Your face.
Right?
We should, like, project
a movie
on his forehead or something.
Okay, okay.
Laugh it up.
My eyebrows will grow back in...
Four to six months?
What?
You know what?
Normally, I wouldn't leave
the house
without my eyebrow
pencil, but right now,
all I have is this marker.
So make it work and fast.
Thank you.
Who got a CHoFMA?
Trish got a CHoFMA.
And to all the haters who said
it wouldn't happen, uh,
new phone, who dis?
Thank you,
and remember to compost.
And now, my creative partner
and the man I love
would like to say something.
Watch big daddy Bryce
bring it home.
I want to thank my...
My husband would like
to thank his mama.
Thank you, and good night.
So many people.
You ready to go out there
and kill it, Lay Lay?
Let's do this, Sadie.
It's slay time.
Let's hear it for Trish
and Bryce Alexander.
And to show how deep
the talent runs in this family,
please welcome
their daughter Sadie
and her best friend Lay Lay.
♪ If I dream it,
I believe it ♪
♪ I'ma be it ♪
♪ I'ma be it, yeah ♪
♪ They say effort
beats talent any day ♪
♪ So I'ma work hard every
single time I play ♪
♪ 'Cause haters gonna hate ♪
♪ It don't matter
what they say ♪
♪ If you got big goals,
then you got to be brave ♪
♪ Living proof,
hard work pays off ♪
♪ I'ma follow in
their footsteps, no days off ♪
♪ Because I'm chasing dreams ♪
♪ Yeah, you see me
making moves ♪
♪ Putting everything I got
into everything I do ♪
♪ Because I know, if I see it,
I'ma be it ♪
♪ I set my mind to my goals,
and I believe it ♪
♪ And I set my goals high,
and I try to reach them ♪
♪ I put the pedal to the metal
in achieving dreams ♪
- ♪ I got big dreams ♪
- ♪ Big dreams ♪
♪ Big dreams
doing big things ♪
♪ Yeah, big ♪
♪ I'ma be whatever
I want to be ♪
♪ You can do it, as long
as you got a dream ♪
♪ If I dream it,
I believe it ♪
- ♪ I'ma be it ♪
♪ - If I dream it, I believe
it, I'ma be it ♪
♪ I'ma be it ♪
♪ If I dream it,
I believe it, I'ma be it ♪
- ♪ I'ma be it ♪
♪ I'ma be it ♪
- We love you, Cleveland.
- Yes.
Let's give it up one more time
for Trish and Bryce Alexander.
Where's Marky?
He should be out here too.
Boy, what did you do
to your eyebrows?
InstaShave
and a can-do attitude.
Smile and wave, Marky.
Smile and wave.
Fashion is very, very,
very important to me.
It is the way that
I keep my confidence up.
I like to be done up for sure,
but like if
you see me in the airport,
joggers, hoodies...
Y'know, I got some
cute stuff in here.
So it's really just my comfort.
I feel comfortable when
I wear clothes like that.
We're gonna go with that.
I wanna pick it out.
- Let's go red.
- Red?
I have to wear something that
makes me happy.
And that's life
with That Girl Lay Lay.
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/aqnnk
Help other users to choose the best subtitles