- [Cell doors clanging]
- BRAITHWAITE: Hey! You!
I'm onto you.
I know all about you.
REYNOLDS:
What's all this for?
We was done last week.
Why us again?
JACKSON:
Quit moaning, Harry.
You. Out.
Move!
WOLTON: Sorry, Mr. Jackson.
Just saying hello.
OFFICER: Right, that's it.
Get this lot packed up.
Get sorted.
WOLTON: What have you
got with you, then?
Any money?
Phone cards?
Have you got stuff
you can trade, have you?
BRINKLEY:
Bastards.
OFFICER:
Right, Brinkley, shut it.
[Indistinct conversations]
[Screaming]
[Thud]
I want my visiting order!
Will have contacts for 14 hour
per day out of cell periods!
[Dog barking]
Let him go.
Let him out.
I'll pluck his eyes out!
You know what this is about,
don't you?
Look, I ain't no ruddy nonce.
Let's prove it.
We'll hold a kangaroo court
right here.
- Harry, you can be judge.
- [Chuckles]
You... defense counsel.
And you... What's your name?
Kelly. [Clears throat]
Anthony.
Right, Anthony.
You're his solicitor.
What are you, Victor?
Oh.
Oh, I'm the hangman.
[Grunts]
No!
BRAITHWAITE:
Over the top.
There.
There you go, nonce.
Now.
[Grunts, chair clatters]
You've had confirmation that the
trial will begin on Wednesday?
Yes.
All four of the prisoners have
their own legal representative,
and three of them have been
awarded legal aid.
However, prisoner
Anthony Kelly's family
have hired the services of...
Christina Knatchbull.
She's a pretty formidable
criminal barrister.
Very well known for her
manipulation of the media,
specifically the press.
Our main concern is with regard
to the prisoner Anthony Kelly.
Was it your decision to place
Kelly with, um, Foster
and Reynolds?
You never thought it might
be preferable to put this young
and first-time offender
into a cell by himself?
No, I did not.
In the past,
I have invariably discovered
that it's better for
a first-time offender to bunk up
with someone who can show them
the ropes.
Well, he was most certainly
shown them.
Colin Foster was tried
and hanged in his bloody cell.
Are you okay to drive?
I'm fine to drive, but don't for
a second think that I'm okay.
[Siren wailing in distance]
[Keys jingling]
I didn't hear you coming
to my defense.
I didn't hear you admit
that we had discussed which cell
to put Anthony Kelly in.
And the area manager kept
bloody quiet, didn't he?
He knew all about it.
And what about Andrews?
He was on the wing
10 minutes before the hanging.
I bet he's not coming to court.
You were on duty that night.
How come it's all
my responsibility?
'Cause you're the governor.
Tray collection!
Stand at your pad door!
OFFICER:
Slop out!
Watch any video online with Open-SUBTITLES
Free Browser extension: osdb.link/ext
Slop out.
[Indistinct shouting]
Can you hurry it up, please?
They're bringing
the food trolleys up.
MAN:
Whoo-hoo-hoo!
This is a two-man cell, correct?
Yes.
So when three men
were in this cell,
where was the third bunk,
and which one was allocated
to Anthony Kelly?
It was anchored to this one
and raised up as a bunk bed.
KNATCHBULL: The body was found
hanging from the air vent.
Yes.
Chair fallen to one side.
The four prisoners involved
are in the segregation unit
and have been since the hanging.
- Anthony, you okay?
- No talking, Braithwaite.
- All right, son.
- Get back from your door.
BRAITHWAITE:
Anthony?
Slop out.
Step out.
Visitor.
All right, Mr. Kelly.
Let's go.
BRAITHWAITE:
Anthony?
Pay no mind, Anthony!
- Shut it, Victor!
- BRAITHWAITE: Oi! Kelly!
- No talking!
- Kelly! Kelly, can you hear me?
I have never,
ever had to interview a client
preparing for trial
in this manner.
I would like my objection
to be placed on record.
I'm sorry, Ms. Knatchbull,
but it's the governor's orders.
All the other counsel
have been required to do so.
Are you all right, Anthony?
I'm sorry they put us in here
for our last conference
before the trial.
- It's okay.
- No, it isn't.
The next time I see you
will be in court.
[Sighs] But I won't waste time
on that now.
Will my girlfriend, Sandra,
be there?
Only if she's been called
as a witness.
Because all the defendants
are currently serving sentences
the trial will be held
in camera.
I believe you are innocent.
Look at me, Anthony.
You understand the charges?
You played no part
in the murder of Colin Foster.
I didn't.
I swear before God I didn't.
I'm so scared.
[Jackhammer clanking]
[Horn honks]
Oi, love.
No staff vehicles.
I'm the governor!
You got a 12:00 with a POA,
then one at 11:00 with, uh,
the HMS.
And these are the lists
of interviews.
Now, I've spaced them
15 minutes each.
And the applicants
from the educational department,
they're in that file,
so I've listed them as well.
We've got a full afternoon.
When do I not have one, Mavis?
You also wanted to start
checking the meals,
at the main kitchen's
almost functional.
- I can pull that back.
- No. No.
I've had a lot of complaints
about boiled potatoes.
Boiled potatoes
and more boiled potatoes.
Right.
[Exhales deeply]
Right, Mavis.
Start them coming in.
[Door closes]
Are these in the right order?
Mavis?
Mr. Udding, Governor.
Come in.
Please sit down.
- Thank you.
- [Door closes]
Sorry. I was, uh,
very late this morning.
That's, uh, that's all right.
I suppose with all
the construction going on,
you've had your hands full.
Yes.
It's, uh, double security
and checking every man
and moving all the inmates
we have here around
as the work progresses.
And it is progressing.
Right...
John.
This is very impressive.
Do you want to tell me why
you're leaving your present job?
The governor and I
do not see eye to eye.
He seems to think
that because I am black,
I should be concentrating
on black prisoners,
whereas I feel whatever I am
should in no way differentiate
me from the other officers.
How do they... uh,
the inmates... react to you?
Once they see the brother act
doesn't work,
they're probably
more antagonistic towards me
than they are
with the other officers.
But I...
I reckon you've just got to
give it time.
There's no need to go in
heavy-handed.
About the other officers.
How do they react?
Pretty much the same
as the inmates.
[Laughs]
Sorry.
[Machine whirring]
UDDING:
I will. Thank you.
- Thank you very much.
- Thank you.
I'll walk you through
to the gate guard, Mr. Udding.
It's this way.
Shall I bring in the next, Gov?
Yes. I would say
that was the intention.
I'm sorry about, uh,
commandeering your office.
Shouldn't be too inconvenient.
Um, Anthony Kelly's counsel
has complained
about having to interview him
in a no-contact section.
Yes. I received
her terse little memo.
Next.
Mavis, next.
Mavis, who was the black bloke?
They all are.
Well, so far.
What, black?
The Governor, Ms. Hewitt.
HEWITT:
Good morning. Please sit down.
It's Zania, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
[Door closes]
I'm sorry.
I'm running a bit late.
So excuse me if I just get
straight to the point.
Okay.
[Telephone ringing]
Sorry.
Excuse me.
Governor.
OFFICER: Trolley's going down
on the wing.
No. Could you just hold
the trolley for two minutes?
Vegetable soup,
bread rolls as starter,
steak and kidney pie,
boiled potatoes,
peas and green beans,
main course,
jam roly-poly, pudding.
Could I have a plate?
I've had a few complaints that
the food served isn't very hot.
And, um, how many times
have you served boiled potatoes
since...
Well, since I've been here?
It's not my fault.
It's 'cause of the rebuilding.
It's got to go through
three corridors, outside,
then onto the wings.
The vegetables
are a bit overcooked,
and the boiled potatoes could do
with a few more minutes.
Is there custard served
with this?
Not today.
Milk was late arriving.
Where are the specials...
The diets and the allergy trays?
With the work going on,
I haven't got the space
to prepare the specials.
I do the medical ones,
but the diets,
they can just eat less.
[Pager beeps]
You were in the army
weren't you?
Yes, ma'am.
Fifteen years.
I thought so.
Thank you.
Governor.
I've segregated him
in the cubicle.
I think you'd better come
and see him.
Is the doc... arranging
a visiting order for me?
JONES:
[Shouting indistinctly]
- HEWITT: Morning.
- OFFICER: Morning.
How is he?
Not good.
His breathing is very erratic.
It's liver failure.
Recommendation 10 from Judge...
- Governor?
- In a second.
Is he dying?
Yes, he is.
Doc, are you gonna see him?
I've got to get back
on the wing.
I think he should wear
a surgical mask.
He's had severe nosebleeds.
I have asked to re-examine
prisoner Norman Jones.
I'll be right with you.
JONES: into line
with the private-sector jails...
So, this one's trouble, huh?
You can say that again.
[Down-tempo music plays]
[Jones shouting in distance]
I've been in contact
with the medics
at two of Jones'
previous prisons.
Apparently without medication,
he becomes excessively violent.
How are you doing, Arnie?
What do you want?
Huh?
What is it?
Hold me hand, son.
[Music continues]
Help me get through this.
DR. THOMAS:
Just let go, Arnie.
Everything's gonna be just fine.
That's a good lad.
Is this all there is to it, Doc?
[Shouting continues]
should be accorded
automatic access
to the same quality of life
as those detained
in psychiatric hospitals!
Shut up!
Now, shut up!
There is a man dying in there.
Thank you.
He's dead.
You know, when the, um,
when the prison's full up,
for want of a better
description,
we'll be needing
a full-time doctor.
Not my idea of heaven.
Sorry.
I knew the previous doctor.
That's why I stepped in
after the riot.
But as full time, no way.
Some of your inmates,
Ms. Hewitt, they, um, scare me.
And some of them repel me.
There's just so little kindness
in here,
and not everybody is able to
deal with the dregs of humanity.
They're not all dregs, Doctor.
Perhaps you have a vocation.
[Down-tempo music plays]
Maybe I have.
[Indistinct conversations]
MORGAN: All I can do is repeat
what I was told.
The education department
should be ready next week.
Mr. Morgan?
I don't suppose you have
any news for me, have you?
What about?
My probation officer.
Before the riot, he said I was
on the list for a weekend visit.
I don't know, Fisher.
Best thing is to ask the
governor on her rounds tomorrow.
I just work here, mate.
Hey, Jumbo!
Let's get on it.
Waste of time, mate.
Doc reckons he's got
a screw loose.
Mr. Morgan?
Did you find out about me query?
Brian, you have been asking the
same question for months now.
If you get 21 days added
to your original sentence,
it stands to reason
the days will be attached
to your release date.
Now, I told you that.
The gov told you that.
Half the wing has told you that.
Piss off.
Go on.
But I got some off
for good behavior.
Tell you who you should ask.
Norman, bloke in cell 48.
He'll put you straight, Brian.
Real friendly.
Go on. Ask him.
Nice one, Walter.
Thanks.
All right, mate.
Walter sent me over.
Said you'd help me with me EDI.
I don't know what to do.
What would you do?
They s-said a weekend, Walter.
Due for a weekend.
You know, start adjusting.
When was the last time
you was out?
Fifteenth of May 1981.
Christ.
BRINKLEY: You'll need more
than a weekend to adjust, mate.
There's been a lot of changes
since '81.
All right?
Explain it to you, did he?
[Exhales deeply]
You want to know what he said?
He said if I spoke to him again
he'd bite the tongue
out of me head.
Nice one, Walter.
Ms. Hewitt?
- [Door closes]
- Malcolm Smith.
Thank you for coming in.
It's about Alan Fisher.
I am attempting to get
all the records,
but it's a long process.
You know, the entire department
went up in smoke.
But according to his file,
he was put forward
for a weekend visit.
He's got a parole date
in 18 months...
Well, seven now.
It was suggested
he be transferred
to an open prison near his home.
This is appalling.
Well, the new Home Office ruling
regarding home leave
is making
a lot of extra paperwork.
We have got to get
this department organized...
And fast.
I'll look into it.
Thank you very much for this.
[Telephone ringing]
Yes?
MOIRA:
Call on line 2. It's Mr. Soames.
Is it all right if I go out
for lunch now?
Yes.
Thank you, Moira.
I'll contact you as soon
as I've checked through this.
[Door opens, closes]
Helen Hewitt, Mr. Soames.
I'm sorry.
I meant to return your call.
Yes. Yes.
Well, I can appreciate that.
But you must understand that
I was not on duty that night.
In fact,
on the night that it happened,
I was having dinner
with Mr. Andrews
and my area manager, John Bunny.
I suppose after the riot
at Barfield,
the prison must be
in a very disorganized state.
Not that disorganized,
Mr. Soames.
Good.
I was hoping you'd say that.
I'm very confident that the case
will be conclusive
and things will be dealt with
in as short a time as possible.
That said, there is one area
that troubles me.
The defendant, Anthony Kelly,
like all four men is pleading...
Not guilty. Yes.
Yeah.
Have you met Ms. Knatchbull?
No.
But she's obviously had
a lot of visits with Kelly
over the past six months,
and she's seen the cell.
Why did you ask if I'd met her?
Ms. Knatchbull's worried
that her client can be... got at.
I'm sorry?
Well, it's obviously
not meant to sound
as if I'm undermining
Barfield's security.
The men involved in the hanging
have all been segregated
for the past six months
and remain in secure cells.
Am I right in assuming
that during cell association
on the night of the hanging, all
the cell doors were kept open?
Yes, which means
that Anthony Kelly
could have walked out
at any time but didn't.
And I'm also correct
that shortly before the incident
occurred, two other...
Incident?
You call a man hanged
an incident?
A man hanged in a cell
built for two prisoners
which was accommodating three.
In the Barfield rules,
there is no cell association.
I am sure the defense
will want to know
why five men were allowed
in that cell.
Why was Kelly in there?
Well, in perfect conditions,
he wouldn't have been,
but there was no alternative.
So you admit
that by an administrative error
you placed a young
and vulnerable boy at risk?
No.
I admit no such thing.
Good.
I believe if there was
any possible inference
that the present conditions
at Barfield might be used
in Anthony Kelly's defense,
if any negligence...
Anthony Kelly committed a crime.
I didn't sentence him.
I didn't send him to Barfield.
I'm glad to hear you have
such a positive attitude.
Ms. Knatchbull
is a formidable lady.
[Down-tempo music plays]
I have no intention of calling
you for the prosecution,
and I presume,
as you've had no contact from
Ms. Knatchbull's solicitors,
you are not called
for the defense?
If I was, it would be highly
unethical to speak to her,
but I am perfectly willing
to be a witness.
Good.
And I feel confident
you will prove more than a match
for the delectable
Ms. Knatchbull.
Do you think I might be called
for the defense?
Not if I've got in first.
Morning, Doctor.
How are you?
Are they Kelly's parents?
Yeah.
Well, here we go.
[Siren wailing in distance]
DR. THOMAS: Death was caused
by strangulation.
The deceased had
no other external injuries.
On my examination,
the flex was still attached
to the victim's neck
but had been loosened,
as mouth-to-mouth resuscitation
had been performed
by two auxiliary nurses.
Both noted the victim showed
no sign of life
on admittance
to the hospital wing.
Dr. Thomas, can you identify
that, exhibit 3,
as the flex
removed from the victim?
Uh, yes, this is the flex that I
removed from the victim's neck.
I ask you also to identify
the next exhibit, number 4,
a gray sock.
This item or one similar was
removed from the victim's mouth.
Uh, I did not remove it myself,
but Auxiliary Nurse Jones did.
The item was then...
Do you know if that was the sock
that was discovered
in the victim's mouth,
Dr. Thomas?
I really couldn't say.
One gray sock looks
pretty like another.
I'm sorry, but the said item
was, I believe,
put into a plastic bag
in the hospital wing
and removed by the police.
[Indistinct conversations]
HEWITT:
Good morning.
- Good morning.
- Good morning, Governor.
It's not a rude question,
but who's sort of running
my prison this morning?
It's not Walter Brinkley, is it?
Could I please check your names?
- Ms. Hewitt?
- Yes.
- WOMAN: Mr. Malahide?
- That's the governor.
- I'm sure of it.
- WOMAN: DCI Dunes?
Here.
- WOMAN: Mr. Marshall?
- Here.
- Mr. Clark?
- Miss.
Um, I was just wondering
how long I'd have to wait.
I'm sorry.
I really couldn't say.
- Mr. Clark?
- Yes.
- Mr. Edwards?
Mr. and Mrs. Kelly.
- Yes.
[Down-tempo music plays]
[Cellphone ringing]
WOMAN:
Excuse me, Ms. Hewitt.
No portable phones are allowed
inside the courtroom.
Okay.
Hello?
OFFICER: Know that all bags
are to be left at reception.
Next.
[Engine idling]
June Fisher,
visiting Alan Fisher.
Know that all bags are to be
left at reception.
Next.
Mel Snooper,
visiting Oswald Snooper.
Next.
Lastly, I questioned
Prisoner Anthony Kelly.
This was approximately
two and a half hours
after the incident had occurred.
He was still
in a very distressed state
but agreed to be interviewed.
May I refer to my summary,
my lord?
Yes.
Please continue.
Mr. Kelly stated,
"I was just leaving the cell
when Victor..."
that would be
Victor Braithwaite, my lord...
"walked in.
I was very uneasy because I had
just been given a spliff."
That is a marijuana cigarette,
my lord.
"I had never smoked one before,
and I was feeling sick
and dizzy."
Have we had his interview
transcribed?
No, we haven't.
[Indistinct conversations]
You know I've been waiting
a long time.
I've done what you told me.
I've never brought the papers
with me
because they check everything
at the gates.
I know.
But one of the reasons
they're going to release me
is because they don't know
anything about the divorce.
I can't keep on waiting.
You say I can't send them,
but you've also got to sign
the deeds over to me.
They read the mail, June.
They'd know.
I'll sign them when I come out.
You've got my word.
I'll sign.
I promise.
[Down-tempo music plays]
MEL:
She snores.
- What do you mean, she snores?
- [Laughs] She does.
Baby don't snore.
[Laughs]
She does.
Hey, listen. Everything went
all right at the gate?
Yeah. They searched my bag
and my coat.
Arnold, I told you.
Play with your puzzle.
Right.
Come sit beside me.
He's getting to be
such a handful, you know.
Arnold, sit down
and stop messing about, right?
- You got it.
- Mm-hmm.
Um, is it all right
if I hold my kid?
Yes.
Cheers.
Okay.
Shall we go see Daddy?
Daddy's gonna hold you now.
- Come on.
- Ooh!
- Ooh.
- She is heavy.
[Laughs]
[Chuckles]
You are heavy.
You eat.
But you're beautiful, darling.
You're so beautiful.
Where is it?
They checked the nappy
last time.
There's some under her sweater
and some in the bottle.
- Hey.
- Arnold, give me that.
- Give me this.
- Don't put it in your mouth.
[Indistinct conversations]
MEL:
Go oh. Give your daddy a smile.
[Laughs]
Detective Chief Inspector Dunes,
from Anthony Kelly's interview
with you,
he determined that all three
were actually smoking.
- Is that correct?
- Yes, my lord.
When I questioned Kelly
regarding the smoking, um...
Continue.
He answered that Steven...
That's Mr. Wolton...
Was rolling them in the cell.
I then asked the defendant
how many he had smoked.
He said two.
And all the three
other defendants
have denied partaking
in this spliff... joint?
Yes, my lord.
Yes.
You can tell Fisher.
Yeah.
They've risen
till 10:30 tomorrow.
Oh, shit.
And I've been here
all bloody day.
And this is the best gear
in the street.
But it's expensive.
You know what I mean?
How much?
[Chuckles]
Fisher?
Fisher!
You've got your weekend, Alan.
What?
Is it this month?
Three weeks' time.
I wanted you to know.
Oh, thank you.
Thank you very much!
Pleased to.
Mr., um, Smith,
I've got to ask you...
Uh...
What is it, Brian?
[Sighs]
You said it was important.
I've lost me paper.
I've lost it.
One minute.
I'm going out!
[Laughs]
I am already totally out of it.
[Mid-tempo music plays]
Is Ms. Hewitt
in the witness box?
Prosecution counsel
just called her.
HEWITT: Having interviewed
every officer on duty
on the night in question...
That included my deputy
and my senior officers...
I am satisfied
that there was at no time
any sign of disturbance
on the wing
and that no blame
for the tragic outcome of events
can be leveled at any officer
on duty that night.
I have no further questions,
my lord.
Ms. Knatchbull.
May I ask your age, Ms. Hewitt?
I'm 33.
Could you explain to the court
governor ranks?
Governors are scaled in ranks
from 5 upwards,
Governor 1 being
the highest rank.
And what rank from 1 to 5
are you, Ms. Hewitt?
I'm a Governor 3 rank.
How long have you been
a Governor 3 rank?
Nine months.
So you were Governor 4
until recently taking over
Barfield Prison,
a category B all-male prison?
Yes.
That is correct.
And before taking over
the running of Barfield Prison,
you were deputy governor
at Kettering Hall,
an all-female prison?
Yes.
That is correct.
KNATCHBULL:
You took over Barfield
after the highly publicized
riot.
My lord,
may I ask my learned friend
why she feels it necessary
to give details
of Ms. Hewitt's career
and what possible relevance
it can have in the case?
My lord, the circumstances
at Barfield Prison at that time
are very important
to the defense of Anthony Kelly.
You may continue,
Ms. Knatchbull.
Thank you, my lord.
Perhaps I should clarify
the reasoning
behind my line of questioning.
Anthony Kelly was placed at risk
the moment he was admitted
to Barfield,
as Ms. Hewitt is a new
and very young governor.
My Lord, Ms. Hewitt's
professional credibility
is not in question
at this trial.
I suggest my learned friend
should read the papers.
Since Ms. Hewitt took over
the running of Barfield,
two men escaped
in a helicopter...
My Lord.
Very well.
You may continue.
KNATCHBULL: Ms. Hewitt,
how long was Anthony Kelly held
at Barfield?
Almost two days.
Did you interview him?
No, I did not.
So you didn't actually know him
at all?
I knew his age,
plus information regarding
his crime and his sentence.
But you did not actually see him
on his admittance?
Until a prisoner
has been interviewed
by the probation department
and the medical staff,
until I have received a full
and detailed report
regarding his needs,
be they educational,
medical, or domestic...
How long does that take?
In Anthony Kelly's situation,
almost two days.
I would just like to point out,
in case you're not aware of it,
that each wing also has
its own governor
and its own senior officer.
I'm sorry, Ms. Hewitt,
but who put Anthony Kelly,
a young 24-year-old
first offender,
into a cell with two prisoners,
both serving long sentences
for violent crimes?
- Objection, my lord.
- I object.
My client's previous record has
no bearing on the present case.
Please rephrase the question,
Ms. Knatchbull.
Ms. Hewitt, is cell 29, D Wing,
designed for two occupants?
Yes.
That is correct.
How many occupants were
allocated to cell 29, D Wing,
the night Colin Foster hanged?
Three.
We have heard in court today
that it is against
Barfield Prison regulations
to allow men to associate
in their cells.
We have also heard that on
the night Colin Foster died,
four men were in the cell.
The deceased makes five.
My lord, I really cannot see why
my learned friend feels obliged
to repeat what has already
been proved without objection.
Please rephrase your question,
Ms. Knatchbull.
Ms. Hewitt, you stated
that no officer was to be blamed
for the tragic events.
Yet surely they were
sadly lacking
in their duty that evening
to allow five men in cell 29.
I'm sorry.
What exactly is your question?
Do you admit
that there was a negligence
on the part of the officers
on duty that night,
the night Colin Foster died?
I'm satisfied that there
was no negligence.
You are satisfied?
That in this cramped cell,
Anthony Kelly,
a young 24-year-old boy who'd
never been in prison before
and only arrived
the day before...
My lord, Ms. Knatchbull
is goading the witness.
Please make your questions
more direct, Ms. Knatchbull.
Why was Anthony Kelly placed
in cell 29, D Wing, Ms. Hewitt?
I had no alternative, no other
accommodation available.
May I ask, Ms. Hewitt,
if you had had an alternative,
would you still have delegated
Mr. Kelly to cell 29?
Not necessarily.
Not necessarily?
These three men
then forced Anthony Kelly
to take part
in a sickening trial,
accusing the deceased
of being a nonce... a nonce!
Anthony Kelly
only 24 hours earlier
had never even heard
the expression.
JUDGE:
Ms. Knatchbull.
Members of the jury, you will
please ignore the implication
that force was used
by any of the defendants.
May I ask you Ms. Hewitt,
from a humanitarian aspect,
do you believe any proportion
of blame can be attached
to Barfield Prison?
Ms. Knatchbull,
I take full responsibility
for the present running
of Barfield.
I am trying every possible means
to curb the use of drugs...
Thank you very much
for admitting responsibility.
I have no further questions,
my lord.
No questions?
Thank you, Ms. Hewitt.
I think this will be
a suitable time to adjourn.
WOMAN:
Be upstanding.
This court stands adjourned
until 10:30 tomorrow morning.
[Down-tempo music plays]
OFFICER: Prisoners Kelly,
Reynolds, Braithwaite,
and Wolton are being taken back
to Barfield.
Transportation officer,
stand by.
If necessary, move him,
Mr. Gordon.
I do not want Anthony Kelly
harassed in any way.
Now, is that clear?
Right.
Thank you.
I take full responsibility.
We were all messing about,
and Colin...
That's Colin Foster...
He was sort of the main joker.
I made some remark
about him being a nonce.
It's a sex offender, sir.
Anyway, Colin takes this
the wrong way.
He, uh, got a bit uptight
and says, you know,
"If I'm a nonce, you prove it."
But we were still joking.
It wasn't serious.
It...
Even Colin was laughing.
It was just a joke.
If we may go on.
Did you ever refer to yourself
as "the hangman"?
[Sniffs]
No, I did not.
Did you give the titles
judge, jury, and solicitor
to any of the other members
in cell 29?
No.
No, I did not.
Did you tie the hands
of the deceased, Colin Foster,
behind his back?
No, I did not.
I never touched him.
Mr. Braithwaite,
did you assist in the hanging
of the deceased, Colin Foster,
in any way?
No, I did not.
He done it himself.
I have no further questions,
my lord.
Mr. Braithwaite,
may I ask you how long
you are presently serving
at Barfield Prison?
Fourteen years.
I beg your pardon,
Mr. Braithwaite.
Fourteen years.
Mr. Braithwaite, were you,
on the evening
of Colin Foster's death,
smoking illegal substances
in cell 29?
No, I was not.
I've never in my life smoked
cannabis resin or marijuana.
I can't.
I've got asthma.
KNATCHBULL:
Oh. I see.
Why were you in cell 29 on the
evening of Colin Foster's death?
I was just getting in
some tobacco.
KNATCHBULL: But you have just
stated that you did not smoke
because you have asthma.
He got up on the chair.
He was just fooling, like,
and then...
Oh, yeah. Officer Malahide,
I think, uh, walked past.
Or somebody did.
You hearing all this, Anthony?
You getting it all, Anthony?
You'd better be hearing this
good, Anthony. Understand me?
BRAITHWAITE:
You do the right thing, son,
we're all on the same place,
right?
WOLTON: I just thought
he were kidding, you know?
His body was all limp, you see,
and...
It was just a joke.
No further questions, my lord.
Could I ask how long
you are serving
your present sentence,
Mr. Wolton?
Please answer the question,
Mr. Wolton.
Five years.
Thank you.
I have no further questions.
I didn't even take any notice.
I was reading.
They was just messing about,
so I kept reading.
Next thing Colin,
he was on the floor.
Then the alarm went, and
Mr. Malahide came running in.
Colin didn't make a sound
or call out.
They were laughing one second,
and then...
I was told he was dead.
I have no further questions,
my lord.
Mr. Reynolds, could I ask you
how long you were acquainted
with my client
before this unfortunate
and tragic incident took place?
No more than a day and a half.
Thank you, Mr. Reynolds.
There's just one more question.
Could I ask how long
you're presently serving
at Barfield Prison?
Eleven years.
I have no further questions.
Thank you, my lord.
[Clears throat]
You were reading a book,
they were messing around,
and the deceased made no sound,
he did not call out.
Am I correct, Mr. Reynolds?
Yes.
Like they was cracking jokes.
Know what I mean?
I'm trying to know
what you mean, Mr. Reynolds.
I believe that the length
of your cell
would be about the same
as the distance
between Ms. Knatchbull
and myself.
Would you agree?
Maybe.
Well, we can give you
a few inches,
but the distance is not great.
It is, by any estimation,
very small and claustrophobic,
Is it not?
I don't know.
SOAMES: There are five men
in this small space,
including yourself.
Am I correct?
Yes, it's only a double cell,
but they moved in an extra bunk
for Kelly.
See, Anthony?
We're all backing each other.
If we all do it,
none of us will go down for it.
Only needs one of us
to screw it up, Anthony.
Don't even think about it.
Tied the other end
to an air vent,
fell from the chair,
breaking his neck.
And you... you, Mr. Reynolds...
Did not see anything
because you were immersed
in your book?
I had earplugs in.
[Laughter]
[Down-tempo music plays]
Mr. Kelly, you will be
in the witness box tomorrow.
Do you mind if I sit down?
No.
[Clears throat]
I want you to be very positive.
I want you to tell the court
exactly what you have told me.
Um...
[Clears throat]
So much has happened since then,
I, um...
I-I can't remember it all.
Every time I think about it,
I...
I feel the same way over again.
They're all lying.
We were all smoking,
Ms. Knatchbull.
They're lying.
Yes, I know.
But you tell the truth.
It'll go against me,
though, won't it?
I was stoned.
Anthony, I will have to ask you
why you didn't leave the cell.
They wouldn't let me!
Yes!
Now, you just remember that,
because if they had,
you wouldn't be on trial
for murder.
[Down-tempo music plays]
[Keys jingling]
You not up for your breakfast,
then, Norman?
You sick?
I am not sick!
KNATCHBULL: My lord, I now ask
to call Anthony Kelly.
[Whispering]
That bastard Norman Jones
has taken Mr. Morgan hostage.
Oh, my God.
Come on.
Ask me nicely.
Go on.
OFFICER: Prisoner Norman Jones
is locked inside his cell
- with Officer Morgan.
- Down on your knees.
OFFICER:
We have a hostage situation.
Over.
Don't do this, Norman.
I know what they're going to do
to me,
so I want a bit of respect!
Get... down... on... your... knees!
Please let me out of your cell,
Norman.
[Engine rumbling]
JONES:
You shagging gorillas!
I'll kill every one of you!
Let me go!
Get off me!
Every last one of you monsters
are trash!
[Men shouting in distance]
Stay out of here.
Russell, it's me... Gary.
Screw it!
Okay.
Back off. Go on.
Back off.
JACKSON:
Go on, lads. Move it.
Sit him down.
Come on.
[Down-tempo music plays]
I'm okay.
- You sure?
- I'm okay.
[Inhales deeply]
I'm okay.
KNATCHBULL:
Do you smoke, Mr. Kelly?
[Clears throat]
No, I don't.
On the night of your first day
in Barfield Prison,
were you offered any substances
to smoke?
No, I was not.
Mr. Kelly... can I just clarify?
When I asked you
if you were smoking substances,
I was not referring
to ordinary cigarettes.
Now I ask you again...
On the night that Colin Foster
died in cell 21, D Wing,
were you offered any substances
to smoke?
No, I was not.
So you were not under
the influence of any narcotics
during the so-called
kangaroo court held in cell 29?
No... I was not.
I'll need a full report
as to how Norman Jones
was able to take Morgan hostage.
Mm-hmm.
What's the update on the trial?
I left just before Kelly went
into the witness box.
I think she might get him off,
you know.
He is innocent.
We all know it.
Yeah.
To a point.
Kelly put himself in that cell.
He did it when he committed
his first crime.
[Down-tempo music plays]
Fooling around?
I wonder if you'd clarify that,
Mr. Kelly.
[Clears throat]
Colin, um, took some flex
out of his own pocket.
He said he wasn't a-a nonce
and he would prove it
by hanging himself.
Just out of court.
Anthony Kelly denied
everything...
Smoking pot, the lot.
His counsel couldn't budge him.
What?
Well, they got to him,
didn't they?
Stupid little bugger lied.
Damn it!
[Sighs]
I'm sorry.
It's bad news.
Well, for Kelly.
JONES:
[Shouting indistinctly]
Let me have a look at Norman,
see if he needs to be sedated.
[Down-tempo music plays]
Seen enough?!
You want some more?!
Okay!
[Grunting]
No. I think we should let him
cool off.
Wait till he comes
to his senses... or not.
You're not going in there
with him.
[Shouting continues]
And I want that belt off him.
Are you gonna do it?
I'll tell you what.
You can use one of those darts
they use in zoos
to knock out a rhino.
JUDGE:
Anthony John Kelly,
in his interview
with the police,
made it plain
that drugs were being smoked,
that his co-defendants tried
and hanged
the deceased, Colin Foster.
Before you today, he has denied
that version of events
and said that Colin Foster
hanged himself.
Now it is up to you to decide
if this retraction
of his statement taken
by DCI Dunes is now the truth.
If it's capable
of being believed,
then Anthony Kelly
is entitled to be acquitted.
Harry Reynolds
and Steven Wolton, seven years,
Victor Braithwaite, 11 years.
Bloody hell.
What about Kelly?
[Down-tempo music plays]
He's all yours for
the next six years, Ms. Hewitt.
I hope you can live with it.
Anthony John Kelly
was an innocent.
You should have protected him.
-== [ www.OpenSubtitles.com ] ==-