Yumi's Cells 2
Episode 36
Extremely Polite Yumi
Yumi.
Should we...
get married?
Let's get married.
The sky is pretty.
- Eonni Yi Da, good morning!
- Hey, good morning.
Wow. It's been so long since she made a comeback on here.
I'm talking about Yumi. She uploaded a post. What's going on?
Really? I'll have to leave a comment.
A nice day for a change. Spring. A new feeling. A good hunch.
So she just uploaded it.
Wait. This isn't just a normal picture of a ring.
Why?
- Hello?
- Hey, is there something going on?
Huh?
- Hurry up and come clean, something good happened, right?
Listen. Ruby and Writer Yumi are having dinner together today.
I'm going to act like I came to look for Ruby and join in.
Then if Hyeong and Hyeong Wung act like you
just happened to come to that restaurant for dinner
I'll naturally invite you to join us.
So I'll get there first and you guys
come in ten minutes later. Then we'll meet.
But you said that Yumi is dating her
ex-boyfriend again. So isn't it already game over?
No, no, no. Don't dare call yourself a
person if you haven't tried your best.
Isn't that something that stalkers say?
So you don't trust me, Hyeongnim.
You can trust me when it comes to dating.
Why?
Do you know why people call me Control Z?
No, but I'm not really that curious.
It's a bit embarrasing to say it myself,
but I'm a dating expert.
You must have a lot of dating experience then.
Rather than a lot, it's deep.
Then, how many times...?
You know that how deep your relationships are is
more important than how many you've had, right?
I'm the type who stays in a relationship
for a long time when I date. That's all I'll say.
I got it, so how many times?
Three times, officially.
Three times?
Three times. Hey, I've been in over seven relationships!
How dare you act like a know-it-all when you've only dated three times?
- Hey.
- Huh?
You said seven times? You?
Yeah.
Really?
Well...
I'm saying it's seven times if you include flirting.
You said it's seven times if you include flirting?
Hyeongnim, I would have been in a
relationship over 30 times if I included flirting.
Wait, if you've only dated seven times
including flirting, then this is serious.
Hyung Wung, I'm telling you that Yumi is lonely right now.
Although they're back together, it's awkward.
A relationship like this can't last long.
Now's your chance.
"Don't put off until tomorrow what you can do today."
(A Benjamin Franklin quote)
Ruby.
Hello?
- Oppa Z!
Hey, Ruby. I was planning to call you...
Oppa Z! Big news! Big news!
Eonni Yumi said she's getting married!
With Team Leader Ba Bi. She said he proposed to her.
I thought things weren't going well for them, but this is a big twist!
Oh, I have to go to a meeting. I'll call you back.
- Wait...
- Are you telling me that Yumi's getting married to her ex-boyfriend right now?
Hello?
What are you up to?
I'm drinking coffee, cleaning, and cooking.
I didn't tell you yesterday, did I?
Tell me what?
I've always had a feeling that I'd live happily when I got married.
Based on what?
A strong signal came to me from the future.
What are you saying?
But I became certain that it's not just a hunch yesterday.
I think we'll be happy.
You don't have much going on today,
right? Do you want to go out for lunch?
Lunch? I'm making a lunchbox right now.
There was somewhere I wanted to go with you.
Where?
Your father?
Huh? Aunt, Su Cheol didn't get divorced.
It was the younger sibling that got divorced.
Su Cheol doesn't have a younger sibling.
What? Why doesn't he have a younger sibling? There's two of them.
What's the youngest one's name?
What is it?
Yumi grew up around a lot of adult relatives from a
young age, so she never found it difficult to interact with adults.
Do you have a boyfriend? Did you get a job?
No, I don't have a boyfriend, and I'm getting ready to get a job.
Is that so?
However...
It's different with her boyfriend's father.
Babi's Street Food
But is it okay for me to suddenly come see him?
I thought that you'd feel more burdened if we made plans to see him.
So we can say that we decided to stop in since we were passing by,
greet him, and then leave.
Let's take the official meeting slow.
- Let's go in.
- Okay.
Welcome.
Father!
I stopped by.
Why did you come here with your foot like that? You should be at home.
I came with my girlfriend.
That's Ba Bi's father?
He doesn't look like his son at all.
He looks scarier than his picture.
He looks like an actor.
Who does he look like?
Move!
You all need to get yourselves together!
Is it important which actor he looks like right now?
He's going to be our father-in-law!
Marriage? Don't you know if we make
a mistake, we'll get intercepted here!
Say hi. He's my father.
Hello, nice to meet you. I'm Kim Yumi.
Nice to meet you.
You should have let me know you were coming.
Sorry. We happened to have an
appointment in the area, so we just stopped by.
We thought it would be good to say hello.
Oh, I got this...
Yu Mi bought it to give it to you.
You didn't have to.
Oh it's nothing, it's just snacks.
We don't have any food because lunchtime
is over. We've only got tteokbokki left now.
Oh, no, it's okay. I really like tteokbokki.
Tteokbokki, Soondae, Ramen, Kimbap
The atmosphere is so nice.
It's been around for a while, so it's a bit old-fashioned, isn't it?
No, that makes it better! It really seems like it will be delicious.
My father is usually quite blunt. Especially since my mother died.
Yeah, you told me.
He's not doing it to you specifically, so don't worry about it.
What is it, Bon Hui?
I'm outside at the moment.
What?
I'll send it to you as a photo.
Fax? But why...
Yes, I understand. I'll call you once I've sent it.
Yu Mi, just a second.
Do you need to go somewhere?
I'll just send a fax and then I'll be back.
I'll go.
No, I need to go myself.
Father, the stationary store is open, right?
Of course, it's open.
What is the highest form of respect you
can show to someone who made you food?
Of course it's to eat everything
deliciously so there's nothing left over!
Exactly! That is the highest form of respect.
Hold on, this...
Father, that's too much.
Leave some.
So much...
I'll be right back. Eat.
Okay, come quickly.
How many portions is that exactly?! 3? 4?
Even if it's respectful, this is too much.
One second. Don't be scared already.
Ba Bi's Street Food's tteokbokki is made
of wheat rice cakes. That's my preference.
Then shall I quickly get started on this difficult task?
Who are you? You're going to take all of us on?
You'd better prepare yourselves!
There isn't a tteokbokki target I don't know.
I think he's serious!
Where are you running to?
My back!
You can't run away from this plate!
I'm not a rice cake, I'm green onion.
Sorry, you look like a rice cake.
It's delicious, so delicious. Even the green onion is good.
It can't compare to what you get at a food cart.
Yumi! You need to eat modestly here.
Don't jump around.
She's not saying anything. Does it not suit her taste?
No, that's not it.
Look at her feet bouncing.
Bouncing feet: Something you do when eating delicious food.
It's like a standing ovation at a performance.
And she's even sweeping up the sauce.
Sweeping up the soup: Mopping up the leftover tteokbokki
sauce. The highest form of praise in the tteokbokki industry.
Yu Mi scored highly on her first impression.
You ate all of this? Alone?
It was so yummy...
- Oh, I'll...
- No need.
Yu Mi must have really liked your tteokbokki.
There's none for you.
I'm okay.
If you're done eating, get going.
Okay.
Is he angry?
No. He's usually like that.
We'll be going now.
Bye.
- Should we go?
- I'm just going to pop to the bathroom.
Okay.
He's so stiff. I have no idea what to say.
Still, we can't just eat and leave.
Of course we can't just go.
In that case... it's metamorphosis.
Metamorphosis: The ability to temporarily maximise and transfer
the ability of one cell to another. It
lasts for no more than 30 minutes.
🎵 No matter what ordeals come for me 🎵
🎵 No matter where or when, politely. 🎵
🎵 My future father-in-law 🎵
🎵 can't help but love me. 🎵
🎵 Afraid of nothing in this world. 🎵
🎵 Politeness can solve everything 🎵
Today it is you! Etiquette!
🎵 Yu Mi overflows with politeness 🎵
🎵 Full of manners 🎵
[Bridge]
🎵 Amongst the many cards 🎵
🎵 The most shining 🎵
🎵 Full, full, full, full of manners 🎵
[Etiquette]
Full of manners Yu Mi!
We'll be going.
Go on.
Let's go Yu Mi.
It was really delicious.
Full of Manners Yu Mi: Respectfulness
increases 300%. Filial daughter state as bonus.
That's enough. What's so special about tteokbokki?
I'm sorry for visiting so unexpectedly.
Next time, we'll be sure to contact you before we come.
It's nothing. As for me, well it would be nice if you came again.
And I'm glad you enjoyed the tteokbokki.
In that case, please do be going.
Okay. I'll come and visit you again.
Fa—
Fa?
Father.
[Father]
[Ba Bi Snack Bar]
Did I make a mistake?
You did well. What mistake? He'll like it if you pop by occasionally.
One second.
What is it?
- Yu Mi-yah.
- Yes?
Here.
Buy something delicious to eat.
Take it.
Thank you.
Come over to hang out again.
Yes, Father.
♫ I only wanna be with you everyday ♫
♫ Your smile makes my heart dance ♫
I'll buy you something since I got
spending money. What do you want to drink?
Do you know what my father's nickname is?
What is it?
Scrooge Jeong.
Why? He gave me this much spending money.
I've never gotten any.
Really?
Know that you're the first person to
ever get spending money from my father.
Wow. Then I shouldn't use this and laminate it to commemorate.
Hang it up on the wall.
I should iron this and laminate it.
Wow, you're rich.
Yumi safely made it through the first hurdle on the road to marriage.
You know that's really important, right?
I'm jealous. I've never gotten any from him before.
I'll get a lot from him.
♫ Everyday ♫
Episode 37
The Unanswered Phone Call
♫ Everyday ♫
Throat
Is this the throat?
Here!
Who are you?!
Knock the throat!
I am a cold virus!
Then I just have to send it by the weekend, right?
That would be good. But will you be able to?
I'll edit it. There's isn't a lot...
Writer, did you catch a cold?
I don't know. My throat stings.
- Okay. I'll see you next week.
- Okay!
Should I drink some ginger tea?
Hey! Where is that jerk Cold?
I'll make him aware of the greatness
of Ginger!
Bug off!
How dare you come here.
If you're busy, I can tell you later.
Health is public property
Cold is weak to heat. Let's raise her temperature and chase him away!
Yes, Ma'am! Understood!
38.5° C (101.3° Fahrenheit)
I've got a fever, too.
I made plans to meet Ba Bi later. What should I do?
Text message from Yumi
Ba Bi.
I think I caught a cold. My throat hurts and I have a fever.
Shall we change our movie reservation to tomorrow?
Hello? Ba Bi.
Have you taken medicine? What about food?
I'm at the pharmacy now.
Shall I stop by for a bit?
No. I think I'll get better if I just rest today.
I think it would be best if I stop by for a bit.
I'm really okay. I'm sorry.
No, get some rest.
- Okay. I'll call you later.
- Okay.
Should I not have told him? He'll worry.
Yumi, are you busy?
I came to Ilsan for work, so I thought of you.
I'm not at home. What is it?
There's no reason for us to meet since
we're not working together or friends,
but do you want to have a cup of coffee?
Alright, Yumi is coming soon. Let's speak coolly.
As if we're just asking how she's doing.
Show me the best answer.
[Which of the following is the coolest way to greet Yumi?]
A. Yumi, congratulations. I heard that you're getting married soon.
B. I heard you got a proposal? Good for you.
C. Mr. Yu Ba Bi is a good man. You made a good decision.
A good man? Yeah, right.
Does he really have to say that?
Hey. Hey, Love. Calm down.
We can just brush past it.
Do we really have to call her out and say this?
Love! This is something that makes Yumi happy.
It's the same as leaving comments on her web novel.
What's so hard about wishing her well?
I don't want to do it! Why do I have to go this far?
Wung.
Hey. You made it?
What do you want to drink?
Nothing.
I had some tea right before I came, so I'm okay.
Are you sick?
I must have a cold. I'm okay.
How have you been?
What about your finger?
It's fine.
That's a relief.
Congratulations.
Huh?
About that.
That?
You getting that thing.
Being proposed to.
Thank you.
I didn't think that you'd say that to me.
No need to be thankful.
Look at that. Yumi's happy.
Don't get married, Yumi!
I contacted you because I wanted to tell you that.
I could say it over the phone, but still...
Yeah.
When are you getting married?
Not right away. I think it will be
better after I finish writing the sequel.
So it will probably be late fall or winter.
We're thinking around November or December.
Oh, I see.
It's still far away, so it doesn't feel real.
Are you happy?
Yeah.
I think I am happy.
That's good.
Good.
When you get married, send me a wedding invitation, too.
I'm not sure.
Why?
You can't do that either because I'm your ex-boyfriend?
I'll discuss it with him.
With your boyfriend?
Yeah. I think I should ask him.
Then I won't be able to go. Would Yu Ba Bi allow it?
Why are you acting like that? Are you still upset with Ba Bi?
Do you have to get married to that guy?
If you're going to do it, can't you do it with some other guy instead?
Why does it have to be that guy?
Wung.
I'm saying these words for the first time in a long time.
What?
Goodness.
Goodness, Wung.
I'll take you home.
- That's okay.
- It's because you look sick.
I'm okay. My house is right around the corner.
Can I say one more thing?
Stop it.
Do you know what I regret the most in my life?
It's when I couldn't answer when you said let's get married.
I thought I would have another chance after I earned some money.
Do you love that guy?
Do you love him?
Of course! Yeah!
Huh? Why isn't she saying anything? Yeah!
What are you doing? Yumi, you have to answer him!
Say that you love him! It's Wung!
She can't answer.
- Why?
- Love isn't here!
Huh?
- Love!
- I haven't seen Love either.
- Love, where are you?
You're saying Love isn't here?
Love still hasn't come back.
Is that possible? Has no one seen Love?
- I haven't.
- No.
- Have you seen her?
Love is the only one who can answer if she loves him.
But you said that Love isn't here!
That's why she can't say yes.
Darn it! Then I'll just answer it!
Why are you asking something so obvious?!
Why are you asking something so obvious? How childish.
I've always been childish. You know that.
Hurry up and go.
Bye.
Go home.
When I wondered what love was, I realized
it was when I couldn't control how I felt.
Congratulations. Be happy.
Hey! Why won't you die? It's 39°C (102.2°F) out here!
It's still bearable. Why?!
Hey! We'll all die first at this rate.
I don't care. Let's see who'll win!
Let's go over 39 degrees!
Do you have to go this far just to get rid of one cold?
You stupid fool...
You're crazy!
We'll all die. Lower the fever.
We don't have a temperature-lowering function, though.
Wait, are you determined to kill Yumi?!
Huh? She suddenly got cool.
It's Ba Bi.
Are you okay?
- When did you get here?
- A little while ago.
You've got a really high fever. Should we go to the hospital?
It's not that bad. What about work?
I worked outside the office and got off work from there.
Let's monitor it a little longer and go
to the hospital if it doesn't get any lower.
You didn't eat dinner either, did you? I'll make you something.
I'm not hungry.
Get some more sleep.
♫ It's not about something I can understand ♫
♫ To me who am spending an unexpected day ♫
♫ Sing a song song song song song ♫
♫ so I can feel your love love love love ♫
♫ Can't think the word that I wanna say ♫
♫ To me who is about to cry ♫
♫ Sing a song song song song song ♫
♫ so that I can feel your love love love love ♫
Who is it?
Who was it?
Father sent you some tteokbboki.
What?
I spoke with him on the phone earlier, and he asked me for your address when I
said that you're sick. 30 years of traditional tteokbboki - Babi's Street Food
He said that since you eat tteokbboki so well,
you should eat some if you don't have an appetite.
Do you want some? The soup is almost ready, too.
I'm so thankful.
Have the soup first. Let's eat the
tteokbboki when you get a little better.
Okay.
Go back to sleep.
I'm so touched.
I'm so touched! I'm touched by Ba Bi and his father!
Why are they so sweet?
When Yumi's sick, Sensitivity gets more excited than usual.
Is sweetness hereditary for the men in this family?
That's crazy! I'm going crazy!
Ah, Yumi. Aren't you doing too well with your marriage?
Eat some more.
I ate a lot. It's so delicious.
Shall we take a look?
I think it went down a bit.
Aren't you going to eat dinner?
I'll take care of it. Go back to sleep.
I'll take this away.
Oh, that's right. Yumi, what do you think about Hawaii?
- Hawaii?
- I told you that my older sister lives in Hawaii, right?
What do you think about getting married
in Hawaii? I suddenly thought about it.
It was really nice every time I went to Nuna's house.
A small wedding in Hawaii?
A small wedding in Hawaii.
What? Are you saying that because you know?
My dream is to have a small wedding in Hawaii.
Really? I didn't know. How would I know that?
Then, you're saying it's really a coincidence?
Wow.
I like it! I love it.
I knew you would like it.
Get some more sleep. You're sick.
I think it would be nice to have a small wedding in Hawaii.
Yeah. Let's talk about it again later.
Go to sleep.
Ha-Hawaii?
Don't talk anymore. Go back to sleep.
You're sick.
I think I'd love to have a small wedding in Hawaii.
How can he be like this?
How could his Nuna live in Hawaii?
I thought that we'd end up having a small wedding in Hawaii with Wung.
You really never know how things will turn out.
Life is mysterious.
When she's sick, she gets twice as touched and twice as annoyed.
She also fantasizes twice as much.
Yumi, you're awake?
Your fever went down.
How do you feel?
I think I'm okay now.
Ba Bi, hurry up and go.
I'm not going to go.
You have to go to work tomorrow.
I'll just sleep here.
You seem like you've gotten a little better, so I'll go buy some beer.
A soccer game is on soon.
I'll have some beer before I go to bed.
I'll be back.
No, don't go.
I can't?
Go, go.
Ba Bi's Street Food.
His sweetness and his cooking skills must be hereditary.
Totally!
I should wash my face.
What's with this look?
Did he leave his phone?
Yu Da Eun (Intern)
Missed Call-Yu Da Eun
The wedding invitation has arrived!
Episode 38: The Wedding Invitation
Eight months later
Ladies and gentlemen, we are approacing Incheon International Airport.
Please keep the seat back and table in
place, and keep large electronic devices
such as luggage or laptops under the front seat or on the shelf again.
Thank you.
CEO, you're tired, aren't you? You couldn't
get any rest as soon as you came here.
I slept during the plane ride, so not really.
Miss Seo Yeon said she was bringing
clothes for you to change into earlier.
And this is your mail that came while you were on the business trip.
Why is there so much?
Park Yong Seon, Lee Som Yi
Yong Seon, that punk, is getting married.
Seok Ju is, too.
Are these guys all getting married in a row?
Why are they all wedding invitations?
From: Kim Yumi
To: Gu Wung
When you get married, send me a wedding invitation, too.
I'm not sure. I'll discuss it with him.
Alright, guys. Let's hold hands.
That day has finally come.
You've prepared your heart, right?
We got rid of all the lingering feelings.
We decided to calmly let Yumi go.
It is a wedding invitation.
[Invitation]
Seriously...
Why is the wedding invitation so pretty?
Yumi probably picked it out, right?
- I don't want to look at it.
- I don't want to see it.
- To think that her groom is Yu Ba Bi!
- Damnit.
Special Invitational Speech for Startup
Executives - Ku Woong Games CEO Gu Wung
Convention Centre
CEO, we've arrived.
Okay.
That's right, let's look at it later.
We'll ruin the speech for no reason.
Mr. CEO, you're not going to the company. You're going home, right?
I'll go home and get some rest.
Please schedule the meeting after four o'clock.
Yes, sir.
- Please go to Hannam-do.
- Yes, sir.
This is Yumi's neighborhood.
It's our old neighborhood, too.
That was when we had the least money, but were the happiest.
One moment. Please stop the car.
Please take my luggage to my house and
leave it there. I'll head straight to the company.
Where are you going, CEO?
There's somewhere I want to visit for a bit.
Then it would be best to go by car.
When he would get off work, Yumi would wait for him there.
Wung!
Come in!
Put it there.
- Put it down there.
Huh?
Isn't that sofa from Yumi's place?
You're right. That's Yumi's bookcase.
Are they moving to Ba Bi's place?
Or to a new newlywed home?
Newlywed home?
Don't cry, Love.
We said we would smile when she gets married.
Stop!
While we're here, let's say hi to Yumi before we go.
Yes, let's tell her we look forward to seeing her in her wedding dress.
Yumi!
It's the dining table that Wung bought.
The dining table that he bought with borrowed
money because he didn't have 150,000 won (≈ $114).
We will take the dining table out now.
Sure, but where is the tenant?
Are you her husband?
No, I'm not.
I thought you were her husband.
She said she had to stop by somewhere for a bit and left.
Please be careful.
She's even taking that dining table to the newlywed home?
They're going to even eat at that dining table...
He didn't buy it for that to happen...
There you again! If you're going to be like this then let's just go.
We're not going to see Yumi.
Come on, let's just go. Come on.
- Let's just go.
Yes, the deposit went through. I verified it.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
- No problem.
- Get home safely.
- I will.
Wung!
It was you.
What are you doing here?
I had a lecture nearby, so I stopped by.
I see.
I'm here because of my house.
Congratulations.
You know?
Of course, I know.
So you heard. Thanks.
But I don't know if it was a good idea. The loan was a lot.
You took out the loan?
Of course, I would.
Is that necessary?
I don't have enough money, so what else would I do?
What the heck, Yu Ba Bi? You're making
Yumi take out a loan and getting married?
He has no conscience. If they're going to get married
like that then Wung would have married her by now!
That's right.
Guys, please stop!
I mean... well...
It's not my business.
I will pay back the debt slowly.
Exactly, why are you paying that debt—
Yes, anyway, congratulations.
That's not important anyway.
Still, I'm excited.
As long as you are happy.
You got the wedding invitation, right? I sent it.
Yeah.
Are you going to come to the wedding?
Of course.
I'm glad.
Why? Did you think I wouldn't go?
Possibly. I thought it was a 50/50 chance.
It's too bad. It would have been nice to grab a coffee,
but I have to get back. They're moving out my things right now.
Head back. I'm also leaving now.
A taxi is coming.
- I'll get going.
- Okay.
I'll see you at the wedding.
Okay.
I will look forward to seeing you in a wedding dress.
What?
I think you will look really beautiful.
Bye.
What? Me?
Hold on. Wasn't there something weird
about the end of that conversation just now?
It was weird. Something was off.
The wedding invitation! Check the wedding invitation!
What the! What's this?
The bride isn't Kim Yumi!
[Bride - Kang Yi Da]
Kang Yi Da?!
[Groom - Ahn Dae Yong]
Yumi's friend, Kang Yi Da?
Yi Da was debating on whether she should give you a wedding invitation.
You told her to send her an invitation whenever she gets married.
Sir, please go backwards!
Sure.
- Excuse me?!
- Please drive backwards. Backwards!
Right now?
I said go back! Go back!
So I am sending one on her behalf.
She won't be hurt if you don't come. Yumi.
Hurry! Hurry! Hurry!
Wung!
It's Yi Da's wedding.
What?
- The wedding invitation. It's Yi Da's wedding invitation.
- Yeah.
Then what we're you just talking about?
You weren't talking about coming to Yi Da's wedding?
Why are you moving?
- Moving?
- You moved out all of your things.
I saw them putting things into the moving van.
I bought my apartment.
I thought it was a waste to keep paying rent,
so I took my deposit and took out a loan to buy
the place even though it was a little impractical.
Since I bought it, I'm going to put in new wallpaper and flooring.
That's why I'm moving everything to storage.
You weren't congratulating me on buying a place?
No.
Then what were you talking about earlier?
- I thought you knew.
- What about you?
Me?
Your wedding?
Are you not getting married? It's been a while.
Oh...
I'm not.
Then when are you going to?
We broke up.
I guess you didn't know. I thought you heard.
I— I didn't know.
That's what happened.
I see.
I didn't know, sorry.
It's fine.
Then I'll see you at Yi Da's wedding.
All right.
I'll get going.
Okay.
Sir, let's go, please.
But why...
Wung probably wanted to ask why we broke up.
Goodbye, ajeossi.
Eight months ago.
Goodbye!
♪ Happy Birthday to you ♪
That night
That's enough...
when I was drunk on my birthday.
♪ Dear Da Eun ♪
The moment I wasn't thinking right, I called him just once.
Calling Team Leader Yu Ba Bi
Yu Da Eun (Intern)
That's a relief he didn't answer.
Team Leader Yu Ba Bi
That's a relief.
I didn't know this was love.
My feelings not being what I want them to be.
Does she want to eat tteokbokki?
Yumi, are you sleeping?
Missed call from Yu Da Eun (Intern)
Yu Da Eun (Intern)
Delete contact
The contact has been deleted.
How are you feeling?
I'm fine. I think I'm all better.
Then let's eat breakfast.
Okay.
Did you reply?
Huh?
To your father. Did you reply back?
That the tteokbokki arrived well.
Oh... No.
I will have to do it. I will call him later.
You don't have to. I will tell him later.
Still, won't he like it more if I do it?
Of course, he would.
The reason we broke up
Yu Da Eun (Intern)
is not because Da Eun called Ba Bi in the middle of the night
is also not because Ba Bi still has Da Eun's number in his contacts.
The reason we broke up is
because even though I saw that
I was calm.
How could someone in love be calm?
♫ Oh love, Will this love ♫
♫ which fills a small fist ♫
♫ If it can make you happy ♫
♫ become used to even being alone? ♫
♫ That's fine with me ♫
Yumi's Cells 2
Preview
I'm sorry.
♫ Of all things when the song coming out of the radio ♫
You're coming when you finish with your deadline, right?
What should we do?
Love!
Their meeting has to be as if it's fate. As if it's a miracle.
Yumi.
♫ takes me back to the the time ♫
♫ which shined most beautifully ♫