ENJOY ALL VOD IN HIGH QUALITY @ 4KVOD.TV
GET LIVE TV,MOVIES,SHOWS IN ONE PACKAGE
FAMILY MOTTO
A HARMONIOUS FAMILY WITH LOVE
-Wasn't it good?
-It was the best.
-That's my point.
-So the kids…
I know a really good place.
The second round is on me.
What do you say?
-Come on, let's go.
-Let's go!
Even some photos
from that time make me so sad.
How is Dad facing
his 22-year-old self again?
Dad!
Dad.
I knew…
that this day would come.
I've always imagined.
My happy house
started to crumble
when that man's careful footsteps began.
Hello?
He was careful at first,
but he gradually became
more and more shameless.
Hello?
My happy house
turned into hell,
where I couldn't even breathe.
I decided to kill myself
as a man's wife and live as a mother.
I swept and wiped the house
more than a dozen times a day.
I had to protect my house for my kids.
Did you…
just call me Dad?
Who is she?
Where's your common sense?
She's obviously his wife.
-Right?
-I see.
I didn't expect you
to come out of there, ma'am.
Come on. What's wrong with you?
We all call you "Dad" here.
She may get the wrong idea.
Right.
Driver Kim says we're his sons
when he's drunk,
so we call him Dad.
You're a bit weird today.
Are you not well?
Well…
No.
Dad!
See?
Everyone calls him Dad here.
I was on my way to work,
so I'll get going.
Dad.
Have a safe trip back.
We should get going too.
-Okay.
-All right.
-We're leaving, Driver Kim.
-Goodbye.
Dad attempted suicide?
My Dad tried to do that
and leave me behind?
No…
And leave our family behind?
How do you know about that?
I got his medical chart from the hospital.
He was in a critical state
when he was found.
They couldn't even get his temperature
due to hypothermia.
Considering that,
he's recovering very fast.
When the rescuers found him,
they found a medicine bottle nearby.
It was almost empty,
but they didn't detect
any pills in his body.
Was it sleeping pills?
Yes.
Dad has insomnia.
Because his sleeping routine is irregular.
Are you going to overlook it?
You said it wasn't in his system.
He didn't take it.
Your mother knows, too.
She asked them if any trace of
sleeping pills were found in his body.
Why are you telling me now?
I was going to see him first
when his memories come back,
but I thought it'd be better if you do.
You should tell him.
An illness of the mind is also a disease.
It needs to be prescribed.
You tell him.
I have to go to the seminar
and it's not good to waste time.
I can't.
I know I shouldn't be like this,
but I hate my mom.
Graduation from marriage all of a sudden?
I hate it.
I have something to tell you.
My brother sent me photos
from my university days
before I came here.
Aren't all girls at that age pretty?
But I wasn't pretty.
I think I look better now.
You're not laughing.
I also broke up
after nine years of dating.
He cheated on me.
He was dating another woman
for three years,
but I didn't know.
I wonder what the man who dated me
for nine years told her about me.
Did he tell her
we were drifting apart slowly?
that our relationship was ending?
Were you disappointed because I said that?
Disappointed…
It was arrogant.
I was just being honest.
Why do I sense confidence?
I was worried about what you might say,
but I'm relieved.
I didn't say it to relieve you.
Think from a different point of view.
Dating for nine years
isn't a common experience.
But we're similar in that way as well.
Isn't this fate?
You know from experience
that nine years is just a matter of time.
Drifting apart,
starting to hate each other,
and expecting nothing from each other.
You'd understand my situation so well,
so I feel at ease.
Are you saying
I'll keep your secrets and hide
because I understand it?
No.
I never wanted you
to keep the secret or hide.
I will keep the secret
and hide completely,
and will not care
about what situation you two are in.
So we can…
keep seeing each other?
I will do as I wish.
Yes. Do as you wish, Eun-hee.
Before that, I have a favor to ask you.
Show me the photos your brother sent you.
I'm so curious.
You were pretty.
You said you weren't pretty
to make me curious.
This is not pretty.
I'm frowning without knowing
how wonderful that age was.
By the way, your brother
is a great photographer.
My brother didn't take it.
Oh.
Why are you making that sound?
My friend took it.
That friend from last time.
I wasn't going to say this,
but I'm a good photographer myself.
I can take it better than this.
-I'll take it.
-I don't like taking photos.
-Come on.
-No.
Here we go. One, two…
Should I have opened
a wedding photography studio?
What a nice photo.
How do you know Chan-hyuk?
My mom and his mom know each other.
That's why I started working for him.
It's sort of nepotism.
That applies to me too then.
At least you studied abroad.
I have to try really hard.
I got kicked out
even without finishing one year.
I didn't really study abroad.
Don't ask with those eyes.
No.
I need to ask.
I'm sick of that damn curiosity.
If we become social media friends
and surf around,
you'll hear ridiculous rumors soon.
No, not that.
If you're working after getting
kicked out in less than a year…
How old are you?
I was born in 1995.
What about you?
When we empty these glasses,
let's speak casually at the same time.
What on earth are you thinking?
Who is it?
I'm sorry.
I'm really drunk.
I'm leaving.
I shouldn't stop you, right?
The photo I showed you earlier.
At that time,
I wasn't happy.
Good job. See you tomorrow.
I'll move this.
But it's heavy.
It's light.
Back then,
-I was independent.
-I'm so sorry.
-See you tomorrow.
-I was free.
I was always bright,
whenever and wherever.
I exhausted myself
to be the great girlfriend
who didn't restrain her boyfriend.
Why?
Because that's how
I've been living my life.
I wanted to impress people
and be a good person to others.
I was in a relationship
with that personality.
Imagine how much I tried to impress him.
You don't have to do that to me.
Exactly.
I'm doing everything as I wish.
I'm leaving because I want to leave.
Bye.
Eun-hee.
Try to find the root of your personality.
What a cliché prescription.
You want something more cliché?
If you talk to someone about it,
it gets easier.
I do have a private safe
that I talk to about everything.
If you go over there
you can see the place where I always sit.
I'm so happy to be with you, Ms. Sook.
You're good at finding your way
in the complex alleys.
We had both Eun-joo and Eun-hee
when you started truck driving.
You said it was your first time
going to Ulsan.
And…
you know the area well?
You're lying about not remembering, right?
-Where's Ji-woo?
-Restroom.
You should've told me
he can't handle alcohol.
Thank you.
Chan-hyuk.
We decided to speak casually
with each other.
She got the wrong idea
about you liking Eun-hee
because you had her photo.
I told her
that you and Eun-hee
don't have that kind of relationship.
Why?
Why are you so certain?
Oh.
Is it wrong for me to be certain?
No, you can be certain.
But there must be a reason
why you're so certain.
I've seen you guys for a long time
and I never felt anything like that.
What an absurd certainty.
Family. Friends. Lovers.
It's easier to trick those
you've known for a long time.
Right.
Family members trick each other.
When are you going to
meet my eldest sister?
That's hot.
Why are you mentioning
your eldest sister all of a sudden?
I love my eldest sister so much.
My eldest sister.
A doctor's wife.
Ulsan…
is my hometown.
I was orphaned at the age of 14.
I felt like I was going to starve
to death and wasn't sure about life.
So I started helping truck drivers load
and unload, and I came to Seoul.
You were a university student,
and you were so pretty and wonderful.
I knew I wasn't a good match.
So I learned the Seoul dialect
so as not to seem like country folk.
I could've grown taller,
but I starved a lot at the time.
I was so nervous about when to tell you
but I guess…
I didn't tell you until I got this old.
But…
I really don't remember.
Our son-in-law said
my memories will come back soon,
so please believe me.
Let's go back before the last bus leaves.
If the last bus leaves,
we can spend the night here
and see the sunrise together.
I can't get used to this.
Ms. Sook.
Ms. Sook!
What's so great
about the poor and hungry days?
I forgot about it.
Don't remember anything.
You know the story of the fairy
and the woodcutter, right?
The fairy had two children,
so she flew up to the sky
with each of them in her hands.
You…
were like a fairy that came to me,
so I was always scared
that you might fly away.
That's why…
I decided that I will have
three kids.
Our kids
are not like me.
They studied a lot,
and they grew up into wonderful
and beautiful people.
Ms. Sook.
You've done so much.
I wish…
I can remember everything soon as well.
I suddenly remembered.
This man
cried a lot.
A man who believes in soulmates
and a woman who thinks
there's no such thing met.
There was a time when there were
only two of us in the world,
and we were everything to each other.
I asked you to send me the address.
You didn't have to come.
Aren't you pampering him
for being the youngest?
I'm not.
Goodness.
How can he survive
in the real world like this?
He knocks down before his boss?
Do I look fine to you?
Where's Seo-young?
I sent her back.
He seems to have a secret,
but he won't tell me.
Our youngest?
He never keeps secrets, worries,
and emotions bottled up.
This is what's annoying about families.
He has a secret.
Talk to him gently and listen to him.
It seems quite serious to him.
Were you with Mr. Playboy?
So you're not going
to dump your trash on me anymore?
I hate that expression.
Let's call it a private safe instead.
Safe or trash can,
you look tired already.
It's because I'm embarrassed.
What on earth are you thinking?
That's embarrassing.
"What are you thinking?" actually means
"You are putting on a show
when you were acting cool."
"Do you think I would've brought you here
if my nine-year girlfriend may show up?"
Yes.
I was really embarrassed.
I saw the photo
of that nine-year girlfriend.
He's a true Mr. Playboy.
He actually left that out?
Yes.
I acted like I didn't see it.
Well done.
At least you didn't compliment her looks.
Hey.
If you decided to date him,
then just focus on that.
Why are you bringing in a woman
who's not even there
as if there are three of you?
It's all because of the photos.
Photos?
Ji-woo sent me the photos you took of me.
Why do you have them?
Did Jong-pal give them to you?
Hey!
Goodness me.
-Ji-woo, wake up.
-Goodness, Ji-woo.
This punk has no worries.
Hey, Ji-woo.
Ji-woo!
Is something troubling you?
He has absolutely no worries.
-Eun-hee.
-You scared me!
I'm going to kill you!
Let's go to Eun-joo's house!
Let us three siblings have a meeting.
Shut up and sleep!
If we go to her house now,
she'll nag us like crazy.
Eun-joo.
How can he be such a lightweight?
Is he adopted or something?
Eun-hee.
What?
I liked you more.
I liked everything about you
and thought you were more comfortable.
"Liked?"
Why is it past tense?
How can love change?
I hate that.
I hate that so much!
Are you saying that to me?
It's crappy.
We threw away all of the luggage.
Is there anything you can use to pack?
I still have a few days left.
What's with the rush?
I won't take many things.
Okay, you can take care of it then.
About your father.
Did you tell Eun-hee?
I'll take care of that myself.
It seems like your father
attempted suicide.
Your mother knows, too.
MOM
Goodness. Why did he drink so much?
OCTOBER 13, 1983
Hey, Youngest.
Now that I think about it,
I think this is the first time
they went somewhere
on their own.
Ms. Sook…
must feel weird.
Okay, back up.
A little further.
Little more.
Back up.
Don’t do things like this.
Let's be mature and not be obvious.
Okay.
I want each team
to take care of everything I said.
I have a good feeling about this.
Dismissed.
-Well done.
So mature.
Excuse me.
How can I help you?
-What business do you…
-I'm here to see Ms. Kim Eun-hee.
Ms. Kim.
Okay, then.
Tae-hyung.
We need to talk.
-Go ahead and eat.
-Okay.
Is something going on?
I just stopped by
because I thought of you.
What a cliché answer.
This is not a place
where you just stop by.
What about the clinic?
I'm going to a seminar in New Zealand.
So I only worked during the morning today.
I see.
Your sister will be alone.
So I wanted to ask you
to go see her often.
Since when did you become so romantic?
I want you sisters to get closer.
Goodness.
It's awkward just to imagine
being close to her.
I know your sister is the problem.
You have a better personality
and you're more generous.
She's not the problem.
I'm not the problem either.
She and I are just…
ordinary sisters.
I don't think
you two are ordinary sisters.
Sisters who love and miss
each other are the weird ones.
If something happens to her,
I'll be on her side no matter what,
so don't worry.
But…
you didn't come here
just to tell me that, did you?
There's something big, isn't there?
I don't think your sister will tell you.
But I think you should know, too.
It seems like your father
attempted suicide.
DAD
That's not true. Right, Dad?
That makes no sense.
Hello. I'm Ji Yong-geun, the CEO.
Our company…
only uses domestic
agricultural products as ingredients,
therefore is loved by the consumers.
Especially domestic agricultural…
Excuse me.
What are you doing?
Let's move to a different place.
Get up.
I'm sorry.
You could've just tapped me.
You would've gotten startled
if I tapped you.
I think the shop will be great.
Okay, let me just take a look.
You told him about me, right?
He's sharp-witted.
Nonsense.
Guys his age
are either idiots or just dogs.
It's either one of those two.
Check it yourself.
Stop bothering me during work.
-Thank you.
Is he just an idiot?
THE YOO'S FRUIT SHOP
What do you need?
EFFECTS OF BANANAS
PREVENTS CHRONIC DEPRESSION
Do bananas prevent chronic depression?
I didn't know either, but I guess so.
Where's Mr. Yoo?
My dad?
He went on a date.
Do you like Korean melons?
What?
How disappointing.
Wash your hands and come out.
FAMILY MOTTO
A HARMONIOUS FAMILY WITH LOVE
FAMILY WELFARE
WELFARE ADMINISTRATION
HEALTHCARE REGULATIONS
VOLUNTEER COORDINATION
THE YOO'S FRUIT SHOP
THAT STUDY FRUITS AND VEGETABLES
THEORIES OF FAMILY WELFARE
TECHNIQUES IN PRACTICING SOCIAL WELFARE
Dad.
What is it?
You know how to peel fruit?
Are you saying I never did this?
Well…
Where did Mom go?
She went out right after dinner
to go to the community center.
She said she'll be a bit late.
I see.
Ms. Sook
is learning poetry.
That itself is a poem.
What?
"Ms. Sook is learning poetry."
That's a poem.
How cool.
It does sound like a poem.
Well…
Eun-hee.
Did we…
get along?
Was I…
a decent father?
It seems like your mother is angry at me.
Is there anything you want to tell me?
Dad.
Yes?
I was…
always curious about something.
Two, two, nine.
Dad, I know all the songs
from the Campus Song Festival
that you always asked me to record.
I was always curious about your singing
skills when I recorded those songs.
Mr. Kim Sang-sik sings "I."
I have a happy dream of love
So snow falls on plenty of love
And if our love has a song
We will find a beautiful life
It was us
It has been living
In our dreams
With the biggest heart
I love this entire world
It seems like…
your father attempted suicide.
Following the falling leaves
He left
"My Love."
What?
By Youshimcho.
I want to sing "My Love."
"MY LOVE" BY YOUSHIMCHO
Oh
Love is a flame that has burnt
-Oh
-Love is like the wind
-Even though I try to forget her entirely
-But why can't I forget Jin-sook?
-But why can't I forget you?
Oh, my Jin-sook
Dad.
Do you remember the movie
Back To The Future?
What?
I guess the current you
wouldn't have seen it.
It's a movie where the main character
goes to the past and the future.
If the main character goes
to the past and changes something
and returns to the future,
the future is changed
in a complicated way.
I guess…
that's how you feel right now, right?
From the eyes of a 22-year-old you,
the 60-year-old Ms. Lee Jin-sook
may seem angry and cold.
But…
if you accept the things
that she does and understand her,
then would the future change?
What am I saying?
Ms. Sook didn't do anything wrong.
I'm sure it’s all my fault.
I have to gain my memory back quickly.
Dad.
I hated you a bit.
You didn't talk much when you came home
and you only loved Eun-joo.
I was always on Mom's side.
I'm sorry.
It's good that you're
on your mother's side.
I'm sorry, too.
But…
Dad, promise me one thing.
What?
When your memories
come back, tell me first.
Why?
So we can find a way to surprise
our precious Ms. Jin-sook
How?
I'll tell you later.
Promise me.
When your memories come back,
you will come to me first.
Okay.
-Thank you, Dad.
-Yes.
Thank you.
Thank you for being alive, Dad.
-I'm sure he'll come.
-What?
Ms. Sook.
Why are you here?
You scared me.
Eun-hee bought Korean melons.
Would you like me to cut them for you?
It's bedtime. No, thanks.
You don't want any?
By the way, I'm not a kid.
Were you looking for me
because you were worried about me?
You don't need to worry about anything.
I'm going to start working, too.
I must make money.
First, I'm going to go to
Ulsan soon.
They were selling it down there.
Isn't it lovely?
It was cheap too.
You said you'd never come to my house.
Did I promise that? No way.
You vacuumed the house at this hour?
That's good.
Forget the wine.
Beer is the best after cleaning.
Yes, let's go out and have a beer.
I ordered delivery on my way.
Beer, too.
Why did you ring the doorbell?
You know the passcode.
You even left the photo on the shelf.
My hands were full
because of the flower pot.
I've been so stressed until now.
I'm staying for the weekend.
The phone is turned off.
Please record a message.
Once you're connected…
The phone is turned off.
-Delivery.
-Thank you.
Is it good?
Not really.
I gifted that book to Eun-joo.
Eun-joo lent it to you, right?
Yes.
What about the receipt?
No, thanks.
You're a good driver.
I'm bad at being bad.
I was just kidding.
Get used to driving this car.
I don't drive that much.
This house is bigger than we thought.
I think it's actually small.
-Come on.
-Children.
Don't run. Goodness.
Let's go outside.
Thanks for showing it to us.
We'll call you, ma'am.
Put your shoes on.
Our house is up for sale?
Yes, let's talk
when your memories come back.
But I like this house.
Hey.
Did Tae-hyung leave safely?
Yes.
You're here.
Dad, how are you?
I'm good.
But my memories aren't back yet.
I heard you drove the truck.
I could do it with my eyes closed.
Mom and I will be back
after grocery shopping.
Let's eat what we have.
Should I go too?
You shouldn't carry heavy things.
I have something to say.
You stay home.
What is it?
Mom.
Remember when you ran away with me
when I was in elementary school?
What are you talking about
all of a sudden?
Why did you only take me?
Why did you leave Eun-hee behind
and only take me?
Mom.
I remember everything.
I was starving because I didn't
eat anything all day,
but I didn't tell you.
Because would've told me
to drink the juice
if I told you I was hungry.
I saw you putting a drug
into the juice bottle.
No.
It's not what you think.
Mom.
You tried to commit suicide with me.
I've committed such a big sin.
It's my fault.
We went back home…
and Dad was cooking
in the kitchen to feed Eun-hee.
When you were trying to kill me,
Dad stayed home from work
and was cooking for Eun-hee,
I can never forget that.
It wasn't a drug.
It was a herbal powder.
A poisonous one.
I was trying to abort Ji-woo.
I wasn't trying to kill you.
I've committed such a big sin.
What would've happened
if I didn't give birth to him?
Aren’t you going to see Young-sik?
Dad!
Dad.
Have a safe trip back.
YOUNG-SIK
Hello?
I am…
You know?
Right. It shows on the phone.
I'm calling you
after thinking for a few days.
Do you want to meet?
Why did you do that?
Two is fine,
but if it was three,
I thought I wouldn't
be able to do anything.
What's so bad about having three kids?
What are you, a fairy?
I am a fairy.
Then is Dad the woodcutter?
By the way, did you come here
to talk about this?
Tae-hyung told me.
About what?
About Dad.
About the medicine bottle
when he was found.
He didn't take it.
Regardless, he did
carry the medicine with him.
Are you
saying it's my fault?
That's not what I'm saying.
What are you going to do
when Dad's memories come back?
Isn't it obvious?
We just live our lives as we planned.
-Thank you.
-Thank you. Goodbye.
Okay.
Chan-hyuk.
Eun-hee said your phone is off.
I turned it off before the shoot.
You asked her
about registering a trademark?
She scheduled a dinner with Eun-joo.
It'll be perfect if you go now.
Why did she do that without talking to me?
I smell like cheonggukjang.
Eun-joo said today
was the best day for her.
Gosh.
MARCH 2016
How's Jong-min?
Relax and tell me the truth.
We fought as well and he moved out.
He'll take his things soon.
That's good.
That means you're home alone now.
Yes.
I have a favor to ask you.
Go ahead.
Eun-hee is going to end it just like this.
She won't even consider
having a proper closure.
And she won't even think about
getting rid of his traces.
I want you to clean things
for her instead.
Get rid of all items related
to Eun-hee in Jong-min's room.
Like photos
or anything Eun-hee left there.
I heard they share a bank account.
Tell him to split it equally
and get rid of traces of Eun-hee
as much as possible.
Okay.
I'll take care of everything.
You're being too polite.
Right.
Thank you for taking my wedding photos.
But you took too many.
I'm not good at keeping them,
so I should've told you
not to take too many.
It seemed like you took a lot on purpose.
No.
It's normal to take that many.
You two met before without telling me?
It was that time
when we fought and cut ties.
How could I call you
when we cut ties to tell you
"I met your sister today."
Right.
That's when I was antisocial.
That's why I had your photos
that were given to Jong-min.
Thanks for not throwing it away.
I didn't even think
about throwing it away.
It was indifference.
I didn't even know that I had it.
She told us to come in front of her house,
but why isn't she here?
It's the weekend.
Are you not meeting Mr. Playboy?
He's out of reach.
What do you think that means?
He's probably slowly drifting apart.
So I'm staying quiet and not calling him.
He'll feel empty, right?
You wish.
He's probably enjoying his freedom.
Because his hidden woman
number 2 is cool and generous,
he must be thinking it's perfect.
Hidden woman number 2?
He may have hidden women
number 3 and 4 too.
No matter how harsh your criticism is,
I'll take everything as advice.
Don't leave any traces behind.
Trace?
Have you seen Mr. Playboy's trace?
Have you seen his footprints?
Don't introduce him to friends or family.
Don't show any signs.
Playboys hate that.
You're enjoying this, aren't you?
In order to leave no trace,
go to his house
and don't bring him to your house.
I'll stop here.
That was too nosy.
I didn’t know.
We don't go to the movies,
famous restaurants,
or nice cafes.
We always go to his house.
I thought we were just lazy
because we're old,
but we were actually
trying not to leave any trace.
Now I understand
after hearing it from you.
He's a real pro.
-Here are your two cups of coffee.
-Thanks.
-Hello.
-You should've waited.
I was going to pay.
Buy us dinner then.
I'd like coffee too.
Let's have a drink today.
I'm free today.
I see.
Take those first. I'll bring mine.
Okay.
Did she talk casually to him?
I think so.
She didn't even talk casually
to Ji-woo's friends.
-You don't have to drink it.
-Why not?
You said you're going to drink.
Alcohol and coffee are different.
Hey, why are they whispering?
Are you free today?
I'm free for a while.
Hey, did you see the way she moved?
Just drink coffee.
Why? Where's Dr. Yoon?
He went to a seminar.
I see. A seminar.
To where?
New Zealand.
I'll bring it.
You will?
Thanks.
When the blood…
rushes to the brain all of a sudden,
it's good for your brain.
Gosh, I'm dizzy.
Ms. Sook, do you want to do that together?
Ms. Sook.
I thought about it.
About why I didn't tell you
I was born in Ulsan until now.
Was it because I was worried
that you might think of me as a liar
or because I was embarrassed
about lying about that to you?
If I saw the future
when I was 22 years old,
if I knew that we would have three kids
and live happily for a long time,
I would've told you everything,
embarrassing or not.
Did you think I would leave?
I'm not good enough for you.
I was going to go there alone
but come to Ulsan with me tomorrow.
It seems like you're bothered
so let's go meet him.
I'm not keeping any more secrets from you.
Let's talk when your memories come back.
Come with me.
I don't know the way either,
so you should be by my side.
Okay?
There's still no beer in this place
and you're still close to that barista.
Because Tae-hyung and I are regulars here.
We do trademark registrations,
but we don't do business registrations.
I have something to look into
regarding trademark registration.
Then I'll do it for you
instead of connecting you to someone else.
I started working again, anyway.
You started working?
Did you get reinstated to your old work?
I'll send you
the list of documents you need.
I'm a freelancer.
Also…
Here.
You prepared them already?
No, I was organizing some photos recently
and found some photos of you and Eun-hee.
I developed some of your
wedding photos in black-and-white.
It's nice.
You're a good photographer.
This is so sudden.
Are you organizing
your photo albums these days?
I wanted to give them to you
as a wedding gift but had no chance.
So I'm giving them to you now.
I thought you might be glad to see them.
You're talking so politely.
I can see the emotions show better
since the photos are black-and-white.
I have a 50% off coupon for chicken.
Will you eat it if I order it?
-I have one too.
-One chicken per person?
-No, use mine.
-I asked to eat first, so use mine.
-Cola or lemon-lime soda?
-Lemon-lime soda.
Fried or baked?
Fried.
-Radish or pickle as a side?
-Radish.
Cola, baked, and pickle?
None of them fit my taste.
Why did you even ask then?
I thought you'd just let me pick.
Gosh.
Though it doesn't
fit your taste, enjoy the food.
This is what sudden use
of honorifics feels like.
When the time comes and the vibe is right,
do something with me.
I knew there was something.
What is it?
Isn't it obvious
between a young man and a woman?
Have a fling and date?
I have a girlfriend.
You acted like you didn't.
I never did that.
You never said
you're going on a date or anything.
Right.
She lives far away. Really far away.
Why does the food keep coming?
You should eat well when you drink.
You're old.
Eun-joo.
The one who said
you're perfect and wonderful
is this guy.
It was Chan-hyuk.
He said you're perfect and wonderful.
You're insightful.
-Yes.
-Order some more.
I just remembered.
Jong-pal told me before.
He said you liked my sister.
You said she was
perfect and wonderful. Right?
Are you drunk?
It's because she lacks insight.
What about me?
Be honest.
You liked my sister, right?
Hey, just eat your food.
Eun-joo, when were you
planning to tell me about Dad?
How did you know?
That's not important.
Were you trying to
keep it to yourself again?
What are you? A problem solver?
Never mind.
Nothing was solved anyway.
I hate it when you talk
about serious things when you're drunk.
I'm not drunk.
I'm not!
Mr. Yoo, who studies
fruits and vegetables, please come out.
You know nothing.
Eun-joo.
I feel sick.
Why did my Dad…
do such a thing?
This is so embarrassing.
Don't sneak out. Let's finish talking.
What now?
Why is she not letting me go?
What will she nag about this time?
Darn it.
How come there's no outlet
in such a big house?
CLOSET: PETER YOON'S CHATROOM
What are you doing in there?
Charging.
Charging my phone.
Tae-hyung left his laptop.
Does he not need it?
What's with your face?
Oh.
Hangover.
Eun-joo.
Don't look.
CLOSET: PETER YOON'S CHATROOM
DIANA: COMING OUT IS GIVING UP
HER 23: A FEMALE EMPLOYEE SAID I LOOK GAY
DIANA: SHE'S GOT KEEN EYES
HER 23: WHY DO I FEEL BAD
WHEN SOMEONE SAYS I'M GAY?
ATO: PETER YOON, DID YOU REALLY
COME OUT TO YOUR WIFE?
DIANA: DID YOU GO
TO THE SEMINAR OR RUN AWAY?!
PETER YOON
We're family.
We are family…
but we don't know much
about each other.
You've been ignoring me for years
and now you're worried about me?
My eldest sister has no father.
I hope he's not getting weird ideas.
It's my house
and it's the matter of my family. Go.
He remembers things so clearly, but…
You wrote "I love you" on the note.
But sometimes he says
something totally different.
I remember everything now.
Tell me.
Why did you act that way on that day?
Subtitle translation by: Hae-lim Lee
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/ah6xk
Help other users to choose the best subtitles