- [Cell doors clanging]
- BRAITHWAITE: Hey! You!
I'm onto you.
I know all about you.
MORGAN: I'm sick to death
with people talking about me
behind my back.
BUFFY: I'm gonna write to
the home secretary about this.
OFFICER: Lockup!
Lockup!
SNOOPER: There's deals
going down all the time.
Every day.
Every night.
MAN:
What's a fax machine?
BUFFY: Put that bastard
on the wing, and I'll kill him.
JACKSON: Bastards.
Put it down!
Now!
Shoot! Shoot!
[Officers groan]
SAMORA: There you are.
I told you I knew him, didn't I?
He's my mate.
Tarzan!
MEN: [Chanting] Tarzan!
Tarzan! Tarzan!
I won't talk to anyone
but the frigging governor!
I want my mother!
I want a blow-up rubber doll!
He wants a blow-up rubber doll.
Mm-hmm.
And to see you blowing it up.
He's out.
Is he out? Gary?
Can you stand?
I'm just a bit stiff.
[Cell door closes, locks]
ENJOY ALL VOD IN HIGH QUALITY @ 4KVOD.TV
GET LIVE TV,MOVIES,SHOWS IN ONE PACKAGE
Gary!
Oh, good morning.
Sorry.
Hi.
How's Russell Morgan?
Oh, he's fine.
He insisted on returning to duty
after a few days.
After you.
[Keys clinking]
Helen Hewitt.
Prison board.
These hostage situations,
they have a kind of
whiplash effect, do you know?
He's an old pro.
We just get on with it.
It's like falling off a bike.
Well, frankly, I don't think
it's that simple,
but I hope you prove me wrong.
- [Tires screeching]
- [Horn beeping]
- You cut me off, bastard!
- Piss off!
You want to look
where you're going, pal!
- Hey, do you hear me?
- Piss off!
You cut me off back there!
Piss off!
- [Tires screeching]
- [Horn honking]
You stupid git.
What's your problem?
You think you can ride roughshod
over people, pal.
Well, you've picked
the wrong one.
Bastard!
[Horns honking]
- Bastard!
- Bugger off.
Bugger off.
Get out of here.
MAN:
What's going on up there?
All right, mate?
Get away from me!
MAN:
Move your ruddy bike, then.
FALLA: I'm gonna start
messing with him!
I mean it!
I'm gonna start cutting him!
- What happened to Mavis?
- Contract wasn't renewed.
Governor Keller brought in
a load of new staff.
Here you go.
Keller wasn't here, you know,
when it went down.
Oh, he says he was,
but he was playing golf.
His secretary, Mrs. Gill,
covered for him.
How do you know?
I know one of the stewards.
He told me.
- Miss Hewitt, good morning.
- Morning.
I'm to take you through
to the boardroom.
- Okay.
- Want me with you?
No, you'll be called
when you're required.
Miss Hewitt.
- [Knock on door]
- Yeah.
Mr. Marshall, could I have
a moment, please?
Sure, Miss Bullock.
That was Helen Hewitt.
She was overseeing Barfield
during the rebuilding.
BULLOCK: Oh.
What's she here for?
HQ are here to discuss
the hostage situation
that went down
a couple of weeks ago.
- [Telephone rings]
- I just want to run past you
the rehearsal schedule
for the musical.
Sorry.
Yeah, Marshall.
Yeah, hang on.
Yeah, he's supposed to be
on duty.
Okay, I'll get someone
to call his home.
[Beeps]
Margaret, will you call
Russell Morgan's home,
see if he's on his way in?
Only they're expecting him
in the boardroom.
Oh, and get back to me
on it, yeah?
Thanks.
This is a list of the inmates
that want to be involved.
- It's a musical, isn't it?
- Yes.
And I need Kevin Watts,
prisoner 678, C Wing.
He said he can play the piano.
Okay, I'll get this lot
checked out with head office.
Thank you.
I instructed prison routine
to continue as normal,
staff to go about their duties,
except for
the known trained negotiators.
Doctor to be in attendance.
Clear all inmates
from around the hostage cell.
Screen the area,
set up surveillance equipment.
Works governor to be brought in
to advise if necessary...
Cell construction.
And door jack to be at hand.
And the C-and-R squad to deploy,
fully kitted but out of sight.
Under the circumstances,
I don't think there was anything
else I could have instigated.
Oh, Barfield's
head of psychology
was unfortunately at
Newgate House with Miss Hewitt.
Please, Gordon,
this is not an inquiry.
We just like all the facts.
Miss Hewitt.
KELLER:
Damn well feels like it.
My main observation
is that there were too many
people in silver command,
trying to be helpful
but nevertheless
an unnecessary presence.
Excuse me, Miss Hewitt.
S.O. Russell Morgan
hasn't turned up for work.
Phoned his home,
but there's no reply.
Check up where the hell he is.
We need him here.
It's the entire point
of the meeting.
DR. HARRIS: very confusing to
know exactly who was doing what.
I agree with Dr. Harris.
I mean, I was receiving
duplicate information
from two different officers
in the healthcare center.
So it would be helpful if...
Mr. Keller, are you aware of the
new procedures instigated by HQ?
Barfield is severely lacking
in trained negotiating officers.
In a prison of this size, that
should have been a priority.
I did what I could
as soon as I was informed
we had a hostage situation.
Now, that was not...
Mr. Keller, we are not here
to apportion any blame.
Miss Hewitt has kindly agreed
to join us again.
As you know,
she was instrumental
in releasing Mr. Morgan,
so she is obviously familiar
with siege and hostage training.
Miss Hewitt has a hidden agenda.
[Knock on door]
Ah, coffee.
Good.
Then I think we'll adjourn
to the healthcare center.
Shall I be mother?
WOMAN: Coffee?
I think he's drunk.
- SMITH: [Singsong] Ja-son.
- [Laughs]
- Ja-son.
- Cut that out. Sit down.
Go on, sit down.
Front row.
C Wing inmates.
For one hour.
Quiet.
Quiet, please.
Eric, Roddy.
Hand out these music sheets.
All I'll do this morning
is start auditioning
for named roles and chorus.
Let's settle down.
Come on.
Those chosen to be in the show
with leading roles will get...
Quiet! Quiet!
Special privileges of three
rehearsal periods a week
and will be excused workshop.
[Cheering and whistling]
- Miss Bollock, I'm going...
- [Laughter]
Miss Bullock.
Don't tell her anyway.
You've got two more weeks.
I'm going out. I won't be here
for the first night.
Yeah, but you're
getting out of workshop.
- BULLOCK: Quiet! Quiet!
- You's right.
Sorry, we were just wondering
who was gonna go soprano.
Will you come up
on the stage, please, Brian?
I never did anything Miss Bull...
Miss Bollock... Bullock.
I want to hear you sing, Brian.
- Oooh!
[Laughter]
Play the first few bars
of the opening song, Kevin.
[Playing down-tempo piano music]
[Playing dissonantly]
[Laughter]
Why, yes, give me a C, boy!
[Plays boogie-woogie]
[Men whistling]
Need to get some practice in,
Miss Bullock.
[Plays notes]
[Panting]
All right?
FALLA: I mean it!
I'm gonna start cutting him!
Transferral of a prisoner,
was not available
to S.O. Russell Morgan.
The nominal index card,
the prisoner's
long-term allocation report,
OCA Birmingham,
his reallocation report,
OCA Wandsworth,
and his security sheet...
Apparently remained
at reception.
I wasn't given
any details whatsoever,
apart from his medical reports.
So at no time... Dr. Harris,
at no time were you made aware
or any of the staff on duty
that morning
that the inmate George Falla
was extremely dangerous?
Didn't take us long
to find out, Miss Hewitt.
HEWITT: I'm sure it didn't,
since he was threatening
to kill the hostage,
and according to this report,
there was a belief that
he would carry out that threat.
I'm sorry, but we're still
unable to contact S.O. Morgan.
Keep trying.
I want him here.
Dr. Harris.
When you examined Mr. Morgan,
was he in good shape?
Well, he had a bad nick
to the side of his neck,
and his neck was also bruised
from where the noose
had been tied 'round it.
Both wrists had signs
of burn-type bruising.
No, no, no.
I meant his mental state.
Fine.
Appeared absolutely fine.
Look, is this going to
go on much longer.
I've got my morning rounds
to do.
Right, I don't think there's any
need to delay you any longer.
Thanks.
Mr. Keller,
I meant Dr. Harris.
Do you mind if we just take up
another half hour or so?
I'm beginning to mind.
If I'm going to be subjected
to this kind of scrutiny,
then you will get
my resignation.
[Siren wailing]
MORGAN: [Sobbing]
I do not know of anything more
I could have done!
Senior Officer Morgan
returned to work
three days after the incident
of his own volition,
so I don't think...
Did you set up
a care-bear support team?
Care bear.
HQ have
a post-incident support team
for counseling
within the service for staff.
Officer Morgan
returned to duties
and without any ill effects.
Now, I'm sorry,
but I've got three adjudications
this morning,
so if there is anything else,
could we leave it
to another time?
Most unfortunate that Mr. Morgan
wasn't present this morning.
Thank you very much for
your cooperation, Mr. Keller.
Just one more thing, Mr. Keller.
According to the logbook,
there was
almost over an hour's delay
before you actually instigated
the silver and bronze teams.
Now, was there
a reason for this?
Well, you were actually here
at Barfield, weren't you?
Yes, Miss Hewitt.
I was.
I have to report to HQ,
but I'd like to see the prison
chaplain before I leave.
[Playing dissonantly]
No, no, Kevin!
Look, if you hum it again,
I can usually pick up anything.
Well, can't you sight-read
anything at all?
I'm sorry, Miss Bullock,
I'm gonna have to take Mr. Watts
back to the wing.
They're serving lunch
in 10 minutes.
We've got more tone-deaf inmates
on C Wing
than we have on D and E,
and I'm beginning to think
it could be the fault
of my pianist.
Miss Bullock,
have you met Helen Hewitt?
No.
I saw you earlier.
- How do you do?
- I'm a psychologist.
Ah, yes,
you work with Dr. Williams.
- Yes.
- Is he back here yet?
No, his wife's suffering
from postnatal depression.
Oh.
Well, nice to meet you.
Bye-bye.
Governor Keller did say
that he was here at Barfield
at the time the hostage incident
started, didn't he?
Yes, he did.
I think you'll find he was
not even in the building.
Mr. Fuller,
this is Helen Hewitt.
She'd like to talk to you.
She's from the Prison Service.
- How do you do?
- Hi. Nice to meet you.
Would you escort Miss Hewitt
back to the office area, please?
I do know the way, Mr. Bunny.
I daresay you do.
It's security.
Could we go into your office,
do you think?
Oh, yes, yes.
It's this way.
I know.
I used to work here.
Oh, really?
Doing what exactly?
Governor.
I can see I'm gonna miss
this culinary expertise.
What is?
Fatty?
I don't know.
Spotted dick and custard.
If you don't want yours,
I'll have it.
Hey, Roddy, for a bloke
who ate his granny,
it's no wonder
you're not choosy.
Who told him?
Who told him about me?
I'll get him.
What are you doing serving
steak and kidney pie
on a Tuesday?
I'm gonna complain about this.
Come on, hurry up.
I've got a letter to write.
Brian, I said hum any tune...
Any tune...
And I can usually pick it up.
She never asked
if I could read music.
What have we got
steak and kidney on today for?
SMITH: Jason!
Hey! Jason! Jason?
Jason!
Keeps on doing it,
all day, all night.
I don't know why.
Why does he do it?
Just to aggravate you, son.
- Any word on S.O. Morgan?
- Nope, not since I've been here.
- Come on, Eugene.
- All right, Bri!
Oswald Snooper!
Back to your cell, please.
Yo, gov.
I've got a complaint.
They're serving the wrong food
on the wrong day here.
You, you should be pleased,
mate.
You always complain
about the boredom.
This is keeping you happy.
Piss off.
Oh! Oh, oh.
That's funny.
SMITH: Woof!
Oi, Eugene,
has he got it in for me?
Why does he keep on
calling out my name?
I don't know.
It's your name, innit? Jason.
Yeah, right.
[Mockingly] Why does
he keep calling out my name?
So I stayed with Mrs. Morgan...
Uh, her name's Nora...
Until, well, very late.
Well, until her husband
was released.
And you haven't seen her again?
No, I-I said she should call me
if she needed me.
And you haven't spoken
to Senior Officer Morgan
since the incident?
No, no, I haven't, actually.
Um, well,
he's a very experienced officer
and I doubt if there's anything
to be unduly worried about.
I'm sure there isn't.
But, you know, there should be
a hostage-support scheme.
Well, there isn't one, is there?
Well, no, uh, I don't think so.
Um, well, I do agree.
One should have been instigated
by Mr. Keller.
He hasn't exactly instilled, um,
too much confidence.
There was a lot of ill feeling
about his delaying
coming to grips
with this hostage situation.
Well, thanks for the coffee.
On the day
of the hostage incident,
Governor Keller
was at a management conference.
Really?
And they usually take place
on the ninth hole
of a golf course, do they?
According to all the reports
the doctor,
even without much experience,
proved to be an able negotiator.
The perpetrator,
according to the control room
log and the incident area log,
refused to speak to any of
the negotiators, full stop.
Said he didn't trust them.
Now, possibly
if I hadn't have arrived,
they would have provided him
with the blow-up rubber dolly
he requested.
I am only here to ensure
that should such an incident
occur again,
then any mistakes that were made
will be rectified.
If you've anything
further to add...
Yes, you could start by making
all prison staff more aware
of the hostage
and siege programs.
Perhaps you could even get
the acting governor
to take a refresher course, hmm?
Do you want to know
where S.O. Russell Morgan is?
He's in
the emergency psychiatric ward
of the local hospital.
Now, you'd better take
my accusations seriously,
Mr. Bunny,
or I'll have every governor,
officer, at Barfield Prison
to sign a petition
and vote him out.
Just calm down.
This isn't gonna be
brushed under the carpet.
If HQ try it,
you'll have a riot.
Only not from the inmates.
If there is to be a petition,
then I think my observations
should be
taken into consideration.
Perhaps you have
a personal motive, Miss Hewitt?
This isn't personal.
That is my professional opinion.
Just as I presume
that you had no personal motive
when you felt
that I was too inexperienced
to continue running Barfield.
Well, I hope you don't retain
any personal motives against me,
Mr. Bunny.
Your own inexperience
in handling a siege situation
might possibly
come under scrutiny.
You'll get copies of my report.
Good morning.
Morning.
Full of herself, isn't she?
There's a vote of no confidence,
Gordon,
and I don't think I can stop it.
Or her.
SAMORA: Tarzan!
[Men singing indistinctly]
Tarzan!
Tarzan, it's me... Brian.
You remember me.
I was in the block with you.
We're doing a musical.
They've got... aah!
Aah! Eugene!
He's pulling me hair out!
- [Indistinct shouting]
- Glasses!
No one's scared of you, Tarzan!
- [Glass breaks]
- Oh!
- Oh, your glasses, Eugene!
- Jesus.
Broken.
Your new glasses.
Get a move on!
Show's over.
Bastards.
I'll be glad when I get out of
this shithole!
Be glad when you go as well.
Your moaning and your whingeing.
You'll be sick
when I'm gone, Eugene.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
You'll be sick about me too,
because in two weeks, I gone.
Yeah, man, we'll meet up
and have a curry.
- Boom!
- Yes, boy!
Thank you.
Hello.
Been a long time.
Do sit down.
Thank you.
Can I offer you some coffee
or tea?
No.
Nothing, thank you.
Did you enjoy your time
in the United States?
Well, I don't whether "enjoy"
is quite the word I would've
used to describe it,
but it was very informative.
I've been back
almost six months.
You must be aware
of why you're here.
Mm-hmm.
Governor Keller implemented
a number of changes,
some of which were not
as successful as others,
and Barfield
could possibly be market tested.
Um, this is
not yet public knowledge,
but Governor Keller
has resigned,
and until
we have time to replace him,
the position
of governor of Barfield
would be a transitory posting.
Mr. Andrews,
I'm obviously very grateful
for the research opportunities,
and teaching
at the training college
has been very satisfactory,
but I am not interested
in any transitory posting.
No, no, no.
I-I think we're slightly
at cross purposes here,
Miss Hewitt.
I'm not offering you
a transitory post.
Oh.
With your experience
and interest
in the psychology
of serious offenders,
together with your training
in the U.S.,
I want to ask you to take over
the psychology department
of Barfield.
Um...
Uh, I misunderstood.
[Laughs]
Uh, Mr. Andrews, I don't want to
head any psychology department.
I would have liked
to have returned to Barfield
as governor,
not on any transitory contract,
but with a guarantee
that I would be there
for a minimum of three years.
Well, there is a short list
being drawn up.
I'm sorry, Mr. Andrews.
But your offer clearly indicates
where you feel my experience
would be most advantageous,
and it is not what I envisage
for my future.
Therefore you leave me
no alternative
but to resign
from the Prison Service.
[Door closes]
Bugger.
I'm sorry, but Mr. Morgan
is in the Edith Cavell room.
Thank you.
Nora!
They sent me to the wrong ward.
And I'm sorry
I couldn't get here before.
I was on duty.
How is he?
He wants to come home.
Oh, I don't know what to do.
I've already had to
take time off work.
I knew something
was gonna happen.
I just knew it.
What do the doctors say?
You know Russell.
They walk in,
and he puts on a big act.
The moment they walk out,
it's...
He doesn't seem to be able
to stop crying.
They've given him something
for depression today.
He's not been himself.
He won't talk to me and...
Why didn't you call me?
Because he didn't want
anyone to know.
Typical.
He's ashamed to admit there's
anything wrong with him.
He won't admit it, and when
he does talk to me, he's...
He can get really nasty.
As if it's all my fault.
I'm a bit scared of him, Gary.
I don't know what to do.
Hey. Come here.
I'll go and have a chat to him,
and you wait
down in the coffee bar for me.
- All right?
- Mm.
Good girl.
Go on.
[Indistinct conversation]
Okay, time's up.
Right, you have a prisoner
sent to the hospital wing
on transferral,
and he takes an officer hostage
in his cell.
Let's start with you.
List two errors.
Well, uh, it shows the
importance of being aware
from the transferrals arrival,
that you have his prison record.
If it was known
he was a dangerous prisoner...
Excuse me.
Miss Stapleton.
Would you let us all
join in your conversation?
It was nothing important.
Really?
So what we're discussing here
is not important?
Well, let me tell you
that everything you learn here
is of utmost importance.
You will be taking care...
And believe me, it is care...
Of men and women whose lives
are your responsibility.
[Sighs] Okay, take 15.
No more.
Good morning.
Ah, good, you're here.
We have a session
after coffee break.
Yep.
How's Susan?
She cries if I look at her,
but the baby's fine.
So you're not going back
to Barfield?
Yeah, of course.
I'm only on a sort of
an extended maternity leave.
We get it now, you know,
as well.
Well, I think you'll find
it's more than extended.
I was just offered your job.
[Gasps] What?
It's all right.
I turned it down.
Well, no, it's not all right.
And I will not be made
the scapegoat
for Gordon Keller's cock-ups.
For goodness' sake,
this hostage wasn't the first.
What, did he offer you
my position?
No, Mr. Andrews at HQ.
Then do you mind
if I take this up with him?
Not at all.
And I were you,
I'd make him fully aware
of whatever else
is wrong at Barfield.
Just be delayed reaction,
that's all.
Well, they haven't found
anything serious, have they?
And you look well.
I'd better get a move on.
Is there anything you need?
I just need a good night's kip,
that's all.
I'm not sleeping, you see?
I can't sleep.
Well, then, lay back now.
Come on.
Get your head down.
Lift up.
There you go.
Now, I'll come back again
tomorrow, yeah?
Put your grapes there,
and I'll get one of the nurses
to bring a vase in
to put the flowers in.
All right?
I haven't let them down once,
not in 15 years.
I'll be back on the wing
this afternoon.
You tell 'em.
You make sure they know.
Russell, Russell.
They already know that, son.
But why don't you grab
forty winks now, hmm?
Hmm?
Come on.
I'll see you tomorrow, yeah?
Miss Purvis.
[Plays "A Wand'ring Minstrel"]
♪ A wand'ring minstrel I... ♪
[Indistinct singing]
BULLOCK: No, no, no.
- Are you in charge?
- Hey!
That's it. That's enough.
And again.
One, two, three, four
♪ A wand'ring minstrel I... ♪
♪ A thing of shreds... ♪
You go.
♪ ...of ballads, songs... ♪
Miss Bullock.
Have you cast
any of the staff yet?
Only I'd like to audition.
Oh, good, but can you wait till
after rehearsal, Curtis, okay?
All right, thanks.
You wait for my nod
before you turn the page.
You're doing very well. It's
just you're a little bit fast.
Gilbert and Sullivan
is quite tricky, you know?
Ohh.
I do apologize.
BULLOCK:
Okay, and again.
So go on now, boy, tell me...
How much you asking?
It's high grade.
This is £10 a crystal.
And I can
keep the supply coming.
Why, it was a joke, yes?
10 quid a crystal?
I was selling rocks for five.
Well, take it
or leave it, Snoopy.
But you ain't ever had gear
this good.
There's crack,
and there's crack.
You'll make some readies
with this before you get out.
No, no, no, no.
That stuff makes me go crazy.
And me no want no trouble, boy.
'Cause in ten days, I'm walking.
[Indistinct singing]
Brian.
Well, what's the matter
with you?
You're not singing anything.
It's a waste of time anyway.
He gets released next week.
He won't be here for the show.
- Is that true, Brian?
- Yeah.
Well, what are you wasting my
time and everybody's time for?
SNOOPER:
How many rocks you got?
Take Brian back to the wing.
- SAMORA: Nice one, Eugene.
- SMITH: How many do you want?
Snoopy, come up here now.
Miss Purvis, please stand by.
Where do you want me?
There.
And...
["A Wand'ring Minstrel" plays]
One, two, three, four.
♪ A wand'ring minstrel I... ♪
♪ A thing of shreds
and patches ♪
♪ Of ballads, songs,
and snatches ♪
♪ And dreamy lullaby ♪
You are talking bullshit!
How can you rape a tart?
How can you rape a woman
who trades sex for cash?
Mr. Jones, you were charged
with forcing your victim
into giving you
oral satisfaction.
The victim said she did not want
to get into your car.
You threatened her and then
forced her to give you oral sex.
You then became violent.
I admitted that.
I did pick the slag up.
She was on the game, right?
I've had enough of this.
I'm not wasting any more time.
HEWITT: Right.
Thank you.
Officer Henley, very good.
Not very impressive from you.
Miss Stapleton, did you read
the prisoner's case history?
Yeah. Three previous convictions
for rape.
So, he's committed the same
offense, not once, not twice,
but three times, correct?
Been sentenced three times,
rape of prostitutes,
in each rape
using excessive violence
when they refused
to give oral satisfaction
and have unprotected sex...
[Knock on door]
Okay.
So starting off
discussing oral sex
wasn't really advisable, was it?
You should have
tried to discover
why he doesn't see prostitutes
as women.
Could you take over
for a minute, Jim?
Hi.
Have you seen Mr. Andrews?
Yeah.
Can you cover for me here?
Sure, if you put in
a good word for me.
Hey, I'm trying to
hang onto my job here.
Anyway, I thought you said
you resigned.
I'm not after your job,
just Keller's.
Now, listen,
do you want some advice?
Threaten to go to the press.
Right now
they don't want that in any way.
Better get back
to Miss Stapleton.
She just blew the oral sex case.
Good luck.
Cheers.
[Plays "Willow, Titwillow"]
♪ On a tree by a river,
a little tom-tit ♪
♪ Sang "Willow, titwillow,
titwillow!" ♪
♪ And I said to him,
"Dicky-bird..." ♪
Curtis, this is your copy,
if you'd like to look over it.
- Snoopy?
- CHISWICK: Come on, now.
BULLOCK:
Is Mr. Oswald here?
CHISWICK: Those not wanted
on the stage, please move out.
Snoopy?
- CHISWICK: Come on.
- BULLOCK: Oh.
We're a bit short of time,
and I'm sorry
you've been left hanging about.
Ohh, you've been
asking for this.
Aah!
Oh! Aah!
I can sing that!
Shut your mouth, bitch.
♪ He slapped at his chest
as he sat on that bough ♪
♪ Singing, "Willow, titwillow,
titwillow!" ♪
♪ And a cold perspiration
bespangled his brow ♪
♪ Oh, willow, titwillow,
titwillow! ♪
♪ And he sobbed and he sighed,
and a gurgle he gave ♪
♪ Then he plunged himself
into that billowy wave ♪
♪ And an echo arose
from the suicide's grave ♪
♪ "Oh, willow, titwillow,
titwillow!" ♪
[Breathing heavily]
♪ Now, I feel just as sure
as I'm sure that my name ♪
♪ Isn't Willow... ♪
Aah!
Come here, Snoopy.
- Pack it in.
- Big man now.
Get up here.
- I'm warning you!
- [Laughs, bellowing]
Aah!
[Bellowing]
Ah, he bit me!
Bastard!
Get him downstairs!
[Gasps]
[Crying]
Better get a medic
up here quick.
Fast.
[Howling]
[Woofing]
What's going on, Reg?
I've asked, we've all asked,
and he won't shut up.
He says he wants raw vegetables,
raw meat, and, uh, bananas,
but, then,
he was doing his ape man.
TARZAN: [Howling]
Victor?
Will you stop messing about?
You're getting
on everyone's nerves.
- Victor!
- [Howling continues]
Victor!
Me Tarzan!
Well, I'm not your bloody Jane,
so shut up!
[Howling]
If you don't like the food,
put in an official complaint.
[Howling]
MAN: He's crazy.
He should be in Broadmoor.
[Howling]
Victor.
You keep this up, son,
and you're going
to the isolation unit.
Tarzan. Tarzan.
Tarzan!
[Spits]
That's his new llama technique.
I've already tasted it.
He's playing around with us.
TARZAN:
Hey, you, Marshall.
Dickhead.
I want to talk to you.
- You there?
- Yeah, I'm here.
Listen, I've got a visitor.
Who is it, Nelly the Elephant?
[Laughs]
Not it's not Nelly, no.
It's me dad.
I want to see me dad.
Can you fix that for me,
Marshall?
Will you put your clothes on
for him?
Yeah.
Okay. Okay.
- OFFICER: Keep it moving.
- SNOOPER: [Screaming]
Keep it moving.
SNOOPER:
[Shouting indistinctly]
Get off!
OFFICER:
Get that cell open now!
MARSHALL: Easy, easy.
OFFICER: Take him 'round.
Take him 'round.
Keep him moving!
Search him!
Search that bastard!
Look at this.
That bastard bit me all over.
[Indistinct shouting]
MARSHALL: Snoopy!
I haven't seen him like this
in three years.
What the hell is he on?
Hey, whatever it is,
I'd love some of it!
It's Miss Bullock.
She's in a bad way.
Right, Governor Syons
is calling the local Bill.
We sealed off the cinema
as a crime area.
He raped her.
He raped her!
You'll have to go
and see Doc Harris.
- What?
- Found this. It's crack.
- Where did you find it?
- It was in his tracksuit.
- Get off and see Doc Harris.
- We got problems.
Dr. Williams has gone to HQ.
I said he wasn't here, and they
asked to be put through to you.
It's Barfield's HOC,
Gary Marshall.
Gary.
Miss Hewitt, we've had a rape.
Is it possible
for you to come to Barfield?
No. Sorry.
But you were called in
over the hostage situation.
That was different.
We've had a woman raped, and
we can't contact Dr. Williams.
Gary, do me a favor.
Phone HQ.
Put some pressure on them.
Tell them you need me.
Okay?
FULLER: Mr. Marshall!
Gary, can you come over
to the lounge with me?
- Not right now.
- I'm afraid it's Mr. Morgan.
Yeah. He said he came back
for a clean shirt.
He said he had some appointment.
MARSHALL: Where is he?
[Metallic thudding]
- Anyone in here with him?
- No, not yet.
Look, he's very angry.
He keeps punching the locker.
Can't get through to him.
You can't be rational with him.
It's really upset me I'm sorry.
What are you playing at,
you silly bastard?
You'll get them all worried sick
out there.
I needed a clean shirt.
- [Bangs]
- Easy.
[Exhales sharply]
I have to have a clean shirt.
I went home.
I couldn't find one.
I had to get a clean shirt.
I've got the see
the area manager.
I've got to go over
the hostage situation.
I have got to pick myself up
and get on with it.
I needed a clean shirt.
Well, have you got one?
Yeah, I've got
a clean shirt now, Gary.
I always have one in my locker.
Good.
What is the matter with me?
I don't know what I'm doing.
I'd better go home now.
You going off duty soon?
Couldn't give me a lift,
could you?
I didn't come on the bike today.
Not on the bike.
- Hey, Gary?
- Yeah?
It's not like
falling off a bike.
I can't get back up.
Can't make it.
Sorry.
I am sorry.
It's okay, mate.
- Andrews.
- Mr. Andrews?
HOC Marshall at Barfield.
Have you heard yet
what went down today?
No, I haven't.
A member of the staff was raped.
- What?
- Yes, raped.
Give me the details.
Who was involved?
It was a Miss Bullock.
She's locked herself
in her office.
And she refused to give
a statement to the police.
So I suggest
you contact Miss Hewitt
and get her here
as a matter of priority.
All right, stand up.
The doctor wants to examine you.
- Has he been body searched?
- Of course he has.
[Speaking indistinctly]
All right, breathe in.
And out.
In.
Out.
Good.
Arms up, please.
Up.
All right.
Give him a hot milky drink,
lots of sugar.
What did I do?
Lock him up.
♪ Oblivion ♪
♪ It's my oblivion ♪
[Sobs]
MAVIS: I know she's been having
a terrible time with him.
I feel sorry for her.
He leaves all the doors open.
Goes into a rage
if she shuts the front door.
She said he's taken knives,
God knows what, to bed with him.
Leaves them under the pillow.
He's like a stranger.
Well, you know how cheerful
he always was.
I mean, nothing affected him,
did it?
She said he's been diagnosed
as clinically depressed.
Anyway, I'd better
get back to work.
Obviously not a good time
to bother you.
That's all right.
Are you still liking it?
Is it the library, innit?
You still working there?
I just can't settle.
I was wondering with him,
Keller, going...
He is, isn't he, going,
Mr. Keller?
Yes, but keep it quiet.
Excuse me.
Mrs. Gill,
this is Mavis O'Connell.
- I used to work here.
- Really?
There's a list of the members
of the amateur dramatic society
that will need clearance.
Yeah, well, cancel them.
There's no bloody musical.
I'll show you out, Mavis.
Nice to meet you.
MARSHALL: Doc Harris
has been trying to coax her out.
Seems like ages.
Don't know what else to do.
DR. HARRIS: Annette...
Nobody's forcing you
to do anything.
We just want to do
what's best for you.
BULLOCK:
Leave me alone, please.
- What did she say then?
- She wants to be left alone.
[Speaks indistinctly]
She's refused to go to the local
hospital for an examination.
I mean, what else
am I supposed to do?
Ah, this is bloody ridiculous,
this is.
She's the one supposed to be
handling this kind of situation.
That's right.
Did he actually do it?
I don't know, do I?
Ruddy area manager's
about as helpful as a whippet.
So, what do we do now?
An omen,
or just wishful thinking?
Mr. Andrews said it was urgent.
He's worried about this rape
getting into the press.
So would I be.
Coming on the heels
of the hostage situation.
[Car alarm chirps]
Not looking good for Barfield
or you, is it, Mr. Bunny?
Mrs. Gill, Miss Hewitt is here
to see Miss Bullock.
You can use
Governor Keller's office.
I've had no instructions
from Governor Keller,
so I thought,
for security purposes,
I should keep the office locked.
The report.
Mr. Andrews called you in, then,
did he?
- Yeah.
- She's still in her office.
Okay, just let me
look over the report,
and then ask Miss Bullock
if she'll see me.
- Just give me a minute.
- Yeah.
Just wishful thinking.
You obviously haven't spoken
to Mr. Andrews.
Well, I'm sorry to be the one
to have to tell you,
but as from 9:00 tomorrow,
I am the official governor
of Barfield Prison.
Now, it's up to you whether
you accept that posting or not.
Everyone's replaceable,
be they area manager
or governor, correct?
Well, I think there may have
been some misunderstanding.
I don't think so.
Still, whatever our
personal differences,
now is not the time
to discuss them.
Congratulations.
Is it a transitory posting?
No.
I'll have a three-year
guarantee, actually.
[Indistinct conversations]
Uh, please, could you clear
everyone from the corridor?
MARSHALL: This way.
Go on, there's tea and coffee
in the governor's office.
Come on, everyone,
this isn't a show.
Miss Bullock,
I'm unlocking your door.
Annette.
It's Helen Hewitt.
Hope you don't mind.
We've met.
Is the detective still waiting?
Yep.
Corridor was
a bit like Piccadilly.
Pitiful, really.
Still, you can also take it
that everyone is very concerned
about you.
Can I call you Annette?
Please don't talk down to me.
I do know the routine.
All I wanted
was to be left alone.
I'm sure you do know the
routine, but not as a victim.
You might not be able
to make the right decision.
Because I'm in shock?
Yes.
Of course you are.
[Lighter clicking]
[Inhales deeply]
[Exhales]
This was my fault.
I should have been
more wary, watchful, whatever.
I allowed myself to be lulled
into a false sense of security.
He was drugged out.
His eyes, his speech.
His aggression,
his physical violence.
He didn't know
what he was doing.
Was he able to penetrate you?
Yes, briefly.
I'll have
all the necessary tests.
Obviously I want him punished,
but I don't want to
bring criminal charges
outside the prison itself.
I'd like this to be kept
as private as is possible.
It's finished, over, done with.
I just want to
get back to my work.
Which is what I've been doing.
Uh, it may not be possible
to keep it quiet.
You see,
there were no eyewitnesses.
And since you do not wish
to press charges,
Mr. Snooper therefore
cannot be charged with assault.
But you have admitted
that it took place.
Of course.
It did.
So, what could happen
is that Mr. Snooper
will get 28 days
for committing an illegal act
within the prison.
The illegal act
is having intercourse
with a member of staff.
You could also be fired,
Miss Bullock,
for the same offense.
Oh, for God's sake,
you can't be serious.
I'm afraid I am.
It means you are up against it
to press charges, Annette.
Is this what you've come in here
to tell me?
That I might be fired
for having intercourse
with a prisoner that raped me?
Hopefully we may be able to
charge Mr. Snooper
with dealing drugs.
I just don't want you
to make any decision
without giving it
due consideration.
I am not going to press charges.
I have no intention
of being forced into court
to give evidence.
Or of being coerced into giving
a statement to the police.
I was mistaken.
Nothing happened.
So you see, Miss Hewitt,
I've made my decision.
I am not hysterical
or, as you inferred,
suffering from shock.
Do you mind if I go home?
And if Miss Purvis
is still here.
Sorry?
Pianist.
"His vomit spluttered
on the thick, hairy rug."
Bloody hell.
"Sever... "Is that "severed"?
"Severed from its body,
the black, silky head
of the great hor..."
Bloody hell,
it's his horse, man.
He cut off
the head of his horse!
Oh, shut it, Bri.
Everybody knows he found
a horse's head in his bed.
Didn't you see the film?
Yeah, it was on telly,
but I missed it.
- Reading is fantastic, isn't it?
- [Man singing indistinctly]
Opened up a whole world for me.
I'll be able to write to you,
Eugene.
Be writing to Snoopy as well.
[Exhales sharply]
You won't be going out
for frigging curry.
Tell you,
he'll get about six years
for what he did to Miss Bullock.
Why did he do it, eh?
Why did he do it?
I mean, I won't be here
for the show,
but they'll cancel it now,
won't they?
- Bastard.
- [Singing continues]
Tell you, he'd better not
come back on this wing.
If he does, I'll kill him.
Oh, shut it, you tit head.
[Singing indistinctly]
♪ Titwillow, titwillow ♪
Can I ask you something, Gary?
And I want a straight answer.
Mm-hmm.
It was you who started the vote
of no confidence
against Keller, right?
Yeah.
Why didn't you
put yourself forward?
Not the right rank.
Could have stood in.
Even just temporarily.
No.
You see, I can't distance meself
like you can.
I don't have
the education you have.
And I'm not a number one.
I know that now,
but I didn't before.
[Howling]
Did they move the kennels?
Nope.
That's, uh, Tarzan.
- Sorry?
- Victor Braithwaite, as was.
Good night.
I tipped the boys off
at the gate.
[Car alarm chirps]
HEWITT:
Well, I'm touched.
Uh, there is
just one thing, though.
This isn't my Range Rover,
so I hope that foam comes off
in a car wash.
- Good night.
Good night, Governor.
Welcome back.
[Triumphant music plays]
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today