ENJOY ALL VOD IN HIGH QUALITY @ 4KVOD.TV
GET LIVE TV,MOVIES,SHOWS IN ONE PACKAGE
FAMILY MOTTO
A HARMONIOUS FAMILY WITH LOVE
What?
If you replied to my text,
I wouldn't be here.
There was a get-together.
How lowly do you think of me?
What are you talking about?
Never mind.
I'll finish it soon and leave as promised.
I had to say this face to face.
As of today,
I'm done with you.
You're out.
As of today,
I'm done with you too.
You're out.
You didn't have to come
all the way here for that.
You could've called me.
All right.
Hi.
I'm not going for a second round,
so I'm on my way home.
I'll get going.
It's a meditation book team dinner,
so it'd be nice to introduce him.
Okay, goodbye.
Let's have a drink next time.
Go to the second round.
I said everything so I'm leaving.
Eun-hee, do you even know what you want?
Do you have a goal?
Don't you have any desires for yourself?
How lowly do you think of me?
Eun-joo.
I'm sorry.
Why are you sorry all of a sudden?
I couldn't keep my promise…
to you.
What promise?
On the day I took the photo
in the living room,
I made a promise to you
in your mother's womb.
"I will raise you to be the best."
"I will let you do anything you want."
"I will be the best father in the world."
I couldn't keep any of those.
None of it.
In my opinion, you raised her wonderfully.
Did I?
How lovely do you think Eun-joo is?
Why are you asking that all of a sudden?
He's not the kind of person
to answer questions like that.
Yes, I know how my son-in-law is.
But I asked so I can brag.
Eun-joo…
has been lovely
from the moment she was born.
It's not because she's my daughter.
The nurses all said so.
The said newborn babies don't have
defined facial features,
so they all look similar,
but she was different.
She had large eyes.
She smiled so well too.
When she was in university…
she shined so brightly.
When she…
was at her loveliest…
I'm home.
Hi, Eun-joo.
When she was young and beautiful
she was busy making money
because of her pathetic father.
I was uneducated,
and I couldn't do anything else
when I was injured,
so I felt so sorry.
I have to…
pay it back.
Take it as the love from
your pathetic father.
I couldn't tell you at the time,
but when I got this bankbook…
I was flustered.
Did you live your life
feeling like you're indebted?
To pay back the money
that cannot even be calculated?
This money would have
helped Mom to live better
and struggle less every month.
Don't you ever think about Mom?
If it was Eun-hee…
do you think you'd try this hard?
"If it was Eun-hee?"
She's trying to tell you
she can't take it.
I'll take it.
Because you feel uncomfortable.
Don't go.
I want to know why you're doing this.
I need to know why I'm out.
At that time, at least
I had a clear reason.
A clear reason?
Do you still think I was happily
eating, drinking, and hanging out
with Jong-pal and that woman?
You weren't even cleared up
but just apologized
because you ran into me?
I cleared that.
I thought it was cleared.
I thought that woman took it her own way
and got the wrong idea.
Let's not talk about that time.
I'm talking about right now.
Explain why I'm out.
"Familiarity breeds contempt."
I hate this quote.
Even to someone close…
It implies I have to be even more polite
to someone close.
Then are there no honest relationships
in this world?
Isn't that too sad?
But…
"Familiarity breeds contempt."
This crappy quote was true.
You've been too rude to me.
That's why you're out.
What about you?
Have you always been polite to me?
A lot.
I think I have been polite enough to you.
You told Seo-young.
She knows about dating class
and Mr. Playboy too.
Just how much did you tell her?
Is it okay to do that behind my back?
Just what do you see me as?
You never change.
It's the same as last time.
"You are so low, but I'll embrace you
with my big, warm heart."
Is that it?
That's a lot of love for humanity.
It was just
between you and me.
She was saying
the exact same words I used.
Then how was I…
supposed to interpret that?
You already made up your mind,
so why am I so angry at you?
I'm the weird one for getting angry.
To you,
I'm the idiot who showed
photos from the stone wall to others,
not knowing that was a secret.
That's what I am to you.
Let's stop here.
She's better now.
She'll come out when she calms down.
Tae-hyung.
Yes, sir.
Our first house after we got married
was smaller than half of this living room.
A small kitchen and a room
were all we had.
My wife
is shy, so she told me
to go to the kitchen
whenever she was changing clothes.
I don't know why I'm saying this.
Is it because this house is too big?
Are you two
living happily together?
Yes.
Eun-joo, where are you?
Eun-hee.
Eun-joo is resting.
Oh.
Is she sick again?
No, that's not what it is…
Is something wrong?
I'm going to have a change
in family relations.
As we know now, it'll change.
Tae-hyung.
Is Eun-joo…
avoiding my calls?
No, that's not what it is.
Want to talk to her?
No.
It's okay.
The only person I want to see
at this moment.
My sister.
Why are you here?
Yes.
I'm here to give you the bankbook.
I brought it back.
I made a mistake.
I didn't know how thoughtful Eun-joo was,
and I was selfish. So I made her cry.
Eun-joo…
She cried?
She resented me saying that if I gave that
money to you every month,
you would've been more comfortable
about living expenses.
I thought you would've
felt the same as I did.
I wanted to pay back the money
my daughter tried so hard for.
You go in and explain it to her.
I…
I can't go in.
Didn't Eun-joo…
tell you?
Tell me what?
Eun-joo…
She knows.
She knows that you're not
her biological father.
Eun-hee
and Ji-woo…
know about it too.
Did you tell them?
Why?
So you can graduate kids from me too?
Is it always my fault
when something happens?
You agreed with me to keep it
a secret forever,
but you couldn't even keep it.
Dad, why…
Why do you take responsibility
for things you can't handle?
Do you think it's easy
to be responsible for someone else?
If it was Eun-hee…
do you think you'd try
so hard to pay it back?
I'll take it.
Because you feel uncomfortable!
I'm a loser.
I'm a loser!
Stop it!
Stop it.
Why are you still here?
Do you have more to search for?
How did it go?
What?
Didn't you go to see Eun-hee?
If a misunderstanding occurred
between friends, you should've cleared it.
Did she act fine and then
get upset behind your back?
I'm sure she didn't want
to make the same mistake again.
That frustrates me so much.
Why did you secretly look at my phone?
I need an answer.
When that incident happened,
I saw my mom's phone by coincidence,
and she was comforting that punk's mom.
She said it's because I'm sensitive.
I totally fell apart at the time.
You exchange messages…
with my mom as well.
So…
I wanted to check it.
What did you want
your parents to do for you at the time?
I didn't want much.
I just wanted them to admit
that it happened to me.
What do you mean? They all know.
No.
They turned a blind eye to it.
They're nice to me like nothing happened.
They laugh,
buy me expensive gifts…
and act like everything
is the same as before.
I hate that so much.
They might've thought
acting like nothing happened
would be safer than making things worse.
A method of protecting the family…
can be cowardly sometimes.
Why don't you go into the room?
He took the bankbook back.
You stopped me earlier, right?
We all know. He should know too.
I stopped you because it seemed
overwhelming for you to say.
I haven't talked to my father for decades.
A biological father
isn't important at this age.
Why are you bringing up my age for this?
Divorce isn't important at this age.
A birth secret isn't important
at this age.
Does that mean nothing
should be important at this age?
What's wrong with my age?
Right.
Eun-hee called.
She didn’t sound well.
And she asked
if you were avoiding her calls.
She and I don't mix at all.
Why ask such
an unnecessary question to you?
EUN-HEE
Where's Tae-hyung?
Did he go inside?
Should I say hi to him?
No. He never comes out once
that door is closed.
I did some searching on my way here,
and the price of this house
makes no sense.
Why did you search
for the price of this house?
Unlike my logic, my fingers
were searching.
You and I are not in the same class.
I'm going to be rude to this house today.
-Hi.
I'm sleeping over today.
You're taking medication now,
so don’t drink.
I'm going inside.
Yes.
You're cursing with your eyes.
Some jerk told me
it's over between me and him.
He said I'm out.
I said that, but when I heard that again…
it broke my heart.
It's good that you learned
how hurtful those words are.
If you were heartbroken
after hearing that,
it means you like him.
Were you heartbroken
when I said that?
No.
Not at all.
As you know, we don't like each other.
This isn't the end.
This other jerk…
said I want nothing,
I have no goals,
and I have no desires.
I think it's ridiculous.
That's how you want people to see you.
If he doesn't want people
to see you like that,
it means he likes you.
Why are you talking like
you know everything?
Eun-joo…
I'm sorry.
It may be serious enough for you
to come all the way here,
but it sounds unimportant to me.
It's unimportant. Yes.
To be honest…
I came to see you
every time something happened.
And every time I did that,
you never comforted me.
I know that so well,
so why do I
always think of you?
The words of comfort
are sweet for a short moment,
but your hurtful words,
disgusting words,
and critical words…
make me react to them a few days later,
and give me the strength to get back up.
You take care of your things
on your own now.
I'm not going to give you
any more advice.
Playing a villain is so exhausting.
How can a big sister
not advise a little sister…
I get that you're not a villain.
I'll be good to you.
Even if you got it…
You can't fix it.
Well…
That may be true.
You're right, I can’t fix it.
But…
still…
Having a change in family relations
or being estranged…
Don't say anything like that.
It's disgusting.
Today…
I came simply because I wanted to see you.
Really,
suddenly,
I wanted to see you so much.
I couldn't tell Dad.
It's fine if you can't tell him.
By the way…
About that bankbook
that went here and there…
How much is in it?
Why are you curious about that money?
You and I are not in the same class.
My ears are open to the mention of money.
Can Dad…
Get a place to stay?
He still hasn't found a place to stay?
Then where is he staying now?
Goodness.
I know, right?
I don’t know.
I hated that house so much.
The room was small,
the floor was bumpy,
I could smell the sewer,
and there were too many
dogs in the neighborhood.
The doggies in that neighborhood
all played with me.
The rain leaked into the house in summer,
and it was cold in winter.
I miss the bulgogi Mom cooked at the time.
The bulgogi with spinach and cabbage,
so she could save money for the meat.
That recipe is so modern-style.
Dad loved it.
He said he only likes Mom's food,
and he made her make lunch boxes for him.
Why do memories show our personalities?
Eun-joo. Be honest with me.
Have you ever dated anyone?
Passionately?
Stop talking nonsense and go to sleep.
You never did, of course.
You know nothing about my relationships.
So you did?
Go to sleep.
You did, right?
Tell me. I'm listening.
-Ji-woo.
-Yes?
Go shoot an insert. With Seo-young.
-I can do it by myself.
-What do you need?
I'll do it.
You looked so happy
to get out of the office.
Something wrong?
You don't need to know.
I checked your social media page, and…
And? What?
You only uploaded photos
of Chan-hyuk looking handsome,
but why did you upload photos of me
looking like this?
The CEO is handsome.
If you saw my social media page,
I'm sure you know now
from reading the comments.
My nickname is something, isn't it?
A crazy ex who acts like
a rape victim because she got
dumped by her boyfriend.
"You look well."
"Unboxing products will be sold out."
"You got prettier. Cheer up."
You don't read those comments?
"I'm hurt."
"I'm going to go out of control."
Don't do that to those who like you.
I'm not like Chan-hyuk.
Forgiving you because of your scars…
That doesn't work for me.
I'm going to treat you the same.
Those who like me?
Are you included in them?
I thought all guys your age
are all stupid losers,
but you're slightly okay.
It's all thanks to your sisters.
Why is it thanks to my sisters
that I'm okay?
I'm okay because I'm okay.
You stupid loser.
He's coming.
Shall I drive?
It’s okay. But…
There are materials in the back seat,
so it'll be uncomfortable for you to sit.
Shall I go to the back seat?
I'll go to the back seat.
It's right for me to go to the back seat.
-Sit here, please.
-Okay, thank you.
You can just accompany us to a few places,
and we can go to small places on our own.
That's for me to decide.
A call from Youngest Brat.
Hey, Eun-hee. Are you busy?
I'm busy. Finish it in 30 seconds.
30 seconds?
What is it? Hurry up and say it.
You see…
Someone who works with me…
It's me, Seo-young.
She wants to talk to you.
Hi.
I saw the texts
you and CEO Chan-hyuk exchanged.
I said those things mindlessly.
The CEO didn't tell me about it.
He never did.
Eun-hee. I don't understand
what she said, but she said so.
Hey, why did Chan-hyuk
let her see his phone…
Okay, I got it. Bye.
What on earth is going on?
What text message
did you see between them?
I have to know in order to help you.
Here is the promotional material.
Please write a good article.
-We're counting on you.
-Okay.
-Goodbye.
To you,
I am an idiot who showed the stone
wall of Deoksugung Palace
to my friends, not knowing
that was a secret.
That's what I am to you.
Let's stop here.
When I let you borrow
my handkerchief for the first time,
you said you have to wash
the handkerchief before returning it,
so I hand washed it.
You came all the way here
to give this back.
Goodness.
Are you okay?
It's just a scratch.
It's not a big deal.
I wasn't asking about that.
You couldn't even walk well
that day like you were going to fall ill.
I thought about it.
I heard…
nothing from you.
It looks like our eldest daughter
isn’t going to tell me.
So don't tell her that you told me.
Don't tell anyone.
No secret remains a secret forever.
Why did you come back to your old self?
You should've kept quiet and lived your
life in the past like you don't remember.
Just like that strange
coffee shop back then,
you should've just enjoyed
your life like before.
I would've done that if I were you.
Let's do that.
It wasn't fun when I was there alone.
Let's all go together.
I loved my children so much.
There isn't any one-sided
love like this in the world.
So…
there are no regrets either.
Mr. Kim Sang-sik.
You said you wanted to die
because that one-sided love is unfair.
I was an absolute idiot.
What's one-sided love about?
It's about madly loving the other
even if they don't know.
I don't think it's unfair anymore.
You must be happy.
I have no debt or regrets
regarding the kids.
I'm only indebted…
to you.
So…
Let's go.
Were you offended yesterday?
No.
Don’t mind it.
I don't mind it either.
I said it so you would mind it.
What should I mind, exactly?
You said you don't want
a childish relationship.
Don't judge me based on weird rumors.
Think about what would change.
Think about what we can do together.
I wanted you to think about it.
Do you think I never thought about that?
Surprisingly enough,
I thought hard about it.
I thought about your
background and capability.
That's why you began
with an advantage.
I know I seem soft and easy to others.
I know how harmful, harsh,
and hurtful words can scar people,
so I can never say them.
But…
Someone who tells me that
I look like I have no goals or desires
right at my face, making an excuse
for it being advice and love…
cannot get points from me.
I didn't say you're soft and easy.
I felt like
I was completely out of your sight.
So I wanted to tell you to see me.
Don’t try too hard to avoid
the same mistake in the past.
If it isn't because you totally hate me
or like someone else,
I'm going to try more.
Because I know you're a wonderful person.
All right, let's do it this way.
Okay.
Eun-hee.
What was that call about?
Why did she look at someone else's phone?
Did Chan-hyuk let her do it?
It's not like they're dating.
Why let her take his phone?
I don't know.
Is everyone there?
Go outside and talk.
I don't have anything else
to tell you. That's all.
I don't know.
Hey, that's a crime.
Even families shouldn't
look at each other's phones.
Didn't he say anything to you?
It's not like she looked at your phone.
Why are you so angry?
Come here.
What the heck? Did you two do something?
I confessed to Ms. Eun-hee
about secretly looking at your phone.
Goodness.
How do you like it?
I saw young people with this
on the street,
so I wanted to try it too.
We were so happy
when we lived in the hillside village.
I guess we were the happiest
when we were the poorest.
Do you know when I started to
get angry with you with fire in my heart?
How should I know when the exact time was?
I just remember
you throwing things and yelling
out of the blue, at all times.
I know.
That book.
It's because of that book.
You were so focused on reading it,
I bought it and read it secretly too.
What book?
"In a universe of ambiguity…"
"In a universe of ambiguity,
this certainty comes only once,
and never comes again."
THE BRIDGES OF MADISON COUNTY
I read the part you underlined,
and though I'm uneducated,
I could understand what that meant.
I thought…
you missed Eun-joo's father
your entire life.
That's when I became a loser.
Both of our lives
were all about misunderstandings.
CAN YOU TALK ON THE PHONE NOW?
I'M SORRY
Whenever there was work,
I worked from dawn to lunch
at a supermarket storage room.
I took a break
and then worked as a barista.
My life was so hard,
so I couldn't even think
of running away from the world.
So when I saw Dr. Yoon
running away to Goheung,
I got so angry,
so I behaved badly.
His life, which seems
easy and comfortable to you…
It's not easy to throw those away, either.
I didn't think about that.
Still, I'm sure you hated him
because he seemed like
a big coward to you.
I have so many cowards around me.
I didn't suddenly start hating him.
I'm going to New Zealand.
I know it's reckless,
but I decided to be with him
and live happily, once more.
Please tell him this.
Me?
I don't think I'll ever tell him.
If you're not going to protect
him like a baby forever,
tell him.
He'll realize his emotions.
It's my last gift.
EUN-HEE'S
NO NEED FOR LOVE
I KNEW I'D END UP LOVING YOU
What's with all of these titles?
TALKATIVE WOMAN, UNTALKATIVE WOMEN
KIM EUN-HEE
I have desires too.
Was someone here?
Barista Ahn is…
leaving for New Zealand tomorrow.
I said my last goodbye to him.
Hi.
Why won't you answer Attorney Lee's calls?
Ma'am.
Talk with me. He's a bit drunk.
Let me ask you one thing.
Did you come up
with the alimony that was billed?
Yes.
I calculated it.
Calculated…
Money shows the worst part
of a human being.
We're strangers now,
so I don't want to quarrel with you.
It's right to talk with family.
Open the door.
Avoiding it isn't the way.
If you avoid it,
things will get more complicated.
Open the door.
What is it?
He usually doesn't drink
until he gets drunk,
and he doesn't do that, either…
I said, what is it?
He got dumped.
I didn't know, but…
I guess he liked him a lot.
You…
How could you say that to me…
with that face, like it's nothing…
Are you doing that on purpose?
Because it's true.
Ma'am.
You…
you love him.
You keep ignoring it
and act like you don't know.
Do you feel nothing?
Is it that difficult to see him
as who he is? I…
I can accept him now.
It should be easier for you than for me.
CAN YOU TALK ON THE PHONE?
Can you talk on the phone?
I came to ask you something.
I did my laundry with a washing machine,
but the unpleasant smell won't go away.
Aren't you getting in?
At that time we ordered
one double portion and shared it.
You told me to eat more
and I told you to eat more,
and the noodles got soggy.
I came to ask you something.
I made stir-fried anchovies,
but they're so hard and I can't chew them.
Hey!
Come and get me!
Take it easy.
Why are you so good?
Bye.
Ms. Sook.
How about we go…
on a real date next time?
Yes?
It's your day off,
so take care of your own meals.
I'm coming home after eating dinner.
From Mom.
Wait a second…
What is this?
Ms. Lee the penny pincher bought clothes?
This is obviously a stuffed toy
from a crane machine.
Do you like radish?
Three types of radish kimchi
are delivered.
They are at your door now.
Stop acting.
How would you bring all those here?
Don't try to let it pass.
I'm not letting off steam this time.
I know. I'd do the same too.
I didn’t want this to happen again,
so I thought of holding it back.
I couldn't hold it back,
but I kept holding it back.
See?
You've been thinking
I have the worst kind of personality.
No.
This time, I had
another emotion mixed into it.
And it was Seo-young
who delivered the words,
so I believed it wholly and got angrier.
Seo-young shines brightly.
She's pretty, flamboyant, and honest.
And more than anything, she likes you.
She's not lacking anything.
"I get it."
"They're close enough
to share everything."
"I hope they can be together."
My emotions went that far.
For being out of control alone…
you held back pretty well.
I know, right?
Gosh.
Hey. I even made such
an embarrassing confession.
Let me go inside, at least.
Kkakdugi for Kimbap. Kimbap for Ramen.
Altari kimchi for ramen.
Kimbap for Altari kimchi.
If you consume carbohydrates
in an infinite cycle,
your brain experiences sweetness.
The apology event lacks
sincerity and it's cliched.
Wrong.
If you accepted the apology,
then it's game over.
You must be really sorry.
You can't even look me in the eye.
Let's go outside after.
I have things to say.
You also need to get out
of this place at times.
Why are you making sad eyes
like you're never coming back here?
You're so keen.
I told Ms. Kim Eun-hee
that we slept together on our last day.
But it's too quiet.
It's too quiet,
so I wondered if you don't know about it.
Is she an awesome woman who doesn't care
and doesn't ask about it?
Since the day I met you
at the meditation center and until now,
all of my behavior
had a reason.
I was so happy to see you again.
Let's eat soup and rice.
I'm in.
Let's go eat soup and rice.
"So our friendship can instantly overcome"
"the time we haven't kept in touch."
I don't want to add something
to this simple emotion.
"I will not lose this assuring
and stable friendliness again."
I even promised myself.
What are you doing?
How did you get here?
When I went to see you
and told you everything,
it was to set the boundaries as friends,
not as man and woman.
It was a promise to myself
that I'll never make any changes
to this relationship.
It was that meaningful?
So you told me
about your mistake with Mr. Playboy
to prevent us from having a relationship
between man and woman?
Did I get it right?
Yes.
Personal safe. Emptying the trash can.
A class about playboys.
It wasn't about that.
In that case, what you mean is
that I can never date you
because you made a mistake
with another man
and because I'm too small-minded.
Right?
What?
That's not what it is.
I'm the one who can’t.
I can never be
in a romantic relationship with you
since I told you everything in detail.
It's not that you’re small-minded.
It's just that I can’t.
I get it.
I get it so clearly.
What's with that look?
When I said I'll peep at you,
keep your smile in my heart
and look at it before going to sleep.
Was that too uncomfortable?
You said you did everything when you were
20 years old like it was nothing,
so why draw boundaries?
Aren't you glad you got out of the office?
What nice weather.
Hi.
Did he quit working here?
Yes.
He went to New Zealand.
I'm super jealous.
What's with Mom?
Mom…
kicked Dad out completely.
She moved to the main bedroom.
Dad's room is gone.
And Mom…
is having a fling.
He must be giving her flowers
every time they meet.
Don't tell me she played
a crane machine game.
And I think it's…
Mr. Yoo.
-So what?
Why are you tattling on it to us?
How childish.
Can't Mom have a boyfriend?
Do you not keep secrets?
Why? Why are you looking at me?
You have something.
I knew it. You have a secret too.
I have a secret.
I'm sure Eun-hee does too.
It's not like families
have to know everything.
Let's keep the boundaries.
No, I can't keep the boundaries.
What is it? What's your secret?
Eun-joo told us to keep the boundaries.
Your leg is shaking.
It's a habit.
Tae-hyung.
How are you doing?
-Good.
Did you have lunch?
Yes.
What would you like to drink?
Yes, the same one, please.
Eun-joo and Tae-hyung
look like they're
at their best these days.
Really?
I was an idiot to listen and believe you
that Mom is having a fling.
Why? It's true.
Whether it's true or false,
let's just cheer for the lives of
Mom and Dad so they can be free.
I didn't say anything.
I just
made an excuse, so I can see Eun-joo.
-Right, about Seo-young…
-Please.
It was just a mistake.
Just let it pass.
Why are you defending her?
Eun-hee.
What?
Have you ever wondered why Chan-hyuk
doesn't have a driver's license?
Ms. Jin-sook.
The green light is on.
You may cross the street.
Ms. Jin-sook.
It's not too late, is it?
You're smiling.
Mr. Sang-sik!
Can I…
love you again?
Mom, what was the first thing you planned
to do after graduating from marriage?
Don't you think you're too indifferent
to your friend's family story?
Give me a chance
to be your personal safe for once.
-Dad.
-Hey, get in!
I behaved like a kid that day.
I forgot to say something important.
Don't tell the kids.
Subtitle translation by: Hae-lim Lee
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/ah33z
Help other users to choose the best subtitles