Use the free code JOINNOW at
www.playships.eu
There's no point
keeping us captive here, Naad.
You won't be able to find
Raga Sanjivani without me.
The people who are after the raga...
will not let you live.
You don't have to worry about that.
You killed my mom and Salamat Uncle.
Saaz...
I've brought you guys here
to save you.
- I love you Saaz, trust me.
- I don't trust you.
A killer can never...
He can never love someone.
Do you know me?
How well do you know me?
Do you know how we survive?
Does anyone here know?
Give me a chance.
Make me a part of your life.
Naad.
I can love too, Saaz.
I can love too.
I'm capable of love too, Saaz.
Go away.
- Saaz...
- Stay away.
Believe me, Saaz.
Get lost.
- Get away from me...
- Saaz...
Go away.
- Don't come near me...
- Saaz, I...
Just get lost!
Go away.
Love, my foot!
You can never love anyone.
You can only harass people.
You can only break a glass
with your songs.
Can you win over people with your music
like Alap can?
Hey!
Shut up!
Challenge?
You up for it?
Yes, I am.
Are you ready?
Take me to the Shiva Temple.
Let's see who finds Raga Sanjivani.
Bring them to the temple.
Come.
Welcome.
CURSE OF THE RUDRABINA
PART 2
Come in.
Welcome to the Shiva Temple
of Rudrapur.
What's going on?
You're here as well?
Yes.
It's me.
I'm like the tanpura.
I guide the musician
from the background.
But then,
I'm not the director of this act.
In Amanat Khan's treasure of ragas
I'm one of the seven notes
like the rest of you.
Let's gather everyone
and begin the musical game.
Naad.
Shruti!
Where are you taking me?
Alap.
Rudrabhairav, it'll be a grave sin.
The holy temple of Rudrapur
contaminated by a whore.
Hey!
I'll bury you alive
if you insult my mom again.
Is this what you have taught your son?
Shame on you!
It is an unforgivable sin, Rudrabhairav.
You can't create an idol of Goddess Durga
without soil from a brothel.
We must tolerate this sin
for some more time.
Maestro Sasikanta, you here?
Yes, me.
I'm the director.
The master.
The master of Rudrapur.
Your master Kedar Mishra...
was once the Naad of Rudrapur.
I was the Rudrabhairav then.
Please release me now.
But you are...
you're associated
with Gandhargarh School of Music.
I deceived you.
Besides my music...
I got involved in a murder
in my youth.
I had also vexed
an influential person.
He had provided the police
with evidence against me.
If they caught me,
they wouldn't just have buried me.
They would've hanged me to death.
So he ran away from Rudrapur
and took refuge in Gandhargarh.
Then I took on a new name...
Sasikanta Bharadwaj.
Soon, I had fame, glory, respect.
But Master always maintained ties
with Rudrapur.
When Hemanta was in police custody...
one of our followers saw the symbol
of the rudrabina on his back.
He had informed us about it.
I've told you the secrets
of your master.
I know that your peers
are defaming you.
You were meant to receive
the national music award this year.
But Ranjan Ghosh got it instead of you.
Don't you want revenge?
Yes, I do.
Then?
This is your golden opportunity.
Join us.
What do I have to do?
First of all, tell us...
who else among your peers
has this symbol on their body?
Um...
Yes...
An old servant of the house
called Anadi.
So you forced Anadi...
to reveal all the names
and had them murdered.
You also verified the names
with a DNA test, right?
Wow!
You know this as well?
I've never seen a detective who sings.
Yes I did it.
I did it because unnecessary bloodshed
goes against our morality.
My goodness!
Morality!
Isn't lying against your morality?
You knew nothing about the notation.
You lied.
I admit it...
I admit I lied to you.
Amanat Khan used his brains
to compose it.
You used your brains to find it.
And I used my brains to copy it.
What a brilliant composition!
You're...
You're such a renowned musician.
You're our country's pride.
But you're so greedy.
Greedy?
No.
I'm not that greedy.
Believe me.
It's just that...
I'm greedy for my life.
The fame, glory and wealth
which I've earned throughout my life...
I want it all forever.
I'm scared of death.
I can't share my glory with anyone.
I can't share it.
I'm the absolute authority of Rudrapur.
Huge as the Himalayas.
Vast as the seas.
That's why I want
Tansen's Raga Sanjivani.
I'll...
I'll be immortal.
I know that it's not possible.
But I crave it.
It's the only thing I want.
I want to be immortal.
An artist becomes immortal
through his creations.
A greedy person like you
can never create something.
I know that!
I know everything.
I've seen the world
long before you.
I know that an artist becomes
immortal through his creations.
You can't create something
with a greedy mind.
But this coming from a foolish guy
like you is funny.
It's funny.
This is the Shiva lake.
Let's see you if you can find
Raga Sanjivani here.
Look for it.
"In the heart of Rudrapur
lies a Shiva lake.
When the discs are aligned
And the notes are played
at twice the pace of time
Raga Sanjivani you shall find."
I know all that.
We've followed the notation
but nothing happened.
You people play it now.
The discs are already in place.
Start playing.
What's this, Bahadur?
This was designed
by Madhubanti's grandfather.
Came to know about it
from the map of the temple.
Basically, if the instruments are played
according to this notation...
then we'll find Raga Sanjivani.
"And the notes are played
at twice the pace of time
Raga Sanjivani you shall find."
Hmm.
But why "at twice the pace of time"?
Look, Shruti.
The normal tempo of time
is 60 beats per minute.
So, "twice the pace of time" would be...
Sixty into two.
- As in, 120 beats per minute.
- Right!
So, basically...
if the notation is played
at 120 beats per minute on every instrument
then we'll find Raga Sanjivani.
Sarod.
Sitar.
Flute.
Santoor.
Shehnai.
Sarangi, rudrabina.
I get it.
But who will play the rudrabina?
A whore will play the rudrabina?
Is there any other way?
But...
H-How did Rohini learn
to play the rudrabina?
Pandit Kedar Mishra secretly taught you
to play the rudrabina.
Isn't it, Mom?
Hmmph!
Rohini...
the rudrabina is the king
of all instruments.
Earlier...
maestros taught the rudrabina
only to their sons or sons-in-law.
At my first music school...
girls were forbidden to touch
the rudrabina.
But I don't obey these rules now.
Among my students...
you're the only one who is worthy
of learning the rudrabina.
But...
you need a pure mind
to play the rudrabina.
If you play it with an impure mind...
a curse will befall you.
Nobody can escape the curse.
Nobody.
- What happened, Master?
- Hmm?
My master Amanat Khan...
gave me special instructions
while teaching the rudrabina.
He asked me to teach you
the rudrabina.
But don't tell anybody about it.
Got it?
No one lives in this house now.
Come secretly and take lessons
in the rudrabina from me.
Okay?
There'll be some magic today.
Record everything.
Come on, get started.
(vocalising)
THIS SECRET BANDISH
IF YOU SING
FROM THE HEART
YOU SHALL PACIFY SHIVA'S "TANDAV"
THE BEATS OF "DADRA"
SHALL NULLIFY THE POISON
THEN RAGA SANJIVANI YOU SHALL FIND
THIS SECRET BANDISH
IF YOU SING FROM THE HEART
YOU SHALL PACIFY SHIVA's "TANDAV"
THE BEATS OF "DADRA"
SHALL NULLIFY THE POISON
THEN RAGA SANJIVANI
YOU SHALL FIND
Hey, what's this?
Where is Raga Sanjivani?
Huh?
This secret "bandish"
if you sing from the heart
You pacify Shiva's "tandav".
The beats of "Dadra"
Shall nullify the poison.
Then you shall find Raga Sanjivani."
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/agwy6
Help other users to choose the best subtitles