ENJOY ALL VOD IN HIGH QUALITY @ 4KVOD.TV
GET LIVE TV,MOVIES,SHOWS IN ONE PACKAGE
Some kind of boarding highlight is coming from Betul to the route
It has been only 10 years since the Russian army was told
Swahili want to impose some rules Russian intelligence especially GRU is very active in our area
In any case, a spy is needed here, an attempt must have failed in Ladla, but who knows how successful it has been and we do not think.
We need better people to use the spy Banaras here as well.
It's true that I can't stress you to break the doors of hotels
understand
Forget bin Laden, leave the local
you this i ate well
eat a little more want to talk to you
you can't go without eating
no thanks rent
Hi!
who is pappu
engineering to work
office is not a training school do we have to work it is not me
you have to see
Vipin
Think no one came or say thank you those people ruled
We know where we can't let anyone roam like this
to handle from Gandhidham
Some idiot has made a plane about you
how to complain
Bhopal City Room Wala Mail Park
He has written that you were checking the camera by going to the room.
did you have a fight
no big not at all
He has written that you were unnecessarily happy in those things which are not your responsibility, I just see this
Was trying to figure out what's how Islam works here and there's a little bit below
Must have gone mad sitting in front of the monitor all day
really at the oscars
I've never done anything before
talk to myself
i talk to my tv
shoe chopra wedding
Show picture of Parvati month
you are mad
i don't understand what happened to him
Why Nice Weekend We Kate
i have to quit eating crazy
speaking taking me to cannabis recovery
OK let
Ok
Alfred Banks
Ministry of Defense's Department of Classified Information face to face
sit it later
where did you get it from
It is not known it is not allowed
yes then why are you doing this
you think
There should be an investigation on the old players that they must have remembered the day of fighting together.
how much are you able to read because he didn't check us man it's not like that
why don't we
we have to focus on the locus
Ok
Rinku will tell
Ticket
He had just fallen asleep knowing that he
Why did you go to the Ministry of Defense so soon?
dash
what kind of person is this vent
is he there yet
didn't say anything about me
No
not till now
15:00 background check from us
all that mehndi
Understanding
and when is
But one thing is there
his hobbies
is a bit expensive
what kind of song
she is fond of beautiful things
on 8
And
And that's what every man likes
young girls
It is no secret that he had many relationships with many girls.
But it's good if this thing is behind us
I don't want her to know anything about this
Yes
will be between us
Ok
but i still
why did he leave the police department
left by mutual consent
for which reason
people jobs
keep changing
can say that
we didn't get along
and he understood it very well
i wouldn't say that
he has a lot of passion
Josh it was more ambiguous
I have just come after 1 hour cross-examination.
Hope
We worked together in 1988
Manisha Govt Pay
in place of ruby
for criminal investigation
and after that he went to death to study
Yes
some of it had trouble
No no, he was facing some problem before but he had gone through this kind of problem.
the incident took place
what kind of event
is a bit down
girl case
it was a woman
Getting Landslide Up Online Brought A Lot
they were banned at that time
then it was a crime to do so
and nothing was done to him
stopped his investment
and shortly after that he went to study
Did we talk about going to Moscow to study at that time?
Yes it was not a big deal to go there and study
He must have got the help of the right people at the right time
I am talking to Defense Force Intelligence today that you have some time, I have to ask some questions.
I need help regarding some old employees of USSR Ministry of Interior
who went where
Have to connect with today's Russian Security Service General and extract some information
I want to find a person with the help of an old picture
Did you work with Arvind?
Got them yesterday in the government's post department
Hi!
and who are you
Marco Yar a Defense Force Intelligence
2 meters
Every weirdo has to write in the log book, whatever the document is, they come in the room, a photo about it
And about the general rule, I have already told that the mobile phone has to be kept
We have this multi-layer in the office
then there will be no problem you will do my work
Don't know why it must have been almost 2 years what to find
your friends are good aren't you
and lazy
Classification is the responsibility of the ladies, isn't it?
Found something Didn't know anything till now
This is also an old player of paint just like the kids
Those people are together and want to suppress the youth, so it happens everywhere.
tell me what to do
I don't know
known for now
at least you tried
Hi!
yes i am coming
Ok
got it
Thank you
was a call from the police department
they found someone's body near the breast border
what is the line
tonight is at my house
sense of shoe
Charger
i'm sleeping on the couch with you
my neck is stiff
I'll do my best to let you know you're right at 8:00
you sonia pillow
no it's not mine it's
The cheapest one for Bareilly was forgotten by mine
I am thinking that I should take something similar for the liar, maybe it gives him a better mood
This is very good, to be honest, before making everyday, I also put my phone up
Since then I was in all that trouble
cute always says there is no network here
My dad told me I shouldn't be trans
but i didn't listen to them
i see you in the evening
okay brother
There is no fingerprint, nothing can be traced
whole body completely burnt
became coal
We will take necessary action and mix it with the data of Letrin.
Ok
one more
next to the man
we got it
chingam
we will test it too
Thank you
can you tell me
Because who went to Rome in the last 2 days
I belonged to a man, was asking about you, who is my son, so he cut it and
speaking the number
there is a news
Some military men are investigating about you
Have they given your state secret?
Amit has increased
any
Hey something is speaking Defense Force Interior
someone found out about your relationship
woman and child ne ne ne ne ne ne ne
case is over
Oh ok cool
someone is trying to do something
baby is a little too enthusiastic
satka matka
but it's not a good thing
thank you for calling
Your Defense Force Intelligence is investigating Shakti, there is nothing to fear
Zulu is wrong, Kaku asked me to handle the events here, everything is fine, let him have
work in top classified information he will check everything will be ok if you stay calm
Or is there some other thing that is bothering you, some intervention at our office and the guy with him has complained to me
Muzaffarnagar
Mohan ji meets Bagayati wala can be harassed i understand
A few years ago the bouquet was in the IT department, what is the relaxation called?
we will do something
keep calm and focus on work
And keep your personal affairs just a little bit
we understand you like women don't spoil everything
What are you thinking
alfred
Oscar's wife
old thing old thing
all ok i handled the matter
Ok
be at peace be at peace
Sanjay
well hello hello good evening good evening
I think near twisting formation
took 3 more for those before
what is awesome it is quite romantic isn't it
our wedding ring happy marriage anniversary is about to come
so drink the same thing
no i won't drink drive me
take a little brother
Ok
sorry but
can't can't
and get mad
I will not be of any use toss the click will be less
If he's gone mad by the time he doesn't have friends, what brother are you expecting?
What should I do with your love?
it would be better if i met him
we can only play each other for half an hour really
I go too
Vacation
I'm sitting here nothing
What are you talking
you see
Come
Hey don't even turn off the phone
the story is
Samalkha
relax
Hi!
Kapus told me half an hour cooking weight with Rosra Singh
you are forcibly behind the pint
Have checked with clothes, done her papers
He abused me so much, I also got a pain in my ear
what are you doing guys
it was my decision
I'm thinking
Can't even sleep that we can't even touch a person
Who has it there is so much to see in court
took part in the fight
Yes it is OK
you gonna open my file
I have also served in the Ullu Bear Special Force inside the cutting plant
I'm in there too
I got a voice from inside, the voice of success
nonsense
There's a lot of voice from inside you
Sitting here, we hold each other's hands and take long breaths.
the system sings
I don't want anyone to point fingers at me
fridge
It was my decision and I am responsible for it
request
walk in group
find a way to make a new design for a teenager
trying to see through the eyes getting caught with the hero
So
Sanam Re
Asking kind of person is very smart, tells everyone for work but not without meaning
Her assistant Rita told me she has a problem that she
Spider doesn't enter every time he goes to the room
free diary
and time itself
And
Nothing much
Yet it has got such a big responsibility
He has his Russia his best friend
so there is no room for doubt
I'll be able to stay there for a few days
if anything
Ok thanks
you don't know anything about this
I will continue my search, have to keep an eye on the paint, man it is clearly forbidden, not us, but to tell something or the other
What do you think it's just because of old friendship I know why you know so what you know only what you know
Is it that if you had come to respect, then you also know that something is wrong and you did not see it
is his friend and do i know you stop you from someone you have to do the same thing
now you shut up
Was made to keep an eye on the stomach, had sought help from Prajapat
refused
No one wants to help keep an eye on Defense Force intelligence
Health iron with alarm and private security of weasel
let it be why don't you do a good job as marco
Blue are old cops and most importantly they don't have government money
We will take their help and work for us and no one will know
we have to keep an eye on the paint
you don't know anything about this
do it dude
The one who followed me in trouble no one is following me
But someone from behind me take my men
A new recording candle has surfaced
An employee of a security company was keeping an eye on people illegally in collaboration with the Intelligence Agency.
Security company has been raided
Recordings from the Ministry of the Interior have been found
The party is demanding that the Minister of State resigns
The recording found in the security company
There is a conversation between a lot of politicians in it.
private security company
Leader was kept illegally on government properties
And it turns out that they got help from somewhere
it needs to be thoroughly checked
And catch all the people who used to work in government departments and are now in the security company.
have to do
unfriend
you news from surina call
We didn't even think we had people like this
What does it mean
Our IT guy got caught
Why?
His
The child's conference has been received from the computer
You see the government is falling and what are we doing
nothing
you can come to me sometime with your stuff
Ok
The ministry of interior is immersed in politics
Everyone is trying to save himself
ministry of defense
is included
And the prime minister is calling an emergency meeting
what the fuck is this
under our nose
watching over our people
it's a very small problem
All Politicians In Recording
very angry
They think they must have been recorded too
but for what
Nobody Knows My Mr. of Interior
what is the need to do all this
It suddenly appeared in front of everyone
and such recording is illegal according to the state
Demanding Amit's investigation, take out that he will be sacrificed and he
People in high positions of intelligence will be fired
Well, behind everyone, the boss of intelligence is the mother-in-law, isn't it?
And no one will believe that without his knowledge his people were doing all this
what the fuck is all this
go talk to the ministry and
keep me informed
went very wrong
I couldn't leave her
And I think I'm doing it right
I'm sorry if my actions bothered you
trouble again
I will be transferred is on some rubbish department
you will be demoted
we will have trouble
The recording is no longer considered good at all.
Camera can't go
understand
If the ID is made, then in which case is it stuck for the zodiac signs?
It has become of use to find such people for espionage
I don't know what I will be doing sitting in our office, I will leave soon
good that
What happened to the network bus?
In front of Sonu Frenchman, our minister
stopped talking
Were saying it is not happening is writing a lot hey our own we 50 him
if you do it will happen
Indore Russia
ears should hold
would say
how ever he just wanna ruin us
Our situation had just started to improve
so everyone at home
How?
Ok
Strict action was taken against each one and his department.
mother-in-law fired
he will be fired soon
he created your file
This boy has gone crazy, was spying on everyone from the politician
Watchman I can understand why you are upset
The report of that child has not come yet
i mean his dna
Arun
we will see hussain even further
Military intelligence will no longer be used for classified purposes
and how are we 1 days
Politicians are furious that they were monitored
Wrong
It is wrong
that's what russians want
Our
all promising idiots should be removed
and government departments kept fighting among themselves
We have given some pictures there
he went to the cemetery
then to the city
don't know but something was weird
maybe he knew he was being chased and he was scared ok
Thanks
what happens to you
I was questioned a lot
they took all the tapes
Maybe you were right and check our connection with Usha
don't know what will happen next here
everything turned upside down
We also welcome all this to the North Atlantic Treaty Organization, today we
Bulgaria
Romania
slaves of the empire
in today's july 3
Rita
yes thank u in all the best all the best u too hope will benefit
I also think
Goodbye
Congratulate you for a successful mission
For this achievement of yours you will get both bonus and madam
I can't give it to you personally ma'am
but it will look something like this
It will have both name and stuff
Thanks
Sivan Problems has a special mission for you
You have to be the head of your department, remove the helmet Oscar
it may be very easy to remove it
After that all the weaknesses are there, you will find a way out
we are in big trouble
I will get reward for this work
This whole scandal is out because of your interference
Be ready Your mail file has arrived on the President's tax
Thanks
don't let it get in your mind
never
Twitter
how much off
Shivnagar
bar quite cold
I have come to leave you till the top, you have done a lot for me, really thank you very much
so it becomes
Were going to come home on dedicated and then have to take care of them
thank them without
The information found in the forest is to put the burnt corpse to sleep.
Gotta find a match for Lepsus
Ok
ok don't sleep
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/ah2fw
Help other users to choose the best subtitles