Ah! There's Princess
Dawn and Terry with the
Blooney Looney soldiers
protecting them.
Oh, Terry, look!
Here comes the Grump.
Yeah! And looks like he's going to
shoot some darts at our balloon.
Well, if they think king blooney's gas
bag guards can protect them from me.
We got another thing coming.
Okay! When I get the signal,
we'll make our move.
This will fix him.
Okay.
Everybody up!
Oh, Terry, I'm frightened.
Isn't there some way
we can fight back?
I'd better do something,
and quick. Here he comes again.
I'll show them they
can't outsmart me.
Maybe if I can put these two stove
pipes together it just might work.
Oh boy!
It's working great.
Old grump has turned around
he's heading the other way.
Come on, dragon,
step on it, step on it!
Before we get our
pride puncture.
Faster! Faster!
Uh-oh. old Grump
hasn't given up yet.
Hey sergeant,
what do we do now?
We all hide in that cloud.
The boys and I have a surprise
planned for Mr. Grump.
Faster dragon, faster.
We got him cornered in that cloud.
Oh, you dumb-dumb, you.
Hey, maybe that knocked some
sense into Grump's head.
No I don't think so.
Because here he comes again.
Ah! Getting tricky with clouds, eh?
Well, let's see how
they like my cloud.
Of sleeping gas that is.
Quick, Terry. do something.
It's sleeping gas.
This fan ought to do it.
You could keep your
sleeping gas, Grump.
He's blowing it back on us.
Stop, dragon.
Whoa! look out!
Wait, wake up dragon,
wake up, wake up.
Do something, stupid.
No long, Dragon.
I'll bail out.
Geronimo!
Don't guess on me,
you dumb-dumb.
That stupid dragon.
Oh, dear. Terry, look!
The Blooney Looneys.
Well, they'll be okay.
The way they're drifting by the time,
they wake up they'll be back
in Blooney Looney land.
Look princess. I wonder what
kind of place that is up ahead.
I don't know.
Hey, maybe this is
where we'll find the
Cave of the Whispering
Orchids and the Crystal Key.
- Oh, I sure hope so, Terry.
- Let's have a look around.
I wonder where
this road goes.
It goes to the village.
Who said that?
I did!
I'm farmer Jack.
Welcome to Jack-in-boxia.
I'm pleased to meet you.
I am princess Dawn and this
is my friend Terry, and uh...
Where's Bip?
Oh, he must be out
playing somewhere.
Gosh! Is everybody
a jack in the box?
Of course. That's what
makes this Jack-in-boxia.
- Goodbye now.
- What do we do now, Terry?
Maybe we'd better deflate the
balloon and drive to the village.
Maybe someone there will
have more time to talk.
That's a good idea.
Ao this is the village?
It's kind of different isn't it?
You can say that again.
I wonder if there's
anybody around.
I'll find out.
Hello!
Farmer Jack send us.
For Farmer Jack?
I'm officer jack and over
there is store keeper Jack.
Hi there, friends.
You cal me, Jackie.
I'm seward Jack.
Do you know what I mean?
You know who I am.
And my name isn't Jack.
You know what I mean?
Can any of you folks
tell us where we might
find the Cave of the
Whispering Orchids?
We're sure it's where Grump
is hidden the Crystal Key.
And we must find it to save my
country from the curse of gloom.
Speaking of Grump,
I wonder where he is.
Keep your eyes peeled dragon, they
must be around here somewhere.
You know, Terry. I get the feeling
that Grump isn't too far away.
Yeah, we've got to keep
a sharp lookout for him.
Look out? look out?
All lookouts hear this.
Get up there and
look out for uh, uh...
What was her name again?
- Uh, Grump and his dragon.
- And his dragon.
They're going, you look outs.
No sign of Grump.
Two o'clock an noise while.
All work here.
Still two o'clock and all's well.
What was that up ahead there?
I saw some,
faster, dragon.
Oh-oh! It's not all's well.
No matter what time it is.
Run for your life!
It's the Grump with his dragon!
Ah-ha! Did you hear that, dragon?
We got him this time.
He's here.
The Grump is here!
Ah-Ha! There we go.
After them, dragon.
Whoa!
Why you no-good
sneak jack.
Wherever you are,
come back here!
Shh! We are sleeping down here.
You smart alley jack.
So you gonna sush me?
You hear?
Well, say something down there.
Look, Terry.
Mr. Grump is really getting it.
Yes and he really deserves it too.
Hey sporty jack,
how about a game of tennis?
Okay, I'll serve.
Oh stop it!
Take it easy! Hold it! Whoa!
Watch fellas, easy now.
Don't you guys haven't missed?
I might have taken a coffee break.
Well, when Grump is busy playing
tennis we might as well take off.
Okay, Terry.
Bye, everybody.
- Goodbye, friends.
- Good luck.
Bon voyage.
Gee, it was sure nice the
way they helped us out.
It sure was.
Oh, by the way,
which way are we headed?
In a direction as far away
from Grump as we can get.
Subtitles: Kilo