You know
that Naads have less patience.
Who smuggled the children
out of Rudrapur?
Me.
It was me.
Oh!
Naad.
This child has been brought
from the Domor village
for working in the temple.
This is Janak's son.
Janak is a good singer...
so they've already marked his body.
I heard that four more children
have been selected.
Will they be Domor village too?
Yes.
But...
there's no symbol
on their bodies.
There's a girl among them.
Karal's daughter.
I'll take them with me.
I won't let their futures go
to waste, Kirat.
That's best.
Let's visit the all the houses.
And you can take the kids with you.
Keep them away from all this
and raise them to be musicians.
Kedar took five children with him
and left for Anandagarh.
When everyone found out
what we had done...
I left Rudrapur for two years.
After that, I came to Anandagarh
to meet Naad.
By then, he was known as...
Kedar Mishra.
I started working as a servant
in his house.
And I changed my name...
to Anadi.
- Anadi.
- Yes.
We have all the information.
The descendants of Madanti's son Abdul...
are still alive.
Who are they?
I'm sure you know.
Decide who you'll save.
Your grandson...
or the descendants of Madanti?
Who are the descendants of Abdul?
Kedar Mishra's wife Mumtaz.
And Bahadur.
We know that Bahadur
had a son and a daughter.
He had sent them away
when they were babies.
Who are they?
The famous santoor player
Salamat Khan.
And the renowned shehnai player
Noorjahan Sen.
Hey...
Hey!
No...
No!
Hey...
just because Anandi Uncle is no more
doesn't mean you won't keep in touch.
Couldn't you tell us?
But Grandpa Bahadur and Ramnidhi Uncle
had called after Grandpa's death.
Dad asked them to give you the news.
Didn't they tell you anything?
Ramnidhi Uncle?
What's going on?
Let's go, Shruti.
CURSE OF THE RUDRABINA
PART 2
Shruti.
That means Amanat Khan
knew everything.
And he revealed it all
in his riddle.
"All who possess the discs are 'udara'."
What?
See.
There are three octaves
in Indian classical music, right?
Yes.
- High octave, mid octave, low octave.
- Hmm.
"Tara", "mudara", "udara".
High octave is called "tara".
Mid octave is "mudara".
And the low octave is called "udara".
Think about it.
In the cursed caste system of Rudrapur...
the Domors are considered
to be the lower caste.
Now consider something else.
Think about those who received the discs
from amanat Khan.
Their parents belong
to the lower-caste Domor community.
Oh! I get it.
That's why he wrote,
"All who possess the discs are 'udara' ".
Now I understand
why there was an oblique mark
at the bottom of the rudrabina.
Because the lower octave
is signified by an oblique mark
in musical notation.
Correct.
Hmm.
Why did he have to give the disc
to my mom?
There'd been no trouble
if he'd given it to your mom.
Besides, why did he call my mom
"bibadi"?
That is the question!
Let's see...
if Ramnidhi Uncle has an answer.
Wait, wait, wait.
Pull over.
Isn't this the flute player?
Why did he come out
of Ramnidhi Uncle's house?
What are you afraid of, Ramnidhi Uncle?
Shruti
Master has been terrified
ever since he met that man.
This is the third time
he's come here.
Every time he speaks
in hushed tones
and leaves Master terrified.
Didn't I tell you
to never talk about this?
Leave my house right now!
I... I will if you ask me to.
But...
I can't see you
in this condition, Master.
Master's health is deteriorating.
He has stopped eating.
Who else do I have
other than you, Master?
I have no one.
No one...
No one.
Who's that guy, Ramnidhi Uncle?
What does he want?
I've seen him in Anandagarh many times.
He's been trying to caution me.
What does he want to say?
What's he cautioning me against?
Don't ask me these questions.
Ramnidhi Uncle, my...
my mom has been kidnapped.
The people of Rudrapur have...
Hmm.
I know that.
You...
You know this too?
Listen, Ramnidhi Uncle...
if something happens to Mom,
you too will be responsible.
I won't spare any of you.
Alap.
Who was that guy?
Tell me his name, Ramnidhi Uncle.
What does he want?
His name is Gopal.
I was one of the musicians
at Najafgarh's nautch parties.
I met him there.
Gopal was a fan of Rohini's music.
He often came
to listen to her songs.
For years, I had no contact with him.
Suddenly...
he came to me a month ago.
And told me about our connection
to Rudrapur.
Did Anadi tell you all this?
Yes.
Ramnidhi...
We were good friends
back in Najafgarh.
And that's why I risked my life...
to give you this information.
How did you get to know
these secrets?
I work for the Rudrapur royal family.
Do you know what a DNA test is?
A strand of hair or a single fingernail
can reveal your bloodline.
The royal family assigned me...
to collect all your DNA samples.
After a lot of effort I've finally managed
to collect them.
All of them can be traced back
to your real families in Rudrapur.
They tried to match the samples
with the present members of those families.
And the DNA matched.
The DNA matched?
What do they want, Gopal?
I don't know, brother.
But let me tell you something.
The people of Rudrapur are dangerous.
Your life is at risk.
Please be careful.
And don't step out of the house.
Keep this information to yourself.
Or else you'll be in more trouble.
Goodbye, my friend.
Buddhu.
Shut the door!
Don't let anyone enter.
I called up Anadi
to verify this information.
But they told me...
that he has been murdered.
Then one by one, Salamat...
Noorjahan...
And they had the same symbol
on their bodies.
I don't know who's next.
I am very scared, Alap.
I think they'll kill everyone.
You have nothing to worry about.
They're only targeting the descendents
of Madanti.
At least, that's what we think.
But you're not one of her descendents.
They'll...
not harm Rohini, right?
I will rescue Mom, Ramnidhi Uncle.
For that, I have to find
Raga Sanjivani.
I need your help, Ramnidhi Uncle.
And you're hiding in your room
like this?
Is this the way to avert danger?
- Why don't you come with us?
- Yes.
You'll stay in Anandagarh.
We all are there.
Huh?
Are you sure?
I had guessed...
that something like this would happen.
After Salamat's death...
I called up Ramnidhi.
That means you knew...
that we belong to the Domor community
of Rudrapur?
Yes, I knew.
Master Kedar never told me.
I got to know about it from Anadi
much later.
I'm really scared for Rohini, Alap.
Alap, you shouldn't have kept it
from us.
You know what, Alap?
Mom should use her contacts
to put more pressure on the police.
The more we fear them,
the more they'll take us for...
I...
- I told you, I can't do this.
- But...
I have only one way to find Mom.
I have to find Raga Sanjivani
at any cost.
Lolit.
Take your daughter and go away.
Yes, but...
she's a stubborn girl.
She won't agree to leave in this situation.
Convince her.
I couldn't save any of my relatives.
Lolit Uncle.
I'll convince Saaz.
And I give you my word.
I'll find and punish
the murderers of Noor Aunty.
But before that...
I have to crack this notation.
Lolit Uncle.
I need the contacts
of all the senior musicians you know.
I want to talk to them
in case they can give me a hint.
Hail, Rudrabhairav.
Hmm.
Naad is not good enough.
You have to finish the rest of the work.
Can you do it?
Yes, Rudrabhairav.
Hmm.
I'm really worried for Alap, Moti.
Don't worry.
Gopal is keeping an eye on him.
He won't let anyone harm your son.
(inaudible)
PANDIT OMKARNATH TRIVEDI
My goodness!
This is a very old record.
Pandit Sasikanta Bharadwaj.
Come on, let's look for him.
You want to try?
- Yes.
- Okay.
SASIKANTA BHARADWAJ
MUSIC INSTITUTE