So you're assuming
that my grandma Mumtaz
is Abdul's own daughter
just like Bahadur Uncle?
Hmm.
Seems like it.
Amanat Khan adopted Mumtaz
as his granddaughter.
All this time we've known
that my grandma died mysteriously.
So my grandpa was responsible
for it?
I can't accept it, Alap.
You think I can, Shruti?
A maestro like him
is actually a murderer?
Hey!
Something must be wrong.
But Amanat Khan's riddle...
has shown me a way.
What way?
"Sarod, sitar, flute, santoor,
shehnai, sarangi, rudrabina.
All who possess the discs are 'udara'.
'Bibadi' is Mumtaz's daughter".
The last line is very significant.
It is central
to cracking the mystery.
What makes you think so?
"Sarod, sitar, flute,
santoor, shehnai, sarangi".
Those who received the discs
play the respective instruments.
But your mom?
She was given the disc
with a rudrabina on it.
Why?
She never learnt to play the rudrabina.
Hmm.
And who is "bibadi Mumtaz's daughter"?
We don't have time
to think about all this.
I think we need to go to Rudrapur
immediately.
Naad stole the discs
to find Raga Sanjivani...
- Rohini Aunty is in danger and here we're...
- No, Shruti.
There's no point going there
before solving this riddle.
Mom might get into bigger trouble.
Shruti.
For the next few days,
don't go anywhere without me.
Why?
It's clear that Naad was behind the attack
on Ma'am.
Hmm.
And...
it wasn't for Kedar Mishra.
It was for Mumtaz.
Someone might attack
you and Saaz too.
Because both of you
are Madanti's descendants.
This is such a fix.
We should file a police complaint
against Naad.
No point.
However...
we'll need your mom's help
for something else from the police.
For something else?
Some... About what?
Such files aren't ready at hand.
It's a case from 50 years ago.
I looked for it urgently
only because you requested me.
What are you looking at?
There's nothing to see.
Nothing abnormal in the case.
In your mother Mumtaz's case
it was a plain and simple
brain haemorrhage.
- Tell me something.
- Yes?
Did my mother's corpse have a symbol
like Noorjahan's?
I didn't find anything.
Did you?
Are you investigating the symbol
we saw this time?
I admit...
that it looks like the symbol
of the Shiva temple in Rudrapur.
But suppose someone commits a murder
and puts a stamp
of the Ashok Stambh on the body.
Can I arrest the Government of India
for that?
What?
What is he even...
I think he means to say that
the temple is a public place, after all.
If someone uses the symbol
for a crime...
Exactly.
Besides, you are classical musicians.
You know how it is.
The royal family of Rudrapur
is extremely influential.
Politically influential.
They are well-respected people.
Should we really drag them into this?
Do you have anything more to know?
No, Ma'am.
We will arrest Naad.
I've alerted
all the nearby police stations.
- Naad is from Rudrapur. Definitely...
- No.
He's from Sanatanpur.
I've checked his voter ID.
We've verified that he's a resident
of that village.
Huh!
Are we done?
- Yes, let's go.
- Hmm.
- Thank you.
- See you.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
What's the matter with you?
Why do you keep coming back
without finishing the job?
- Answer me.
- You asked me to kill Noorjahan.
I did.
You asked me to get the disc.
Please release me now.
Why is Noorjahan's daughter Saaz
still alive?
Hmm?
What has that innocent girl
ever done to you?
Why do you want to kill her?
Innocent?
Innocent, huh?
They are lower-caste people
like you.
The woman who dared to touch the rudrabina
was their ancestor.
Those sinners deserve to die.
Instead, they're leading
a respectable life.
- And your people are paying for it.
- I don't believe you.
What's the problem
with women musicians?
I've seen women singing
outside Rudrapur.
And publicly.
They're not inferior to you.
You've deceived us all these years.
Going outside the village
has corrupted your mind.
You need to cleanse yourself.
Do as I say.
Go.
What happened?
Go!
CURSE OF THE RUDRABINA
PART 2
What happened?
Go!
Hey.
- Don't kick me...
- Hey!
Why did you beat my mom like that?
Do I owe you an explanation?
Huh?
We are human too.
We have self respect too.
Get that into your head.
Such audacity!
I don't think we can use Naad anymore.
But we've got the disc.
Unless we crack the notation...
we won't be able to do anything.
Can you lose hope right now?
No, right?
Come here.
Okay, forget all this for some time.
- Shruti.
- Hmm?
They won't harm Mom, right?
I just got five months with her.
Nothing will happen.
Everything will be fine.
Please sing a song.
I haven't heard you sing in so long.
Please sing.
Listen to me.
You'll feel better.
At least, sing for Rohini Aunty.
Hmm?
If I sing...
will Mom be able to hear me?
Of course.
She's your mom, after all.
Moms can just feel it.
Please sing.
Time stands still without you
Where are you, Mom?
While the world sleeps in peace
I'm awake all night, Mom
You brought me peace
But sleep comes no more
Time stands still without you
Where are you, Mom?
Who wakes alone
With the love of a mother?
The delusional ties
Keep her awake
You're living far away
And all I have is pain
You brought me peace
But sleep comes no more
When will your pains
Wither away?
Your eyes will find
The long-lost happiness
When will the pain of our birth
Ebb away?
In the everlasting night
The dawn is never to be found
Time stands still without you
Where are you, Mom?
While the world sleeps in peace
I am awake all night, Mom
You brought me peace
But sleep comes no more
What happened?
Nightmare?
Shruti.
I've seen that symbol before.
Symbol?
- Oh...
- On someone else's body.
Who?
On whose body?
Hey!
Come fast!
- Where?
- Fast!
Wait up.
On whose body did you see it?
This way.
I think this is the lane.
Hey, it's Chotu.
Hey.
How are you Chotu?
Where's Anadi Uncle?
What?
He ran away!
Hey... wait!
Chotu!
Hey...
Why did you run away...
Oh my God!
Chotu...
When did this happen?
See?
Nothing can be kept secret forever.
I have a lot to know from you.
What...
- do you want to know?
- History.
The history of how Rudrapur
is connected to Anandagarh.
I don't know... what you mean.
Are you going to risk this child's life?
Tell me the truth.
We know about Kedar Mishra's connection
to Rudrapur.
Now tell me, how are you connected
to Rudrapur?
I beg of you...
please don't kill my grandson.
I'll...
I'll tell you everything.
Everything.
I'm one of you.
I'm a Domor too.
I used to work
in the Shiva Temple of Rudrapur.
It's true.
Yes.
Back then, the Naad of Rudrapur was...
Kedar Mishra.
Hmm.
You had committed a grave crime.
Tell me about it.
Come on, speak up!
-== [ www.OpenSubtitles.org ] ==-