ENJOY ALL VOD IN HIGH QUALITY @ 4KVOD.TV
GET LIVE TV,MOVIES,SHOWS IN ONE PACKAGE
OFFICER: Lockup!
Lockup!
Put the lights out!
South Wing!
Lockup!
Lights out, Main Wing.
[Indistinct talking]
[Explosion]
[Indistinct shouting]
[Alarm ringing]
[Shouts indistinctly]
Get someone in here!
[Alarm wailing]
[Explosions]
[Man shouting indistinctly
on P.A.]
[Shouting indistinctly]
Get them out of there!
[Indistinct shouting]
[Helicopter blades whirring]
[Siren wails]
HEWITT:
[Speaking indistinctly]
To counteract this situation,
I would advocate that...
You are, Miss Hewitt, lacking
in actual practical experience.
I see no reason why my age
should be held against me
when applying for
governor rank three.
They've got
the fire under control,
but the media are swarming
around the place like flies.
Three have absconded,
two are still...
- You're not married?
- No, I'm divorced.
And Michael Winchwood
died on his way to the hospital.
Oh, that's all we need.
Do we have any further questions
for Miss Hewitt?
Have you got
any estimation of the damage?
BUNNY:
Oh, it's catastrophic.
Three of the four accommodation
wings are virtually demolished.
They've systematically
smashed every bathroom,
plumbing ripped from the walls.
There's water dripping down
and gas cylinders ignited
to fuel the fire.
It's bloody tragic.
Thank you very much,
Miss Hewitt.
[Indistinct shouting
and pounding]
Beryl! Beryl!
Beryl!
Ah, well,
we've found a foster home,
so we can't delay it any longer.
Oh, shit.
- Did you tell her?
- What do you think?
She knows it was coming,
and the longer the delay,
the worse it'll be.
Wait, wait.
Beryl.
Wait.
I wanted to be with her
when she was told.
I waited, Helen.
She'll need supervision
for a while.
- HEWITT: Yes!
- Did it go well at HQ?
Right now my prisoners
are displaying all the symptoms
of an endemic drug culture.
When we began to move
the inmates from their cells,
the trouble spread.
It was now 2:00 a.m.
More fires were started,
some inside the cells,
and the prisoners
began their rampage.
By 5:00, it was estimated
that there were
some 400 prisoners involved.
By 5:30, the ambulances
had taken all the casualties
to the hospital wing,
and at 10... 10:00...
The riot was under control.
- [Music box playing]
- [Babies cooing and fussing]
Oh.
[Exhales sharply]
- All right?
- WOMAN: Better.
Hello.
WOMAN:
Shh, shh, shh, shh.
How you doing?
All right?
Hello, sweetheart.
Don't let them take her.
Come on, Tina. You knew
this was gonna have to happen.
We've been preparing for it.
Tina.
She only knows me.
She's mine.
Of course she is. But it's
upsetting for everybody else.
You're just gonna have to
accept it, I'm afraid.
- Tina.
- I know!
But not yet.
You can't take Karen yet.
I won't let her go.
I have asked for more officers
to deal specifically
with the inflood of drugs.
But you instigated
this personal lockup method,
and the prisoners have keys.
Yes!
Only to their cell!
They couldn't leave the spur.
Obviously doesn't work.
The press are assuming
that your employees
not only shop for groceries
for the inmates,
but could have
brought the drugs in as well.
You seen The Independent
this morning?
I have had my car vandalized,
I've had my house burgled,
and I have lost my nerve
to go out at night.
And I don't want to hear
that if and when
they find the criminal
who ransacked my home,
that he's living in luxury.
There should be stricter
regimes in all the prisoners.
£40 million worth of damage.
I think that those men who
destroyed Barfield Prison...
- You off then, Gov?
- We've had to segregate Tina.
She's causing problems.
Pity Mona wouldn't help out.
I don't think it would have
been any good anyway.
This riot's causing a storm.
- Can I have a word?
- Mm?
Wasn't very convenient,
your taking the morning off,
especially with
the Tina situation.
In the future,
give me more warning.
Keep your eye on her.
See you tomorrow.
Good night.
Good night, then.
- Good night, Governor.
I told her I was going days ago.
We got hold of balloons.
Do you want to see what we got?
- What are you talking about?
- For Beryl.
- She's getting married Saturday.
- Oh. Oh, yes.
The hen party's Thursday night.
She's got a second
honors degree, in psychology.
Played a substantial part
in suicide awareness support.
[Chuckles]
We'll all be needing
more than support.
Mm.
Excellent result from the field.
Well, she is very accomplished.
She's not married.
Very dedicated.
She's still very young.
Even so,
she spent two years in the U.S.
studying their penal system.
No, I think she is
a very good candidate
to put on
the investigation team.
Mm.
Good to have one woman.
ANDREWS: I might as well
come straight to the point.
[Spoon clinking]
There's to be a full-scale
investigation into the riot,
and into the subsequent death of
the prisoner Michael Winchwood.
As part of your studies,
you are,
I note from your records,
familiar with
prison suicide awareness.
I would therefore like you
to agree to be part of
the investigation team,
Miss Hewitt.
[Engine cranking]
[Up-tempo classical music plays]
Come on.
[Cranking continues]
[Cellphone rings]
Helen Hewitt.
REDWOOD: I've been trying to
contact you. We have a problem.
- Tina's tried to kill herself.
- [Music stops]
- What did you say?
- Tina's tried to kill herself.
[Sighs]
Shit!
Okay, listen.
Listen, just...
Just try and keep her calm,
and I'll be right there.
- You coming in?
- Yes, now!
[Indistinct shouting]
[Shouts indistinctly]
She cut both wrists.
She seemed to accept it,
but the next minute
she went into association.
She did it
with Doreen Rigby's glasses.
Wait outside.
[Door opens]
I'm sorry I wasn't here, Tina.
Did you hear what I said?
Aye.
I said to meself,
if they take her,
really take her,
then I'll kill meself.
Soon as I'd made me mind up,
I could sleep,
like I'd made
the right decision.
I knew she'd gone.
I'm really sorry I wasn't here.
That's all right, Miss Hewitt.
It was funny.
I got that fat girl's glasses.
You know her... Doreen?
Anyway, I nicked her glasses.
I planned it!
They took me baby,
so I'd nobody else!
Tina.
The bloody things
wouldn't break!
I trod on them,
I jumped on them,
and I could barely break the
skin, never mind kill meself!
It was ridiculous.
[Laughing] And I
started laughing.
[Laughing]
[Sobbing]
HEWITT:
I just want to know why,
after I left
specific instructions,
why nobody took the time to sit
with her, to stay with her.
Do you know what
she actually did?
She couldn't smash the glass,
so she broke one of the arms
and tried to gouge out
the veins in her arms!
We had
three new admissions today.
Well, that is no excuse.
What about one of
the probation officers,
any one of the officers?
I'm short-staffed as it is,
and the last thing I needed
was my deputy disappearing.
So it's my fault?
Nobody is directing blame
at anybody, Helen.
Oh, I am.
I am saying
that we are to blame.
And I am saying
you should not
have taken time out
without consulting me.
I understand you've been asked
to be a part
of the investigation team
looking into the riots
at Barfield Prison.
I think it'll be very good
for you, but a word of advice...
Just look and listen.
Don't run before you can walk,
or you'll fall down
right on top of your ambition.
Thanks for your advice,
Governor.
Congratulations.
MAN: Try now.
[Engine starts]
Miss Hewitt, sir.
Thanks.
I'm sorry, I'm very late.
Gary Marshall,
the deputy governor.
- Ah.
- Would you like some coffee?
Uh, no, I think
we should join the others.
- Is everyone here?
- Yes, they're all here.
I've been instructed to, uh,
take you on a tour.
We'll catch the others up later.
As you said, you're very late.
There's a lot of mess in here,
so be careful.
I don't want to rush you,
but, um...
- Are these inmates?
- No, contractors.
There's about 20 men allocated
to clear this place out
as fast as possible.
- Private contractors?
- Yeah.
They're dumping the rubble
in the exercise yard
for the moment.
So the men held here
now have no exercise area?
From what I've gathered,
there were major drug problems.
No more than any other prison
of this size.
Right, everyone.
Lunch, I think.
- Tell Miss...
- Hewitt, sir.
Hewitt to carry on.
[Indistinct conversations]
MAN ON WALKIE-TALKIE:
Arnie Franks is getting worse.
- Where's the governor?
- In his office.
All right,
I'll speak to Marshall.
The gov's in his office.
Now, I've told him you were
still showing her around,
but it's just that Arnie Franks
is creating a bit of the usual,
only he's getting very het up.
Look, when she's through here,
buzz me.
I'll collect her
and wheel her out.
- Where are the others?
- Not back from lunch.
Bit young, ain't she, Gary?
And a know-all.
Bloody university highflier.
Four years I waited
for governor three,
and I've just heard that she's
been promoted to it first time.
Bloody stupid.
Now, look, I'll sort Arnie out.
You just keep her busy.
Blimey, I didn't realize
you had him here.
Yeah, and he's not a happy man.
We got a formal complaint
after Winchwood.
Doesn't feel safe
with a murderer on the loose.
Considering he's a mass killer,
he's got a bloody nerve.
Does he reckon
Winchwood was murdered?
No, Winchwood was just the spark
that started the riot.
HEWITT: So have you got
all the ringleaders, then?
- Yeah, we got them.
- Yeah?
In fact, they were the problem.
We tried to get them out without
a row, and all hell broke loose.
Well, they're not
our problem anymore.
They've been shipped out.
So is Governor Langham
gonna be shafted?
I wouldn't know.
Tell me some more
about Winchwood.
I presume with his record,
he'd be a vulnerable prisoner,
so was he segregated?
Will Marshall be taking over
if Langham retires?
That'll be up to headquarters.
Could you take me
to Mr. Marshall, please?
See if you can calm him down.
If not, get back to me.
Governor.
Oh, excuse me. I was just
waiting for Mr. Marshall.
I'm Brian Langham.
Helen Hewitt, part of
the investigation team.
I have to uproot my wife,
my kids from their school.
I think I'm still in shock.
The riot was bad enough,
but they really pulled the rug
from under me.
Enforced retirement.
Well, somebody had to be
the scapegoat, I suppose.
I'm sorry.
Can I ask you something?
Michael Winchwood. It's been
put out it was suicide.
We won't get verification
until the autopsy reports
are finalized.
[Telephone rings]
Yes?
MAN: You'd better come
on the VP Wing, sir.
LANGHAM:
I'll be right down.
I'm sorry, I have to
go to the VP Wing.
Do you mind if I come along?
FRANKS:
I want to see Mr. Langham!
MAN: Shut up!
FRANKS:
I'd nothing to do with it!
I need him!
[Shouting indistinctly]
- Arnie.
- [Wailing]
Just listen to me.
I told you.
Arnie, don't!
Just listen to me!
Arnie.
- Open it up.
- [Wailing]
Hey, hey, Arnie!
What do you think
you're doing, mate?
You got the whole corridor here.
I want my visiting order!
Arnie, you'll go
to the visiting rooms
at 10 minutes to 2:00,
okay, Arnie?
Does he need a sedative?
Look, give me a minute.
- [Wailing]
- 10 to 2:00, Arnie. Okay?
You'll get the visiting order
at 10 to 2:00.
[Wailing]
[Thud]
[Wailing continues]
Right, in you go!
Oh, this is a little bit
over the top, isn't it?
He hasn't had a visitor
for five years,
and because he's got
full-blown AIDS,
he's very dangerous.
He's also mentally subnormal
and as strong as an ox.
And very active sexually.
FRANKS: Oh, please, no!
[Wailing]
[Sobbing] Oh, no!
No!
HEWITT:
Is that Winchwood's cell?
Not anymore, ma'am.
Doughen, will you get
Miss Hewitt out in safety?
- Get her out!
- Governor.
Winchwood's cell.
They're coming in now. They want
to see Winchwood's cell.
Right!
Back to your cells!
Go on, move it!
[Man wolf-whistles]
Judge Simms,
Miss Hewitt has just arrived.
Uh, not just, actually.
I've been on a guided tour.
Miss Hewitt.
Now, these are
Governors Effinger, Swallow,
Hartington, Littlejohn, and...
Are we to wait for Mr. Langham?
Hello, Matthew.
Hello, Norman.
Have you been taking notes?
He barks out at the secretary,
but I've made...
SIMMS:
Ah. Governor Langham.
Right, gentlemen, I've asked
to see Winchwood's cell.
If we could cut the chitchat.
LANGHAM: It's this way.
Which one's the psychologist?
The nervous one.
With the twitch.
[Laughs]
The police have asked
that we don't touch anything
inside the cell.
You want to go inside?
I don't think
it will be necessary
for all of us to go in.
Good God.
Suicide?
Get yourselves a coffee
and grab a chair.
Ah, Miss Hewitt.
Have you had a moment
to study the file?
No, I've only just
been given it.
Excuse me.
I want to start
the discussion straightaway.
As you can see,
the prison services
have supplied a scale model
of Barfield,
showing the relationship
of the various wings.
Uh, Mr. Effinger, do you feel
that the governor in charge,
Mr. Langham, is liable to
any disciplinary action?
Please keep your answer short
and to the point.
EFFINGER:
Well, to be quite honest...
That is the point.
Yes?
Well, I do think
there's some time discrepancy
in the statements
of several of the officers,
in particular, O'Keefe,
Doughen, Jensen,
Smith, and Mallard.
SIMMS: All these stated
that A Wing...
That is, the VP Wing...
Was, at the time
of the first fire, locked.
Yes, continue.
Well, if you take
into consideration
the victim's injuries,
he could have been attacked.
SIMMS: But it has not been
verified by the police
that Michael Winchwood
was attacked.
To the contrary, we must accept
that the wounds
were self-inflicted...
Yes, but, sir...
his right and left
wrist artery, throat frontal,
and two chest wounds.
Excessive, I'll agree.
Yes, well, Winchwood, according
to the medical reports,
also received
extensive bruising.
But these have not been proved
to be inflicted
on the night of the riot.
They were in fact...
Do you have the medical report
from his previous prison?
MAN: Winchwood arrived
at Barfield from Hull
two weeks prior to the riot,
with bruising to his abdomen,
back, and buttocks.
I think we must move on from the
Winchwood injuries, as I said,
until we have verification
that it was suicide,
and not, for want
of a better word, murder.
I am uppermost interested
in finding out
how and why this riot occurred,
and where the blame
is to be directed.
Miss Hewitt,
I would appreciate it
if you read the file
in your own time.
Please pay attention
to the discussion.
Is the judge going
in his own car or with us?
- Is my car here?
- Mm.
Could you get social services
to make a set of photographs
of Tina's baby?
Because I'm asking you to, Enid.
If necessary,
I'll pay for them myself!
The known ringleaders have been
named and are being dispersed.
However, as there were more than
150 prisoners
all admitting to taking part
in the riot,
it would be a time-consuming
and financially punitive
undertaking
to review each man's sentence.
Now, that being said,
I think in time
the ringleaders
must be publicly named
and their sentences
adjusted accordingly.
Governor Langham has agreed
to take an early retirement,
and no disciplinary action
will be taken
against any of
Barfield's officers.
The Home Office pathology report
is being sent by courier.
It is determined
that Michael Winchwood
committed suicide.
HEWITT: Suicide.
It's now been made public.
It is a complete
bloody whitewash.
Not entirely.
Brian Langham's lost his job.
Only one record adds...
Here it is...
"Detectives conducting
the inquiry
had previously thought
it was impossible
for a man to sustain
such injuries."
If you had anything
to say about it,
you've missed your opportunity.
I took your advice.
I looked, I listened,
I said nothing.
But I wish I had.
If Michael Winchwood
killed himself,
he was a bloody contortionist.
A moment.
Mr. Bunny...
Barfield's area manager...
You've, uh, met him?
Yes.
He just called
to offer me Barfield Prison.
You gonna take it?
Does that mean I'd... Does that
mean I'd run Kettering?
I turned it down.
He asked me about
your operational experience
in male prisons.
Me?
As governor?
Are you serious?
Did he say
there was a possibility?
- [Knock on door]
- Sorry to interrupt.
But the photos
of Tina's baby have arrived.
Enid said you were
going to pay for them.
What?
Oh, yes, yes, I did.
Apparently you said
it was urgent.
Right!
Right, I'll deal with it.
You have two adjudications,
Mrs. Redwood.
Thank you, Joyce.
Hmm.
You don't think they'll
offer her Barfield, do you?
I have a nasty feeling
they might.
Right, we want the new governor
settled and primed
before we announce it
to the field,
and in particular to the press.
Thank you.
You're taking a big chance.
Risk, more like it.
Oh, I don't think so.
I think the risk is minimal.
She'll have
200 prisoner officers
to look after 88 men.
See, she's strong academically.
Practical experience.
♪ One for the money,
two for the show ♪
♪ Three to get ready,
now go, cat, go ♪
♪ But don't you
step on my blue suede shoes ♪
♪ You can do anything, but lay
off my blue suede shoes ♪
[Laughter]
♪ You can knock me down,
step in my face ♪
♪ Slander my name
all over the place ♪
♪ Do anything
that you want to do ♪
♪ But, unh-unh, honey,
lay off of my shoes ♪
BERYL: Hi, Helen!
Over here!
Sorry I'm late, Beryl.
I said I'm sorry I'm late!
- Sit down!
- Oh!
Drinks for Helen!
Cheers.
Good luck, Beryl.
Cheers!
I thought you'd given it up.
God, I hate this.
I don't know how any sane person
could get up there
and make themselves
look so ridiculous.
You would never get me
doing that
in a month of bloody Sundays.
If she works out,
she can stay on.
If not, well, there's
a possibility that the prison
will be recategorized
and someone of a higher rank
will automatically take over.
You're right.
It's a good choice.
The press will love her.
She fitted in very well
on the investigation team.
Knows how to keep
her mouth shut.
So it's agreed?
Helen Hewitt will be
the new governor of Barfield.
♪ Oh, no, not I ♪
♪ I will survive ♪
♪ Oh, as long as
I know how to love ♪
♪ I know I'll stay alive ♪
♪ I've got all my life to live ♪
♪ I've got all my love to give ♪
♪ I'll survive ♪
♪ I will survive ♪
[Music and cheering fades]
Congratulations.
I presumed I'd be taking over.
They at least had the decency
to let me know.
I'm sorry,
but as my deputy, Gary,
I'm gonna need
all the backup I can get.
You'll have it.
[Knock on door]
Uh, do you want coffee?
I'm sorry,
I don't know your name.
Mavis O'Connell.
I'm...
Secretary. Good.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to know I'm not alone.
This is Miss Helen Hewitt,
Mavis... the new governor.
I like my coffee black
and in a china mug.
Do you have a percolator?
Uh, yeah, I think so.
It's Amaretto coffee.
I got used to it in the States.
Are we computerized here?
Pardon?
Are the staff files on computer?
Uh, no.
Well, not all of them.
Ah, right, well we'll have to
get that sorted out.
Thank you, Mavis.
What's this?
Uh, Michael Winchwood's family
are not too happy
with the findings
of the investigation results.
What?
I referred them to
the prison authorities.
Did you?
Do you want my honest opinion?
I don't think it was suicide.
We've got a problem.
New governor doesn't believe
Winchwood committed suicide.
- [Locker door slams]
- Bollocks.
Just stick to the same stories,
okay? Agreed?
It'll be all right.
She can't prove anything,
can she?
Not if we make sure of it, no.
MAN: Governor Hewitt would like
to meet all personnel available
in the cinema in 30 minutes.
Oh.
Where's the ladies?
You go to the end
of the corridor,
first right, past the lifts,
and it's at the bottom
of the stairs
at the end
of the second corridor.
You'll need a key.
I haven't got the time
to walk half a mile
if I need to pee.
We'll make this one the ladies.
Got you working hard,
has she, Mavis?
You can say that again.
You know this toilet?
Can you get maintenance
to fix up
a proper "ladies only" notice
on the door?
Oh, yeah, Michael Winchwood's
family'll need visiting orders
for tomorrow.
They're coming here?
Oh.
I want that replumbed
and a shower unit put in.
Right.
Where's the cinema?
[Indistinct conversations]
Here she comes.
That's Langham out, then.
[Indistinct conversations
continue]
That's enough!
Have a bit of respect.
HEWITT: Good morning.
Thank you.
First of all can I say
how pleased I am to be here
as the new governor of Barfield.
[Men murmuring]
There are three things
that are probably worrying you
about my appointment.
One, that I'm a woman.
Two, my age.
And three, am I going to stay?
Well, the first two
I can do nothing about,
but with regards to the third,
let me tell you
that I am staying.
As you must all be aware,
the rebuilding of Barfield
will continue,
so our priority during
this period will be security,
but we are in
the enviable position
of having only 88 inmates
and enough officers
to control 400.
I intend to take a harsh line
with any inmate attempting
to create further disturbances
whilst Barfield
undergoes refurbishment.
MAN:
Who does she think she is?
I will put my intentions in
writing on the bulletin board,
and I ask each of you
to give me every assistance
in establishing the new regime.
My first order, as from today,
is to withdraw
all inmates' personal cell keys.
- [Men groaning]
- Quiet!
HEWITT: Thank you.
[Indistinct talking]
I look forward to working
with you all
and getting to know each of you
on a personal basis.
If any of you now have
any complaints or queries,
please feel free to voice them.
Thank you very much.
[Men wolf-whistling]
All right, that's enough.
- Mavis, what...
- I know, I know.
"or passed on any narcotic
substances," blah, blah, blah.
"As from now, every man and
woman coming into this prison
must be willing to be searched,
and that includes
all staff members.
My intentional priority is to
clear Barfield Prison of drugs."
She also wants every cell
and inmate strip-searched
as from 11:30 tomorrow morning.
[Up-tempo folk music playing]
Right, Murphy, strip search!
[Indistinct shouting]
[Up-tempo rock music plays]
[Indistinct shouting continues]
You tell them new bastards
they'll be sorry!
You can do it yourself, Murphy.
Right, now, move it!
You better put that on your
possessions list, Vernon.
- [Rock music stops]
- Come on! Get back in!
Get yourself in order!
Governor's doing her rounds.
Make sure we're doing her orders
to the letter.
Governor's doing her rounds.
- All clear?
- Yeah, we're clear.
Strip search completed.
Ready for inspection.
No problems.
[Clanging]
Right, then!
New governor coming around!
One of you put one foot out
of line, you're down the block!
Staff are very edgy about
the landing being searched.
If there are drugs
in this prison, Gary,
then I am going to find them,
and I am going to find out
who is bringing them in.
- Morning.
- Morning, ma'am.
Did you ever think that maybe,
just maybe,
it could be the prisoners?
What are you telling me, that
the prisoners are going out,
they're leaving,
they're scoring,
and they're bringing it
back in again?
- I meant their visitors.
- Ah, visiting rights.
As from tomorrow,
they will be reinstated.
It's gonna weigh very heavy
with security.
And we need to get back
to the basics of security.
Any visitor discovered
passing or bringing in drugs
will have their visit curtailed
and further visits reviewed,
possibly facing
criminal charges.
I'm warning you...
And I'm warning you
'cause I have not finished.
I have only just started.
- Mr. Morgan?
- Ma'am.
Good morning.
It's Mr. Layton, isn't it?
This is the new governor,
Miss Hewitt.
Good morning, Miss Hewitt.
- Pleased to meet you.
- How do you do?
[Indistinct conversations]
I'll need to tour the VP Wing
tomorrow morning.
Yes.
Mr. and Mrs. Winchwood,
plus a Norman Sewell,
and I've two girls
from the temp agency
waiting to be interviewed,
and the furniture removal firm
have called twice.
Hold the Winchwoods,
send in one girl at a time,
give them five minutes each.
And Mavis, call an agency, get
them to clean my flat, anything.
It is a complete mess.
And tell the removal company
I'm missing two crates.
I'm sorry, Gary, you're gonna
have to excuse me.
Don't you want me
in on the Winchwood meeting?
No.
[Sighs]
Mavis.
Has HQ called her
about the Winchwood visit?
I don't think so.
[Knocks on door]
You have Sarah Green
and Moira Levitt
to see you... the temps.
I'll send in Sarah Green.
Royston Andrews speaking.
It's Marshall.
I think you should know
the Winchwood family
have turned up here.
Just find out what
the Winchwoods want
and then get back to me
as soon as you can.
No.
Get Miss Hewitt to contact me.
It's the WordPerfect program.
Good.
Mind you, probably with
the amount of staff references,
it would be best to have the
Windows program on disc as well.
Does it worry you,
working in a prison?
Even just temporarily?
No.
Why should it?
They're not running the offices,
are they?
I don't know about that.
Thank you very much
for coming in.
I'll call your agency.
Mavis.
Thanks for seeing me.
Send in Mr. and Mrs. Winchwood.
Who's the man with them?
I don't know.
Oh, ask, Mavis,
and all will be divulged.
And the last girl,
if her details check out,
and she's okay with security,
give her the job.
- That one?
- There were only two, Mavis.
Oh, and ask her to wear
a longer skirt.
Oh, Mavis, did you get someone
to clean my flat?
[Sighs] Shit.
Oh!
Mr. and Mrs. Henry Winchwood
and their legal advisor,
Mr. Norman Sewell.
Please, do come in.
I do apologize
for the state of my office.
Coffee, Mavis.
Please, sit down.
Thank you.
We wished to see you with regard
to the police investigation
into our son's death.
We're very disappointed.
No arrest has been made,
and yet everybody concerned
in this tragic affair
knows that Michael died
in what can only be described
as a horrific, violent,
and disgusting manner.
He was prepared to do his
sentence, serve his punishment.
He should have been protected
from the other inmates
and from himself.
Michael was,
as you must have been aware,
due to the type of crimes
he had committed,
segregated from
the main prison wings.
Mr. and Mrs. Winchwood
have asked me to undertake
a private civil action
against Barfield Prison,
citing gross negligence
to blame for the death
of their son Michael.
Did Michael ever mention
any particular prisoner
who made threats?
Not at his first prison,
but here at Barfield.
No.
You must understand.
Even though every precaution
is taken
to protect sex offenders...
Particularly
child sex offenders,
and in Michael's case
a brutal child murder.
There's no need for this,
Miss Hewitt.
I am, Mr. Sewell,
simply stating facts
and the problems
that we have with men on Rule 43
within a prison of this size.
You see, they're not all
sex offenders.
Some are in debt and scared
to be on the main prison wings.
Others are mentally vulnerable.
[Door opens, closes]
And there was
a full-scale police inquiry
and an investigation
by the prison authorities
into Michael's death.
Investigation or cover-up?
Have you seen
the medical reports?
There was, to my knowledge,
no cover-up, Mr. Sewell.
None whatsoever.
Thank you, Mavis.
Black or white, Mrs. Winchwood?
- What's going on?
- She said there was no cover-up.
None whatsoever.
Would you drop the civil action
if I personally undertake
an investigation
into your son's death?
All I want is justice.
I shall see that you get it,
Mr. Winchwood.
[Keys jingle, door unlocks]
I'm the new governor.
I'm afraid Mr. Langham
isn't here anymore.
I know.
They've told me.
You've requested
a visiting order.
There you are.
All you have to do
is fill in the form.
[Sobbing]
It is what you wanted, isn't it?
- Morning Miss.
- Morning.
[Door closes]
[Keys jingling]
[Door locks]
How long has Arnie Franks
been on all this medication?
Ain't got a clue.
He's just been brought back
on the wing from the hospital.
He should be in Broadmoor,
not in here.
I don't know
what gets him going.
You should try and find out.
These men are in your care.
It does help if you know or
are aware of what upsets them.
I'll speak to Dr. Thomas.
Hey.
That form you gave him...
He's eating it.
[Sobbing]
Perhaps it's preferable
to that congealed mess
we call breakfast.
See if you can get him
some exercise today.
JACKSON:
If you say so.
You weren't on duty the night
Michael Winchwood died.
No. I was called in
for the riot. We all were.
- How did you get on with him?
- I didn't.
It's, um, Mr. Jackson,
isn't it?
Yes.
What's your first name?
Curtis.
Well, Curtis, I worked very hard
for the title "governor."
Please use it.
- [Indistinct shouting]
- You keep that dog away from me!
Keep away from me!
[Dog barking]
Okay, let's move it.
Where's she this morning?
VP Wing.
Stop panicking.
Just as long as she's not
talking to those two bastards.
Bit of trouble there.
Good morning, ma'am.
[Down-tempo big-band music
playing]
Prisoner 653.
Gregory Colly, ma'am.
[Music stops]
Good morning, Gregory.
Good morning, miss.
Welcome to my billet.
Did they tell you
about my glue situation.
Mr. Langham
always saw to it personally.
Oh.
I never cheat.
Never stick a few together.
Always one at a time.
Perfectionist, me.
Very, very impressive.
You were
on the same landing as...
Michael Winchwood, yes.
That is correct, miss.
But it's imperative
that I get me glue.
Now, I know the problem, I know.
I have, swear on the Bible,
never been under the influences.
It's too precious a substance
to me.
You understand, miss?
I know about
your request, Gregory.
I'll see that you get your glue.
Oh, God bless you.
I've not been able to sleep.
Where were you on the night
that Michael Winchwood
attempted suicide?
Out for the count.
Heavy sleeper, miss.
Did you ever hear anyone
make any threats against him?
Did you talk to him?
Me?! Who me?
I-I'm a special.
I used to be segregated
for my own safety.
I still don't ever see nobody.
Thank you, Gregory.
I miss the music, though.
Winchwood played nice music.
Opera.
- Know what he's in for?
- Yeah.
Ah, well.
He's still got his hobby.
Did Michael Winchwood
have a hobby?
Oh, yeah... making our life
bloody difficult.
[Shouting indistinctly]
Right! Button it!
Any more of this,
and they're gonna blow.
Can you put the pace on?
[Indistinct shouting
and banging]
Quiet down up there!
Quiet down!
HEWITT: But is this really
all we got from the cells?
They're tossing it.
They're just flinging it
out of the windows?
No matter how decent the cell...
Own toilet, et cetera...
They still have to chuck
their shit out the window.
And not just the type you smoke.
Thank you, Mr. O'Keefe.
Home brew from the slop bucket.
Disgusting.
I'd say this is about
all we're likely to get.
Hmm.
Is there any way that
any prisoner from B Wing
can transfer goods
from one division to another?
Other than just
throwing it out the window.
DOUGHEN: Yeah.
They tie it with a bit
of dental floss and swallow it.
I mean,
what do you want us to do,
get X-ray units in here next?
They stuff it in their ears,
stuff it up their nose,
stuff it up their ass.
Thank you.
I still want another search.
This time we'll go in at night
when they're not expecting it.
I want all prisoners
out of their cells.
That is, all non-VP prisoners.
What? No way.
At this moment,
tension is way out of hand.
Right,
so we'll give them something
to take their minds
off the tension.
In my office, please, Gary.
Do you want to speak
to Dr. Thomas?
Well, these are his surgery
and home numbers.
Fine. Thank you.
See if he's free for lunch.
Have you ever heard of caution?
Hmm?
You've only dealt with women.
Let me tell you, these men here
are ready to blow.
They're already uptight over
losing their cell-key privileges
and you can't keep
pushing prisoners
like Murphy and Jellings.
When did these men
last have a movie?
I don't know.
Uh, before the riots.
Right, so we'll give them
a movie night.
And, Gary, in future
will you please remember
that I am the governor here,
not you.
What you do want?
"Aladdin"?
I want them to see
the movie voluntarily, Gary.
Oh, right. We'll give them
Sharon Stone then, eh?
That'll do fine.
And could you
tell Officer O'Keefe
I'd like to speak to him
this morning?
I'll be in the gymnasium
in 10 minutes.
[Up-tempo electronic music
playing]
Could you tell me about
the night of the riots?
Exactly where you were
and what interaction you had
with the prisoners.
We've all given statements
to the police,
to the investigation team.
Yes, I know, so it shouldn't
be too difficult
to recall your movements
that night, should it?
I did the lockup checks
on B Wing about 7:30.
Then I checked all
the open areas that's near...
The cinema, the laundry,
then I went to the canteen.
Alone?
No, Tom Doughen was with me,
Russell Morgan,
and I think Jensen.
Jensen, Smith, and Mallard.
Yes, go on.
Had a cup of coffee
and a sandwich,
then, oh, maybe about half 8:00
I went to do the VP Wing.
Where Michael Winchwood
was held?
Yes.
Alone?
Yeah, he was segregated.
No, were you alone?
No.
Tom Doughen was with me.
This is all in the report book,
you know?
Yes, I know.
Do go on.
We checked Winchwood.
We had a few threats
against him,
so we were keeping him
under supervision.
A few threats?
Would you care to elaborate?
Well, we always get them
with child molesters.
Sex offenders,
it's part of the norm.
I am aware of that.
But which prisoners
did you know or were aware
had made threats
against Michael Winchwood?
Most of them
at some time or other.
But on the night in question,
two prisoners...
Murphy and Jellings...
Became excessively violent.
Do you think they could
have had anything to do
with Michael Winchwood's death?
No, I don't.
You and Officer Doughen
were instigating lockup
when the fire broke out.
Yes.
Were all the prisoners
locked in their cells?
- Yes.
- Including Vernon Black?
Yes.
Could you ask Officer Doughen
to be in my office in, say,
10 minutes?
Yes, Governor.
Mavis, if Officer Doughen
is there,
can you send him in, please?
On the night of the riots,
you have stated that
all prisoners on the VP Wing
were locked up
when the fire started.
Yeah, that's right.
On that night, Vernon Black
was in the VP Wing.
Yes, but he's subsequently
been transferred to C Wing.
- After the fire?
- Yes.
So he's not
a vulnerable prisoner?
Not anymore.
I think he owed money.
They're not all sex offenders.
I do know that, Mr. Doughen.
I am simply making sure
that Vernon Black was,
on the night of the fire,
locked in his cell.
The reason must be obvious.
Sorry?
Vernon Black is an arsonist,
and according
to the fire team's findings,
the first fire began
in the kitchen area
of the VP Wing.
Well, he must have
been questioned.
Yes, he was.
Thank you, Mr. Doughen.
[Door closes]
[Up-tempo heavy metal music
plays]
[Indistinct conversations
in distance]
It's Mr. Black, isn't it?
[Music stops]
You're here for five years,
and you've done...
18 months.
Transferred from Leeds.
Mm-hmm.
Did you prefer it there?
Well, it was easier
for me mother to see there.
Mm.
Why were you in the VP Wing,
Mr. Black?
Well, I owed Murphy
a few quid for phone cards.
I had to wait for a visit
before I could pay him back.
- Have you paid him back now?
- Oh, yes, ma'am.
- Thank you very much, Mr. Black.
- It's okay.
HEWITT: [Coughs]
It's okay.
- Sorry I'm late.
- Oh, hi.
- Can I get you another?
- No, thanks. I'm fine.
Usual for me, Don.
Do you mind if we go to a table?
I sit at the bar,
and it's open surgery.
Sure.
So, Miss Hewitt.
Or do I call you Governor?
Helen.
Have a sandwich.
Thanks.
Mm! Mmm.
Lovely, thank you.
- [Chuckles]
- Thanks.
- Cheers.
Was Michael Winchwood suicidal?
I don't know.
I've looked over his records,
obviously.
My predecessor
didn't appear to think so,
or he would have
made a note of it.
Is this tuna?
Quite possibly.
You ever worked
in a prison before?
No.
But you must be aware of our
present problems with narcotics?
Well, of course I'm aware,
but until the government
or the Home Office
admit that it's a problem,
as far as I can ascertain,
it's turned a blind a eye
if it keeps them quiet.
Well, not any longer.
Any prisoner
discovered taking drugs
will get an extra 28 days
on his sentence,
solitary confinement,
and loss of privileges.
Possession and drug trafficking
is illegal,
and mandatory drug tests will
become the regular procedure.
MAN ON P.A.:
A Wing... showers.
They bring those friggin' dogs
inside our pads again,
and I'll have her.
You hear me?!
Listen, all the men
are on our side.
They try to pin anything on us,
we'll start a nice little riot
for that stiff whore bitch.
Anybody having her, and it's me.
Piss off, Vernon.
Hey, have you heard?
We've got a film showing.
It's that one with Sharon Stone
showing her [Whistles]
Vernon, piss off.
Go on.
Get out of it.
- Give me a towel.
- Honest.
Doughen told us.
Hey, O'Keefe,
is he having us on?
On the level, Murphy.
Sharon Stone?
You're a lying bastard.
Not in person, Murphy.
Come on. You've been in here
over your time.
You having a problem with that?
Or are you shitting yourself
because Winchwood's parents
came here?
Ha ha ha ha!
Look, Miss...
Helen.
I'm a doctor.
I don't know anything
about running a prison,
and I don't take any sides.
I just do my job
when I'm called out.
And I intend to do my job
and rid Barfield of drugs.
[Pager beeping]
Well, I'll give you
every assistance I can.
And you're gonna need it.
Thanks.
Um, listen...
- Excuse me.
Maybe we could meet again
and discuss drug rehabilitation.
Sure. You know where I am.
All you need to do is call.
Don, okay if I use the phone?
I can arrange for you to meet
the local rehab center's
administrator.
Oh, brilliant.
And perhaps we could
also instigate
some sessions inside the prison,
And, um, if you're free
for dinner...
I'm on your side, Miss Hewitt.
It's Dr. Thomas.
Mm-hmm.
Murphy.
So, what do you think
of the food here?
It's okay.
But you work out,
though, don't you?
Do you think you get
enough protein?
Yeah, I get in extra.
You get in brought in?
Yeah.
We all do.
Those that can afford it.
Not telling tales.
It was even in the papers.
Do you smoke?
No.
So you're the new governor,
then?
My, my, my.
Whose face did you sit on?
I didn't hear that.
What other perks do you get?
On the night of the riot,
Mr. Murphy,
could you tell me what happened?
You a bull dyke, then?
HEWITT:
What did you say?
You a dyke?
- Am I a what?
- Lesbian.
You're one, are you?
That's why you got the job.
Act like a man.
You a dyke?
The night of the riot,
Mr. Murphy.
Answer the question.
Banged up as usual.
Then the fire started.
They unlocked our spurs,
held us over in the quad.
That's it.
What time were taken
out of lockup?
I don't know.
My watch stopped.
"Prisoner 493, Anthony Murphy,
became violent and abusive."
That was at 8:30.
Mr. Murphy, is that correct?
I don't know.
My watch stopped.
- Do you know Michael Winchwood?
- No.
But you knew who he was?
Yeah, we knew he was here.
What did you think of him?
He raped and tortured two little
girls aged nine and seven.
He buggered an eight-year-old
boy, then buried him.
So why don't you tell me
what you think about him?
Did you ever threaten him?
- Personally? No.
- You didn't?
You must be the only man here
who didn't.
Par for the course, isn't it?
A perverted, twisted animal.
All nonces should be castrated.
So you did threaten him?
You're putting words
into my mouth, love.
I never said I did,
and I never said I didn't.
He topped himself.
Saves a lot of aggravation.
Saves the government
a lot of cash.
Costs a grand a week to keep
filth like him segregated.
Costs almost as much
to keep you too, Mr. Murphy.
You're new to this job,
aren't you?
Otherwise you wouldn't bother
wasting your time
with shits like Winchwood.
What time's
this movie starting, then?
Mr. Murphy,
I will treat you with respect
as long as you apply
the same rules to me.
When I interview you again, one,
just one sexual innuendo,
and I will take it personally.
I am the governor
of this prison.
You will stand up when I enter
your cell and when I leave.
Now, is that clear?
Thank you, Mr. Morgan.
Suck on it, sweetheart.
[Indistinct shouting]
MAN: Nonce!
Nonce!
You dirty bastard!
[Bellowing]
[Thud]
[Continues bellowing]
Come on, Arnie.
Come away.
- Come on.
- [Sobbing]
Murphy knows
Winchwood's family are here.
Who knows
how they get to know everything
that's bloody going on?
As long as we stick
to what we've said throughout,
nothing can happen.
And at the rate
Wonder Woman's going on,
she won't last out the week.
First we lock up the VP
straightaway.
Choose a few number of officers
to do the strip searches.
Use as few as possible
'cause we'll need
all the officers for the cinema.
C Wing is priority, then D Wing.
We've got to keep them in
the cinema as long as possible.
We've got a good two hours
to do the strip search.
I don't think she has any idea
what she's bloody doing.
What if they don't
want to see the movie?
What, Sharon Stone? Hmm!
You kidding?
Jammy sods.
Maybe she's not the pushover
we thought.
There is such a thing
as being overloyal.
What's that supposed to mean?
I'm not involved in this,
and you don't have to be.
You'd better tell her
before she finds out.
[Indistinct shouting]
[Indistinct walkie-talkie
chatter]
I think
we've almost got a full house.
These are the no-shows.
Well, let's hope
Sharon simmers them down.
I wouldn't bank on it.
There's a Mr. Andrews
from prison services.
- Oh.
- No, no, he's here.
Oh, boy,
that's what I call timing.
How are we doing?
- Waiting on another 15, ma'am.
- Hurry them along.
MARSHALL: Evening, sir.
We're all ready to go.
We've got 70 men.
All of them, after today's
business, very edgy.
We've got every officer on duty.
That's day and night staff.
Do you think
she's just out of her depth?
I'd say she's drowning.
Joke.
Just a joke.
Seriously, it should be...
[Indistinct conversation]
Has Gary given you an update?
Right, as soon as the men
are in the cinema, let me know.
Mr. and Mrs. Winchwood
have informed me
that you have instigated
a new investigation
into the death of their son.
Is that correct, Miss Hewitt?
[Indistinct shouting]
MEN:
[Chanting] We want Sharon!
We want Sharon!
Sharon, Sharon!
I do not believe
that Michael Winchwood
committed suicide,
but that he was
physically attacked.
I am not sure which of
the officers were involved,
but I think they were prepared
to turn a blind eye
as long as Michael Winchwood
only got a severe beating,
and it got out of hand.
Do you have any evidence
to substantiate
what you've just said?
Or is it all supposition?
[Knock on door]
I suggest you come
to the cinema immediately.
[Indistinct shouting
and whistling]
[Up-tempo rock music plays]
MAN ON WALKIE-TALKIE: Strip
search of C Wing in progress.
Okay, we've got two hours,
so there's no hurry.
Be thorough.
Go through everything.
Go on.
Get on with it.
♪ What you looking for? ♪
MAN:
[Speaking indistinctly]
the new governor, Miss Hewitt.
♪ What you looking for? ♪
[Indistinct shouting]
Would you be quiet
and let Miss Hewitt finish?
We want to see the film!
HEWITT:
[Speaking indistinctly]
[Prisoners booing]
[Indistinct shouting]
I have a complaint.
Where's the movie?!
- Yeah!
- Where is it?!
Put the movie on.
Show the bloody film!
[Retching]
Ohh.
Temazepam sleeping tablets.
The prisoner's that are
on prescribed tabs store them...
Especially these...
Crush them, and mainline them.
They're using their own kettles
to clean needles.
We found three so far.
[Grunts, exhales slowly]
Do you want me to get someone
to take you home?
No, I'll be fine, really.
I'm fine.
Well, I made
a really big fool of myself.
Oh, we all have at one time.
Made a fool of ourselves.
The discovery of drugs
was very good,
but when the film finishes
there's gonna be trouble.
Fortunately we've got enough
prison officers to handle it,
so go home, Helen.
We're all at your disposal
whenever you need us.
Thank you.
Just drop this
Winchwood business, hmm?
And, uh, put tonight behind you.
[Sighs]
[Groans]
[Down-tempo instrumental music
playing]
Governor, Miss Hewitt's
here on the stairs.
I think you'd better come down.
She misses you.
HEWITT: [Chuckles]
Yeah, I didn't
think you'd still be here.
Catching up with paperwork.
My youngest has been ill.
She's better now.
I just popped up to see Tina.
She seems fine too.
Hmm.
[Coughs]
She seems to be coming to terms
with everything.
[Clears throat]
- How's everything at Barfield?
- Oh, completely out of control.
I made a very big
fool of myself tonight,
right in front of
the operationals director.
I'm sorry.
He was very nice
about it, actually.
There's been a lot of resentment
about my appointment.
Well, that was expected,
wasn't it?
[Sighs]
Since my divorce, you know,
my job, heh,
is everything to me.
Barfield was the ultimate prize.
It isn't a prize, Helen.
It's a tough and thankless job.
I could have prewarned you,
but you wouldn't have listened.
I didn't think it would be
quite so, um...
lonely.
Well, it is.
So use me, Helen.
Talk to me.
I've lost my confidence.
I don't think I can finish
what I started.
Oh! I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
I didn't, uh, mean to do this.
I've just got nobody else
to talk to.
You know when I was a kid,
I always used to talk to my dad.
He'd be somewhere on the farm.
He'd give me really big hug,
and he'd say,
"Come on, now, spit it out."
He was a really, um, big man.
I mean, um, his heart.
I wanted John to be like my dad,
but he wasn't.
[Laughs] I don't know why
I'm telling you this crap.
You're not going to quit,
are you?
I feel like it.
[Sniffling]
Michael Winchwood
didn't commit suicide.
He was murdered.
But yet
I look at his case histories,
I read what he actually did,
and the men are right.
He was a disgusting
piece of humanity,
and I think he got
everything he deserved,
and why should I bother?!
If you believe
there's been any injustice,
any cover-up at Barfield Prison,
it's your job to prove it.
You be angry
and get to the truth.
[Indistinct shouting]
We have trouble in C Wing!
Need some backup, over!
Do you know
why they gave me Barfield?
I think when the prison
is refurbished,
the category will
possibly be changed,
which would mean you are not
at high enough rank and...
- I'd be replaced.
- It's just supposition.
I may be wrong,
but it's gonna cost millions
to put that prison
back in order.
The bastards.
And Marshall.
My bloody deputy.
Do you think he knows?
I think it's common knowledge,
Helen.
That's why I turned it down.
[Sighs]
So I'm just a caretaker?
Well, I'm a hell of a lot more
than that.
And I shall prove it.
I'm gonna
see this thing through,
and then just let them
try and shift me.
[Speaking indistinctly]
We're more bloody pissed off
than they are!
We want in!
I want to go in!
Don't go in there!
Are you crazy?!
Now, listen to me!
This is Officer Morgan,
and we are coming in!
Any prisoner not in his cell
[Shouting indistinctly]
Do you hear me?!
It's over, mate.
You coming in with us?
[Cellphone rings]
Helen Hewitt.
MORGAN: It's Morgan.
The riot situation
[Speaking indistinctly]
I'll be right there.
No, I said I'm on my way.
I want every available officer
standing by on C Wing landing.
They want to go in!
Nobody goes into that
bloody wing until I say so.
Don't you think
it's until I say so?
This is the governor!
This is Governor Hewitt!
Get back in your cells now!
[Indistinct talking]
MAN: I'm not going
down the block for any woman.
Move it!
Get back in your cells!
Go!
Get out of my way!
Bastards!
Bastards! Bastards!
This is the big riot?
You.
Back to your cell.
What are you doing?
[Thuds]
Nothing.
Tell every man I want every cell
back in order
by the time
I do my morning rounds.
MORGAN: Yes, ma'am.
Lockup!
- Lockup!
Mr. Morgan.
Thanks for calling me.
Why did you?
This isn't tales
out of school, right?
I don't think the cons
should have been allowed
such privileges.
They could lock us out.
They could do
whatever they want in there.
You were right to withdraw
cell keys, that's all.
And that's why
you tipped me off?
Ma'am, talk to Vernon Black.
I already have.
He's an arsonist.
He's also a junkie,
and with nothing on the wing,
he'll be needing a fix.
He might just talk to you.
About what?
Michael Winchwood.
[Gasps]
You gave me a shock.
I was just checking
Winchwood's belongings.
His parents want them.
Did you want me?
O'KEEFE: Officer Doughen said
you wanted to see Vernon Black.
He's in metalwork.
He's got the shakes.
You won't get
any sense out of him.
[Grinding]
DOUGHEN: Okay!
Hold it!
Hold it down a minute!
Five-minute tea break.
Governor's on her way.
OFFICER:
Please remain in the area.
Tool and equipment check.
Could you wait over there?
Over there, please.
On the night of the riot,
Vernon,
you told me
you were on the VP Wing.
And when the fire started
you were locked in your cell.
Yeah.
You are serving a prison
sentence for arson, aren't you?
Yeah.
Did you begin one of the fires
the night Winchwood was killed?
Officer Doughen,
would you wait over there!
What's the matter
with you, Vernon? Are you sick?
Are you running a temperature?
What's the matter with you,
Vernon?
I don't know anything.
But I might.
I want to go back closer
to where me mum can visit me.
It'd help me to remember.
Don't play games with me,
Vernon.
I am not here
to make deals with you.
- When was your last visit?
- It's been over a month.
So you lied to me.
You told me you were on the
VP Wing because you owed money,
which you were able to pay back
after your last visit.
Now I am asking you again,
on the night of the fire,
were you locked in your cell?
On the night Winchwood died,
did you see anything?
Did you hear anything?
Take him back to his cell.
He shouldn't be in metalwork
in his condition.
Michael Winchwood
had a radio/CD player,
and it's not in his cell.
Do you know where it is?
MARSHALL: He didn't have one,
did he?
Well, he must have had one.
There were two CDs in his cell.
Would you check it out
for me, please?
Oh, better still,
get me prisoners'
possession lists, C Wing.
Know anything
about Winchwood's CD player?
The governor wants all C Wing's
inmates' possessions lists.
Shit.
Did Vernon Black put that
on his bloody list?
I don't know.
Don't back the wrong horse,
Gary.
She's getting closer.
Ah, do you recall what make
it was, Mr. Winchwood?
- [Speaking indistinctly]
- Yeah.
Yeah.
And any of the CDs
that Michael might have had.
Pavarotti, miss.
- Oh, that's wonderful.
- [Knock on door]
I need to talk to you.
- Not now.
- When?
I don't know, Gary.
I'm sorry, what was that?
Serial number LP-249.
Thank you very much indeed,
Mr. Winchwood.
- Yes.
- [Alarm blaring]
[Shouting indistinctly]
Eight minutes!
HEWITT:
Is there a fire?!
- Don't go in.
- What's happened in there?
- I wouldn't go in.
- Excuse me!
Come on, breathe.
Breathe, come on.
Get him into the ward
as fast as you can.
Come on.
Okay, Vernon.
- MAN: Steady.
- It's okay, Vernon.
- MAN: You'll be all right.
- Come on, quick, lads.
MAN: One, two, three.
Lift.
Steady.
DR. THOMAS: It's okay, Vernon.
It's okay. We're here.
Come on.
That's it.
Stay calm.
Did he take something?
Who did this to him?
DR. THOMAS: Come on.
Gotcha!
Come on, Gary.
This is ridiculous.
You know the rules.
Every prisoner must list
his personal possessions.
This is a bloody CD player,
and it is not on Vernon Black's
list of possessions.
It never was on his list,
because you know and I know
it was Michael Winchwood's.
Now, you were part
of that strip search,
so who is covering up for who?
I'm not covering up for anybody.
Somebody is.
At least admit you'll know that.
No, I don't know that.
You are aware by now that there
could be a murder inquiry.
This is your opportunity
to come clean with me, Gary.
I have nothing to hide.
Good.
In the meantime,
I want a list of names
of every single officer
on that strip search.
I want the names
of every officer
by Vernon Black's cell
before he was beaten.
- Beaten?
- Beaten.
He's also an arsonist,
and if I find out
that he was not in his cell
the night of the riots,
then he will be a witness.
Plot thickens.
With me?
Good night.
What's going on?
I want the list of who was
on duty in C right now.
You know Vernon Black's
in hospital?
I talk to you,
and they'll kill me.
Murphy and Jellings
will kill me.
Who are you more
afraid of, Vernon?
Murphy and Jellings
or certain prison officers?
I fell down the stairs.
I can't protect you
unless you tell me
who you're afraid of.
Just tell me the truth, Vernon,
and no one will hurt you.
I saw him.
It's... It isn't
the way you think.
I can explain.
I just...
We want to talk to you.
Please.
Cigarette?
I don't smoke.
Well, Michael Winchwood
used to taunt us,
taunt the other prisoners.
He's been made out to be
some kind of victim,
but in reality the man was
a perverted, twisted bastard!
O'KEEFE: He wasn't like
the other segregated nonces.
He was always sort of gloating,
like he was somehow superior,
playing his classical music,
his opera.
- Get to the point.
- Tom's got two kids.
Winchwood used to keep on
about what he'd do to them.
I was bathing my little boy,
and I drew the curtains 'cause
I didn't want anyone to see me
holding me own little boy.
That's what Winchwood did to me.
We just wanted to shut him up,
make him scared.
We knew we couldn't do it.
So you used Murphy and Jellings.
We wanted to talk to you,
to tell you, ask you if you'd...
Look...
I think I know what you're gonna
ask me, and the answer is no.
There's been enough covering up.
If Murphy and Jellings
killed Winchwood,
then he has a right to justice.
Or his family does.
He deserved all he got!
We just wanted to teach him
a lesson, nothing more.
Oh, but it was more, wasn't it?
It was a lot more.
Governor Langham covered up
for you, didn't he?
No?
What about Gary Marshall?
Did he know?
Did he?
These are the self-confessed
officers involved,
Officers O'Keefe and Doughen.
But they didn't act alone.
Also involved in the events
of that night
were Officers Jensen,
Smith, Mallard.
They're all named.
I'll leave you
to make your own decision
regarding
Deputy Governor Gary Marshall,
as he is not yet privy
to this information.
Prisoners Anthony Murphy
and Douglas Jellings'
case histories,
and lastly Vernon Black's
tape recording.
May I play this now?
This was actually recorded
on Michael Winchwood's
own cassette player.
BLACK: When Murphy and Jellings
was brought in,
I was in the kitchen area.
Officers O'Keefe and Doughen
gave them the nod.
[Indistinct conversations]
[Down-tempo classical music
playing]
[Man singing operatically]
OFFICER: Lockup.
Back to your cells.
Come on.
Lockup.
Get back in your cells.
Lockup, lockup.
Come on, lads.
Right now.
[Man singing operatically
continues]
- Okay?
- Now.
Get in your cell, Black!
Lockup!
Stay out of it.
Right?
[Classical music continues]
Ooooh.
[Man singing operatically
continues]
Ooooh.
[Volume increases]
Lockup secure on landing.
[Man singing operatically
continues]
WINCHWOOD: [Screaming]
[Man singing operatically
continues]
[Explosions]
[Glass breaking, alarm rings]
Oi, Doughen!
[Alarm blares]
[Banging]
[Indistinct shouting
and banging]
BLACK:
I didn't start no fire
but the one in the VP kitchen.
'Cause I hate the animals
in there.
But I never did anything
to Michael Winchwood.
Murphy and Officers O'Keefe
and Doughen
agreed to say nothing about it.
They gave me the stereo.
I-I didn't nick it.
Then they tried to
take it off me.
They beat me up.
Thank you, Miss Hewitt.
I think we would now like
to discuss these developments.
You have been very tenacious.
Please would you leave
the tape recording?
There is a copy in the file,
plus a written transcript.
Thank you.
MAN: Miss Hewitt, can you
tell me what it feels like
to be taking on
the notorious Barfield Prison?
It's a challenge, and I know
it will be hard work.
But as the new investigation
into the death of
Michael Winchwood proves,
every man, whether inside
or outside prison,
deserves and has a right
to justice.
MAN: Is it true you're the
youngest governor in England?
- Yes, I believe so.
- WOMAN: Miss Hewitt, please...
MAN:
Is it true that you're
the youngest female governor
in England?
Yes, I am.
MAN: Miss Hewitt, can you look
this way, please?
MAN #2: Miss Hewitt.
[Mid-tempo instrumental music
plays]
[Indistinct shouting]
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/agzww
Help other users to choose the best subtitles