[Projector ratcheting]
[indistinct conversation]
[upbeat music playing]
api.OpenSubtitles.org is deprecated, please
implement REST API from OpenSubtitles.com
- Hey, Pete.
You're not leaving already,
are you?
- Uh, no, it's... -
my wife is waiting up for me.
- Come on.
One more drink, huh?
I have a little
going-away present for you.
I, uh...
I got you a raise.
I know it must be tough
for you
trying to start a family
in this economy.
Now, it's not much,
$2,000 a year.
I tried to make it more,
but only vPs
make that kind of money.
And the company policy
is pretty firm on it, so...
- Thank you for that.
- It's my pleasure.
- Do you have any idea
who's replacing you?
- [Sighs]
No.
Uh, yeah, it's a woman.
I don't know her.
She's coming from Slater's,
ACS banner out west.
And all I heard about her,
she's a real ballbuster.
[Chuckles]
So good luck with that,
my friend.
[Chuckles]
The last seven years
in this department
have been, um...
have been some of
the most meaningful in my life.
No, I'm being serious
for a moment.
A lot has happened,
a lot of great memories.
My second child was born
while I've been working here.
Some of you were there
at his baptism.
You're all like family to me,
and, uh...
[sighs]
I hate to say it, but I'm
gonna miss you all very much.
So...
[sighs emotionally]
Cheers, cheers, huh?
- To Jim.
- All right.
- Thank you to all of you.
Cheers, cheers.
- Cheers.
[upbeat music]
-Iceman, iceman,
candy man, and sandman
All the things
I wanted for
Someone else took them
Lonely in a new shirt,
lonely watching baseball
If I had to do it all again,
I wouldn't
Throw it all away
I want a holiday
I want
[dishes clinking,
water running]
- Sorry.
I couldn't get away.
- Did you eat?
- I had some nachos.
What is this?
- That's to fix the car.
$1,500.
- What was wrong with it?
- I don't know.
Something with the brakes.
Hey, could you put Henry
to sleep?
He's driving me crazy.
- Kids, it's me, Racer Steve!
- And I'm Princess Katie.
Welcome to our... -
- Come on, buddy.
Time for bed.
- No.
- Come on.
[Groans]
- We don't go to bed.
[telephone rings]
Dad, get it.
[answering machine beeps]
- This message
Is for Pete Cozy.
I'm calling
from Banking Services Credit.
- It would have been more,
but he would had
to have made me vice president.
- So why didn't he make you
vice president?
- I don't know.
I guess it's a big deal.
- We could use the money.
- [Scoffs]
I don't want
to be vice president.
I don't want any more
responsibility at that place
than I already have.
I mean, vice presidents
stay late at the office.
They work weekends.
I don't want to do that.
I want to do my job,
come home,
and spend as much time
with my family as I can.
- Did you ever hear back
from that other job?
- No.
Not yet.
[Calm instrumental music]
[sighs]
What's up?
- It's her new car,
our new boss.
Looks brand-new.
- Did you see her?
- Nope.
We got a meeting at 10:00
in the conference room.
- [Sighs]
Morning.
- I feel like shit.
Being human sucks.
I hope someone brought
doughnuts.
I'm starving.
[Indistinct conversation]
- Just look at this.
Look at him.
There he is.
[Laughter]
- Have you seen him?
- Her.
He's a she.
- No way.
- You didn't know?
- No, no shit.
I hope she's hot.
- Hi, everybody.
I'd like to introduce myself
and tell you all
a little bit about
what we'll be doing
for the next few months.
My name is Susan Felders.
I've been in pricing
and marketing for 11 years.
[Laughs]
Before moving to ACS,
I was president of pricing
at Safeway, SoCal region.
ACS then hired me to run
their Slater's Markets banner,
200 stores on the West Coast.
And here I am at Wolski's.
I'm passing out my résumé.
My cell phone number's
at the top.
Wolski's
is the lowest performance banner
on the ACS chain.
We are losing sales.
Our stores
look like time vaults from 1985.
Our corporate image
has nothing to do
with pricing or value.
What we have, mostly,
is locations.
You know, we're the store
that managed to stay in business
when Walmart
opened down by the highway.
We're the store
for the little old lady
who takes ten minutes
counting out exact change,
the store for the husband
who forgot to buy milk
at the Super Saver.
Now, I took this job
to change that.
We are gonna change that,
starting here,
right now,
in this room.
- Hey... -
- Hi, Matt, right?
I know you all
have a lot of questions,
and I will have answers
for you.
But I don't want to waste
anyone's time in a conference.
I will be meeting
with each one of you
in the next few days,
So thank you.
This is exciting.
- [Whispers]
She's hot.
- Hi, Brian.
Hey, it's Pete Cozy.
Yeah, no... -
Okay, um...
Do you know of anyone else
that might be hiring?
[Sighs]
- [Mouthing words]
- Can I help you?
- Hi, Pete, right?
I was just checking out
your playlists.
I approve.
- Thank you.
- I was just curious 'cause
all the jobs on your résumé
were in the music industry.
It's not every day
someone transfers
to the supermarket business.
How'd you end up here?
- I don't know.
- [Laughs]
Is there anything fun
to do around here?
See any good shows?
- I don't really get out much.
I have a kid.
- Aww.
Boy or girl?
- A boy.
His name's Henry.
He's three.
- That's so cute.
I'd like to talk to you
outside of the office
for a few minutes,
a more casual atmosphere.
But if you have to go home,
I totally understand.
- I don't mind
that she's coming over.
I just wish you would have
given me some time to prepare.
- She's just coming over
for a drink.
She's not expecting
anything.
- The place is a mess.
- Seemed like
the easiest thing to do.
[Knocking at door]
Hey, come on in.
- I was so lost.
I didn't realize
you had it so rough.
- Oh, no,
it's not a bad neighborhood.
- Oh, okay.
I needed to get out of L.A.
I was in a lousy relationship.
It wasn't working out
at Slater's.
ACS made me an offer
I couldn't refuse.
They said
if I took over here,
I could do anything
I wanted.
We are going to transform
this company.
- Wow.
You know, I don't even know
what Pete does, actually.
- 'Cause it sounds so boring
when I talk about it.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- I love talking shop.
Our department takes data
that represents
customers' behavior,
like what customers
are buying.
It then translates that data
into strategies
that can be used in stores
to increase sales.
- Oh, you mean
like putting soda cans
at the ends of the aisle.
- Yeah, that kind of thing,
but so much more.
Look, you guys
drink organic milk, right?
- Yeah.
- Right, one child,
suburban,
I know how much you make.
You're an easy demographic.
I bet I could guess
75% of what's in your fridge.
I mean, the stuff you buy
doesn't happen by accident.
What do you do, Sara?
- I'm not actually working
right now.
You know, raising Henry
is a full-time job.
- She's going back to work soon.
- Yeah, maybe.
- Oh, what is that?
- We're having a Halloween party
at the office.
Spouses are invited.
- On Halloween?
- Yeah, when else?
- Oh, you know what?
That's Henry's party.
They're having
a little Halloween party
at his school, so...
- It's earlier,
so we could go to both.
- Can I come?
- To Henry's party?
- Yeah,
unless it's not cool.
- [Laughs]
No.
I guess it would be okay.
- Good night.
- No.
- [Sighs]
I better go too.
Here's what
I wanted to talk to you about.
A lot of bosses coming into
a department like this
would lay off
a lot of people.
I don't have time
to go out and rehire.
We're just going to have to work
with what we have.
But I do have to fire someone,
just to trim costs.
- Mm.
- It's not you, obviously.
But I thought you might know
who it should be.
Who is the worst performer
in the office?
Who's bringing morale down?
- Can I think about it?
- No, I don't want you
to think about it.
I'm sure as soon as I said it,
a name came into your head.
- Matt Davis?
- Really?
Why him?
- He's always missing deadlines.
I mean,
he's kind of half-assed.
- What about Tony Gomes?
- Tony?
No.
I mean,
I think we should keep him.
He's all right.
He's a good worker.
- All right.
Thanks.
I'm glad I asked you that.
- Good morning.
Wolski's.
Yes, mm-hmm, please hold.
- What's going on?
- She fired Tony.
- No way.
- She wants to see you too.
- Dude...
I'm sorry.
- I hated this place anyway.
[Knock at door]
- Yeah, come in.
Shut the door.
- I thought
you weren't gonna fire Tony.
- I never said that.
I just wanted your opinion.
- He's got four kids.
- I don't feel good about it.
Firing people sucks.
It's sweet that
you're worried about his kids,
but he was slacking.
He wasn't happy here.
Sit.
We've got a lot of work
to do here.
We don't have time
to fuck around,
feeling bad for Tony Gomes.
He'll land on his feet.
Sit.
When I was working at Slater's,
I hired a company
called Intellichoice
to look over our stores
and to suggest strategies.
These guys are cutting-edge.
- Yeah, they're consultants.
- Yeah, they're very good
at what they do.
When the preliminary results
came in,
I was blown away.
And my boss at Slater's,
an asshole named D'asarlo,
decided to can
the whole thing.
- Why?
- Because he's an asshole.
He didn't give me a reason.
He said it was his decision,
and that was it.
And that's what pissed me off.
So I did something that
I probably shouldn't have done,
which is, I went to his boss
at ACS, Jack Bennington,
to try to get him
to change D'asarlo's mind.
Bennington didn't like the idea,
but he offered me this job.
- Where you can do
whatever you want.
- Yeah.
Slater's is a banner
under ACS,
so as far as I'm concerned,
ACS owns the strategies
that Intellichoice came up with.
I'm counting on you
to understand
what's behind
these strategies.
But you can handle that,
right?
You went to Dartmouth.
- Yeah.
How did you know
I went to Dartmouth?
- It's on your résumé... -
Dartmouth, economics,
Sony Music, Matador Records.
I need someone
I can count on, Pete, okay,
someone
who's not gonna bullshit me.
You be honest with me,
and I'll be honest with you.
- Okay?
- Sure.
- Miss Felders,
Ernie on line one.
- [Groans]
It's the guy I left in L.A.
He's turning into a stalker.
I'll talk to you later.
Don't forget those files.
Those books are for you too.
Hey, what's up?
Would you stop?
I'm not going to talk to you
if you're gonna cry.
- That guy
has been calling nonstop.
Good.
You got all those files.
Here's some more for you.
I can't keep up with her.
She's stressing me out.
Halloween party.
Fun, fun, fun.
What are you gonna be?
- Oh, I'm not dressing up.
- Oh, yes, you are... -
costume mandatory.
Read the memo,
fun, fun, fun.
- Ernie!
- I'm gonna be Condoleezza Rice.
Do you think people
still remember who she is?
- I'm not the one
who peed in the bed!
Fuck you!
[Door rattles]
Under no circumstances
do his calls
come into my office.
He's a fucking asshole.
Is Matt Davis here yet?
- No, he's late.
- He better get his fucking ass
in here soon.
[Toy beeping and buzzing]
- Oh, Henry, Daddy's... -
Sara!
- Why do you have to read
all this stuff for work?
You never had to read anything
for work before.
- This is exactly
the kind of thing
I've spent my whole life
avoiding.
- Why don't you
find another job?
- What do you think
I've been trying to do?
- I'm sorry.
- Hello, this is Gary
calling from MasterCard
regarding the past-due balance
on your account.
- I thought you paid them.
- With what?
- Look, just send them $30
so they stop calling.
- Okay, I will.
I will take Henry,
and I will go and read to him.
- No.
- I love you.
Say, "I love you, Daddy."
- No.
[Fax machine whirring]
[Upbeat music]
? ?
- "I miss your smells... -
"your breath, sweat, feet,
armpits,
the back of your leg
when it was hot out."
- What the hell is that?
- Oh, Susan's boyfriend in L.A.
He faxed this last night.
It's totally screwed up.
- This guy's crazy.
- Read that thing
about the toy.
- Yeah.
- "When you put yourself
inside me,
"it wasn't just a toy.
It was your love in my ass."
[Laughter]
- Where'd you find that?
- I found it on the fax machine
when I came in.
I made a copy of it.
- It's, like, 12 pages long.
- No one's ever written me
a letter that long.
- Shut up, you guys.
Here she comes.
- [Snickers]
- Good morning.
- Morning.
[Clears throat]
- Who gets this coffee?
It's really good.
- Doug.
He's really weird about coffee.
- Doug, ah.
So does everybody know
what they're gonna be
for Halloween?
- Well, I was thinking
something from Toy Story maybe.
[Stifled laughter]
- Okay, you're not weird.
Did I miss something?
- I think he just choked
on his doughnut.
- Speaking of,
can we just nix these things?
They're totally gross.
Let's have something
a little healthier.
- Mm-hmm.
- There seems to be too much
snacking going on here anyway.
- Did she just call me fat?
Do I look fat to you?
Fuck.
[Knock at door]
[Keyboard clicking]
- You wanted to see me.
- Yeah, shut the door.
[Sniffs]
I'm giving you a raise.
I figure with Henry
and the house and everything,
you could use it.
$40,000.
Does that sound fair?
- That's what I make
right now.
- Yeah, so after that,
you'll make $80,000, okay?
- L... - thank you.
I thought only vice presidents
make that kind of money.
- Yeah.
You're a vice president now.
Congratulations.
- Isn't that a big deal?
- Mm-mm, not for somebody
who went to Dartmouth.
You should be making more
than that if you ask me.
How old are you?
- 36.
- Yeah, what are you
waiting for?
You're married.
You have a kid.
What are you going to do
when Henry
wants to go to Dartmouth?
How are you gonna pay
for that?
- That's not really
your problem.
- Of course not.
[Chuckles]
The truth is...
I need you on my team.
We've got a ton of work
to do here,
and I need to be able
to count on you.
Did you look at those files
I gave you yesterday?
- Yeah, some of them.
- [Sighs]
What about Todd Kenner
from Intellichoice?
Have you talked to him yet?
- I didn't know
I was supposed to.
- Get his number from Donna.
He's coming in next week
to help get us started.
He's an interesting guy.
You'll like him.
I want to get three or four
of his strategies
into our stores in two weeks.
- Two weeks?
No, no, no,
it takes us two months
to turn around
the scanning data... -
- Kroger has three departments
doing what we do here,
and they have better data.
Safeway outspends us
five to one on R&D,
and they're upgrading
their entire checkout system
next month.
- But we're not Safeway.
- Exactly.
And we cannot compete
with them
unless we pull our thumbs
out of our asses!
Come on!
How did you guys get to be
so fucking lazy?
It's like moving wet sandbags
around here!
Oh, Christ...
I'm sorry.
I...
I raised my voice.
I'm sorry.
I'm PMS'ing.
It's just frustrating.
[Sighs heavily]
I know this isn't
what you were planning on doing
for the rest of your life,
but you're a smart guy.
You could do a lot worse
and make a lot less doing it.
So if you want out,
tell me now.
- I'm in.
- Good.
I want you to pick out
three or four easy strategies
that will give us
results quickly
because I want some momentum
from those
that we can use to roll out
some of the tougher stuff.
- Okay.
- Oh, I'm still invited
to Henry's party, right?
- Yeah.
- Good.
Thanks, Pete.
Give this to Donna
on the way out.
- What are you doing here?
- I'm waiting for you
to get out of there.
How was your meeting?
- It was good.
That's exactly
the kind of joke
my wife would get mad at me
for making.
- Yeah, but she'd laugh.
- Maybe.
- Oh, I know how it is.
I was married.
Been there.
Sucked.
You know what the trouble
with marriage is?
It turns women into wives.
See, women laugh at your jokes
and dress nice
and suck your cock.
Wives don't put out
and talk to you
like you're retarded.
- [Chuckles]
- When was the last time
you got laid?
- No comment.
- I've had sex 136 times
in the last six months.
I'm a numbers guy.
I can't help counting.
16 different women.
16.
- For an average
of 81/2 times each.
- Well, the mean is lower.
It was mostly with one woman.
The absolute deviation
is around 3.6.
But you should have seen
those stats when I was married.
Are you married, Donna?
- No.
- No?
- [Laughs]
That's not funny.
You could get fired for that.
- I didn't do it.
- Halloween party tomorrow.
- I'm gonna be
Rudolph valentino.
He was a movie star
during the silent era.
- I know who he is, Doug.
- Mm-hmm.
- Can you get out of my desk,
please?
- Where's your costume?
- Oh, parents
don't really dress up.
I'm gonna change later.
- You need to get
in the spirit of things.
This is supposed to be fun.
[Mellow bass-driven rock music]
? ?
You like that, huh?
It's part of my costume.
You ever hear these guys?
[Radio volume increases]
- Sure, it's Luna.
I love these guys.
- I do too.
- I actually tried to sign them
back when I worked at Sony.
- No way.
I followed them around
one summer
when I was in college.
- Really?
Yeah, Dean's awesome.
- Yeah, he is...
Even though
he doesn't remember me.
[Horn honks]
- Oh, I wish
I were a little bar of soap
Oh, I wish
I would slippy
and I'd slidey
Over everybody's body
- Hi, Henry!
- Hi.
You must be Henry's mother.
- No, I'm not,
but this is Henry's dad.
Hey, you.
I love your costume.
- I'm not wearing a costume.
- Oh, okay.
- I think it's time
for everyone
to play Pin the Nose
on the Pumpkin, yes.
- Yeah!
- Oh, hey.
- Hi.
- You know what,
parents can join too.
- Yay!
- And welcome.
- Thank you.
- Why don't you take your coat
off and stay awhile?
- I feel a little weird
that no one else
is wearing a costume,
but okay.
- I am.
- All right.
- Let's do it.
Okay, here we go.
Happy Halloween!
-We dress ourselves
In stripes and dots
- Sorry I'm late.
Hey.
- Look.
- We dress ourselves
without interference
We dress ourselves
In greens and blues
- None of these people
are your friends, though, right?
- No.
Well, I'm your friend now.
- [Chuckles]
- Do you see that sign
over there?
- Where?
- I know, you can't see it.
It's right there.
- Oh, yeah.
- Yeah.
Who's it for?
Is it for the kids?
- They can't read.
- I know.
So it's... -
it's for the parents,
but it's... - it's so high
that you can't see it.
It's a good sign.
You should put it
where you can see it.
- Yeah.
- That's part of my job.
I put signs
where you can see them.
You'd be surprised
at how hard it is to do.
I wish the people in the office
were as fun as those kids.
- They're not so bad.
- Oh, come on,
you hate them.
I mean,
none of you guys are friends
outside of the office,
are you?
- Not with me.
- That's one of the reasons
why it's so hard
to get any momentum
on anything.
Everything just stops at 5:45.
Don't you ever look forward
to going to work?
I'd like to welcome everyone
to the first annual
Wolski's pricing and marketing
Halloween party, yeah!
All: Yeah.
- Oh, come on.
I had better reception
at my dad's old age home.
I want to welcome everyone
to the first annual
Wolski's pricing and marketing
Halloween party!
[Loud cheering and applause]
All right, that's better.
I want you all
to drink and dance
and mingle
and have fun tonight.
This is the last fun you're
gonna have until Christmas,
and no one leaves
until they karaoke.
I'm serious.
So I'm gonna sing a song
by one of my favorite bands,
Luna, and also
one of Pete's favorite bands.
[Upbeat electric guitar music]
[scattered whooping
and indistinct conversation]
[Laughter]
Do I
Oh, do I
Remain
[scattered cheering]
In your mind
Only
To poison the love
[cheering]
That we find
Desires have misplaced,
our wishes are washes
The air is filled
with vibrations
I'm crying for you,
you're crying for me
From station to station
to station
-  Holding each other
tighter
The sky goes by, dear
Cries in the streets
I am the meat
in your heart
Open your sandwich to me
[cheering]
Open it up
Thank you.
- Nice song, Matt.
- Oh, Pete.
- Huh?
- Hey, I heard
about what you said to Susan,
about how you
wanted me fired, and... -
- I didn't... -
- No, no.
I want to say this.
Fuck you,
you two-faced prick.
I thought you were a cool guy.
But no,
you're just another asshole.
Don't talk to me.
Dick.
- Hey.
- You all right?
- Peachy, yeah.
- What's eating you?
- Happy Halloween.
- Hi.
- [Laughs]
I got us some shots!
- Whoo-ooh!
- Oh, yeah, shots.
- I heard it on the radio,
and it's about time
To play something like...
- Bet you wouldn't mind
getting in the middle
of those two, huh?
- Yeah, right.
- Wish me luck, buddy.
I'm going in.
- Go and get 'em.
- When I felt
that I needed to pump
It's on the radio,
on the radio, on the radio
And it sounded
a little something like this
- Oh, my God.
She's high-energy.
- Yeah, she is.
- Oh, we're gonna go
to the city this weekend, okay?
- Who?
- Susan and I.
We're gonna take Henry
to the Met.
- Oh, good, yeah,
I have work to do this weekend.
- Perfect.
-  And crown thy good with
Brotherhood.
- Yeah.
-  From sea to shining sea
[laughs]
Oh, beautiful...
- Good night, ladies.
- Bye.
- It was so nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you.
- Get home safe, okay?
- Hey, do you know
where Susan is?
- No.
- I really wanted
to say good-bye.
- Come on, it's okay.
- I'll be fine.
- What is she, like, a witch?
- [Moaning loudly]
[Both moaning
and shouting]
- Todd Kenner from Intellichoice
is coming tomorrow.
We don't get a lot of time
with him,
so I want everyone
on top of their game.
Okay?
Uh, Pete, do you
have the latest planograms?
- I do.
They're right here.
- Oh, don't forget
to check the vendor contracts.
If you need help with a vendor,
let me know.
I know how to talk to them.
- Okay.
- Dave, are the new computers
up yet?
- They're all up.
I'm still fixing the network.
- Oh, wow, Dave.
I didn't know
you had it in you.
Big applause.
Come on.
[Applause]
Doug,
I want to see a rough layout
for the store manager
presentation.
You can use some
of the old stuff for now,
but I want to see a new look.
The old stuff
looked like homework.
I want it to look like
a magazine,
emphasis on profit.
Understand?
- Whatever you say,
Susie Q.
- What did you call me?
- What?
Nothing.
- Yes, you did.
What did you call me?
- Susie Q.
I didn't mean anything.
- [Softly]
No.
I...
I think it's nice.
I think everyone
should have nicknames.
It's a great idea.
From now on,
yours is Assface.
So let's get those layouts done,
Assface.
- All right.
- "All right, Susie Q."
Right, Assface?
- Right, Susie Q.
- Thanks, Assface.
Oh, one more thing.
I negotiated a 30% discount
at the gym
across the street.
Our HMO
offers an additional 60%.
That leaves you
with only $10 a month to pay.
See Donna for the paperwork.
I expect
to see some of you there.
Thanks.
This was a great meeting.
Thanks, guys.
- Right, right.
- Weren't you
a little hard on Doug?
- Who?
- Assface.
- No.
What's he thinking,
calling me Susie Q?
He didn't give your old boss
any cute nicknames, did he?
- But you guys, you... -
- Drop it.
- Did you go
to the volvo dealership?
- Yeah,
I went for a test-drive.
We need a new car.
Ours keeps breaking down.
And besides,
I feel like such a loser
when I drop Henry off
in my crappy car.
- I thought you hate
all the moms at school
with their 4x4s.
- I do,
but volvos are different.
- Well, it's a hefty sum.
- Yeah, but look at... -
for the lease.
- Well, that's what
I'm looking at.
I thought
we'd pay off our mortgage.
- It was just an idea.
It's so nice
not to have to worry
about money so much.
- We have to pay off
our credit cards.
- Uh-uh.
I refinanced them.
Because
of your new income level,
we qualify
for a no-fee account,
so I got us a new card,
and I transferred
all the old ones onto that one,
and we get 0%
for three months.
- I'm gonna set my alarm
for 4:30.
I have so much work to do,
it's not even funny.
- So I guess
you don't want to get
all tired out.
- Mm-mm, I got to read
all this stuff.
- I stopped taking the pill.
What do you think?
- I think I don't have much say
in the matter.
- [Chuckles]
Don't blame me later.
Mm.
- Mommy!
- Oh, what's wrong, buddy?
- This is hot.
- Do you have a fever?
- [Grunts]
- I'm sorry, buddy.
I'm gonna go get you
some Tylenol.
I'll be right back.
- Hi.
- Oh, are those anthuriums?
- Uh...
Yeah.
- Todd, hi.
Pete Cozy.
- Pete, face to name.
- Can I get you a coffee?
- No, I'm set, thanks.
- Great.
- This place is great.
You guy are doing a great job
keeping a low profile.
- Yeah.
Thanks.
- I'd like to check out
the computers before we start.
- Okay,
I set you up in my office.
Please.
- Great.
Here's a hard copy
of my itinerary.
It's gonna be tight,
but I've got
a 3:30 flight tomorrow
that I've got to catch.
I'm speaking at UCLA,
and then I'm off to Japan.
And if I don't fit in
some family time,
my wife will kill me,
you know what I mean?
- Yeah.
I was up all night
with a sick kid.
- Oh, I know what it's like.
Last year,
I took my kids down the Amazon.
One of 'em came back
with a tapeworm.
I didn't sleep for a week.
This is perfect.
I think
you're gonna be very excited
with what we've put together.
Slater's was trying to compete
against the superstores
using EDLP modeling.
And of course,
you can't compete with that.
It's the same with Wolski's.
You can't beat them on price
every time
or go chasing
their specials pricing.
Wolski's needs something new
to compete.
What we're proposing
is predictive analysis
at a level unheard of
in this industry.
- This is what we were pushing
at Slater's,
but they just wouldn't listen.
- Well, to be fair,
this industry
seems particularly slow
to adapt to new trends,
but there
are big opportunities here.
Susan wanted big ideas.
- All right,
just so I can find some way
to translate all of this:
What we're seeing is,
we're better off
choosing select products
for big discounts
rather than
the hybrid incentives
we're using right now.
- Correct.
And the key
is which products we select.
We're not just
selling the product.
We are selling our image.
Each featured product
will announce to the customer
who we are,
what makes us special,
not just the product
but the kind of products.
We're not offering
special prices.
We are offering...
specialness.
- What about
our other competitors?
Did you get a chance
to review their strategies?
- Well, as far as we can tell,
none of the other shops
are doing anything like this.
It's very exciting.
- [Laughs]
- But there's a big qualifier.
It's all comes down
to implementation.
If you could
put all these strategies
into your stores tomorrow,
we'd be two years
ahead of everybody,
but realistically,
I know how long it takes
to work these things
through the chain.
Once the strategies
start to go into your stores,
your competitors
are gonna notice.
- So after two years,
there's almost no advantage.
- There's a declining function.
But when these strategies
go into your stores,
your market share
will grow 8% to 10%
within three months.
- 8% to 10%?
- Wow.
- After time,
these numbers decline steeply.
Stealing ideas is what passes
for R&D in this business.
- So has ACS spoken
to the vendors about all this?
- Pete, shh.
- I'm sorry.
I thought ACS was behind you
on this.
- It's complicated.
- You're so happy
to go to work these days.
- I know.
I just... -
I feel better about it now,
like what I'm doing
might actually have some value.
- Pricing groceries?
- I joined the gym
near the office,
thought I'd start going
during lunch.
Got you a membership too.
- [Scoffs]
I'm getting fat, huh?
- No.
It was only 10 bucks.
- When am I gonna have a chance
to go to the gym?
- You just got to make time.
Susan goes
at 5:00 in the morning.
- Susan doesn't have kids.
- You're kidding me!
That Cartwright!
Jesus Christ!
Pete Cozy!
Someone from ACS
got wind that we were using
Slater's strategies
from Intellichoice.
I don't know how, but now
they want to sideline us.
They want us to try out
our strategies
at one of their stores
and see how they fly.
- Isn't that normal,
to see how things work out?
- Fuck that!
No, I'm not gonna sit around
and let Stop & Shop
decide if our experiment
works for them.
What's the fucking point
of that?
Take what we have, go home,
and pack a bag.
[Sighs]
We'll figure something out
on the plane.
Donna?
Bennington will get this.
- Bennington, the CEO?
- Yeah, who else?
- Where is that suit,
the one I wore to Jim's wedding?
- I don't think
it's gonna fit you.
- Can you just help me
find it?
- How come your old boss
never took you to L. A?
- I don't know.
I wasn't a vP then, I guess.
[Plane engine whooshing]
[Upbeat music]
- [sighs]
I mean, 8% to 10%,
how can they say no to that?
The problem is,
these supermarket guys
are all Luddites.
They all grew up
in the supermarket business.
I know who's blocking us too.
It's Cartwright.
- Who's he?
- CFO,
best friends with D'asarlo,
my boss at Slater's.
They used to give each other
hand jobs at the country club
while I was trying
to turn around their company.
Assholes.
[Engine revving]
[Elevator bell dings]
- Morning.
- Is that the only suit
you brought?
- Yes.
- Oh, my God.
Donna?
Uh, call Brioni
in Beverly Hills
and see what time
they open.
And try Bernini too.
10:00?
What about Brooks Brothers?
I don't know.
Fuck!
[Plane engine whooshing]
Where'd you get that suit,
anyway?
Did you think
we were going to a wedding?
- It's the only one I have.
- I don't know about you.
Just...
- [sighs]
- Stand behind a planter
or something.
- He'll see you now,
Miss Felders.
- You understood that we were
gonna try this out gradually.
- You gave me the authority
to do this.
- I know,
but it's complicated.
Maybe I can get the board
to put it in
a couple of more stores.
- No!
You've seen these numbers.
It's all or none.
- Well, now, that's not
going to happen, Susan.
Be realistic.
- Why did you hire me!
Why did you give me
this fucking job!
Why did you hire me!
8% to 10% increase in sales!
- Calm down, Susan.
- No.
I'm not calming down, Jack.
This has to go
in all our stores,
or I quit.
- This is a major operation.
L... -
And it doesn't help that
you're stealing Slater's ideas.
- They threw 'em away.
- I can't do it
without the board's approval.
- Okay, fine,
then let's go to the board.
Just let them hear our case.
- Well, at the monthly meeting,
I'll... -
- When's that?
- Next month.
- No way.
- I can't just summon the board,
chop-chop.
- Yes, you can.
When Ralphs made that
takeover bid last October,
the board met that afternoon.
Come on, Jack.
Work with me on this.
- L... -
- There's no reason to wait.
These strategies
are time-sensitive.
We're losing money.
8% to 10% increase in sales
in three months.
- Yeah, if it works.
- Well, we have to do
something.
What are you gonna do?
Are you gonna go in front
of the shareholders in October
with Slater's plan of EDLP?
- That's just... -
- And 2% growth rate targets
that he'll miss again?
Come on, Jack,
you knew what I was doing.
And I know you want to try this,
so what's stopping you?
- [Sighs]
All right, I will try
to get a board meeting together
for tomorrow.
I will help you with this,
but you,
you have to sell them on this.
- Yes.
- Yes?
- Thank you.
We have to get you
another suit.
You cannot go to the board
in that.
And a haircut.
- So what do you think?
- It's fucking great.
Here, try these on.
- It's $5,000.
- Yeah,
lucky you got a raise, huh?
- We can have the alterations
done this afternoon.
- $6,000?
- Almost $7,000,
and $300 for a haircut.
- [Scoffs]
How's it look?
- I don't know.
I think it looks a little gay.
[Scoffs]
- [Laughs]
Maybe that's a good thing.
I don't want any girls
looking at you in L.A.
- Well, you don't have to worry
about that.
I've been so busy,
I haven't even had time
to go for a swim in the pool.
- Good luck tomorrow.
- I love you.
[Sighs]
[Upbeat music]
? ?
[sighs]
- This is the difference between
retiring on a golf course
in the Bahamas
with your own pool and boat
or, you know, getting bought
out of a reverse mortgage
because you can't afford
to pay the doctor
to get your prostate removed.
I'll do most of the talking.
You sell the numbers.
I make the case.
You back it up.
- These strategies
were paid for by Slater's.
They were the property
of Slater's.
- I thought
we were all working for ACS.
Slater's is a banner under ACS
just like Wolski's.
They don't compete
against each other.
They aren't even
in the same part of the country.
I mean, what's good for Slater's
is good for Wolski's
is good for ACS.
- These strategies
weren't any good for Slater's.
- They may not have been great
for Slater's,
but Wolski's is losing money,
and we have to do something
about that.
- I don't understand how
you could afford Intellichoice
with the consulting budget
that you have.
- To tell you the truth,
I had to make some cuts.
- Yes, yes, cuts... -
Tony Gomes.
12 years at Wolski's, and you... -
you just threw him away.
- He was slacking.
- Yeah, well,
that's funny,
'cause I can't find
a single thing in the reports
saying that he was slacking.
He had seniority.
- He was making three times
what his peers were making.
Was he worth three times
one of them?
No.
Intellichoice has given us
some solid strategies
that we can start putting
in our stores in January.
- January?
At the managers' convention?
- Exactly.
- In five weeks?
- Yeah.
- How are you gonna translate
these statistical models
into strategies
the managers will understand
in five weeks?
- Well, uh, the statistics... -
- Excuse me, uh, Susan,
if I may.
First of all, the HP9726,
the scanning system
we put in all our stores
last year,
can handle this
behind the scenes.
- You have to retrain
the checkout people?
- No, no,
well, uh, the managers
will need a little bit
of training,
but that's mostly
just to understand
why we're doing this.
They already know
how to do these things.
The rest
is just shelving strategies
and scanning feedback,
really.
- On steroids.
- When are we gonna see
the results from this?
- Intellichoice indicates
an 8% to 10% increase in sales
in three months.
- Three months!
I mean, the only time
we see results like that
is when a Walmart opens
near one of our stores,
and then the results are bad.
- I just don't see
how you can do it.
No, personally, I mean,
that department you're running,
it doesn't have the people;
it doesn't have the expertise
to put that kind of plan
into action.
- The only thing wrong
with that department
was the leadership
that it was getting.
- Jim Grady
was an excellent manager,
and he was a personal friend
of mine.
- I've been in this business
my entire life,
and I've never seen a department
come together like this.
They were just waiting
for something
to get excited about!
- Okay, Susan, Pete,
we've heard
what you have to say,
and we'll let you know.
- Mr. Cozy, Mr. Bennington
would like to see you alone.
- Pete Cozy,
I wanted to meet you personally
before you
went back to New York.
Now, I know you're focused
on this project right now,
but when it's done,
I'd like to sit down
and have a chat,
maybe dinner.
Susan says that
you went to Dartmouth.
I have a daughter at Columbia.
- Oh.
- Education is the most
important thing in life.
You can have all the experience
in the world,
but without the foundation
of an education,
it just doesn't amount
to much.
- "Genius without education
is like silver in the mine."
- Indeed.
You're a family man,
aren't you?
- Yes.
- Happiest years of my life,
raising my kids.
- Great.
- I've always believed that
if you surround yourself
with the best people,
they force you to play
at the top of your game.
But Susan is a piece of work.
She was driving everyone crazy
at Slater's.
If I approve these strategies
of yours,
I'm gonna make
some important people angry.
Can your people
back in Long Island
really get this done
in five weeks?
- Susan can get anything done,
sir.
- I'm asking you.
- Um...
I believe
we can get it done.
- You're a good man, Pete,
honest.
I like that.
I'll stay in touch.
Send Miss Felders in.
- [Laughs]
Classic.
- Susan,
the board was...
mostly willing
to go along.
Now, you only have five weeks
to get this set up,
so I guess
you better keep going.
- No, I think he was talking
about giving me a job.
- Higher than vice president?
- I don't know.
- President?
- [Chuckles]
[Knock at door]
Oh, Susan's here.
I got to go.
I love you.
- Love you too.
- Hi.
I'm going out
with some friends.
Do you want to come?
What did Bennington say
to you?
- Well, he said that when
we're done with this project,
he wants to talk to me.
- Yeah, when these strategies
come out,
the headhunters
are gonna be all over you.
He wants to get you
under contract
before that happens.
[upbeat rock music]
Janis, Jake,
this is Pete.
- Hi, I'm Janis.
- He's the only cool guy
in the office, so be nice.
Hey, honey.
- Hey.
- You should see this place
they call Long Island.
It's totally nowheresville.
It's like the valley,
but the people
are pale and yucky.
The only place to eat
is Friday's.
The people are so unhealthy.
- So what do you do?
- I'm an artist.
- She runs a website.
- Just to pay the bills.
Did you always work
in supermarkets?
- Oh, no, no way.
I was working for this guy
in New York,
running his record label.
That fell apart,
so I needed another job.
- I know how it is.
- But I'm not planning
on doing that forever.
- Oh, yeah?
What are you gonna be doing,
Pete?
- Well, I'd like to try and get
back into the music business.
- Haven't you noticed
that the music industry is dead?
- Maybe at an indie label.
- It's dead.
- Okay, it's dead.
- I mean, how are you
gonna support Henry
running an indie label?
Pete's got the cutest kid.
Show 'em a picture.
- Ah, you don't want to see
a picture.
- Yeah.
- Come on, yeah.
- Aww.
- Look at him.
- Is that your wife?
- Ah, yep.
- She's pretty.
- Oh, shit.
- I heard you were in town.
- What are you doing here,
Ernie?
- I come here all the time.
What are you doing here?
So can I buy you a drink,
you know, for old time's sake?
- Uh, no.
How old is she?
- [Stammers]
She's young, okay?
It doesn't mean anything.
- Is she your girlfriend?
- Mm-mm.
Well, yeah, yeah.
[Stammers]
We're seeing each other.
Listen, can l... -
can we just... -
can we talk outside
for a minute?
- No.
- Yes.
- No way.
- Come on.
Come on, what the... -
what the fuck is your problem?
- Hey, Ernie,
leave her alone.
- Yeah, get over it already.
- Okay, you know what?
You guys know one side
of this story, okay?
She lies.
You lie.
You say one thing to my face.
You tell me you love me.
And then you tell everyone else
that I'm an asshole.
- You are an asshole.
- Hey, you know what?
Just come outside with me.
Come on.
- Ah, Jesus.
- Why don't you
leave her alone?
- Who the fuck are you?
- He's my new boyfriend.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- She give you crabs?
'Cause she gave me crabs.
- I did not give you crabs.
You gave me crabs!
Jesus Christ!
Fuck you!
- You know what?
I know... -
I know you still love me.
I do.
Oh, and your boyfriend
looks like a fag.
- Ugh, so sorry about that.
Jesus Christ.
[Indistinct conversation]
- Number 12, you said?
- Can you give me,
like, five... -
- What... -
Ernie, oh, my God.
- Get off her!
[Crunch]
- Oh, my nose!
You fucking dick!
[Upbeat music]
-  You are the treacle
in my pie
You are the splinter
in my eye
You make the ice melt,
the butter run
You make the ink stain,
you are the one
Sleep together,
the Milky Way
Sleep forever and a day
Lovely jewels
in joy designed
La, la, la, la
- Don't sleep with her,
or I'll tell Sara.
-  I am the local
I am express
- Whoo!
-  I am a tourist
in a summer dress
- Ow!
-  I am the night nurse,
I am the most
I am the visitor,
you are the host
Sleep together,
the Milky Way
Sleep forever and a day
Lovely jewels
in joy designed
La, la, la, la
- It's last call.
- No way.
- It's getting late.
- Well, we can raid the minibar
after this.
- Oh, come on.
I don't know.
- Oh, don't bag on me now,
Pete.
- [Grunts]
- You're such a good guy...
- Mm-hmm.
- Such a nice guy.
- Right.
- Why don't I ever meet
nice guys like you?
- What are you talking about?
You met me.
- Yeah, I met you.
- [Chuckles]
- Why don't you come upstairs
and impregnate me?
- [Chuckles]
[Soft music playing]
You're not serious.
- Yeah, I am.
- Well, you're drunk.
- So what if I am?
-  A plateful of promise,
a spoonful of...
- You know, I don't even
find you that attractive.
That's the weird thing.
- I know.
- But you're such a good guy.
You've got good genes.
You're a good father.
Your sperm works.
I'm tired of this stupid job
being my life.
I want to have a baby.
Come on.
You don't have to have anything
to do with it.
I won't tell Sara.
I just want your seed.
-  La, la, la, la
La, la, la-la, la-la
- No one will ever know.
I'll move back to L.A.
I just want to be a mother.
- You've given this
a lot of thought.
-  Brush me,
divide me in two
Drink me and drown me ?
- I'm not unattractive,
am I?
It's not like
you never thought about it.
- Don't do that.
- You're not crazy.
You're cool.
You like good music.
You're smart.
- Don't say I went to Dartmouth,
please.
- You went to Dartmouth.
[Whispers]
Come on.
I want a baby.
You know
I always get what I want.
-  La, la, la-la, la-la
La, la, la, la
La, la, la-la, la-la
La, la, la, la-la
La, la, la, la-la, la-la
?
[water running]
[airplane engine roaring
distantly]
- Oh, we're home.
You can't come in.
- Yep.
- Open the door.
Thank you.
- Oh, I envy you.
Look at that.
And she's pretty too.
Man, you're a bad boy.
[Chuckles]
Wow, thanks!
- Mmm.
You smell like perfume.
- I know.
Susan hugged me at the airport.
She was covered in it.
- [Laughs]
I missed you.
- I missed you too.
- I can't believe how great
your job is going.
I mean, moving to L. A?
God, that would be so sweet.
[Soft electric guitar music]
- Oh.
[Grunts]
[sighs]
-  Oh, her eyes appear
And it always is
- [sighs]
-  And it always is again
[grunts]
-  Oh
Oh
- Hey.
- Hey, nice haircut.
- Hey, you too.
- Hi, everybody.
You will all be pleased to hear,
I've gotten authorization
to double
your Christmas bonuses.
[Cheers and applause]
- Whoo!
- That's what I'm talking about.
- You're gonna have to work hard
for this money, though.
The January manager's convention
is in five weeks.
- Whoa, whoa.
Five weeks?
- What?
- I know
it's not a lot of time.
- Yeah, no,
it's literally impossible.
- Don't say that.
Jack Bennington
has taken a personal interest
in our strategies.
He wants to meet the team.
Pete's going to show him
around the office next week.
We have to stay focused.
- So we want
to start communicating
with the managers now,
so they know what to expect
for the convention.
Doug, we're gonna need stats
on each of the product lines
that Intellichoice
cooked up for promotions.
Lila, you're gonna draft
a newsletter
for each one
of these managers,
just as a way
of preparing them.
- Yeah, and remember,
there's nothing that
store managers hate more
than getting weird instructions
from management.
It has to make sense to them.
So what we're looking for
is simplicity, clarity, results.
Okay?
- Okay.
- I'll leave you guys
to your work.
- No way.
- Ridiculous.
- What's it feel like
being perky?
Like, what does that feel like?
- Pete, can I see you
in my office?
- Yeah.
- [Tapping]
[Soft music]
? ?
- [moans and gasps]
[Panting]
- Todd Kenner
is on line three.
- My God.
- Yeah.
- [Sighs]
Hey, Todd, what's up?
There's just
some software thing going on.
Well, last I heard,
HP was taking care of it.
Hold on a second, Todd.
Do you need anything else?
- No.
- Okay, thanks, Pete.
Hey, Todd.
[Phone beeping]
[Line ringing]
- Hey, Susan,
how are you doing?
- Uh, I'm fine.
What's up?
- We just hadn't talked
in a while, and... -
- I know, I know,
but it's really not a good time.
Can I call you?
- Yeah, okay.
I'll talk to you later.
Bye.
- Hey, so that guy
who called last night,
Bobby McCain?
He said
he's setting up a label.
He's got financing
and a couple of bands,
and he wants me to run it.
- Really?
- Uh-huh.
So I'm thinking
I'm gonna meet him for lunch
on Saturday in the city,
but I don't want Susan
to know about it.
So if you talk to her,
please don't mention anything.
- Pete.
- Hey.
- [Chuckles]
- How you doing, buddy?
- Good, man.
- It's good to see you.
[Chuckles]
Hey, what happened to you?
- What?
- You got a haircut.
- I just... -
I got a corporate job.
- Not EMI, I hope,
fucking broke assholes.
- Yeah.
Uh, no, ACS.
You've never heard of them.
- See, that's why
I wanted to talk to you.
I was out partying
with Brian Specht.
- Mm-hmm.
- You remember Specht?
- Yeah, of course.
- [Laughs]
Fucking asshole.
And we got to talking,
and I told him my whole plan,
'cause, see, I need somebody
to run the business side
of the operation.
- Mm-hmm.
- 'Cause you know
I'm no good with business.
Come on.
I am no good with business.
And so he said
you were looking for something.
Are you?
- Yeah, absolutely, sure.
- Cool.
- Yeah.
- Because you know why?
'Cause it's all
fucking happening.
- So how did it go?
- The money was lame.
I'm not 20 anymore.
- When you were 20,
they didn't pay you anything.
- I got to be honest with you.
I don't think
he has his shit together.
- Dinosaur song.
Dinosaur song.
Dinosaur song!
- [Groans]
You better put it on.
- Dinosaur song!
[Bouncy music]
-  We are the dinosaurs
marching, marching
We are the dinosaurs
What do you think of that
marching, marching
We are the dinosaurs
We make the Earth flat
We stop and eat our food
when we're in the mood
on the ground
We stop and take a rest
over in our nest
We stop and take a rest,
and then you'll hear us say
[phone ringing]
- Hey, sweetie, I'm sorry.
I fell asleep on my desk.
- I stayed up waiting for you.
- Come on.
I told you not to do that.
- I was worried.
- Well, why didn't you
call me then?
- I don't know.
I didn't want to bother you.
I know you're doing
what you have to do.
I love you.
- I love you too.
Yeah, I'll call later.
- Ah.
I went to your office,
but you were sleeping.
- Were you here all night?
- Yeah.
Why?
Do I look bad?
- No.
You look great.
- Thank you.
[Both chuckle]
- So tell me what's gonna happen
when all this is over.
- Bennington's gonna move me
back to L.A.
He's gonna put me in charge
of national strategies.
- He told you that?
- No.
But he knows I want the job.
- Mm-hmm.
- What choice does he have?
I might take you with me.
- Good morning.
- Good morning, Doug.
- Get ready for Bennington
in a couple hours.
- Mm, that's a great pot
of coffee.
- Jack Bennington.
- Matt Davis.
I've been here four years.
I work in advisory projects.
- Ah, nice to know,
nice to know.
Keep up the good work.
- Sure.
I will.
Thank you.
- Douglas Cain,
Jack Bennington.
- Doug Cain, Doug Cain.
How are you?
- [Laughs]
I'm very well, thanks.
- If you need stats,
I'm your guy.
That's what I've been doing
for you.
- Pete.
- I've been proud to do it.
And I'm all about
making a difference
in this company.
- Mr. Bennington
wants to take me, you, and Sara
out to dinner tonight.
I made a reservation for 7:00.
- Okay.
I'll call Sara.
[Laughter]
- No, no, I can't.
- Try it.
Please, please try it.
It's so good.
- I'm on a diet.
I can't.
- You will be so sad
if you don't taste this.
- Oh...
- [laughs]
Right?
It's amazing.
- Yes, it is.
So how are we coming
with the organics, Pete?
- Oh, pretty well.
It's just a shelving issue
at this point,
so it's not like the managers
won't know how to do it.
- What's that about?
- Organics have
a special section in our store,
but Pete is telling us
we should put our organics
next to our regular products.
- Well, what difference
does that make?
- Organics cost more,
so generally,
the feeling has been
to keep them
in their own department.
You keep the price image down,
also offering some quality.
- Our research shows that
organics have come a long way.
It's a trend change.
It's exactly the kind of thing
that ACS
is the last to figure out.
So it's a big deal for us.
- Essentially,
we make more on the organics.
- Most chains
have their own line of organics.
I mean, try getting Cartwright
on board with that.
- Indeed.
Now, are you thinking
of having any more kids?
- I don't think so.
- Yeah.
- Oh.
- Come on.
- Well, excuse... - uh, hello.
- We've been trying.
- Ah.
- But Pete was an only child,
and so he doesn't understand
why Henry would want
a brother or a sister.
- Ah.
Well, I came from a big family,
and I had a big family.
So I guess you're right.
- Oh, I have to take this.
[Cell phone ringing]
- This is just a thought,
Sara,
but how would you feel
about moving to Los Angeles
with your family?
It's a nice place
to raise kids.
- Oh, I mean, we are not
attached to Long Island.
- Well, I've been trying
to find a place for Pete
in our national office.
We know
you're a talented young man,
good education.
You're a good guy,
an honest guy.
I'd hate to see you
wasting your time in...
well, in a regional office.
We'll find you something.
- Did I miss something?
- No, no, no.
- Really?
- No.
- [Clears throat]
- The motherfuckers at national
are screwing us up the ass.
They're turning the vendors
against us.
I saw the memos.
They don't want us
to make the deadline.
- We're just gonna
have to stop relying on them
and do this ourselves.
Tomorrow's Christmas Eve.
We're gonna get screwed
if we don't take care of this.
- Matt had an idea.
- What?
- Yeah, okay, so we only have
a week and a half left.
Even though most of us
are gonna work
through Christmas,
we still got to deal with HP
and Intellichoice closing
and so is communications.
And the store managers
are doing their whole
Christmas overtime thing, so...
- The bottom line is,
we're not gonna make it.
- What are you talking about?
- It's true.
There just aren't enough hours
in the day.
There isn't enough time
to get it all done.
But if we were to cut
just two, three
of the strategies,
we'll be able to finish
everything else free and clear.
Otherwise, we're screwed.
- Does Susan know about this?
- Well, we thought that maybe
you could talk to her.
You know, you seem to have
a special relationship with her.
- What the fuck
is that supposed to mean?
- I don't know, Pete.
What does it mean?
- Okay, it just means
someone has to talk to her... -
- This is bullshit!
Well, we can't just cut
our strategies now!
I can't believe you guys.
We've been busting our balls
here for three months,
and you just want to give up?
- All we're saying is,
we can't get a few
of these strategies ready.
- No way!
I'm not gonna just sit here
and watch you tell Susan
that this can't be done.
I mean, do you know the kind
of pressure that she's under?
Do you know that
she stuck her neck out for us?
No.
No, what we're doing here
is kicking ass.
And I don't care
if we have to stay here
all fucking week
for the next week and a half
to get this done,
or maybe even two weeks.
We don't know how long
it's gonna take,
but we are gonna do this.
- All we are saying is,
we can't get
two of these strategies ready.
- Well, why the fuck not?
Huh?
I mean, you and Pete
understand this stuff.
I know that because you got me
to understand it.
So can we just stop all the talk
about cutting strategies
and apply ourselves?
- She's right.
We can get this done.
- Hey.
Susan wants to see everyone
out in the office
for a Christmas toast.
- I'd like to share
this letter from Mr. Bennington
with all of you.
"In my years,
I've never seen a team
"work so hard
and do such excellent work.
"These presentations
mark a new beginning
"for Wolski's, ACS,
and a new direction
in this industry."
Blah, blah, blah.
"You are all
the best of the best."
[Sniffs]
I just want to say,
I've never seen
a group of people
come together like this.
Now, I want you
to take Christmas off.
Go home.
See your families.
You're gonna need a lot of rest
before next week.
Louisville will be hard work,
but we can do it.
Merry Christmas.
Cheers.
All: Cheers.
- Merry Christmas.
- Happy holidays.
- You guys blow me away.
- Ah, no, we can't eat it.
It's too big.
[Imitates explosions]
Turning into transformer...
[imitates explosions]
[Knock at door]
- Hey.
- Why don't you grab that?
I'm gonna put on a sweater.
I'm freezing.
- Arr, arr!
I'll be right back... -
oh, he's gonna eat the crayon.
- [Babbles]
- Hi.
- I'm not staying.
- What's going on?
- I wanted to drop off
a present for Henry.
- Oh, well, come in.
Wait, you don't have plans
for Christmas?
- I was working, but then...
I got really depressed.
I meant to give this to Pete
at work.
- Come in, come on.
Have a drink.
- Can we open it?
- Yes.
- Yay.
[Babbles]
A Barbie thing.
- It's Barbie.
- Yeah.
- Isn't she pretty?
- I don't like it.
- What do you mean,
you don't like it?
She's a woman.
- I don't like women.
- You don't?
Why not?
- Because.
- Because why?
Do you like me?
- Yeah.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- Sit down next to me.
- Oh.
- You guys
are so great together.
You're so down to earth,
honest.
What's the point of my life?
- You're doing a good job.
- Fuck work.
Who really gives a shit
if Wolski's
gets a few more customers?
[Laughs]
- I thought it was important.
- You know
what I'm talking about.
You know what I like
about Pete?
He really knows me.
He listens.
He notices things.
It's like, I don't even
have to say anything,
and he knows
what I'm thinking.
- We really appreciate
everything you've done for him.
It's...
- Mm-hmm.
- Really changed our lives.
- Yeah, well, that's not what
I'm talking about.
- Pete, why don't you
go put Henry to bed?
And I will get some sheets
for the couch.
- Yeah.
- Thank you.
- Come here.
[Groans]
- But I don't have to do bed.
- Okay.
- She's going to sleep.
Come in here.
- Let me just say good night.
- Don't worry.
You'll see her in the morning.
- Bah!
- What the fuck?
[Whimpers]
[Moans]
Don't do that.
Oh, God.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
You guys obviously
can't handle this stuff.
We have to get ACS
to help you.
- The vendors
are calling ACS to pressure us.
- That's why we need
their help.
- Yeah, but... -
- The vendors
think they can muscle us
because they
aren't taking us seriously.
We have to use ACS
to talk to them.
- Yeah, l... -
- No, just do it.
Then you'll understand,
all right?
How's your stuff
coming along, Pete?
- Good.
We'll be all right.
- I mean,
what do you have to show me?
- Uh, I don't...
have anything to show you.
I was just, you know,
hoping you might cut me
a little slack.
- Why would I do that?
This is a progress meeting.
I need to see progress.
- Okay, uh,
we're making progress.
- I don't need a meeting to know
that you're doing something.
I need a meeting to see
what it is that you're doing.
- What is your problem?
- Just bring it in my office
in an hour, okay?
In an hour.
Go.
- [Sighs]
- There's no reason
for you to be here.
[Knock on door]
- Hi, I'm sorry I didn't
bring this to the meeting.
I was, um... -
I was out of line.
- You lied to me.
- What?
You never went to Dartmouth.
- Did you?
- Yes, I went to Dartmouth.
- Mr. Bennington was planning
on offering you a job in L.A.
As is standard procedure,
they hired a private detective
team to check you out.
Dartmouth
has no record of you.
- Well, they didn't check
properly.
I did go.
- I thought
that might be the case,
so I called them myself.
They have no record of you.
- I didn't graduate.
I went for two years,
and then I left.
My father lost his job.
I couldn't afford it
anymore, so...
- You said you graduated
on your résumé.
- Yeah, I needed the job.
It was not a big lie.
- It's a huge lie.
- Nobody cared
until you came along.
- But I did care.
I do care.
It's important to me.
- What are you gonna do?
- I don't know what I can do.
They want me to press charges.
- What?
Look, I didn't know
it was that big of a deal.
- It's a huge fucking deal,
okay?
You let me down!
I thought you were perfect!
You didn't even look so bad
once you put on a suit.
Now you're just another asshole
who cheats on his wife
and lies about
how smart he is.
- You told me
all you wanted was a baby.
- Well, it didn't work.
I'm not pregnant.
- Well, Sara is.
- That's great.
That's fucking great.
I guess that's my fault too.
Get away from me.
Hey, Donna, send them in.
[Phone clicks]
[Sniffs]
I'll do what I can to stop them
from pressing charges,
but your work here
is no longer tenable.
You should just take your jacket
and leave.
You can't take our work,
obviously.
I have to remind you,
you signed
a confidentiality contract.
- That's it?
- Don't make this any harder
than it already is.
[Somber music]
? ?
- What are we going to do?
- I'll just... -
I'll get another job.
- Yeah,
but what about the car?
What about the mortgage?
- Don't we have money
saved up?
- We have some money
in our checking account, yes,
but we still owe,
like, $28,000 on the visa.
- Bobby, hey, it's Pete.
I know it's been a while.
I was just wondering
if you found anyone
to run your label.
- Oh, yeah.
You know Jim Sall?
- Yeah, I know him.
- The guy's doing a great job.
- I know, Dad.
We just need a little
to get us through
the next couple months.
[Sighs]
He is not that bad.
- Hey, Doug,
just wondering
how the project was going.
How did it go
in Louisville?
- What do you care, man?
- Well, I had a lot
invested in that,
wanted to know
how it was turning out.
- Let me tell you something.
You didn't get fired
because of that thing
on your résumé.
The job that Bennington
was gonna give you
was the job
that Susan wanted.
He was gonna put you
in national marketing at ACS.
Susan found out about it.
- No way.
How do you know that?
- I just know it, okay?
You have to move on.
Strength, brother.
- [Sighs]
[Phone buzzing]
There's a job in the city.
They're hiring
at Arista Records.
- How much does it pay?
- $30,000,
but it's in the music business.
- [Scoffs]
There's no future
in the music business.
- They're hiring.
- $30,000?
- You could get a job.
- I'm pregnant.
Who's gonna hire me?
- I'd hire you.
- [Chuckles]
One more bite of pasta.
- No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
- Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes yes!
- No, no, no, no, no.
- Is Daddy gonna eat
all your pasta?
- Oh, boy, lucky Daddy.
[Phone ringing]
Don't answer it.
It's a creditor.
- Eat all my pasta.
- Yeah, I'm gonna eat
all your pasta.
- Susan Felders
gave me your number.
- Did you eat all of my food?
- I work for a company
called Advantage One.
We're an executive
recruiting agency,
and I'd really like
to talk to you
about your plans
for the future.
I'm in L. A.
- I want to get out of... -
- Hi, sorry, yeah.
- [Shushing]
- Uh, this is Pete Cozy.
Yeah.
- I want to get out
of the seat.
- One sec.
What did he say?
- He said that
with my experience,
he thinks
he could find me a job.
- Well, what kind of job?
- Marketing, supermarkets,
same kind of thing
I've been doing,
maybe even
with my own department.
He said there were a couple
of jobs on the West Coast
he would love
to send me out for,
even with what happened.
- Did he give you any idea
how much these jobs would pay?
- $100,000 plus benefits
and year-end bonus.
- Jesus.
That is great news.
- I told him
I'd think about it.
- What?
Why?
- Because I don't want
to do this my whole life.
The only thing I've ever wanted
to do with my life
is work in music.
I may not have made
that much money,
but I was happier.
- What are you talking about?
What difference does it make
if you market music
or groceries?
- It makes a difference to me.
- $30,000 a year
for an entry-level position?
- No, no way.
I'm too old for that.
I think I'm gonna start
my own label.
- [Groans]
- I've learned a lot
over these past years.
- How are you gonna pay for it?
- I'll draw up a business plan.
I'll get loans,
an investor.
- Who's gonna give you a loan?
We're not even gonna make
next month's mortgage payment.
- So an investor.
- My dad is not gonna give you
any more money.
- I'm not talking
about your father.
Look, if we sold this house,
we would still make money,
even after we paid
the mortgage.
- What are we gonna live on?
- What do other people do,
huh?
They get by.
We can live in a small apartment
in the city for a while.
I know you're not any happier
here than I am.
- God, it's not like any
of those labels you worked on
ever took off
or made any money.
- Well, I didn't know then
what I know now.
- Did you sleep with Susan?
- What?
No.
- It all changed
when you came back from L.A.
I know you slept with her.
- Why are you waiting till now
to bring this up?
- Oh, God, I feel sick.
- Could it be that
you were okay with it
as long as I was making
good money?
- You are so selfish.
How can you say that?
Oh, my God.
- Sara.
- We have a child,
and I am pregnant.
Why would you do this to me?
- Stop it.
You know I love you.
- What am I doing?
I cannot believe
that I am pregnant.
- Let's talk about this.
Listen to me... -
- You stay away from me.
- No.
Sara, come on.
- No!
- Mommy!
- Sara... -
Henry.
[Sighs]
- [Retches, coughs]
- It's all right.
It's okay, buddy.
No, it's okay.
Hey, come on, it's all right.
- I don't want to look
at you.
- Come on,
open up the door.
- I'm done.
- Sara, please.
Please.
Sara!
Come on,
let's talk about this.
[Voices fade]
[Soft music]
-  Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh
Ooh, ooh, ooh
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh
Sun comes up
Sun goes down
Tired old world
Spins round and round
Nothing
chills the summer
And my love comes in...
[music fades]
- Henry.
Henry
Hey, hey, hey.
What are you doing?
You can't run away like that,
come on.
- Pete.
- Susan.
What are you doing here?
- Hi.
Uh, I'm shopping.
I live around here.
- Is that yours?
- Yeah, his name is Syd.
Henry found me.
- So you moved back here.
- Um, yeah,
I'm head of marketing at ACS,
brought Lila and Donna
here with me.
Yeah, it's cool.
- Susie, plain or butter?
- Um, both of 'em.
Do you remember Pete, Ernie?
We're married.
- Oh, hey.
- Congratulations.
[Cell phone ringing]
- Ah, I have to take this.
This is an important call.
- Okay.
- Cute baby.
Looks like you.
- Yeah, you think so?
- I'd better get going.
Come on.
I'll see you around.
- Yeah, later.
Who was that weird guy?
Oh, I'm gonna eat you.
- I think so.
- I want to go on a big plane.
- You want to go
on a big plane?
- Yeah.
- [Groans]
Hello.
- Henry?
Hi, you guys.
How was the supermarket?
Good?
- We saw Daddy's friend.
- Really, who?
- Oh, just someone from work.
- Hey, I was thinking
we could take a walk
down to the beach.
- Uh, maybe you
can take them down,
and I'll just meet you.
I still have some work to do.
- Oh, it's Sunday.
- I know.
What do you want me to say?
- All right.
I love you.
- I love you too.
- Mm.
- Bye, cutie.
- Say,
"See you later, Daddy."
- Bye, cutie.
- See you later.
- Bye.
- Hey, Henry, let's go.
[Upbeat music]
-  Iceman, iceman,
candy man, and sandman
All the things
I wanted for
Someone else took them
Lonely in a new shirt,
lonely watching baseball
If I had to do it all again,
I wouldn't
Throw it all away
I want a holiday
Marigold and tangerine,
I have dreamed an empty dream
? I am slow
and you are too
Someone tell me what to do
Lonely on a Wednesday,
lonely on a Friday
If I had to do it all again,
I wouldn't
Throw it all away
I want a holiday
I'm tired
of having no future
And I'm tired
of pushing my luck
of waiting for the endgame
Watching the stars
turn black
Throw it all away
I want a holiday
Correction and syncronization R.O.D.
Watch any video online with Open-SUBTITLES
Free Browser extension: osdb.link/ext