Listen to me, Saaz.
Where are you going?
Try to understand, Saaz.
Why are you being so stubborn?
Let's go back to Kolkata.
Your visa is in process.
You'll fly off to USA soon.
I've made all the arrangements
in Berkeley.
Why waste your time here?
Dad, the police might not find
any abnormalities.
But take it from me.
I'm sure Mom and Salamat Uncle
have been murdered
- That's ridiculous...
- Even Alap thinks so.
Trust me.
That murderer is definitely somewhere
near Anandagarh.
And he's up for a bigger mission.
He deserves to be punished.
I can't run away like a coward
until he is punished.
Saaz...
please listen to me.
This might put your life at risk.
- Bahadur said so too.
- I don't care what others say.
I can't just escape.
I've never disobeyed you and Mom.
But please...
don't ask me to do this.
I can't keep running away
from my guilty conscience
for the rest of my life.
I can't, Dad.
Saaz, liste...
Saaz.
Greetings, ma’am.
Huh?
How's your mother?
Is she okay now?
Yes, ma'am.
You could've stayed with her
for a few more days.
Since you said she stays alone.
She asked me to come back.
Because I was missing out
on rehearsals.
Very well.
Rest for a while.
- We'll rehearse later.
- Okay, ma'am.
Hmm.
- Ma'am.
- Yes?
The police commissioner in my village
asked me to visit the police station
when I get here.
I followed his instructions.
- Fine.
- Okay.
Come in, Bahadur.
- Did you repair the tabla?
- Yes.
Great.
It's good to see
you're back to normal.
- New student?
- Hmm?
Yes.
He has a wonderful voice.
But he's very poor.
With proper guidance,
he'll go a long way.
We need to find out
more about him.
Things started going wrong
since he came here.
The police are already investigating it.
Besides, seven other students
have been admitted with him.
Hmm.
Then all of them are suspects.
What's his name?
Naad Shankar... Das.
Naad Shankar Das.
(humming)
Hey!
Son of a b♪♪♪h!
Wait!
Stop!
Hey!
CURSE OF THE RUDRABINA
PART 2
Damn it!
Uff!
Alap.
Naad took the box and the disc.
With the disc!
Alap, he escaped.
Doesn't matter.
- What?
- He'll have to come back to me.
I'll kill that rascal!
- Bahadur Uncle.
- Yes?
Who is this Naad?
Someone from Rudrapur?
He killed my son and daughter.
And your sister?
Who killed your sister?
What do you mean?
Found this pen
at Master Kedar's farmhouse.
There's a symbol on the nib.
We saw the same symbol...
on Salamat Uncle
and Noor Aunty's dead bodies.
It's there on Naad's back as well.
How is Master Kedar
connected to this symbol?
We thought Master Kedar was like you,
a descendant of Madanti.
That maybe to protect himself...
he concealed his identity
and lived in Anandagarh.
But it seems
that he had other intentions.
What are you saying?
Bahadur Uncle...
please tell us what happened.
Did Grandpa want
to kill Grandma?
I don't know!
I don't know.
I don't know anything.
Please spare me!
Fine.
We'll let you go.
But let me make this clear.
I will get to the bottom of this.
Let's go, Shruti.
This solitude is painful
Make me yours
The burning candles call out
Put them out
Come let's explore each other
Will the night ever end
If we make love?
This solitude is painful
Make me yours
The burning candles call out
Put them out
Come let's explore each other
Will the night ever end
If we make love?
This solitude is painful
Make me yours
Your burning touch
Melts this fragile glass
I lose myself
In your passionate glance
I give in To your loving touch
The stars hold the secret
To your passionate glance
This solitude is painful
Make me yours
The burning candles call out
Put them out
Come let's explore each other
Will the night ever end
If we make love?
This solitude is painful
Make me yours
Are you sure it was this symbol?
Yes, brother.
Remember what you told me?
To let you know
if I see someone with this symbol.
What does this symbol mean?
Mumtaz.
Kedar Mishra is not a nice man.
He wants to kill you.
- What?
- Yes.
What are you saying?
It can't be true.
I don't believe you...
Ask Grandfather
if you don't believe me.
But don't worry.
Nobody can harm you
as long as I'm alive.
Hail Rudrabhairav!
What's the matter, Naad?
Why is it taking so long
to finish the work?
I request you to have patience.
I'm on it.
Huh! Are you?
Or has the Nawab's granddaughter
made you forget your resolve?
Hmm?
Naad, I sent you here
to find Madanti's descendants
and finish them.
I arranged for Nawab Amanat Khan
to give you music lessons.
What for?
Only so that you can stay here.
Your suspicion is baseless..
I was the one who found
and killed Madanti's son Abdul.
That was long back.
What's taking you so long
to find Abdul's descendants?
I'm almost done.
I will bring the corpse before you soon.
Listen, Naad.
You wanted freedom from your life as Naad
after marrying Mumtaz.
I have not objected to that.
But if you don't finish the job...
I'll destroy your family.
I give you seven more days.
Proceed.
Rascal!
You want to kill my sister?
I'll finish you before that...
You better not reveal
anything you heard.
Or there'll be consequences.
Please come, Rudrabhairav.
He was Abdul's only son.
He was in hiding.
I've found out
that Abdul does not have anymore children.
Madanti's lineage ends with him.
Please release me now.