- [Cell doors clanging]
- BRAITHWAITE: Hey! You!
I'm onto you.
I know all about you.
MORGAN:
I'm sick to death
with people talking about me
behind my back.
BUFFY: I'm gonna write to
the home secretary about this.
OFFICER:
Lockup! Lockup!
SNOOPER: There's deals
going down all the time.
Every day.
Every night.
MAN:
What's a fax machine?
BUFFY: Put that bastard
on the wing, and I'll kill him.
JACKSON:
Bastards.
Put it down!
Now!
[Singsong voice]
Ja-a-a-son!
[Grunts]
You committed rape.
I don't remember.
I was stoned.
Oswald Snooper has asked
to see you.
No. I'm sorry.
I don't want to see him.
And I don't think is the time
or the place even to discuss it.
WATTS: Your mother's name
is Barbara, age 43.
Sister called Diana, age 6.
Address...
44 Elmsworth Crescent.
Officer Brent.
[Keys jingling]
Yes!
[Indistinct conversations]
Right!
Wing governors will split you
into groups,
so you can keep moving
along the corridor.
If you've not got a file...
Mavis!
We've allocated the boardroom
for A and B Wings,
the staff room to C and D Wings,
and E and F Wings
to the recreation room!
Mavis, have you got
any more files?
Oh, I've run out.
- I'll have to xerox some more.
- I think so.
I have to call my solicitor.
It is an emergency.
I have my trial coming up!
[Grunts]
Oi!
I know my rights,
and I have every right
to make a phone call!
I am a remand prisoner!
Take it up
with the wing governor.
Take it up with you, mate.
You want to take it up with me,
eh?
Well, come on, Jason.
If you want to make
a phone call,
you put your name down
on the list.
- [Water splashing]
- Oh.
Sorry.
Don't push your luck,
you bastard.
I just want to make
a phone call.
I'm all for making one wing
drug free,
but as we are short
of cell space at the moment,
to reshuffle the inmates
and also to arrange a detox unit
is...
Oh, I don't know.
Well, it won't work.
She wants them to be put on
the wing at their own request.
It could mean it'd end up
half empty.
"Any prisoner found
in possession of narcotics
or under the influence
of narcotics
will have an alternative
to punishment."
Like a skiing holiday
in Colorado?
Very funny.
"One... agree to the detox unit.
Two... lose all privileges."
"Ministerial requested
all phone cards to be withdrawn.
Eh?
She's got to be joking!
They'll never agree to that.
It's bloody ridiculous.
[Indistinct conversations]
Oi!
Will you shut up?!
[Talking stops]
[Man coughs]
What page are you on?
[Telephone ringing]
Morning, Rose.
What's the problem?
[Sighs]
I've run out of files.
- The Xerox machine's acting up.
- Morning.
Morning.
I've called the engineer.
He'll be two hours.
That lawyer, Mr. Turnbull,
is due at 2:00.
And Simon Lennox called twice.
But medical.
He's not been eating.
He's not sleeping.
Look.
I examined him, and he told me
he wanted a sex change,
which is why I referred him back
to you.
Morning.
Could I see you a moment?
I'm a bit busy at the moment.
Could you have a word
with Mavis?
Could you see what she wants
and fit her in between meetings?
Look. I just need five minutes
of her time this morning.
[Mid-tempo music plays]
[Exhales sharply]
This is his brother coming now.
- It's Colin Watts, right?
- Mm-hmm.
Oh, sorry I'm late.
Look. Sorry about that.
You all right, Mum?
I'm sorry. I got...
OFFICER:
There's his mother.
- Take the back. All right.
- Sister.
And girlfriend.
Ah. She looks about ready
to drop.
[Breathing heavily]
The police are here
about the escapee.
I've still not got it working.
Uh, Simon Lennox, please.
- Have they found him?
- What?
The police.
Have they picked up Kevin Watts?
Oh, I don't know.
Ms. Bullock said she needed
to talk to you about Ms. Purvis,
but she wouldn't say
what it was about.
The pianist.
Simon?
It's me.
Um...
Two minutes.
Welcome home.
[Laughs]
Yeah.
Oh, no, no, no.
No. I'll pick up anything
we need on the way home.
Yeah, yeah.
I'll cook.
[Laughs]
Okay.
All I'm saying is if you remove
prisoners' privileges
on a snakes-and-ladders basis,
it's gonna make our lives
difficult.
All right.
The withdrawal
of all prison phone cards.
Anybody been listening
to the recordings lately?
The bastard Keith Smith
has been making threats
to a prosecution witness.
JACKSON:
What about this suggestion?
Extra enforced exercise periods.
You start making some of those
old lags do a couple press-ups,
- and they're gonna bloody riot.
- [Laughter]
The exercise program is directed
mostly at younger offenders.
Paragraph 3.
More confrontational therapy
programs.
Now, this lot costs,
and we've got cutbacks as it is.
That's exactly
what I was trying to say.
And she doesn't mention if we're
getting extra funding.
It all boils down
to extra hard work for us.
I haven't got one.
A file.
JACKSON: We're already doing
long hours at the same wage.
Everything here is aggravation
for us.
They've got three psychologists
working for the inmates,
bugger-all for us.
You got any extra report files?
Only we've only got two.
- Aw!
[Cellphone rings]
Yeah.
COLIN:
Kev? She's in hospital.
Is she okay?
She's fine.
She's all right.
You gonna make a video
of the birth.
I'm hiring a camera.
Sixty quid.
What?
- Deposit you've got to put down.
- [Static]
Colin?
- Hello?
- Kev?
[Footsteps, wood creaking]
Kev?
You there, Kev?
Tell her I love her.
Yeah.
All right.
[Down-tempo music plays]
All right, all right.
Let's stick to what we're
supposed to be discussing.
What, the penalty?
JACKSON: Where in this
is what she intends doing
- to make our life easier?
- Right.
Where in all this is...
Is there more security,
more protection when we get
a shortage of staff, eh?
It's down to our good will that
this place still ticks over.
I agree.
I agree with Curtis.
Barfield is only running
because of our good relationship
with the inmates.
It's like every nick,
you start up a tough new regime.
No, no.
Dave, j-just hang on a second.
So consensus is Ms. Hewitt
wants to get tough,
but we'll be the ones
taking the brunt of it all.
- That's right.
- Absolutely.
Well, I'm bloody for it, mate.
- MAN: Oh, come on!
- Come on!
- No!
- [Telephone ringing]
- Thanks, Mavis.
[Door closes]
Kevin Watts' cellmate,
prisoner Barry Jones,
was released two weeks
after the escape occurred.
Do you have an address?
He did an extra two weeks
for assisting Kevin Watts,
but he denied
playing any part in it.
Now, you did interview him,
and I'm not allowed to disclose
any personal information
regarding the prisoner.
I was just wondering if there
was any further information
he could give us.
The escapee Kevin Watts'
girlfriend has gone into labor,
but family says Kevin
hasn't made any contact.
Do you think he'll turn up
at the hospital?
Yes.
According to his cellmate,
Kevin only wanted to get out
of Barfield
to be present at the birth
of his child.
We're waiting for him
if he shows.
TULLY: So we'd appreciate
any further information...
- Excuse me.
- BULLOCK: this afternoon.
Ms. Bullock.
I'm sorry to interrupt,
but it's with regard
to Ms. Purvis
and prisoner Wilfred Samuels.
Just a moment.
Ms. Purvis?
Pianist.
She's been playing the piano
for the "Mikado" rehearsals,
and I have reason to believe
that she is now visiting
a prisoner.
It's Wilfred Samuels.
Samuels.
I just think it should be
checked out... or he should.
- Morning.
All she knows is that he's
a lifer,
- and she became very upset...
- Is he in the files yet?
I'm still trying to bring up
some more copies.
The art department are using
the Xerox.
Just a minute.
Uh, thank you.
Mavis, can you contact
Barry Jones' probation officer?
He was in the same cell
as Kevin Watts.
BULLOCK:
But she's my responsibility.
If I have to find someone else
to play the piano, I will.
We're getting very close
to dress rehearsals.
I shall have a word
with Mr. Samuels on my rounds.
She's very naïve,
and I'm worried.
Ms. Bullock,
I said I will look into it
and then I will get back to you.
Now, excuse me, please.
Have they done
the security checks
on all the members of
the amateur dramatic society?
I don't know.
I've got a bit of a problem.
Could I use your Xerox?
I have enough to do
without chasing up
every single request I make!
[Door closes]
[Down-tempo music plays]
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
[Brake clicks, engine shuts off]
It's the grandmother's house.
She's housebound.
Uses a Zimmer frame.
This is car Oscar 010.
We're in position outside
85 Orpington Avenue.
Over.
[Doorbell rings]
[Birds chirping]
Gran?
It's Colin.
- All right, Gran. It's just me.
- Ah.
Yep.
Ms. Hewitt?
The, uh, area manager
just missed you.
He's, um,
he's a bit incapacitated.
So can you hang on for him?
He said he wanted to talk
to you about him.
What do you mean,
he's incapacitated?
He's late.
[Chuckles]
What happened?
JACKSON: You're not gonna
believe me, even if I told you.
- But...
- Shh, shh, shh.
- HEWITT: Good morning.
- Ms. Hewitt.
Oh, I'm so sorry about this.
I'll leave this in Ms. Hewitt's
office for you, Mr. Bunny, okay?
Ms. Hewitt, any word on me going
back on the wing yet?
It's under review.
How long will I have to wait?
Oh, just keep up
the good behavior.
I'll let you know.
BUNNY:
I'm, uh, I'm very skeptical
about taking such a risk
with him.
HEWITT:
I must at least try.
The cost of moving him
from one prison to another
is astronomical.
Twenty-eight prisons
in 18 months with police escort.
So, um, how did this happen?
Oh.
Karate.
I did a leg sweep, and...
[Chuckles]
I like to keep myself fit.
Well, in my job,
I think you should be able
to take care of yourself.
HEWITT:
Mm!
I'll just get some coal
from cellar, okay, Gran?
Right, Colin.
Is she okay?
She's still in labor.
HEWITT: These are your
commissions, Mr. Samuels?
SAMUELS:
Yes, Ms. Hewitt.
Inmates give me a photo.
I paint the portraits.
Christmas, birthdays...
You know.
Mm-hmm.
You're working with Ms. Bullock
on the musical?
Yes, miss.
I don't sing, so I'm doing props
and helping out
on stage management,
painting the scenery and...
HEWITT:
Helping Ms. Purvis.
Uh, I turn the sheet music.
Sometimes she has to play fast.
Can't turn the sheets, you see.
Ms. Purvis has also been
to visit you twice.
Yes.
And you've written to her.
Yes, Ms. Hewitt.
Mm.
Does she know
why you're in Barfield?
No, Ms. Hewitt.
She just knows I've been in
for a long time.
Eighteen years.
Is she aware that it is unlikely
that you'll be up for parole
for some considerable time?
We haven't discussed it.
You haven't had a visit prior
to Ms. Purvis for four years.
That is correct.
And I appreciate her kindness.
She's a very nice, respectable,
trusting lady.
Make sure, Wilfred,
that you do not abuse her trust
or abuse the trust
that we have in you
in allowing you to be
in the musical.
I won't.
I appreciate her kindness
very much.
Good.
Thank you, Mr. Samuels.
- Thank you.
- Governor.
I mean...
what am I supposed to do?
I go into exercise,
and he's starting on at me.
I go into the showers,
and he's goading me.
He's trying to make me lose
my rag.
And I am telling you
that unless he's moved,
I'm going to have to take him.
I can't keep turning away.
Understand me?
I can't not face him,
because I am losing face.
Understand what I'm saying
to you?
It's making me all tensed up.
I can't sleep
for thinking about it
because he won't leave me alone.
People are always getting at me.
I'm not doing anything.
But, Bert, you know
that it's to do with you.
You become aggressive
very easily
and over the smallest thing.
Now, you're telling me
that this most recent
altercation started...
Brian Samora took my chair
in the television lounge.
I always sit in that chair.
He knew it was my chair!
No, Bert, you don't.
You've only just moved
onto the wing.
So perhaps you took
Brian Samora's chair.
Morning.
Carlos, how's the new baby?
Beautiful, Ms. Hewitt.
Thank you.
Good.
Morning, Eugene.
How's the musical going?
Uh, could do with a bit more
rehearsal, Ms. Hewitt,
but it's all right.
I hear you've asked
to be back in the show, Brian.
Yeah. I wondered if I could get
me old part back now I'm back.
[Chuckles]
I don't think
that'll be possible, Brian.
But now that you are back...
Not that I think it's anything
to be quite so cheerful about...
I hope you'll continue
with your education program.
Oh, yeah.
I will, Ms. Hewitt.
Thank you very much, Ms. Hewitt.
Mean cow.
I heard that, Mr. Samora.
HADDOCK:
Ms. Hewitt.
Mr. Haddock, I hear you've got
a big leading role.
I was supposed to be playing
Nanki-Poo, but...
I'm looking forward
to the performance.
They're making me play a girl,
and I learned all the lines
for Nanki-Poo.
[Singsong voice]
Ja-a-a-son!
You're not listening
to what I'm saying.
I am saying
that I am being got at.
Bert, will you do something
for me?
Tonight, when you're watching
television...
If that prick sits in my chair,
I'll do something about it!
Just a minute.
I am telling you
that I'll wrap it over his head,
then I'll put my foot
through the TV!
People are always getting at me.
Come on, Bert.
I've seen Mr. Samuels,
and to be honest,
there is little that I can do.
If Ms. Purvis wishes to visit
him, then I can't really refuse
because I have no grounds
to do so.
I need me medication.
How is he coming along?
He's not.
He's suffering
from deep paranoia.
I don't think he's stable enough
to be on an ordinary wing.
Make sure
the wing governor knows
and we'll see
where we can move him.
Ja-a-a-son!
- Shut it!
- Ooh. Ooh.
- Shut up!
- Jason!
Jason!
Are your pants dry yet?
Officer Hully?
A moment.
SMITH:
Ja-a-a-son!
Are your pants dry yet?
Could you excuse us a second?
Thank you.
Are you settling in all right?
- Only I noticed...
- [Sighs]
It's Keith Smith, Ms. Hewitt.
Ever since I got here, he's
done it, and it drives me nuts.
I know I'm supposed to
ignore it.
Try not to let it get to you.
Thank you.
SMITH:
Ja-a-a-son!
Hey, Eugene.
Do you reckon it's sort of,
like, psychological,
you know, sort of like sublime,
me getting banged up again?
- You know what I mean?
- Yeah.
- You mean you're a pillock.
- [Chuckles]
I want you to do something
for me.
- I'll pay you in smokes, yeah?
- Yeah. Okay. Yeah.
Hang on.
Wait a minute.
What do you want us to do?
That prick Keith Smith.
He's been having a real go at me
since I came here.
I'd just like him given
a bit of a thrashing.
- Beat him up, yeah?
- Yeah.
I mean, not too much.
I don't want him hospitalized.
Just... Well, I don't have to
spell it out, do I?
I don't know, you know?
Keith Smith?
He's down on the I's.
We're stuck up here.
How are we supposed to get
to him?
I'll leave his cell unlocked,
maybe just after association.
Yeah. Come on.
That's got to work.
Well, Keith Smith,
he's a Cockney.
Got loads of mates down here.
You know what I mean?
I've got an idea.
Yeah.
We go in there,
give him a few whacks,
he's gonna know we did it.
Yeah. He wouldn't know who
done him if we had a mask on.
- Can you get any balaclavas?
- Yeah.
Yeah. Okay.
Thanks.
[Door closes]
Everything's on the level.
Come on.
If he's on the level,
we'll get more than a few smokes
out of this.
We're not doing anything.
Don't be crazy.
That's what he's just asked us
to do.
You're a shithouse.
You've been saying you're
gonna do Smith in for ages.
- Hey! Yeah. Yeah.
- You have! You have!
That's between cons,
not some screw paying us.
Yeah.
It's a liberty man,
a bloody liberty.
Well, you can't trust a screw.
I hate screws.
That's all right.
That's normal.
This bastard's bent.
A bent screw, Bri.
Yes!
BULLOCK: I just can't believe
that you'd go behind my back.
I'm responsible for you,
for your being at Barfield.
I just didn't think
it was necessarily anything
to do with you.
Well, how can you say that?
You know what happened to me.
You saw what happened to me.
And then I discover
that you're visiting one of
the prisoners, writing to him,
and without any prior knowledge
of his background.
I'm sorry.
But I just didn't think it would
concern anyone but myself
and Mr. Samuels.
Well, it does.
Months of hard work
have gone into this show.
Well, he is a trustee.
And it's hardly unsupervised.
We have officers with us
at all times.
Ms. Purvis, you have
no knowledge of prisons.
You've never been inside one
before this.
You are not, to my mind,
able to make any judgment
about whether a man
is trustworthy or not.
Well, he's got no family
and had no visits.
But he didn't mention
that he's serving 18 years
for armed robbery
and a further sentence for
the murder of a police officer.
Please remember, Ms. Purvis,
you are here to play the piano
and nothing more.
If there are to be no changes
whatsoever,
then what you are saying is that
Barfield is currently running
without any problems whatsoever,
when it is patently obvious
that we are just filling in
the cracks.
Maybe if you'd implemented
more staff,
more officers
to start your program,
then there'd be some leeway.
It isn't a question
of more staff, Mr. Syons.
- Facts are facts, Helen.
- Just a minute. Excuse me.
George Falla's legal beaver,
Turnbull, is in your office.
Okay.
Thank you.
Facts are facts.
We've got a full house,
but we have not got a full quota
of officers.
I am not advocating that we
begin overnight, but gradually.
All right.
What if we tried in practice
one wing only?
All right.
Why not?
Good.
C Wing it is.
Thank you, Len.
Excuse me.
[Door closes]
[Laughter]
You walked right into that one!
Well, you're gonna need
a bit of extra help anyway,
with Tarzan's moving in.
- What, on my wing?
- [Howls]
Bet you a fiver
he doesn't last the day.
Fifty! I can handle Tarzan.
[Laughs]
Come on, boys.
Fifty!
[Telephone ringing]
I've seen my client, Mr. Falla.
Is he in good health?
I most certainly hope so,
since he's been coddled
the past three weeks.
I would like to set a date
for the police to interview him,
obviously with yourself
and S.O. Russell Morgan present.
Monday is suitable for me.
Morning or afternoon.
Mavis?
Mavis, have you got my diary
for next Monday?
Mr. Turnbull
would like to set up the inquiry
into the hostage situation.
I'll need at least two hours.
MAVIS:
It'll have to be the afternoon.
You're booked up all morning.
Monday afternoon it is, then.
How is Mr. Morgan?
Neither as fit or as able
as your client.
He's still on sick leave.
Is there anything else?
I don't think so.
Unless... Are you free
for dinner one evening?
What?
I'm asking you out to dinner,
Ms. Hewitt.
I'm sorry.
I'm not available.
- I didn't say when.
- It's immaterial.
- I am not available.
- [Telephone buzzes]
Excuse me.
Thank you for your time.
HEWITT:
Yes?
MAVIS: I have Officer Jackson
and Brian Samora here.
They need to see you
immediately.
- Are they waiting?
- Yeah. Can I send them in?
Yes. Yes, you can, Mavis.
Right now.
Mr. Jackson.
Mr. Samora.
Go on, Brian. Tell Ms. Hewitt
what you told me.
Go on, Brian.
Tell her.
You've got a bent officer,
Ms. Hewitt,
and he's bringing in balaclavas.
[Indistinct conversations,
up-tempo music playing]
Ms. Bullock,
they've done something funny
with these socks.
They're supposed to be
like that.
Just put them on
so you can try them out.
MARSH:
Well, they've only got one toe!
I think I'd better not
come see you again.
I'm sorry.
Oh.
That's all right, Ms. Purvis.
I understand.
No hard feelings.
But can I give you this?
They're just some poems I wrote.
Better not take them,
Mr. Samuels.
SAMUELS:
I'll leave them here for you.
MAHILL: Come on, Eugene.
I want to get started.
You try dancing in these shoes,
mate.
[Up-tempo music plays]
You have a bent officer...
Jason Hully.
Hully?
But he's a good steady lad.
Not quite so good.
He has apparently asked
Brian Samora and Eugene Buffy
to beat up another prisoner,
Keith Smith.
I-I wouldn't trust
those two little bastards.
And I should have been told
about this
before Mr. Jackson came to you.
Maybe.
But we will at least have to
listen to what they have to say.
Just front it out with him.
He'll deny it, won't he?
So what I want is to wait
until Buffy is back on the wing
from rehearsals
and we can get them both
to see me.
In the meantime,
I want this kept quiet.
Do not inform Officer Hully.
Have they picked up Kevin Watts,
our tattooed wonder?
No, but the police think
he might try and see
his girlfriend.
She went into labor
this morning.
Good afternoon.
[Up-tempo music playing]
♪ Three little maids from school
are we ♪
♪ Pert as a schoolgirl
well can be ♪
♪ Filled to the brim
with girlish glee ♪
♪ Three little maids
from school ♪
♪ Everything is a source
of fun ♪
♪ Nobody's safe,
for we care for none ♪
MARSH: ♪ Life is a game
that's just begun ♪
Okay.
The bow.
♪ Three little maids
from school ♪
- Aah! Shit.
- [Laughter]
You need to keep to small steps,
Roddy.
I'm trying, Ms. Bullock,
but I keep falling over.
Well, Roddy,
practice makes perfect.
Start again, Ms. Purvis.
HADDOCK:
Me wig's too tight.
Stop crying.
Will you not please meddle
with the props and costumes?
Could you check that skip,
please?
Right. Come on. From the top.
Come on. Come on, then.
Come on. From the top.
Ms. Purvis.
[Up-tempo music plays]
Tea, milk and two sugars,
Ms. Purvis.
Thank you.
MEN: ♪ Pert as a schoolgirl
well can be ♪
♪ Filled to the brim
with girlish glee ♪
♪ Three little maids
from school ♪
MARSH: ♪ Everything is a source
of fun ♪
ALL:
Hee-hee-hee-hee-hee-hee-hee!
BUFFY: ♪ Nobody's safe,
for we care for none ♪
Hee-hee-hee-hee-hee-hee-hee!
HADDOCK: ♪ Life is a game
that has just begun ♪
Hee-hee-hee-hee-hee-hee-hee!
ALL: ♪ Three little maids
from school ♪
[Screaming]
No!
I never touched her.
I never touched her!
[Screaming]
WOMAN:
Deep breaths, Anna.
All right.
Push right through.
That's it. Keep pushing.
Come on.
Keep pushing.
- ANNA: [Exhales sharply]
- WOMAN: Okay.
Another big, deep breath.
Come on.
- Push. Go.
- ANNA: [Grunts, screams]
What did you go
and tell the governor for?
You told me to report it!
Yeah!
I 'm gonna report it!
I've already reported it,
you bastard!
[Grunts]
Stand up!
Governor Syons wants to see you.
I'm not setting foot
outside this cell.
Now, tell Governor Syons
if he wants a word,
he can have a word in here!
What we've got is explosive!
You should be looking after us,
not encouraging us to violence!
And, you see,
you... you are a tosser.
I saw her go towards the skips,
so naturally,
I went to give her a hand.
And she just flipped.
Duffy refuses to come out
of his cell, Gov.
I will wring his bloody neck.
What's all this
about Ms. Bullock?
What really happened?
It was some kind of breakdown,
I think.
But nobody touched her,
and I mean nobody.
DR. HARRIS:
You just bottled it up, Annette.
And then by refusing to...
Face it?
Please.
Annette, listen to me.
There's this colleague
of mine...
Nothing to do with
the prison service.
[Laughing]
A psychologist?
What the hell do you think I am?
I don't need therapy.
And if I do,
I'm perfectly capable
of dishing it out for myself.
Annette, look.
I'm sorry about this.
But as head of this department,
I'm suggesting that you take
at least two weeks' sick leave.
No.
I won't.
Well, then I'm afraid
you leave me no alternative
but to order you off duty.
I counseled rape victims
for two years.
I thought I knew
exactly what they were feeling.
I advised... cajoled...
and encouraged them
to talk about it.
So like a good counselor, every
night I've gone through it.
I wake up every morning
thinking about it.
I know it's not
the physical humiliation,
the brutality...
loss of control, even,
that eats into you.
Do you know what it is?
It's the fear.
I'm frightened.
And I can't make it go away.
[Sobs, screams]
Annette?
[Sobs]
Um, it's all right.
It's all right.
- Uh, could you leave, please?
- No!
Shh, shh, shh.
Annette, it's all right.
[Sobs]
Annette, it's Helen.
Come on.
Shh, shh, shh.
It's all right. It's all right.
It's all right.
Shh, shh, shh.
Come on.
It's all right.
[Mid-tempo classical music
playing]
[Alarm chirps]
LENNOX:
Helen?
[Door closes]
Simon?
Oh.
Oh, I missed you.
Missed you.
[Music continues]
I wanted to be all dressed
for you.
You are distinctly overdressed
for what I have in mind.
[Chuckles]
Really?
Ooh!
Do you know...
that you have the governor of
Barfield Prison on top of you?
I do.
[Chuckles]
You have told me of that fact
at least nine times.
I got it!
I am... the governor...
at Barfield Prison.
He's eight pounds
and five ounces.
Can you see, Kev?
He's got all his fingers
and all his toes.
He's beautiful.
[Baby cooing]
He's perfect.
He's just perfect.
I can't replay it again, Kev.
- ANNA: Yes, you are.
- I've got to go.
They're right outside, man.
And I've got to talk to her,
Colin.
I have to talk to her.
I can't stand to see her crying.
Just be careful, all right?
Cops are in hospital.
They're outside it.
She's being watched, man.
Colin?
Colin, what are you doing
down there?
- Anna?
- ANNA: It's me.
- Can you talk?
- Yeah.
Hey.
Just finishing with coal, Gran.
Then I'll help you upstairs
to bed, all right?
He's beautiful.
I love you.
ANNA:
I miss you, Kev.
- I love you.
Oh, come on, Kev.
I've got to go.
- Anna?
- ANNA: I love you.
- [Static]
- Hello?
Anna, are you still there?
Anna, I'll...
I'll come and see you.
I will.
Anna, I love you.
[Down-tempo music plays]
I've got to see me son.
The case dragged on
longer than anyone anticipated,
but I could be made
a junior partner.
- [Glasses clink]
- Oh, brilliant.
Thank you.
You hungry?
Mm.
Starving.
Okay.
- Have a drink.
- Mm-hmm.
- Have a shower.
- Give me 20 minutes.
- Mm.
And wrap your intellect
around this.
[Groans]
I need to talk to you about it.
Please.
Deal?
Sure.
What's in it?
Details about a prisoner
and a hostage in Barfield.
But apparently, right,
when they arrested him,
they put him in the back
of the patrol car.
Officer gets out
to say something, next minute,
Watts has bolted from
the back seat into the front.
You're kidding?
The bugger nicked a patrol car?
Yeah.
One of the specials.
Had a ruddy arsenal in the boot.
So anyway, he drives around
for about three hours,
clocks up
Christ knows how much mileage,
all hell breaks loose,
and then he dumps it...
Back at a police station.
[Both laugh]
I wondered why the gov had gone
out of his way on it.
Too damn right, mate.
It was his patrol car.
[Both laugh]
Is that what he's banged up for,
then?
Oh. No way.
No.
No, he pulled a few blags.
He is a nasty little bastard.
The suspect's brother,
Colin Watts, is just leaving.
Car Oscar 010.
Suspect's brother just left.
We tail or stay put? Over.
OFFICER:
Wait.
Light's on, top bedroom.
[Indistinct talking on radio]
Now the hall light's on.
See?
Another light.
For someone on a Zimmer frame,
the old lady's moving around
pretty fast.
Look.
Now they're off again.
I'm going to have a look.
Stay in the car.
[Mid-tempo music plays]
[Knock on door]
OFFICER:
Can you open the door, love?
It's the police.
[Plate clatters]
Can you open the door?
[Music continues]
- Aah!
- [Clattering]
[Dog barking]
Aah!
Can you open the door?
Come down, love.
She's deaf,
and she's bad on her feet.
What's going on?
There was someone
out in the alley.
Do you want me to get a key
for the front door?
He might be out back!
[Music continues]
All I need
is some professional advice.
WOMAN ON TELEVISION:
And I just can't believe...
- Simon.
- Mm. What?
Can you just wait
till the movie ends?
[Sighs]
WOMAN ON TELEVISION:
She had a gun?
I've seen it.
He killed her,
she has a dual personality,
and her sister is also Liz
as well as Jill.
You're making this up.
I know,
but it's better than this crap.
It was the cop that did it.
[Television turns off]
Oh. I should have accepted
Turnbull's invitation.
He asked me out to dinner,
you know.
Oh, he did, did he?
Mm-hmm.
I said no, thank you.
He said he hadn't said
which night.
And I said, well...
that I was still unavailable.
[Chuckles]
Oh. All right.
You asked for this.
- [Laughs]
- [Laughs] Ooh.
- And that's not going to work.
- I'm gonna be sick.
[Indistinct talking
on police radio]
Anything come in yet?
No, sir, but we've circulated
the car reg number.
It was parked
up at the top of the road.
Incompetent bastards.
We used clamp stitches,
as it was quite deep.
And the doctor's writing out
a prescription
for some antibiotics.
Thanks.
Is the maternity unit
close to here?
It's two floors up.
You're not pregnant as well,
are you?
No.
Right.
Well, I'll just be a second.
You can put your trousers
back on.
[Down-tempo music plays]
Right.
Let's have your tray.
Is it true
the musical's been canceled?
- Yes.
- Step back.
You have no right to do that!
You can't just cancel it!
Sorry, Wilfred.
It's nothing to do with us.
You know that.
Come on!
Let's have your trays!
You pillock!
[Indistinct conversations,
doors opening, closing]
Come on!
Let's have your trays!
You want me to call you
a doctor?
No. I'm fine.
I'm fine.
- Here.
- Thank you.
Mm.
In fact, do you know
what I think I fancy?
- What?
- A whiskey.
- Whiskey?
- [Chuckles]
Did you get some of that stuff
I like... the Wild Turkey?
Yes.
Well, why don't you get one
yourself and join me?
It's 8:00 in the morning.
It's Saturday.
- Hm?
- Why not?
JACKSON:
I'll do this top row.
You collect the trays
from below.
HULLY: A lot of aggravation
at breakfast.
What about?
Well, the musical's canceled.
On the board.
Gov Syons put it up.
What happened?
Nobody bloody told me.
- Christ.
- Trays!
All right.
Tray's out, lads.
Okay.
I'll take over this landing now.
Why are they canceling
the musical?
Don't say anything.
Here's a good lad.
MARSH:
Is it because of Ms. Bullock?
Don't know anything about it,
Roddy.
Pass out your tray, okay?
Jason.
Tray collection, Mr. Smith.
Here it is.
Come and get it, Jason.
I'm gonna have you.
In your dreams.
In your dreams!
What have they canceled musical
for?
JACKSON:
Eugene? Brian?
- What have we done?
- All right, Eric.
Calm down.
Tell him not to show his face.
Keith Smith nicked
me phone card and all.
- He's... Are you sure?
- Yeah. He's nicked it.
All right.
I'll have a word with him.
Go on.
Jumbo, can you have a word
with Eric?
Another one upset
they've canceled the musical?
No. He says Keith Smith's nicked
his phone card, all right?
[Silverware clattering]
I'll make some woman
a decent husband.
[Chuckles]
Oh, God, Helen.
Is there a pan you missed?
Oh, shut up.
I'll be interested to see
what Turnbull tries to pull
if he succeeds.
Succeeds?
You mean in proving
it was Morgan's own fault
he was taken hostage?
No way.
You are joking.
He just might, Helen,
because I wasn't joking
when I said Turnbull
is one of the best.
Helen?
[Door closes]
You okay?
Right.
Did you get everything you want?
Ta.
[Down-tempo music plays]
[Indistinct talking on radio]
We found it parked
in a side street
not far from the hospital.
And?
- And?!
- The seat's covered in blood.
I've got someone checking
the casualty department now.
I want the main hospital exits
covered.
He's here.
He's either injured
or he's got a hostage,
so I want the armed
response team alerted.
It's all a bit strong, isn't it?
Are you kidding?
The little bastard nicked
the gov's patrol car.
This is personal.
Called "get the egg
off my face."
[Toilet flushes]
[Indistinct talking on radio]
[Water running]
[Indistinct conversations]
[Child crying]
[Bell chimes]
Bye, now.
Bye-bye.
[Baby crying]
ANNA:
Thank you.
I couldn't get away.
I had to wait for ages.
Did anyone see you leave
the ward?
- I don't know.
- Sit down.
You're mad to come here, Kevin.
There's police everywhere.
I know. I know!
I'll give myself up.
I just wanted to hold him.
Can I hold him?
ANNA:
I-I want to call him after you.
Same name as you.
Yeah.
[Down-tempo music plays]
He looks just like you.
Even his hands are the same.
Hold his hand, Kev.
WATTS:
Oh.
Oh, look at his little
fingernails.
Hello, Kevin.
I'm your daddy.
Yeah, mate.
I love you, Anna.
And I love my baby boy.
Don't I?
He's all mine.
He looks like me, doesn't he?
- Yeah.
- [Sneezes]
- Oh, sweetheart.
Bless you.
Are you sure that's him?
That's him.
I'm sure.
Right. We cut off the corridor
both ends.
But we've got to be careful.
Gov, lift.
She's going to the lifts.
- Let her go.
- ♪ The loser ♪
Nobody's to make a move
until she's got in the lift.
- ♪ The beautiful loser ♪
- Has she got the baby?
[Music continues]
WATTS:
Stay away from me.
I mean it!
You make one more move
towards me, and I'll...
I'll drop it.
I'll drop him.
Nobody's going to do anything,
Kevin.
We just don't want any harm
to come to the baby.
Let me take the baby, Kevin,
please.
Oh, no.
I want to walk out of here.
I want to get into a patrol car
outside.
I do not want to be dragged out!
Let him walk.
Back off.
Go on, Kevin.
You keep walking.
Cut him off downstairs!
Move!
Come on!
What's on the sixth floor.
Is that a wing or what?
Uh, no. It's a utility floor.
Fire escape.
He's on the bloody roof.
♪ So I'm walking ♪
♪ Yes, I'm walking ♪
♪ I'll keep on walking ♪
♪ Talking my way... ♪
Kevin!
We're all a long way from you,
son.
No one's gonna harm you.
Step back from the edge, Kevin.
Step back, Kevin.
- Aah!
- No!
You big pillock, Tully!
You stupid git!
- It wasn't my baby!
- [Siren wailing in distance]
You're all stupid bastards!
Come on, then!
I'll take the lot of you on!
Come on!
[Grunts]
You think I'd hurt my baby?!
Do you think I'd hurt
me own baby?!
Ms. Hewitt?
Yeah.
There's a lot of bad feeling
about this musical
being canceled.
We've all, officers and inmates,
put a lot into it.
Mr. Jackson, I have been
called in on an emergency.
Right now this bloody musical
is the last thing on my mind.
Who canceled it?
I don't know.
All right.
You'll get one over, yeah?
Thanks a lot.
Is he ready?
We need a camera, because this
didn't happen at our end.
He arrived in this condition.
We were told
that he resisted arrest
and had to be restrained.
Then we stripped him off.
He's in bad shape.
He fell on the stone steps,
but nobody touched him our end.
[Down-tempo music plays]
DR. HARRIS: I haven't finished
my examination yet,
but he is going to need
a brain scan.
♪ The beautiful loser ♪
Oh.
DR. HARRIS:
His testicles are swollen.
Thighs, shins, back, backside
in the same state as his chest.
He's obviously been given
a very severe beating.
I want him photographed.
I want a list of names
of all the Barfield officers
that were at reception.
None of our lads did this.
I said he fell,
but, I mean, a fall wouldn't do
this much injury.
I'm not making any accusations,
Gary, but somebody did this.
Now, he should never have been
accepted back to Barfield
in this condition.
But he was,
so he's now our responsibility.
DR. HARRIS:
Hey, he's conscious.
Just.
- ♪ So I'm walking ♪
- [Mumbling]
♪ Yes, I'm walking ♪
♪ I'll keep on walking ♪
♪ Talking my way... ♪
Baby.
I doubt we'll ever find out
who did it.
You want to bet?
I want to see the reception
officer, the wing governor,
the duty governor,
and the principal officer.
Oh. Gary, whose decision was it
to cancel the musical?
Well, I suppose it was mine.
I've had a tough enough fight
with the P.O.A.
to keep that show going,
so you can relay
to all those concerned
that the musical goes ahead
as arranged.
Who's going to oversee it?
If necessary, I will.
It's about time
I made my presence felt.
It's time that everyone realized
I'm the governor of Barfield.
- Governor.
- Gate 11 opening.
- The show goes on?
- Yes. The show goes on.
Governor.
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/agzx4
Help other users to choose the best subtitles