Watch any video online with Open-SUBTITLES
Free Browser extension: osdb.link/ext
FAMILY MOTTO
A HARMONIOUS FAMILY WITH LOVE
The Vice CEO…
has a fiancée he will marry soon.
This industry is small.
Someone at the headquarters said
he's been living with this woman
since he was in the US.
His girlfriend he's been dating
for nine years.
Anyway, I heard
they're getting married in Korea.
What's so funny about what I just said?
Just…
You think
I'm a joke, right?
Because I'm always spreading rumors
and acting cute on Monday mornings?
My ex-boyfriend
dumped me after nine years.
I'm traumatized by that.
You just reopened my wound.
That's why I laughed.
The trauma.
Me and my careless mouth.
I'm sorry.
He is Mr. Playboy.
But the class is dismissed!
MESSAGE FROM IM GEON-JOO
Want to have dinner at my place?
I'll cook for you.
I also have something to say to you.
I'll go to your workplace.
Let's talk during lunch.
By the way,
I'm asking just in case I make a mistake.
Does our eldest daughter…
know about it?
Eun-joo knows about what?
Hi.
-Hi.
Does she know
that I am not…
her biological father?
Eun-joo doesn't know.
We…
decided not to talk about that ever again.
I'm sorry.
I was asking so I don't make any mistakes.
What were you doing
until things got this bad?
I think we can still meet the deadline.
Yes.
FATHER
Why are you so early?
Are you going somewhere?
YOUNGER DAUGHTER
ELDEST DAUGHTER
-Yes, Eun-joo.
-Finish your call first.
Dad.
Yes.
Are you okay?
Are you well enough to come home?
Of course.
Don't worry. I'm fine.
I'll go see you in the evening.
What about Mom?
Mom.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Can Dad leave the hospital?
Yes.
Is he still 22 years old?
See you at home.
Gosh. I guess he still is.
Mom, don't cook dinner. Let's order in.
Sure.
Let me talk to the young Dad.
She's with me.
Let me talk to her, please.
I'm here.
Mom, you must be tired.
Don't cook anything.
I'll bring meat, so let's just eat that.
Dad loves meat.
All right.
Dad, congratulations on being
discharged from the hospital!
See you in the evening.
Okay.
You left your precious laptop here?
I could've brought it to you.
The patients must be waiting.
I just took my lunch break early.
I work as a freelancer from time to time.
The office asks me for help
when they encounter a picky client
whom I've dealt with before.
Since when?
It's been a while.
So you really weren't writing.
Why didn't you tell me?
I know, right?
I wonder why I didn't tell you.
Won't you be late?
Right.
This client is quite a handful.
I'm running short on time.
Let's talk later.
No need to talk later.
If you want to work, then work.
This must be why I didn't tell you.
You're not interested in me.
No.
Not just me.
You seem like you're not
interested in the world.
You're getting weirder and weirder.
Have you always been like this?
You really must be working,
seeing that you're getting edgy.
You said you're late.
Yes, I'm late.
I'm late.
Too late.
I can't go to the meeting in this mood.
It's better to relieve it even if I'm late
than frown at work.
There's nothing to relieve.
It's not like
you can't control your emotions.
You're keeping a secret from me, right?
Does the word "secret"
sound inappropriate?
Do you have an issue
you can't tell me about?
Yes, you do.
I know you do.
Tell me.
I'll help you.
Help me?
Yes.
How reassuring.
If there's a secret that can be solved
immediately with your help,
then I'll tell you.
Is the word "help"
that uncomfortable between family?
-Let's stop this.
-Then I take it back.
I'll listen.
Tell me whenever you want to.
Don't forget we're visiting
my family later tonight.
Dad, get in.
I'll get in with your mother.
Let's wait for a bit.
Where's Mom?
Over there.
She's talking on the phone.
Get in.
Come on, get in.
Mom, who did you talk to?
Eun-joo or Eun-hee?
No.
Then who was it?
Are your sisters the only ones
I talk to on the phone?
I mean…
Who was important enough
to leave Dad standing alone?
Ji-woo.
I'm capable of standing out
alone for a moment.
My condition isn't that bad.
It was the community center
asking about my absence.
Community center?
They're not a school.
Why do they care about attendance?
Who called exactly?
Would you even know if I told you?
Focus on driving.
What is a community center?
You learn a variety of things there.
What are you learning there?
What is it? Tell me, Ms. Sook.
What are you learning?
I'm learning about literature.
I told you to write poems
because you love to read books
and you speak so eloquently.
Right?
Aren't you writing poems, Ms. Sook?
I told you to stop calling me Ms. Sook.
I've forgotten about it.
He pouts his lips in three cases.
I want you to
buy these clothes.
I can buy this for you.
I'll be upset if you don't buy it.
Pouts when he's upset.
I want you to eat
three more spoonfuls of rice.
You eat too little.
Like a bird pecking on bird seeds.
Eat a bit more, okay?
Pouts when he begs.
It's so thick it won't fold.
And pouts when he's proud.
Why won't you let me call you Ms. Sook?
Over here.
Why are you hiding there?
I wasn't really hiding but…
To protect an office worker?
Even if rumors spread…
I don't look that bad though, right?
What brings you here all of a sudden?
Did you come here because you were worried
after you got my text?
You said he turned out to be Mr. Playboy,
so I should be worried, right?
So why are you here?
When will the meditation
center book be out?
That?
We just got started. Why?
We shot a promotional video
ten times for social media,
but they aren't paying us a single penny.
They said they'll pay us
when the book is out.
It's because they don't know the industry.
Talk to them again.
I even asked them to pay us 30% for now,
but they won't until the book is out.
I was so furious,
so I had to come to see you.
I'm here but I've cooled down on my way.
How much is it?
Why do you ask?
Should I lend you some money for now?
Why?
Do you have a lot of money?
Office worker loan.
You still don't have a sense of money.
Just buy me a meal.
Will Ji-woo not get paid
if you have no money?
Just buy me a meal.
Why?
I'll lend you money, okay?
By the way,
how did you know Mr. Playboy is a playboy?
He's been dating for nine years.
Nine years?
Yes, nine years.
You can act like nothing happened
and ignore each other.
Yes, I should learn how to seduce
a player from this one-night stand.
That was too self-deprecating.
My female hormones have been building up
for five years, reached the limit,
and I made a mistake.
Yes, just think of it like that.
"Am I in love?"
"His bookshelf looks just like mine."
"We must have similar souls."
Don't be ridiculous.
He wants me to come over tonight to talk.
He wants to end it before it gets messy.
That's right, you told me and Jong-min
not to get messy at school
when we were dating.
You called dating "messy"
at that time too.
Wait.
But why ask you to come over to his place?
You think I'll make
the same mistake twice?
I do.
You little…
You know best what it's like
to date someone for nine years.
You've dated a guy for nine years
and slept with a guy
who's been dating for nine years.
Hey, I didn't know.
In any case,
it's more advantageous for you
since you've experienced both.
You can end it in a nicer, cleaner way.
Blow his mind by ending it nice and clean.
-Hello.
-Welcome.
I had breakfast.
You came here
so you wouldn't run into us, right?
No.
I was craving something greasy today.
Eun-hee isn't introducing us.
Hi, I'm Park Chan-hyuk.
Hi, I'm Seo Kyung-ok.
We're all Eun-hee's co-workers.
-Hi.
He's a university friend.
He's filming videos
for the meditation center.
-Yes.
-I see.
Right.
-I'm Im Geon-joo.
-I'm Park Chan-hyuk.
IM GEON-JOO
Okay, I'm paying today.
Would you like something more to drink?
Chan-hyuk, do you want
something more to drink?
-Let's go order together.
-How gentle.
-Here you go.
-Thank you.
-Coffee for me.
If you two are university friends,
that means you've seen her
since she was a baby.
How long have you been friends?
It's been 15 years,
but we lost touch and met again recently.
Why did you get to meet again recently?
A wedding or a first birthday party?
I'm sorry.
Are you married?
No, I'm not.
He's not married, but he has a young,
smart, and pretty woman by his side.
All right, time for us to go.
You shouldn't use disposable cups
inside the restaurant.
Bye.
-See you next time.
-Sure.
-Goodbye.
-Bye.
We should go, too.
Companies hate employees
who use up their entire lunch break.
I lost my appetite.
Your destination is nearby.
Dad, we're almost there.
It feels familiar, right?
Yes, it does.
It's quite familiar.
I received all my education here.
Slow down when you're near the house.
I can't speed up
because of the speed bumps anyway.
Ji-woo, stop the car for a moment.
Why?
I have something to buy.
But I have no money.
Give me some pocket money.
THE YOO'S FRUIT SHOP
Thank you.
What are you trying to buy?
-I could get lost or…
-You're a 22-year-old man, not a kid.
You became a father at that age.
Stop pouting, for goodness' sake!
I'm going to buy tangerines.
You like tangerines, Ms. Sook.
There are so many fruits here.
Is he Ji-woo's father?
Yes.
I see.
Nice to meet you.
Hello.
Yes.
By the way,
some of the tangerines are sour.
Ji-woo's mother likes Korean melons.
They're very sweet.
Korean melons?
Ms. Sook likes Korean melons?
Ms. Sook.
Which do you prefer?
Tangerines or Korean melons?
How competitive.
He's 22 years old, all right.
I'd like tangerines
and Korean melons, please.
Ji-woo, which one do you prefer?
Tangerines?
I prefer tangerines.
Why does it feel like
I have a younger brother all of a sudden?
How long has this fruit shop been here?
The fruit shop?
It's been here for a few years. Why?
The sign looks weird
and he wrote down such difficult things
as if he's smart or something.
Mr. Yoo used to be a university professor.
Then he opened the shop
because he had a purpose.
A professor?
Why?
Nothing.
Why was it his first time seeing me
if he's been here for a few years?
This was my first time
going to a fruit shop
near my house in the past few years?
But Ms. Sook loves fruit.
I'm Ahn Hyo-seok.
Okay.
Please sit and wait for a bit.
-Who's the next patient?
-The next patient?
Hi.
Why are you here so late?
If you took the case from the start,
Professor Jang and I
wouldn't be in this mess.
I took a look and it doesn't overlap.
You two can both apply for your patents.
It's been so long
and you don't even say hi.
That's very you, Attorney Kim.
Professor, you're the one
who didn't say hi and threw a fit instead.
Hey, bring Ms. Kim a cup of coffee.
I'll do it.
I have a unique taste in coffee,
so it's better that I do it.
How did you get hurt?
I got stabbed with scissors.
Sewing scissors have sharp edges.
Looks like you got stabbed.
Lovers' quarrel.
Your girlfriend is strong.
We're going to treat it
and apply a dressing.
Leave it be for a few days.
-Get the ointment and a shot, please.
-Okay.
A wound this serious
isn't a lovers' quarrel.
Get a grip.
You get a grip.
My girlfriend knows about you.
Tell Eun-joo before I tell her myself.
I'm giving you a chance.
Here you go.
Attorney Kim.
Are you working again?
As you can see.
Is your husband too weak
to have kids with you?
Be honest.
You're starting to work again
since you don't have kids, right?
Your style totally changed.
You're at the age…
when you truly bloom.
Then why aren't your
theses blooming, Professor?
Be careful.
I checked and many of your
patented theses have problems.
Thirty-four years of work
can end in a second.
And stop getting help from your students.
Especially the female students.
You used to say girls should be
thankful for even going to university.
But why are you always
asking for their help?
How cute.
And very immature.
Excuse me.
Hey.
It's me.
I'll pick you up for dinner today.
It's okay, I'll take a taxi.
I have something to say.
Okay.
I'm at Hanguk University.
Come say hi to the professor
I work with then.
He's worried that you might be too weak.
Come on, Attorney Kim.
I said that because I thought of you
as my married daughter.
I'm afraid your husband
might get the wrong idea.
This is why field trips are important.
From what I saw, you like Mr. Playboy.
You were drawing lines to make sure
he doesn't get the wrong idea about us.
I have a young, smart,
and pretty girl by my side?
You do.
She's just an employee.
It's not that I like him,
but I was impressed
that he and I have so many similarities.
My mom
saves wet wipes and paper towels.
She always splits them in half,
and even in quarters at times.
And I'm doing that, too.
You?
After I started the company, I started
saving wet wipes and paper towels.
Gosh, it gives me chills.
I read from a book
that the DNA of cheapskates
is powerfully dominant.
So a family of cheapskates has a
high chance of being cheapskates forever.
How can you interpret
a minor metaphor with science?
Did you study DNA or something?
Yes.
Why?
Because my sister and I aren't alike.
We're different in every aspect.
That's not a DNA problem.
I'm sure it's hard
to find anyone like Eun-joo.
She's…
perfect and wonderful.
Who? Kim Eun-joo? Perfect?
I'm leaving.
Get some rest in the bedroom.
Tae-hyung is going to check on you
when he comes for dinner.
I remember the day we took
this photo like it was yesterday.
I'm sure you do.
You're 22 years old now.
The photographer said
that we look alike and smile the same.
If couples look alike, they live happily.
You wanted to have the photo taken.
I did?
You said you'd frame this
and keep it until you grew old
to remember this day forever.
I don't remember.
You can't remember a few decades at all,
and I can't remember that moment at all.
So it's a tie.
We can't blame each other.
Are you angry at me?
I'm not.
We…
I mean, me.
What's my score?
About what?
I remember saying
that I'll be a 99-point husband
for the rest of my life.
Do you remember when I peeled tangerines
until my hands turned yellow
when you caught a cold
while you were pregnant?
My hands really turned yellow.
You'll know how flustered
I am by your actions
once you get your memories back.
Why did you catch a cold
when you're home all day long?
My throat hurts, too.
You have to treat it early,
so take medicine before you go.
You want me to die?
It takes over six hours to get to Pohang.
What if I doze off at the wheel?
If you're going to die,
get more insurance before you do.
You and your attitude.
Gosh.
What are you doing? It's winter.
Are you purposely pointing it at me?
I can't drive if I catch a cold.
I'm leaving.
I'm furious at least a dozen times a day
and it's killing me inside.
If you think you're going to die
from fury, get some insurance.
If words could kill,
both of us should've been dead already.
Ji-woo saved the CCTV footage
he saw at the police station,
saying that I have to watch it.
Does he go hiking at night often?
I don't know.
You don't know?
I know, right?
I don't think I know much about my family.
But I remember how you
like kkakdugi and your coffee.
A scientist said
that we know more
about the materials in the solar system
than the materials inside Earth.
We think that there's no need to
learn about Earth since we live on it.
That's how families are.
And judging someone
as Mr. Playboy or whatever
when I don't even know much
about my family
seems pointless too.
How does that relate to this?
I don't know. Do as you wish.
I'm leaving.
I heard it's your day off today.
Why are you here?
Because I have some time.
Is your father home now?
Yes.
Is he in bad condition?
No.
No,
He's become a romantic husband.
I thought my parents
need some time on their own,
and I have nowhere to go, so I came here.
I'll leave soon. Don't mind me.
You're shaking your leg.
-What?
-You shake your leg when you're troubled.
Why is a CEO being nosy
about an employee's private life?
To the front of the camera…
What?
Why?
Director Kim, you move the camera.
Treat our employee who's managing
the work of many by herself well, okay?
Okay.
All right, come on.
Get ready.
Aren't they lovely?
I should've worn some make up
when I was their age.
Is wearing too much makeup
and dressing up
to show their figure lovely?
Right, you don't like girly things.
What did you want to talk about?
I'm taking a break starting next week.
Why?
There's a seminar in New Zealand
and I'm attending this time.
We take turns.
Should I go with you?
You started working. Do you have time?
Don't worry. I won't go.
Don't be flustered.
I'm busy too.
Do you have to say it like that?
Did you call me during work
and pick me up to tell me this?
Now, now. It's too quiet here.
We're grilling premium beef here.
How about a shot of soju?
Tae-hyung, call a driver.
Eun-joo, what do you say? Ji-woo?
You drink it.
I can't. I have to
go somewhere after I eat.
Where?
To meet someone.
Who are you meeting that you're
covering yourself completely
to keep you from smelling like barbecue?
Perfect. Just perfect.
What?
Someone said you were born
perfect and wonderful.
What an insightful person.
-Eun-joo, put it there.
-Mom, here.
Put it in front of Tae-hyung.
Don't buy meat next time.
Ordering in is the way to let Mom rest.
You think she'll order in?
She told me she will.
Just take your first wrap.
-No, thanks.
-Take it.
Dad did forget his first daughter.
I don't want it.
Goodness.
Dad.
Give me the first wrap from now on.
I'll give it to the head of the family.
Here.
And you give it to the son
who will carry on the family name.
Don't worry too much.
His blood pressure, temperature,
and pulse are normal.
Sir, don't overstrain yourself
and just be comfortable.
Did you hear what Tae-hyung said?
Yes, doctor.
I mean…
All right.
There are videos that we took
and we have tons of photos, too.
Wouldn't that bring back his memories?
No, don't do that.
Brains work in mysterious ways.
It can create new memories
based on new information.
Sir, you're currently in a state
where you're at a vague borderline.
You're going to be yourself soon,
so why don't you enjoy
being a 22-year-old for a while?
-I'll go get the car.
-Okay.
Dad can't work for a while.
Give it to Mom.
She'll reject it if I do.
Yes, ma'am.
What's up with you?
Why are you being
so respectful and polite?
I did?
I can't help but use honorifics
when I see an envelope with money.
Eun-joo, go back home safely.
Bye, Ji-woo.
Are you dating?
Aren't I too old to be asked
if I'm dating or not?
Since you're old now,
be rational in relationships.
You slavishly cater
to the other person in relationships.
You couldn't just skip dating
on a day like today?
-Why rush out this late?
-I'm not dating.
If you can't even call it dating,
then don't go at this hour.
It was better when I didn't see you.
Then don't see me ever again.
You showed up all of a sudden
and you talk like you're being generous.
Is criticism a part of your life?
Isn't your menopause coming too early?
I'm too old to get nitpicked.
Stop it, Eun-hee. Just go.
-What's wrong?
What do you mean? You're fighting again.
"Again"? People might think
we fight every day.
It's not like I'm nagging
on a stranger's love life.
Don't I have the right
to nag at my sister's love life?
Am I wrong, slavish caterer?
No, early menopausal sister.
And you.
What did you say at the dinner table?
"The son who will
carry on the family name"?
We never differentiated son and daughter.
We didn't raise you like that.
Gosh. You two are so alike.
Be rational in relationships.
You slavishly cater
to the other person in relationships.
Slavishly? She went too far…
Goodness.
Her word choices are so annoying.
Darn it, this is so annoying.
You scared me.
You were too drunk that day
to recall my house number, right?
And you don't want to
call me to ask, right?
No.
What's worse is
that you still don't have
my number on your phone.
These thoughts were
in my mind so came down here.
That's not what it is.
I did save your number.
Here.
What did you want to say to me?
Right.
Want to go up and talk?
No.
Let's…
talk here today.
It seemed like you drink
a lot of coffee at work,
so caffeine-free tea.
Do you only watch me at work?
How did you know?
Hey.
I'm at a cafe near my house.
I'm meeting someone.
Work.
I'm a bit busy.
Good night.
Eun-hee.
I have a girlfriend.
I see.
I've been dating her for a long time.
It's been about nine years.
My first relationship
ended up lasting a long time.
I see.
Nine years.
The first relationship.
Did you hear it from someone else?
Yes.
If I know about it,
everyone at the company knows.
I'm always the last one.
Rumors like that do spread fast.
I understand what you mean.
Let's head out.
Well…
I have something to say.
Didn't you tell me just now?
That wasn't the one.
There's a reason…
why I didn't call you over the weekend.
I'm sure you couldn't.
It's not that I couldn't. I just didn't.
Because I needed time to think.
And the conclusion I came to
after thinking for a long time is…
I wish to keep seeing you, Eun-hee.
Right.
Thanks.
That feels great.
But I'm…
incapable of being a subject of cheating.
Because I'm not coolheaded enough
to not think much of
you kindly answering
her call in front of me
without even trying
to step outside.
I thought stepping outside
would make you misunderstand more.
We're…
slowly drifting apart.
First, we saw each other less.
Then, we called each other less.
And now…
we rarely contact each other.
It may seem cowardly,
but that's what nine years is.
What would Eun-joo say
if she was in this situation?
Did you two agree to slowly drift apart?
How long does "slowly" take?
Can you explain the difference
between breaking up and drifting apart?
I want to be honest with you today.
and I wish to keep seeing you, Eun-hee.
CHILBO DRIVER REST STOP
You must've worked like a horse.
The others had to work a lot more
just because you took a few days off.
Is this my truck?
Mine?
Sang-sik!
Do you really not remember or what?
What the…
What?
To be frank,
we can't say it's your truck.
Only one of the tires is yours.
The rest is all debt.
Can he drive it?
Why?
His memories aren't back yet.
Come on, as soon as he saw the truck,
he knew where to look and check.
His body remembers.
He can do it with his eyes closed.
By the way, it's not dementia
or anything like that, right?
It's completely different.
Ms. Sook, get in.
You can just step on
the foothold and climb up.
Yes. Grab that.
Slowly.
Careful.
You're back to your young days.
You're in your honeymoon days. Good grief.
Are you looking for something?
No.
It's quite high up here.
Is this your first time riding it?
I bought a truck,
but how come you were never in it before?
Is it because you're not
interested in me at all?
Is it because I bought this recently?
I've never been in your
company truck either.
Why…
Why is that?
You'll like the promotional video.
It's well-organized.
She's good at soulless smiles.
You're right.
My second older sister
is a soulless pacifist.
-Please sit.
-Hi.
You know each other, right?
Yes.
She said that releasing
the promotional video first
will help with the publication.
Yes.
You can get the photos
from the video for the book, right?
I can.
If you can pay the rest of the fee,
we can even upload the video today.
I see.
-Let's watch it then.
-Yes, hold on.
"Slowly drifting apart."
This is a fresh one-liner suggesting
a new perception of two-timing.
He should be able to say those lines
if he's a true Mr. Playboy,
So what are you going to do
with Mr. Playboy?
Eun-hee.
I'll wait until you make your decision.
Someone said that
I slavishly cater
to the other person in relationships.
What do you think?
It's true that you're
good at catering to people.
If done in the right way,
it's your greatest strength.
But the word choice of "slavishly"
is annoyingly extreme.
"Annoyingly extreme," right?
My sister, whom you called
perfect and wonderful,
used that word to me.
Don't you think Eun-joo used an extreme
word to make sure you get a grip?
I was about to fight her,
but since we made up after four years,
I'm just holding back.
Eun-hee.
-The car is out.
-Okay.
You made up after four years?
Didn't I tell you?
When I cut ties with you,
I also cut ties with my sister.
I'm leaving. Bye.
You're even more stupid than I thought.
What?
You cut ties with your sister
because of Jong-pal?
Don't look at me like that.
She was harsh to me at the time.
How was she harsh to you? Let me hear it.
She has never comforted me.
She's never on my side.
I went to see her first,
but she said I was pathetic.
Why do you want me to talk about the past?
Kim Eun-joo just isn't
the comforting type.
Do you know
what the problem with family is?
They don't say what they have to say.
They let it settle until it hardens
when they can just shake it off.
Then suddenly, it explodes one day.
Apologize to your sister properly.
I did.
Even in university, you were easily
agitated whenever Eun-joo was mentioned.
-Was I?
-Yes.
Even when you were drunk, you'd be happy
about everything but your sister.
But it's gotten worse.
Go meditate more and find out why.
Look into your heart.
It's because I'm petty and crooked.
That's what I am saying.
You aren't petty and crooked.
But why are you
only like that to your sister?
The car is out. I'm leaving.
Because we're family
some memories cannot be shaken off.
Because we're family.
WELCOME TO ULSAN METROPOLITAN CITY
While flapping its wings
The bright morning takes my song
Heaven's song
And scatters it
Ms. Sook.
You said I'm more charming
than Lee Yong when I sang this.
Do you remember?
Do you remember me doing
a hundred jump ropes every night
because I was becoming a father?
We could see all of Seoul from our house.
How about we take a look?
Do you remember our first house?
I don't remember.
So just be careful with your driving.
Ms. Sook, please wait just a moment.
Hey, be careful.
-It's dangerous to do that alone.
-Yes. I can't pull this.
-Goodness.
-Thank you.
You need to tie it well.
I guess it's tough
to put food on the table.
Considering how his body knows
even without memories.
Is it good enough?
How are you so strong
after staying up a few days?
I slept whenever I had time.
You should've rested while you were out.
I slacked off in my spare time.
Did something bad happen?
About 25 years ago?
Something bad happened then.
I see.
If it was 25 years ago,
you were a minor at the time,
so don't drink at the get-together.
I have a counselor's certificate.
If you don't drink and drive to my house,
I can do healthy counseling for a minor.
Since you didn't say no yet…
I'm sorry.
I wasn't myself
these past few days, so I missed it.
I'll correct it.
I'll organize it
as soon as possible and submit it.
Okay, I'll be waiting.
Mr. Oh?
Eun-hee has been
working late recently to plan this.
Did you give her more work?
You're so mean.
Also, "I'll correct it." "I'll submit it."
Mr. Oh, doesn't this
make you uncomfortable?
Right.
Maybe she's being sarcastic.
"I'm going to do it when I want to do it,
so you just need to wait."
That's what I heard.
You have good hearing.
I'll wait, quietly.
Answer him.
Yes, sir.
"Maybe she's being sarcastic."
He's totally criticizing you, right?
Yes, he's criticizing me.
But don't be so sad.
He acts sweet but makes
our team work like a horse too.
Hey, but he still knew
that you were working outside
during lunch on purpose.
And he even set aside a lunch box for you,
just in case you skipped lunch.
Really?
Yes.
Fix it with that three-minute one
and send it quickly.
Jeez, all right.
Hello, ma'am.
-So you know her.
-Yes.
-Coming back from lunch?
-Yes, Seo-young will be here soon.
He's a new employee.
Hi, I'm Kim Ji-woo.
You must think I'm a helicopter mother
who comes to her daughter's workplace.
No, of course not.
Seo-young's phone is almost
always off, so I had to come.
Yes, we do a lot of filming here.
I heard it's common
to have your phones off.
I'm sorry. Don't mind us,
and go back to work, please.
-Have a good day.
-Goodbye.
Aren't you here…
to say something to me?
Yes, get up.
Let's go to the cafe out front.
You can say it here.
How can I do that? Everyone's working.
I have to work, too.
Get up, Seo-young. It won't take long.
Mr. Park.
How about we have lunch together?
Yes, sure.
After suffering such a thing,
how can you work with a bunch of men?
"Such a thing"?
I suffered it?
Ji-woo, wait for me. I'm hungry, too.
What are you doing?
Don't give others a hard time.
I hate it.
I hate it so much!
You're terrible at lying.
Asking me to lunch
after coming from lunch?
I was startled.
How do you know her?
I just do.
I'm sure all mothers
and daughters are like that.
They fight and laugh.
My mom and sisters aren't like that.
You'll never know
since you grew up in a normal family.
I thought my family
was normal, but we're not.
Let's do well at the book fair.
Good job, everyone!
-Good job!
It's so refreshing.
No way.
My sister does look old.
She hasn't changed much.
Give it to your sister.
I'm sending her this now.
Why not give it to her yourself?
Someone told me she might get
the wrong idea if I give it to her myself.
Come on, Eun-hee won't get
any wrong ideas from you.
Yoon Seo-young.
Answer me.
Say it.
Go home. I'll do the first editing.
If you feeling down,
go have a drink with your co-worker.
Chan-hyuk.
I feel insulted.
She doesn't want to drink with me?
-Correct.
-Chan-hyuk!
-Where are we going?
-What?
Do you know any bars we can go to?
Why?
-Do you want more coffee?
-No.
You have something to say, right?
No.
You're lying.
I think you have something to say.
Why are you glancing at me
and not saying anything these days?
It's my job to glance
to check if my customers need anything.
I see.
So the old woman got the wrong idea
because the handsome
barista kept glancing.
I need a piece of cheesecake
to get myself together.
Orange cheesecake.
Let's have dinner.
You're early.
Cancel the cheesecake.
Okay.
You've been eating cake
as a meal these days. Go have dinner.
You're a very observant
and polite barista.
Get your purse.
Okay.
Bye.
You said we're going to eat.
Let's walk for a bit.
Okay.
I think I should tell you
before I go to the seminar.
Sure, go ahead.
I really liked this walking trail.
A rich neighborhood sure felt different.
I never even dreamed
I would live in a such place.
So?
Just say what you have to say.
You always asked if
I had something to say,
but I'm nervous now that you do.
You talk like you're
going to leave this place.
What do you think I'll say?
I know, right?
I guess at some point
I started to feel
that I would leave this neighborhood.
Stop dragging it and say it.
Sang-sik!
Mr. Kim.
Gosh, we were so worried.
I'm sorry I made you all worry.
I feel light as a feather.
We were struggling without you,
our problem solver.
That's right, I'm the best problem solver.
-You look great.
-Right.
Are you all doing fine?
-Yes.
-I see.
I only rode it once, but it's so tiring.
All jobs in this world are hard.
Why are you waiting here?
The air here isn't good.
So I can see you sooner.
Sang-sik, take all the time
you need to rest.
You can lend your truck.
It's not easy to leave it to someone else.
Gosh, you're so picky.
I'll leave it here,
so pay the double amount
if you want to borrow it.
The double amount, no matter what.
Are you leaving?
Of course, I am.
Oh.
Is there anything else left for me to do?
Sang-sik, you're being weird today.
What?
What's so weird about me?
Aren’t you going to see Young-sik?
Young-sik?
Right.
Young-sik.
Yes, Young-sik.
Dad!
Dad.
I knew…
that this day would come.
I've always imagined it.
Were you with Mr. Playboy?
It's because I'm embarrassed.
Eun-hee.
Family members trick each other.
Where did Mom go?
He's on a date.
I cried every night, but you came home
with wildflowers in your hand.
I was cold and hungry every day.
But I think you should know, too.
I remember everything.
You tried to commit suicide with me.
Subtitle translation by: Hae-lim Lee
Watch any video online with Open-SUBTITLES
Free Browser extension: osdb.link/ext