ENJOY ALL VOD IN HIGH QUALITY @ 4KVOD.TV
GET LIVE TV,MOVIES,SHOWS IN ONE PACKAGE
FAMILY MOTTO
A HARMONIOUS FAMILY WITH LOVE
It's your day off,
so take care of your own meals.
I'm coming home after eating dinner.
From Mom.
I know we've been busy making a living,
but we should've said
these things in our lives.
I love you,
my son.
I drank too much wine that day.
You know that's not an excuse.
I won't make excuses.
Threatening those around you
and giving them a hard time
just because you're hurt
is a terrible thing to do.
Do you know what I tried
the hardest
after you came out of the closet?
I studied you.
You don't have to try that hard.
Just forget me completely and start over.
I can start over
only when the end is good.
Even though I only studied a bit,
I could tell what kind of world
you were living in.
But it's still wrong.
Since that day,
I never opened the door to that room.
You have to see it.
Look for yourself how unproductive
and violent that moment was.
And clean it up.
Don't even leave a shard of glass.
The green light is on.
You may cross the street.
Ms. Jin-sook.
It's not too late, is it?
You're smiling.
Can I…
love you again?
Mr. Sang-sik!
Somebody help!
Somebody help, please!
Please help!
Somebody help!
Do you need help?
Are you okay?
I felt a bit dizzy.
I'm okay.
Dad has a bad liver.
He shouldn't drink.
He's been to the ER
too many times this year.
Liquor bottles were everywhere
in his house.
The ER is a money-eating monster.
I told Mom to watch Dad.
Is she still going to dance classes?
Money doesn't grow on trees.
Whether it's health or money,
when you have troublemaker parents,
that means you are middle-aged.
Both you and I are growing old
because of Mom and Dad.
I'm going to part ways with your father.
He didn't take it.
Regardless, he did
carry the medicine with him.
Are you
saying it's my fault?
Dad.
-Dad.
Tell her I'm going to work!
You'd all feel comfortable without me.
You're Mom is anxious
because I may say something dumb!
Dad, don't do that on this joyful day--
Get out!
All of you, don't stop him!
Let him go!
Mom.
-Dad, are you okay?
-Are you okay?
We're all family.
I thought we should
at least know each other's faces.
Troublemaking parents?
Good grief.
Is your dizziness better?
Yes.
Ringing in the ear and feeling dizzy
are the symptoms of BPPV.
Recently…
he lost his memories.
Shouldn't he have a thorough scan?
Yes, if you want a thorough scan,
please make an appointment
online or over the phone.
Okay.
Hello?
Hi.
Yes, I'm at my office now.
-Hi.
Thank you for doing this
when I asked so suddenly.
It's okay.
It's a new type of favor,
so I'm excited too.
-Please get in.
-Okay.
Lie down and rest.
I'm sorry.
You missed the show because of me.
You should've said
you wanted to rest if you were sick.
Missing a show won't kill us.
They do it all the time.
I never won against you in an argument.
How can I ever win against you
in an argument?
Right?
What's the point of winning
and losing about this?
No one's giving you prize money
for winning.
See? I lost again.
I threw the lunch box
because I couldn't win an argument.
I…
I only threw the lunch box, right?
I didn't smash a window
or anything, right?
The doctor said at the time
that the imagination and memories
would be mixed up.
It looks like you smashed
tons of them in your head.
If you ever did that in front of the kids,
I would've kicked you out
of the house already.
I may be narrow-minded and ignorant,
but I'm not that terrible.
I hope I'm not badly ill.
You…
So you do know how to come here.
I'm sorry about that day.
I will never do that again.
Okay.
Thank you.
I'm going to meet the attorney.
We'll settle things the way Eun-joo wants.
What's the point of seeing
the attorney then?
I don't want to calculate.
Eun-joo would've earned that much
if she kept working.
And…
I'm going to close my clinic,
but keep on working as a doctor.
Because I seem so pathetic,
I won't give up on everything.
Did you find a place to go?
I'm looking for it.
So don't make things worse.
I'll talk to Dad next time.
You hate that, right?
I'm leaving.
Eun-hee.
What?
Have you ever wondered why
Chan-hyuk doesn't have a driver's license?
He said he was going to get it.
He's getting a permit soon.
That's what I mean. He's been carrying
all that heavy camera equipment,
and he's getting a driver's license now?
Why are you suddenly curious?
Well, I didn't think much about it,
but Seo-young looked at him as a loser,
like she knows something.
Chan-hyuk knows everything
about our family story,
Don't you think you're too indifferent
to your friend's family story?
Sharing a family story
isn't a condition to be friends.
I'm the type to say everything,
and he's the type not to say anything.
Have you ever asked him?
Wow.
-It's great.
-Yes.
This is something I wanted
to experience in Korea.
I have no friends here, so I called you.
It's my first time here too.
I guess it is a new type of favor.
If it's your first time,
then I'm less burdened.
"My hometown birds
cry out 'peace.'"
This quote is by a cellist
who escaped the dictator.
He missed his hometown.
After I read that, I thought…
I had to hear the birds singing in Korea.
I guess he missed peace so much,
so the birds' songs sounded like "peace."
We have scops owls.
"Scoop it."
That's their singing sound.
The birds sound so different
depending on where you live…
I guess I didn't know.
After I came here,
everything is difficult,
my comprehension dropped,
and I'm making lots of mistakes.
That's how it is.
When did you leave Korea?
When I was ten,
my parents decided on their own
to send me to the US alone,
where my aunt is.
If you were ten, it must've been hard.
I knew you would understand.
At school, English gave me a hard time,
and at home…
I walked on eggshells with my aunt.
Couldn't they have told me
about what would happen
if I study abroad?
I blamed my parents a bit.
I'm sure your parents didn't know, either.
We're grown-ups too, so I'm saying this.
Grown-ups are a bit…
stupid…
and immature.
Have you ever wondered why
Chan-hyuk doesn't have a driver's license?
EUN-HEE
Hey.
Where are you, Chan-pal?
I'm out to eat.
A blind date?
Sorry. I'll hang up.
Figuring out the situation
just by the tone of your voice
without explaining that
you're meeting someone
and hanging up so she won't bother you.
I guess only old friends can do it, right?
She always pretends to be sharp-witted.
CEO Park.
What does Eun-hee hate the most?
How would I know?
I'm not even sure about what I hate.
Hating someone.
She hates that the most
and feels pain from it.
It looks like…
I've been giving pain to Eun-hee.
Eat it.
Mr. Kim Sang-sik.
You really didn't listen to me
your whole life.
You know that, right?
Start listening to me from now on.
Don't just worry about your illness,
just go to a big hospital
for a checkup and be relieved.
When you're old, you have to learn
to think of hospitals as your friend.
Don't tell the kids.
I'm sure it's nothing serious.
Would that be okay?
Don't you feel sad?
You heard it too.
When parents cause trouble,
the kids get old.
We didn't cause that much trouble.
I caused trouble.
Graduation from marriage,
failing to keep the secret,
becoming 22 years old again,
they're my fault.
You must think it's unfair.
A smart person like you becoming
a troublemaker because of me.
Our kids don't think
of me as a troublemaker.
I doubt that.
Have you ever read their minds?
Even if you graduate from marriage
and break up with me,
to our kids, we're always a pair.
You chose to be with a troublemaker,
which means you're also a troublemaker.
Here.
Troublemaker.
Have some.
Here.
It's about time for her to come.
Why am I hiding?
Go inside.
Don't think too much and go to bed.
Go on.
And drive safely.
Go on first.
Be careful.
Mom is having a fling with Dad,
who was 22 until recently.
EUN-HEE'S
I felt a bit dizzy.
I'm okay.
When did
time pass so quickly?
Just when?
Eun-joo, you were right.
I had no wits, and I was dumb.
They were like,
"Ms.Sook, you go in first."
"No, you go first, Mr. Sang-sik."
They just filmed a romance movie.
AND AFTER THAT
THE LIES OF MEMORIES
The new semester started
even before graduation.
My sisters.
say something, please.
I worked so hard this time.
I even put my soul into it.
Wait, I left my documents there.
I'm sorry.
Patent Attorney Kim.
Hi.
It's been so long.
How are you?
Can you wait for a moment…
I don't think you will.
How about some coffee
from a vending machine?
I have an appointment after.
Okay. See you again.
How's your sister doing?
Your sister
has settled in my heart as my avatar.
Though I don't know her name or looks.
When we were trainees, you told me that
if your sister was born a man,
she would be just like me.
I thought you were thinking
of me as a family-like colleague,
but there was a twist.
Your sister is immature, nosy,
makes things messy,
can't be straightforward, and…
her drinking habits are similar to mine.
I think I was scolded
for like five minutes.
That was when you were a trainee.
You're a CEO now.
I'm not a CEO. I'm a chief.
I don't remember dragging
my sister into it,
but I remember you didn't work hard,
saying trainees don't drop out,
so I worked hard on my own.
Oh.
I didn't remember that.
But I think I was lucky to have you
as my training partner.
Yes, I think this would be
a good way to finish it.
Okay.
Yes, you smelled a get-together, huh?
I'm having a martini
with the vice CEO tonight.
You should join us.
Just the two of you?
I, the incompetent one, have to work late.
There's always a spot for you.
Goodness.
-I approve of it.
-Want me to get you a taxi?
-Okay, see you tomorrow, bye.
-Have a safe trip home.
Kyung-ok…
knows about us.
So…
you shouldn't try too hard
to find out if she knows
or if she
spread rumors or not.
Rumors about me are fine.
But I don't want you to be in it.
I think I'd be too sorry…
to you, Eun-hee.
You were so confident
about knowing people's personalities,
but you know nothing.
Kyung-ok won’t tell anyone.
The rumors about you were
spread before it, so it can’t be helped,
but she will never mention me.
Kyung-ok is moderately timid and nice.
If she wants to spread rumors,
I'm sure she'll spread it
only when one of us
quits working.
And I…
don't care about the rumors.
It's not a made-up story.
I need to bear
that much of a rumor at least.
There were actually rumors about us
because I'm with her all the time.
I didn't meet her just to protect you.
Ms. Seo has lots of her own worries too.
I was wrong about people.
I need to start studying people
from the beginning.
Eun-hee.
Why aren't you asking me about
what Ha-ra told you last time?
You didn't think of asking,
since we're done?
I…
didn't believe what she said.
With a breakup coming up,
can you show your worst,
hurt each other
with words you shouldn't say,
get harmed and scarred,
and then…
suddenly become intimate and make love?
Can't you say it's because you trusted me?
I did trust you a bit too.
For a heartwarming ending.
On my day off, I met Chan-hyuk.
We sank our feet into the valley
and ate boiled chicken.
I'm trying to wrap it up
as a heartwarming ending in my way.
Goodbye. Drive safely.
Okay. Bye.
Over here.
-Hi.
-Yes, hi.
-I'll leave it to you.
-Okay.
When you come out of the closet,
the people around you react in two ways.
They drift apart feeling disgusted,
or they try to be nicer all of a sudden.
Why are you saying that
when we came all the way here?
That's how you behaved.
You acted like my friend, my sister,
and even like my mom at times.
It must've been tiring.
I just felt even more sorry.
If Mom didn't come home on that day,
I would've apologized
with courage while I was drunk.
And then I would've packed
and left quietly.
But when I saw Mom…
I didn't feel anything but anger.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry
that it's difficult to say sorry.
If you two are here together
what am I supposed to do?
Now. Stay alert.
Step on the brake when you begin,
start the car, turn on
the turn signal, and go straight!
You're distracting.
It's a hill.
Brake.
Stop.
Good. Turn your wheel more to the left.
No, to the left.
Slow down.
Hey, go straight.
-Go straight.
-Be quiet.
-Hey, like this.
-Okay, got it.
Now, here's the T-shaped road.
Go slightly slanted.
Turn the wheel to the left.
To the left.
Turn more.
Go in.
Slowly.
You failed.
Gosh.
Try it one more time.
Go away. You're making it worse.
Aren't you busy?
My friend is getting ready
for a very important license.
So I made time to come.
Ji-woo is so obvious.
He can't keep any secrets.
He even told you about this place?
To ask me why I didn't
get my driver's license until now?
I'm here to ask something else.
So many incidents were happening
at the same time that day.
So I suddenly recalled something I forgot.
During the period of coincidence,
when I met Jong-pal.
Right.
The wedding anniversary.
He asked me for your phone number.
Even when we cut ties,
I got your new phone number
via group message.
There's no need to be curious about that.
We blocked each other,
so he didn’t get the group message either.
Exactly.
I'm curious…
about how things ended with you guys.
She came to my house and caused a ruckus.
How can I go to you in the middle of that?
Come on, Soo. I'm done with her.
Please believe me.
I can't go. I drank.
You're coming?
Yes, come and see.
We finished talking. We're done.
All right, see you in a bit.
Did you eat? Do you want a drink?
Hey.
I didn't eat, drink, or hang out with her.
I kept quiet
because I couldn't kick her out.
-That's the same thing.
-Call her, you jerk.
Meet her outside.
I don't ever want to see her again.
Are you loyal to Eun-hee now?
She wouldn't even know.
Don't ever think of seeing Eun-hee.
You damn punk.
Why are you being so grouchy?
You know it gets weird
if you two meet without me, right?
I heard you punched him.
Rumor spreads.
You thought I wouldn't know?
I also know that there was
a rumor about us because of that.
Why ask if you know everything?
To see how you'd answer me.
But again you won't be straight with me.
Do I not mean much to you?
I'd feel really bad then.
Give me a chance
to be your personal safe
for once.
Eun-joo.
What's the emergency?
I'm going to tell Mom
about my divorce today.
Okay.
Tell her.
Tell her about it.
You got this.
I cheered for you, so goodbye.
Stay next to me when I tell her.
You told me not to waste my energy
on mediating conflicts.
Do it. You're the best at doing it.
Okay.
Hi.
I was craving your food, Mom.
You should've told me beforehand.
I was too frazzled these days
to go get groceries.
I just need kimchi.'
Okay.
Did you tell her?
Mom, I'm here.
You're here too? What's going on?
-Are you cooking? Can I help?
-Sure.
First, put beer in the fridge.
Mom, you have some too.
No, thanks.
Mom.
Let's eat first.
Mom…
what were you planning to do
after graduating from marriage?
Me?
DIFFERENT LIVES MEETING ON THE ROAD
Olle Trail and Dulle Trail.
I wanted to walk
the beautiful trails all over Korea.
I liked
Simon and Garfunkle.
You did?
There was this movie
with the song "El Condor Pasa" in it.
It's about a woman
who went through a hard time.
And she walks an extremely rough trail.
I was watching that movie,
and I wanted to try
walking the trail
with a backpack.
It became my dream.
This is the line from the movie.
"How wild it was,
to just let time pass."
Something like that.
I just
love that line so much.
I've been struggling all my life,
and I don't think I had
the chance to slack off
as much as I wanted to.
Your father lived like that too.
Then he got old all of a sudden.
What's wrong with you?
Let's go, Mom. We can go
to the Olle Trail in Jeju,
the Dulre Trail in Jirisan,
and just walk across the entire country.
You…
Don’t make any promises
you can't even keep.
Three women on a trip?
It can be dangerous.
Why can't I keep it?
What's dangerous about it?
You should stop party-pooping
about everything.
Let's go. Say you will go.
Yes.
Let's go, the three of us.
And we'll walk slowly
only on the safe trails.
Give me some of that too.
Okay.
Let me try drinking too.
Yes, you should drink some too.
Ms. Jin-sook, it’s been a while
since you drank.
Cheers!
A toast!
Hurry!
Cheers!
Let's go!
Hey, get in!
-Let's go!
It's so fast!
Go, Dad!
Go!
What brings you here?
Did your mother send you?
I came because I wanted to see you.
That's not how you hold the guitar.
I taught myself.
Dad.
I behaved like a kid that day.
You're the youngest.
Of course, you have to behave like one.
And you're all grown up.
You save all the money,
don't waste it, and you know
how to take care of yourself.
Dad.
You need to work less and drive safely.
And…
Yes, the point.
You should come back home now.
That's just your wish.
No.
I leave the house often too.
I'm worried about Mom being alone
at home all the time,
and you're not well, so…
That's…
for us to decide.
Okay.
You little brat.
Mom.
You need to be firm
if you made up your mind.
Don't worry too much about Dad.
If you keep on looking after him,
pampering him, and seeing him,
it'll be harder for him to move out.
You can look after him a bit.
He's still a beginner.
But if you go see him, you'll get weak,
so send Ji-woo or Eun-hee instead.
I disagree. He has to learn
how to do chores, so don't look after him.
Don't be his mom.
But you should meet him.
Ms. Sook. Mr. Sang-sik.
Call each other like that
and go on a date.
Be quiet.
Why do you care?
That's for us to decide.
"Us?"
-I'm going to go make money.
-Okay, cheer up!
Yes, have a safe trip home.
-Bye.
-Drive safely.
-Have a safe trip.
-Okay.
I liked…
Alain Delon.
-Alain Delon?
-Yes.
Alain Delon?
I don't think I've ever seen an actor
more handsome than he is.
Wow, this is crazy.
You care about looks.
I knew already.
You knew?
So you two shared
your tastes and left me out?
He's so handsome.
LOVELY COUPLE
HOLDING HANDS
FAR AWAY THERE IS OUR PARADISE
I feel left out.
How old is that boring song?
Is it from the Joseon Dynasty?
Ji-woo.
-Why?
-My son, come here, okay?
I'm not done with this.
You brat, come here.
Ji-woo, you brat.
Come and sit when Mom calls you.
You're drunk again.
-All right.
-Stop drinking.
You're becoming an alcoholic.
Have…
Have a drink.
On this joyful day,
we need to have a drink.
Stop drinking.
-Have a drink.
-You drink for a whole week.
Hey, you…
Cheers.
Hey, I have to drink alone
if you drink without me.
The problem is
every day is a joyful day for you.
I drink this beer with the money I make.
You call yourself a young brother
and won't even cooperate.
You're a brat at home.
And you always call me all drunk.
We…
could've lived like this.
Don't be nervous.
I, Kim Sang-sik, am a man
who's never nervous.
Let's make a confession to each other.
Why?
You called me Ms. Sook when you turned 22.
Now that you're memories are back,
you don't have anything to confess?
That's not it.
I'm not good with words.
Then…
you go first.
There were times…
when I felt that
you were like a big mountain.
I…
never thought of him who ran away
because he was afraid
to take responsibility for me.
You've been fighting
an illusion all your life.
When we were young,
when you asked nothing,
and said that we can overcome it together,
and announced that you will
be a good father,
you were wonderful.
Thank you for keeping your promise
to be
a good father
until now.
You only kept that promise
and caused all the ruckus, but…
thank you.
When did so much time pass?
There isn't anything particular
according to the CT scan from last time.
The CT scan has its limitations.
So you need to get
a more thorough checkup.
I'll muster up the courage
and confess something too.
I don't think I've been
fighting an illusion.
I think I've been fighting
my pathetic self.
I felt like a coward who hid the fairy's
robe so she couldn't fly ever again.
I was afraid someone might
criticize me and call me a bastard.
I think I forgot…
about that wonderful young man
of the past before you did.
Now. Stay alert.
Step on the brake when you begin,
start the car, turn on
the turn signal, and go straight!
CHARACTER OVER DRIVING EDUCATION
And stop at the hill.
I passed!
You failed.
Are you hurt?
I'm not.
-You aren't?
-Yes.
Let's check the accident.
An accident at the driving test area.
This rarely happens.
I'm going to take a photo
and make fun of you forever.
You called me…
because you needed a private safe, right?
Want to go to the office?
Fine.
You're the first male human
who came into my house besides my family.
I'll believe you.
Don't believe people easily.
It's quiet.
It's quiet, so I was able to stay
hidden for years.
It seemed like
you were looking for a place like this.
I had an older brother.
During the summer break when I was ten…
he passed away.
Don’t make that face.
It was a long time ago.
I don't like talking about it
so seriously,
so I didn't say anything.
He was only two years older than me,
but he went on a retreat,
and I went to the driving academy
with my mom and my aunt.
Mom said she'll buy me
the newest game console if she passed,
so I was determined
to never let my brother use it.
My mom passed,
and I felt like I could fly.
But then, my aunt
checked her pager.
Then she looked
at the two of us in silence
and started crying.
My brother
had a car accident
on his way to the retreat…
That situation
made no sense at all.
That was the day when my family couldn't
go back to the old days ever again.
My Mom…
No, my family
was never able to laugh
about small things anymore.
My family doesn't even argue.
But…
when I went to your house,
saying we have to babysit your brother,
I saw Ji-woo,
and I suddenly recalled
my late brother, so clearly.
I first saw Chan-hyuk when I was 12 too.
He bought me a digital camera
for my 12th birthday.
A digital camera?
The digital camera of the old days?
Yes.
You and Eun-joo bought me
a hamburger meal or toys
because I was young,
but Chan-hyuk gave me a gift
for grown-ups.
We went to take photos
during summer break.
That was when he started
to teach me how to take photos.
That was when I became a grown-up.
He's my true brother,
through middle school, high school,
and my military service.
So that's why…
you were nice to Ji-woo?
Yes.
When I saw Ji-woo,
I felt…
confused…
A little brother at the same age
when my big brother passed away.
At that time, I finally realized
that my parents have been
enduring all this time.
Ever since then, I felt like
I got a little closer to my parents.
Including my mom,
those who know about it think
that I don't learn to drive
because I lost my brother
in a car accident.
But…
I think
I've been ignoring that place
where my mom collapsed completely,
where our misfortune
had begun.
As I saw Ji-woo growing up…
I thought if my brother was alive…
he would've done all of these with me.
I'm sorry…
I comforted the ten-year-old you
too late.
Goodbye.
I forgot to say something important.
About what I said earlier.
I promised myself to tell
the story to the person
that would be by my side forever.
But you said…
you will be with me forever
already.
I'm going to keep
seeing you, contacting you,
and be on good terms with you, my friend.
"My friend."
You forgot "My friend."
Isn’t that too cowardly?
What's the point of being
friends forever at our age?
At that time…
I told you.
Everything about my relationship…
While you know nothing about mine?
I do.
So,
I don't care about that.
And the you I know
don't care about that, either.
You can be my friend then.
Well, we'll see each other forever anyway,
so I'm sure you'll change
when you get bored.
Drive safely.
Come in.
Sit comfortably.
Mother.
We…
decided to get divorced.
I'm sorry.
I'm not going to be
a troublemaking father.
I'll tell them proudly
after I fully recover.
He stood up for you
when people were bad-mouthing you.
We're not in that kind of relationship.
Eun-joo.
Try looking for your biological father.
He said he was dating someone.
He said she lives in Toronto,
but something feels off.
You know I love you very much, right?
I'm sorry, Chan-hyuk.
We seriously knew
nothing about each other.
Subtitle translation by: Hae-lim Lee
-== [ www.OpenSubtitles.com ] ==-