Hey! You!
I'm onto you.
I know all about you.
What's all this for?
We was done last week.
Why us again?
Quit moaning, Harry.
You. Out.
Move!
Sorry, Mr. Jackson.
Just saying hello.
Right, that's it.
Get this lot packed up.
Get sorted.
What have you got
with you, then?
Any money?
Phone cards?
Have you got stuff
you can trade, have you?
Bastards.
Right, Brinkley, shut it.
I am not sick!
Down on your knees.
Get... down... on... your... knees!
Seen enough?!
You want some more?!
Okay!
One of the reasons
they're going to release me
is that they don't know
anything about the divorce.
I can't keep on waiting.
But you've got to sign the deeds
over to me.
Harry Reynolds
and Steven Wolton, seven years,
Victor Braithwaite, 11 years.
Bloody hell.
What about Kelly?
ENJOY ALL VOD IN HIGH QUALITY @ 4KVOD.TV
GET LIVE TV,MOVIES,SHOWS IN ONE PACKAGE
Liam, come here.
Look up here.
Give me a bump.
Right.
You have the thing?
- Yeah.
- Touch me.
Boom.
Check me.
That's cool.
Learning something interesting,
Brian?
Hello, Mr. Gordon.
Down you come, you wee tosser.
Now.
So have they given you
an exact date?
The secure unit
will be completed on schedule.
Security's still a hazard,
though, isn't it?
Is there any truth in the rumor
that we may be privatized?
It is exactly that,
Ms. Hewitt... just a rumor.
Barfield's cost the government
too much money
to let it go
to private contractors.
I would've thought that was just
the reason to recoup the losses.
I'd keep the hard hat on,
Mr. Bunny.
It suits you.
Good morning.
Good morning, ma'am.
Bloody hell.
Ladies and gentlemen,
will the new personnel sit
in the front seats?
As quickly as possible, please.
Deputy Governor Gary Marshall,
HOC... head of custody.
Now, these two wings, C and D,
the block and the VP Wing
are now secure
until this section of wall
is reopened to the new wings.
Control unit there, and this
is the maximum-security unit.
Ma'am?
As you must all be aware,
the refurbishment
has advanced somewhat
in the past months,
but until the security system
is fully operational,
we still have
major at-risk areas.
We'll also be expecting a new
HHC... head of health care...
And a full-time doctor
in residence.
Ah.
And Ms. Collins will be
our resident psychologist
and drama coach.
Maureen Collins.
Sorry if I kept everyone
waiting.
You didn't,
but I'm sure you'll catch up.
Right.
Now, this morning I intend
to take all the new personnel
on a grand tour of the prison.
So if you have to use it,
sterilize it.
Better still,
don't bloody use it.
Okay.
That's all for this morning.
Come on, guys.
Move it!
Should never have brought him
back to Barfield.
Well, they have done,
and we've got to deal with him.
You got six
for protecting a nonce.
I got six for doing a nonce in.
Yeah.
Big boy now, are you?
Coffee?
You didn't hear me right.
Victor was the nonce.
You protected the nonce.
He's back on D Wing.
Oi.
Stop nattering and move along.
You want some advice?
You seem to be trying to get
some credit.
You have to deal with Victor.
He owes you.
- Morning.
Morning, ma'am.
Dr. Thomas, this is John Udding,
who's been working at Liverpool.
Mr. Tucker, Mr. Peters,
Mr. James,
Mr. Boyd, and Mr. Hood.
Look at this.
God knows how they're gonna
sterilize it.
The rubber
at the end of the plunger
has disintegrated completely
through constant use.
Instead of a rubber,
they're using
a small piece of black polythene
from a dustbin liner,
wrapped and held in place
with a piece of cotton thread.
It's madness, isn't it?
- Uh...
- Yeah.
Until the authorities admit
that we have a drug problem,
I can't instigate
methadone programs.
I'm not allowed
to supply needles,
so all that we can do
is to try and teach the users
to sterilize the needles
that they are
somehow bringing in.
I have tried sniffer dogs.
I have had cell searches.
And somehow,
the stuff is still coming in.
Fisher, come here.
You got to report
to the probation department.
You think I'd forget?
Finally come through.
What?
He's got home leave.
Sewing section
with four machines.
Uh, this isn't finished yet, but
it will be the music section.
Numerous instruments.
And this area here is earmarked
to be a recording studio.
Only needs one of them to blow
and there's a few hundred grand
down the toilet.
They've got one each per cell.
Um, all the corridors
and main areas
are monitored
with a central locking system,
which is operated
from the control room.
Want my personal opinion?
When the inmates see them,
you'll get a few
Des O'Connor impersonations
and a lot of aggravation.
Ms. Collins?
The gymnasium is not in use yet,
but as you can see,
we are fully equipped.
We also have, um, new indoor
squash and netball courts
and a new outdoor, floodlit
Astroturf football pitch.
And if they twist a muscle,
they can put their name down
for a physiotherapy session.
Not be in use until
the prison is officially open.
Remind you of a health farm yet?
It's a bit of a waste, isn't it,
if it's finished?
The security isn't, Ms. Collins.
If you'd like to follow me.
You're going out on trust, Alan.
You know the rules.
We will accept no excuses
if you are not back at Barfield
before 10:00 on Sunday evening.
I will be, Governor.
I know how important it is.
I'll lose my parole date
and the possible transfer
to an open prison nearer home.
So, any I should be
extra wary of?
Cell 47.
Kid called Kelly.
Got a six
on top of his sentence.
I reckon he might want to try
and hurt himself,
so we've got him next to one
we're extra wary of...
Norman Jones.
Keep an eye on them both.
Roddy Marsh.
C2.
He's always checked
through the night.
Self-mutilator... and a bad one.
Right, Fisher.
Gray suit.
Brown shoes.
White shirt.
Tie.
Looks a bit creased.
I don't know.
Going out to see your wife
and kids.
You look like a dosser.
How much would a new one
set me back?
You mean like this?
At least 20 quid, right?
Maybe more.
Twenty quid?
It's yours, you great clod.
Go on.
We had a whip-round for you.
Not all screws are bastards,
Fisher.
Go on.
You'd better have this
to hold your pants up.
You've got no belt.
And here.
Belonged to my uncle.
It's in perfect nick,
and as you're going out of one,
I thought you might need it.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Overloading the RAM
can cause problems.
If you don't back up all this
data onto your hard disk...
Officer Johnson, Gate 2.
Hi.
Is this the first section?
Have a nice weekend, Mr. Fisher.
Senior Officer Russell Morgan,
Zania Smith, assistant
to education department.
Quiet!
If you want to get started, this
place is bulging at the seams.
Zania, is it?
They'll be searched, all right.
I'll leave you to it.
Bollocks.
Shit!
This can't keep happening!
First let me get to know
who each of you are.
Oh, I'd love to get to know you,
sweetheart.
And let me let you know
straight from the start
that I will take
no sexist remarks...
no racial remarks.
You are here to be educated.
If you want to waste your time
and my time, you will be out.
Is that understood?
Right.
I know some of you are hoping to
take Open University degrees
and that due to the closure
of this department
you're behind on your studies.
Will you stop talking?
You.
Let the woman speak, man.
Hey, I see you have one
of my brothers on your team now.
Watch out, now.
Shut up and get down
to association.
Hey, what is it with you?
You have a problem.
You know that?
Oi.
Malahide.
They're letting the coons in
now, are they?
Thought I could smell something
on the wing.
Hey, Braithwaite,
you big ugly pussyhole, you.
You're gonna get
what you deserve.
You know that?
You'll get what you deserve.
I suppose you're used to that.
Victor Braithwaite.
You'll want to watch him.
A few months back, he got
11 years on top of his life.
He's not a happy man.
Four of them strung
an inmate up.
Hanged him.
Trauma suit cost a million quid.
Well, they get it on legal aid.
My mum can't get it just to take
her bastard landlord to court.
And I usually work with
the probation department,
as a lot of insight comes out
of the improvisation sessions.
Mm-hmm.
There is one thing I think I
should make clear
from the outset.
I like as little interference
as possible.
The group usually
functions better
if they feel
they're not being monitored.
I agree.
But I suggest that you also draw
in some of the other officers
to interact
in the improvisations.
I'm not averse to that.
I'm glad you're not.
We've had a lot of people sign
up for the education department.
I think that's mainly because of
the glamorous Ms. Zania Smith.
Not too many signed up for
your drama group, I'm afraid.
I'm sorry.
That sounded awful.
Right.
Is there anything else?
No.
I think I've covered everything.
Thank you.
Hey. Bet you there's
a swimming pool.
Any money on it.
Hey, Walter.
Have a look at this.
What do you think it is?
I don't know.
Nuclear bunker, maybe.
What?
What do they want
a nuclear bunker here for?
Let me down.
Brian, gwan, gwan, gwan, gwan.
Yo, yo, yo, yo.
What happened?
Touch me now.
You don't know how glad I am
for see you.
We need all the brethren
inside here we can get.
You know what I mean?
Listen.
I can ask you something?
You can get me back onto C Wing?
Because there's an arsehole
here named Braithwaite
and he's pure aggravation.
You know what I mean?
- See what I can do.
- Thank you, brother.
- Just one thing.
- What's that?
I'm not your brother.
I hear you.
Cool.
But let's try and maintain
some kind of advantage.
You know what I mean?
Help each other...
All right, puppa.
All right.
Hey.
You pay up here.
Where to?
Oh.
Um, railway station.
That's 50 pence.
See that big stupid claat
over there?
I signed up for classes.
Kelly want him hit.
Ask around.
And it'll be cash.
And so easy,
especially if he's pissed.
Now, I want the whole wing
falling over drunk.
You understand me?
I tell you for why.
'Cause that pussy,
he's like an ox.
You know what I mean?
Hey.
You have any more gear, mate?
No, man. I'm concentrating
on the liquor now.
Hey, Rasta.
I'm gonna cut
your dreadlocks off.
Enjoy your dinner.
Hey, now you're getting
well above your station.
Hey!
On the people.
I ain't eating this shit,
you know.
Give me another tray.
Well, go on. Cha.
- Tucker.
- Thank you.
Yeah.
Dreadlocks there.
When was it last flipped?
I don't know.
Why?
The white slip says
your Rasta's dealing.
Tell your S.A.
Was it you
that tipped off that Rasta
we were gonna strip-search
his cell?
Is that how you're working it?
Want to make this personal,
then?
I mean, are you trying to say
that I'm showing favors
to blacks because I am one?
Is that what you're saying?
What I'm saying is
there's a lot more of us.
You've got the wrong attitude,
mate.
You think cons are sent here
for a bloody holiday.
Their punishment, man,
is being sent down...
Loss of freedom, full stop!
Oh, yeah?
Your sister gets raped.
How do you feel about him
coming in here,
taking frigging music lessons
and getting stoned
from your Rasta pals?
Um, is this a private bout
or can anybody throw a punch?
It was private, Governor.
Excuse me.
Governor.
Office, please.
Excuse me.
Have a good night.
You wanted to see me
about a white slip?
Somebody gave the tip-off
that a Rasta was drug dealing
on D Wing.
But...
But what?
Well, it could be racial.
Racial? No.
The whole point
about the white-slip box
is so that the complainant
can remain anonymous.
Said he's dealing in hard drugs.
I'll look into it.
I think you should look into
Mr. Malahide.
Yes. I did overhear
your conversation, Mr. Udding.
I want no racial tension
between my officers.
Understood?
You also said
that loss of freedom
is the prisoner's punishment.
I used to think like that,
but I've changed my mind.
Loss of freedom isn't enough.
If you haven't got the money
for the taxi, I'll collect you.
All right?
He's at the station.
Well, I'm out of here.
I'm not staying to see him.
I've got nothing to say to him.
If you don't want to see him,
you don't have to.
He's got a bloody cheek
even coming here.
I won't see him either,
you know.
We just want him to sign the
deed to the house over to us.
And the divorce papers.
Then none of us need see him
ever again.
Anyone who wants to
watch the football match,
the video starts
in five minutes.
- That's all.
- There's the video.
Will any prisoner
willing to assist in the library
also put their name down.
Any prisoner
willing to assist...
Come on!
Oh, sod this!
Put me down for the black chick
with the legs, will you?
What do you want, Brian?
Computer training?
Accountancy?
Economics?
Swivel on it.
If you can't read nor write,
Brian, what's the point?
- What's this drama thing about?
- Poofters.
Hey. Those seats are reserved.
Move it!
Got you a seat, Anthony.
Well, if I was you, son,
I'd sign up for something.
You got six years.
You could qualify to be a doctor
in the time you've got.
Aye, you're very cocky now,
eh, Kelly?
Come here, Bri.
Come here.
Is that true what he said...
You can't read or write?
Course not.
He's just being a bastard.
Hang on, now.
Just listen.
There's special classes
for inmates
with learning disabilities.
I haven't got a disability!
Do you think I have one?
Suit yourself, son.
Go in and tell them Italy won
1-0.
Go on.
There's a good man.
Go in and tell them.
If I do this library schlep,
does that mean I don't have to
go to the workshop?
I've done it before, see?
In Wakefield and the Scrubs.
Library.
Sure.
Do you want me to check?
I'm not asking any favors.
What did Stormin' Norman want?
Oh, he wants to work
in the library.
Norman?
Oh, he wants off the workshop,
does he?
Complaining of headaches,
skiving bastard.
Well, it's Saturday.
There's no workshops.
- He's the only volunteer.
- Place your bets, lads!
Nobody's been allowed
to give them the result.
Norman doesn't get
any privileges, right?
You got that?
Italy won 1-0!
1-0!
Breakfast in a few minutes,
Alan.
That is the third
television set in six months.
They'll be lucky if they get
a black-and-white one.
- Morning.
I was just wondering
if you were free tonight.
Yes, I am.
Good. There's this nice
little Italian place.
Um... is it dressy?
No.
Well, it's semi-upmarket.
Uh, casual.
About 8:00?
Fine.
I look forward to it.
Have you found
my replacement yet?
Not yet.
A few weeks to go.
See you tonight.
You know where I am.
Only two days on call.
Oh, you're up.
Ron's just off to the garage.
Sleep all right, did you?
Fine.
Well, I'll see you later.
Ta-ra, June.
It's different.
Table used to be against
that wall, didn't it?
It's a different table, Alan.
And it's been decorated twice,
maybe more.
Tea?
Eggs and bacon?
Don't go to any trouble.
I lied.
Didn't sleep a wink.
Bed was too soft.
Not used to it, I suppose.
Can I have an omelet?
You've kept the house nice,
June.
I-I got this for you.
Your favorite, isn't it?
It's very smart.
Yes.
Well, Ron's a great help.
He's very handy
with cupboards and carpentry
and anything mechanical.
Surprised the social services
haven't copped the fact
he's been living here.
Maybe they reckoned
he was just a decorator.
I needed every penny
I could get.
I don't get subsidence now.
Ron's got his own garage.
And I own this house.
The girls.
Will I be able to see the girls?
They'll be working.
Sarah's got a job at a wine bar,
and Sue's at a new boutique
at the high street.
I know,
but that's not what I asked.
I'd like to see them.
They don't want to see you,
Alan.
I sort of looked forward
to seeing them, June.
And I'll sign the house over
and the divorce papers,
just like we agreed.
Just sit there.
- Ah. Ms. Collins.
- Morning.
Got a couple of helpers.
None of these are in any kind
of alphabetical order.
- I'm Maureen Collins.
- Oi. Where's that black chick?
- Shut it.
- Prisoner 872, Norman Jones.
C Wing, miss.
Well, Norman,
thanks for offering.
If, uh, you could start
unloading some of the boxes
over there.
And you are?
Uh...
Ooh.
Uh, I've got a migraine.
I-I think I'd better go back.
Sorry.
Come on.
Well, it's just you and me,
Norman.
Actually, if you could shift
that box over here
- and start unloading.
- Sure.
On here.
Hi.
Those are 50% off today.
It's me, Susie.
It's your dad.
I wouldn't have known you.
I recognized you straightaway.
Like your mother used to look.
I don't know what to say to you.
You don't have to say anything.
I was here.
Now I'm on my way.
I always loved you.
I'll never stop.
But I-I won't bother you.
Just wanted one last look.
No harm done, eh?
You did the harm.
I know.
And I have to live with it
for the rest of my life.
You know, I think we should try
and get the educational section
down one end,
the bodice-ripping novels
in another section.
- And then there's the...
- The classics?
Where do you want the classics?
Center shelves all along here.
Right.
You know they won't look
for a book.
They prefer to order
from the public library.
It gives them something to do.
Well, uh, that's the way
it was in the other nicks.
Sorry.
I must stink like a polecat.
What do you read, Norman?
Me?
A bit like Mike Tyson.
Well, according to the papers,
he reads Tolstoy.
I'm one ahead.
I read Dostoyevsky.
A man after my own heart
is Genet.
Refreshments.
You're a psychoanalyst,
aren't you, Ms. Collins?
No.
Psychologist.
You reckon any of the men
will read this one?
Margaret, Duchess of Argyll...
"Table Etiquette."
Well, we get what we're given,
Norman.
A bit like life, isn't it?
Ms. Collins, we've come
to take him back to the wing.
Thank you for your help.
I'll be in on Sunday.
If you'd like to give me a hand,
I'd be grateful.
The bastard's still not signed?
Well, when he comes back,
I'll talk to him.
One word from me or you,
and he's never going to get out.
He scares me, Ron.
- All right, Ron.
- Hey.
I've just been 'round
that new shopping mall.
Prices knocked me for six.
What sort of car is that
parked outside?
That's a Mazda.
Ron... I hope you don't mind.
I borrowed your razor.
What did I say, Ron?
One foot out of line,
and I'll call the police.
Come on, now.
Stop gassing. Come on.
Come on, you two.
How much should it cost for me
to have, uh, Victor Braithwaite
taken care of?
What are you asking me for?
It's just that everyone respects
you for knocking off a screw.
The only thing that I did...
was to destroy my life,
and I got 18 years
to think about it.
If you think
that deserves respect,
you need to get
straightened out.
Hey. It was him told me
Victor was a nonce.
So... feel even more of a prick
now, do you?
I own up.
I've been matchmaking.
- Hello.
- Good evening.
Would you like anything else?
Sir?
Would you like another drink?
Ask the young lady to come
and serve me, will you, son?
Uh, yeah. Well, sir,
it's busy at the minute.
Perhaps I can get you
another Coke.
At £1.50?
You must be joking.
I'm her father,
so don't mess around.
Go and get her to speak to me.
I've seen you ringing up
wacky totals, son.
So just do it.
Bloke down there says
he's your father.
Okay.
I don't want to talk to you.
Just leave me alone.
I've been away, Sarah.
I just...
I just wanted to see you.
You've grown into a lovely girl.
No thanks to you.
You've got every right
to feel angry.
I've got every right to tell you
I don't want to see you.
Couldn't we just talk?
No.
I don't want any of my friends
knowing about you.
I'm sorry.
Excuse me.
Um, I wonder, could we, um,
have another wine please?
Thank you very much.
So we... we, uh, we had a very
one-sided, amicable divorce.
She got the house, the kids,
the car, and the savings,
and I got a bag of clubs
and two suitcases.
So... So she...
She was very amicable.
Oh, thank you.
No, no, no. I-I'll...
It's just that I know Barfield
were after a full-time doctor.
- I just thought...
- I don't get much time off,
and I didn't realize
this evening was set up
for me to interview
your replacement.
What about yours?
There was one time
when I was standing in
for this local doctor.
My what?
You said you were divorced.
And I wanted to make
a really good impression, so...
Very friendly, a long time ago,
I got the cat.
Ah.
She left me for my partner.
I'm sweating 'cause I couldn't
find the bloody farm.
I'm sorry?
She said I was always working.
Too bloody right I was.
Standing in for him so that he'd
have more time off for my wife.
Towards this immense
pregnant cow...
In the end, you know,
that's what gets you.
He hands me a bucket and says,
"Well, you can look at the wife
after if it makes you happy."
I'm sorry.
What gets you?
The betrayal.
Women are more deceitful
than men.
Dessert, madam?
Uh, nothing for me, thanks.
Oh. Um, I'll have
the trifle, please.
- Thanks.
- You're not on a diet, are you?
No.
Afraid I have to go home.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry.
Look, I'm... I'm really sorry
about tonight.
You had me worried sick, Alan.
Where have you been?
Everything's changed.
And these.
Three quid.
Used to be 10 bob.
You want salt and vinegar
or anything?
No.
No, thanks.
I threw that in for nothing.
We don't get chips often.
I don't belong here.
I know that.
It's just hard.
I haven't got anyone to blame.
Come in, Ron.
Sit down, have a chip.
You've done well by my girls.
I appreciate it.
I don't suppose you've got
a beer in that fridge, have you?
No.
There's never any drink
in this house.
I won't be bothering you again.
Be all over by tomorrow.
Good heavens.
- This all your doing?
- Yeah.
They brought me in
after breakfast.
I've just got this case and, uh,
one on the far side to finish.
They're all, uh,
in alphabetical order.
And the magazine rack's sorted.
Strange, isn't it, the reading
material they allow in here.
Real-life detective.
Murder stories.
You'd think it would be banned.
And some of it
is pretty horrific...
Rape, torture...
mutilation, sexual deviations.
Still, life is full
of incongruities, isn't it?
Yes.
Have you done something
different with your hair?
No.
No, I've just had a shower.
These drama classes
you're starting...
Do you play those head games?
Not sure what you mean.
Well, act out your mother,
father, yourself.
That's what most of them do...
Shout a lot and wait
for the primal scream.
It can be therapeutic.
And give an insight
into the mind of someone
who finds it difficult
to communicate.
Answer me this.
Suppose you get a prisoner
who during the course
of one of these classes
lets out that he was
an abused child
and that that is
the fundamental seed
of all his criminal activities.
Well, what can you do?
You can't release him.
You can do nothing.
The damage is done.
Well, I disagree.
I can make him come to terms
with the abuse,
help him be able to adjust.
Adjust to what?
Eight, ten more years?
I'm gonna take him back
to the wing.
It's lunch.
Tell me this.
What kind of man
would out of choice choose
to work in a prison all day
locked up,
even if he does have the keys?
Still, I guess, behind bars.
Were you abused?
No.
But I knew you'd ask me that.
You haven't read up on me,
have you, Ms. Collins?
No.
Time to go back on the wing,
Norman.
Where do you want
the Kama Sutra?
Now, Norman. Come on.
You have a wonderful laugh.
It's like music in here.
Thank you, Norman.
Hair.
Come on.
Get back!
Officer down!
You bastard!
Did you actually hear
what was said?
He said something
about the Kama Sutra.
She was laughing.
- Governor.
- Gate 11 opening.
Gate 3 opening.
I honestly find this insulting.
If you're to question
my motives at this stage,
before I've even started...
It is my job to ask questions,
Ms. Collins.
Now, I don't know
what the hell went on here.
Do you really think
I'd be stupid enough
to jeopardize my job?
The prisoner concerned
worked exceptionally hard,
was highly intelligent
and methodical.
The prisoner concerned,
Ms. Collins...
Ms. Collins,
cut the throat of an officer
at his previous prison.
At Barfield,
he has already held one hostage,
and he has just now broken
another one's nose.
Then who was it
gave that prisoner permission
to assist me in the library,
Ms. Hewitt?
Before you start making
any insinuations
or accusations concerning
my professional capabilities,
I would say someone else
should be severely reprimanded
for placing me at risk,
shouldn't they?
Governor Lyons said
he'd told you about Jones.
I told you.
He's a ruddy psychopath.
Russ, he was also
the only available volunteer.
And anyway, since he's been
on his medication, he's been...
Roddy!
Show yourself, son.
Oh, shit!
It's Morgan.
We need a medical team.
We've got
all this bloody equipment.
Why wasn't the library covered?
How the hell did it happen?
I wasn't told
the library was open.
It isn't, but that's no excuse.
Control.
We're moving the prisoner now.
He's a mutilator.
Something must have provoked
him.
He never does that on weekend.
I can't have missed it.
I've got the timetable here.
No.
It's been changed.
New timetable as from yesterday.
£27.50.
What?
Oh, I'd better go back
to the station.
- I haven't got that much money.
- Faster by train.
It'd take a good
four and a half hours by coach!
Due to a fault on the line.
We apologize for the delay.
- Good luck, mate.
- Thanks, mate.
I think the engine overheated.
I'm on the hard shoulder
just after Junction 16.
Oh, God.
There's a man
running towards me!
Help me, please!
He's coming towards me!
Get the police!
Please!
You've got help me!
I'm...
- Get away!
- I don't want to hurt you!
Go away!
Your self-mutilator. Classic.
Somehow managed to shove a razor
right up to here.
Previous doctor
must have stitched him up
and not noticed it,
so he had it in case
of emergency, so to speak.
And what do you want me to do?
Run every self-mutilator
through a metal detector?
Maybe get this one over
to a mental hospital?
Have you been over the block
to see Norman Jones yet?
- I've only just got here.
- He is on medication.
Yes, he is. Largactil.
Three tablets per day.
Governor, are these them?
Found them in Norman Jones'
mattress.
That's the good news.
The bad news...
It looks like Fisher's gone
on extended home leave.
No! Get away!
I need to get to the prison!
I'm from the prison!
Help me!
Oh.
You, sir.
Stand away from that car.
He's an escaped prisoner!
I haven't escaped!
I'm trying to get back!
The 19th of May 1986,
Alan John Fisher admitted
that he had been under
the influence of alcohol
but denied playing any part
in the brutal murder of his son.
Tony John Fisher died
from the multiple injuries
inflicted by his father.
Alan John Fisher was found
guilty of the manslaughter
of his 18-month-old son.
I don't know how to thank
you fellas, but I owe you!
God bless you!
Prisoner Alan Fisher
returning back at...
One minute past bleeding 10:00,
Fisher.
That's what I call
cutting it fine.
Thank you very much indeed,
Mrs. Fisher.
It's all right.
Fisher's back.
No, it's not all right.
Take him down the block.
Oh, come on.
He was only one minute late.
If he had killed
his entire family,
who do you think would be held
responsible for that?
Fisher?
He's a liar.
So she told you, did she,
June, my wife?
Well... let me tell you
something.
If I had told you
about the divorce...
told you that she only wanted me
to sign over the house to her...
that she'd been claiming
Social Security payments
all these years,
I'd have never got out.
You know as well as I do
how much importance they put
on having a secure family.
I served my time.
And I did the hard way
because I wanted to.
You think you understand.
It was me.
Me... that made June not bring
my daughters to visit.
Me.
I battered my own little boy
to death.
Me.
I broke his skull and his arms.
Twisted his legs.
To this day,
I don't know why I did it.
Being drunk was no excuse.
I never thought
I'd ever be released...
I didn't even think
I had the right to hope.
Truth is, miss...
I killed my son.
Mr. Fisher, you will lose
all of your privileges,
and you will be held
in the punishment cells.
Thank you, Mr. Smith.
Take him down.
Yes, ma'am.
Come on.
Hey, Fisher!
Fisher!
Did you have a good time, mate?
Fisher, can you hear me?!
Can't believe they brought you
back in a police car.
One minute after closing time!
My daughters gave me
a big party.
- That's great.
- Nice one, Fisher!
With a cake!
Wife had a banner out!
Lovely!
"Welcome home, Dad!"
Watch any video online with Open-SUBTITLES
Free Browser extension: osdb.link/ext