api.OpenSubtitles.org is deprecated, please
implement REST API from OpenSubtitles.com
People would wonder
if you suddenly disappeared.
Letting others witness you dying in public
will make things much easier.
I would still like to save face.
I hope it will not be a disgraceful death.
- Master!
- My lord!
What is he saying?
- What happened?
- Look!
Assassins!
Master!
I will be sure to use your body well.
Young Master.
Darn it, Uk.
That is fine.
Do not come in.
What a shame.
Uk landed more blows this time.
- Are there two more left?
- Yes.
Cha Beom will be up against him tomorrow.
Darn it. I would hate
to see Uk lose to him.
Should I go instead?
If I let Uk win,
then this will all be over.
I doubt that will make Uk happy.
This is a bet against the Crown Prince.
It will simply be outsmarting him.
Uk may be losing, but he is improving.
Young Master.
Go to your room. Let me bring you a towel.
I do not know
who the last contender will be.
But Uk will not be defeated that easily.
Uk!
Where is Young Master Jang?
You must be here for your young master.
Yes, my lady.
You must be Mu-deok.
- Yes, my lady.
- I see.
You are the one
who is always by Young Master Jang's side.
She must be the egret
that Maidservant Kim mentioned.
I am here to see him before I leave.
Come in. Right.
I even brought some snacks.
Would you like some?
No, thank you.
She is sophisticated and polite
just like Maidservant Kim said.
Why are you still drenched
and standing there?
Hey, look.
This is what that guy did, right?
I should try it again with my sword.
I thought you were dispirited
after being thrown into the lake.
But you were just reviewing your fight.
I was downcast and embarrassed
the first couple of times.
I am just mad
that I have lost eight times.
You used to only wear
neatly-ironed clothes.
Seeing how you are still
in those filthy, wet ones
proves what you just said.
I am truly dirty.
You rushed yourself today.
You should not have charged at him
when he was in defense.
You should have waited for him
to put his guard down.
Right.
Had you suddenly taken a step back
after landing those blows,
he would have been relieved,
stopped defending,
and let down his guard.
Fighting is like a game of tug-of-war.
Your opponent will pull
if you feign letting your guard down.
That is when you should strike.
Thank you for your advice, master.
Where are you going?
I should bathe and get changed.
I think I am reeking as well.
You must be here for your young master.
Do not go.
Do not go to your room and just stay here.
- I will bring you your clothes.
- What for?
I can go get changed.
Why would you be a fool
and tire yourself out?
You are right.
I am just being a fool.
You may go.
Mu-deok.
Stop there.
What is it?
Sit down.
Come on.
Goodness, look at your shoes.
They are drenched.
Why…
Why would you follow me
and try to jump into the water?
You see, there are times
when you are unnecessarily hard-working.
Why do you put your heart into cleaning?
Just use me as your excuse and rest up.
Maidservant Kim sent
some abalones and dried yellow corvina.
You should have some yourself.
Do not give them all to me.
Do not worry.
Everyone treats me well
since I am close with Dang-go,
the heir of Songrim.
That is what I thought.
I knew you would use
your power to your advantage.
You are injured.
I fought for eight days on end.
This is not my only wound.
Then where else?
Let us go to Sejukwon and get you treated.
I still have more fights left.
I should get injured as much as I can,
as much as my master expects of me.
Your feet will freeze.
You should get changed too.
Maidservant Kim?
You are ready, Your Royal Highness.
The medicine does not stop being bitter.
Do you have anything sweet?
I will prepare the sweetest snack.
There should be a red jade
that goes with it.
They are only valuable
when they are together.
Should I just throw this away?
What?
What is wrong with this?
What could this be?
Someone is pulling me in with great force.
This in explain able attraction…
It is calling to me.
- Damn it.
- Damn it!
Why would you fill her jade with energy
and confuse me like that?
This greatly offends me.
Likewise.
I am truly offended that
you were the reason why my heart raced.
Darn it.
By the way,
did you feel it too?
Did your heart thump…
- Darn it.
- Do not say that.
Forget it.
Seeing how surprised you are,
I guess you have never used this properly.
Right.
Since Mu-deok does not know magic,
I doubt you two were able
to share your energy.
You are right.
I did not know this jade had such power.
That is enough!
- Darn it.
- Anyway, I learned something new
because of you.
- Thank you.
- What is it?
Are you planning to use it?
I doubt you will be able to.
Mu-deok will not get this back.
I still have two matches left.
I will get it back and put it to good use.
So please keep it safe until then.
And please do not ever
fill it with your energy again.
The same goes for you.
Your Royal Highness, where have you been?
Should I take you in?
I can do that.
There must be things you can do here too.
No, thank you.
- Eunuch Oh.
- Yes, Your Royal Highness.
Find out who will be up against Uk next.
Yes, Your Royal Highness.
You better be right.
THE ART OF HYEONGONG
Hey.
How was Jang Uk?
Jang Uk? It was a cakewalk to beat him.
- Are you ready for your match?
- Of course.
At the very end, I will use Hyeongong to…
He is a mage from the Cha family
who can use Hyeongong.
He had been watching Uk all along.
He is a coward who has only stepped up
after seeing Uk lose several times.
Uk might be able to beat him.
Hyeongong is a spell that
may look fancy on the outside.
But it will be useless
if the user lacks the skills.
Beom may look intimidating
at first glance,
but that could just be a front.
Yul sure can see through others.
Is that so?
But he was telling others
about how easy it would be
to beat Young Master Jang.
He is just worried.
Uk has improved greatly
in the past several days.
He is scared that Uk will beat him.
I guess my young master has improved
quite a bit for him to be worried.
Are you that thrilled
that Uk has become stronger?
Of course. I cannot be any prouder.
Naksu is training Uk.
Yul.
Did you hear?
There is a commotion in the capital.
What happened?
Master Kang from Daegangtongun
succumbed to his illness.
But rumor has it
that some assassins
attacked him last night.
My uncle and Master Heo
rushed over to his funeral.
What if more assassins
like Naksu have appeared?
THE LATE KANG MAN-CHEON
Why can we not offer our condolences?
Transporting precious goods
is our family business.
But if people find out
that the man of the house
was killed by some assassins,
we could become jobless.
We told everyone
he died of a contagious disease.
That is why no one can enter.
We understand.
Have you found any evidence
that could help us find the assassins?
Has an autopsy been carried out?
Master Kang was stabbed to death
in front of our eyes.
An autopsy is unnecessary.
We will cremate his body tonight.
That soon?
It is unfortunate.
But we must hurry
before the rumor spreads.
I am certain Master Kang would have
also wanted this for his family.
That is unacceptable.
If you cremate his body,
there will be no evidence
that will link to the assassins.
This is a family matter.
I understand that you are worried.
But the leader of Songrim
does not need to concern himself with it.
An autopsy is needed.
Postpone the cremation.
Has Songrim gone as far as to meddle
in other families' funerals?
We are not meddling.
I am simply trying to prevent
the new man of the house
from making an irreversible mistake.
Why is Songrim's leader against this?
What gives you the right?
Only recently did Naksu attack
the mages in the capital.
Now, new assassins have emerged.
There could be a link between this case
and Naksu who used sorcery.
That is why I am interfering.
There was no sorcery involved.
I witnessed it all.
How can you be so sure without an autopsy?
The new man of the house
does not want an autopsy.
Jin Mu! You have no say in this.
We have the right to interfere
if there are suspicions
of sorcery being involved.
Do you not agree, Lady Jin?
I believe
the Assistant Gwanju is right this time.
The family's heir witnessed
Master Kang's death.
And he has no choice but to hide it
due to their family business.
No evidence hinted
at sorcery being involved.
So I do not think Songrim
should cause a commotion here.
I just want to protect his honor.
Please let us proceed
with this funeral discreetly.
Jin Mu does not hesitate
to look down on Songrim now.
Why are they so against the idea?
- It is suspicious.
- By the way,
I had no idea
Lady Jin would take Jin Mu's side.
She used to hate her half-brother.
I was truly pleased when you took my side.
Look.
Songrim had no choice but to back down
once we joined hands.
How close are you to finding Bu-yeon?
We searched all the areas
around Lake Gyeongcheondaeho
for blind girls
who were around Bu-yeon's age.
I have been doing that for ten years now.
To be honest,
I believe I found
the whereabouts of Bu-yeon.
A young girl had washed up
near the lake ten years ago.
- Is that so?
- However…
She was long dead.
Mother, I doubt that was her.
I told my men to dig up her grave.
If Bu-yeon truly is dead,
I will bring her body
back to you at all costs.
That is unacceptable.
Bring my daughter back alive.
I will, so please calm down.
We will find her alive.
Did you take a good look?
They will be your mother
and younger sister.
Do you think
they will think that I am their daughter?
You are dressed
like Bu-yeon when she was young.
But I am not sure if Ho-gyeong will agree.
Then being well-dressed
will not benefit us.
I must look shabbier and more pathetic.
She is a mother who has lost her daughter.
I can only win her heart
by pulling at her heartstrings.
Yes.
You are right, So-i.
I will see to it…
That I become a daughter
of the Jin family.
You look much better now.
I tend to recover quickly.
This Hyeongong technique…
Is quite elaborate.
I have my suspicions
regarding Master Kang's death.
Master Kang was powerful
with a great mastery of spells.
But he was already suffering
from a fatal illness.
There was no need for anyone
to send the assassins.
Maybe someone had a grudge against him
and wanted to kill him themselves.
No.
There must be a reason
why those assassins came,
although we do not know yet.
Once the soul is shifted,
the former body becomes useless.
But we cannot get rid of it that easily.
In other people's eyes,
that body belongs to a powerful mage,
an administrative officer, or a merchant.
They will only suspect something
if that individual disappears.
Naksu was the one who took care of them.
Do you mean the Shadow Assassin?
Thanks to that crazy assassin,
Songrim never suspected
that I was making soul shifters.
Back when I was after Naksu,
I thought she was just a lunatic
who wanted to show off her skills.
That is why I never suspected
the individuals that she killed.
Are you saying that she killed those
whose souls have been shifted by Jin Mu?
To be exact,
they must have been those
who were discarded afterward.
Did you not say
that Naksu was Cho Chung's daughter?
Are you saying he took that little girl
and turned her into an assassin?
That is why I never revealed myself to her
and made her live
in the mountains by herself.
I took care of her
just enough for her to survive.
But she was determined
and grew to be remarkably strong.
Because…
She thought by doing so
she would be avenging her parents.
That is why she obeyed Jin Mu.
She was very useful.
Then a soul shifter ran wild before dying.
Thanks to him,
Songrim got wind of the alchemy of souls.
Once Jin Mu heard that we were after her,
he was probably afraid of getting caught.
He probably sent Naksu to Songrim
despite knowing that she would die.
Mu-deok, go and get some water.
Yes, ma'am.
Mu-deok, will you seriously
not listen to me?
I told you to just get some rest.
Then what about you?
Did I not tell you to treat your wounds?
I stopped by Sejukwon.
At least I listened to you.
Check for yourself.
I smell mugwort.
What is wrong with you?
You know I am struggling these days.
I am just exhausted.
How warm.
Did you get a hot mugwort massage?
Yes. I am warm, right?
Yes. You are.
She was used for all the wrong reasons
and met a terrible death.
Naksu…
I truly pity her.
You are cool now. Let me go.
- Did you change your shoes?
- Yes.
Did you have the food
Maidservant Kim brought?
Yes. I had already had some
before you even mentioned them.
Well done. Mu-deok.
I did not know how fascinating this was.
The yin-and-yang jade?
I only found out because you had given it
to the Crown Prince.
How is it fascinating?
- Show me.
- I cannot.
I will show you
once I get yours back.
You will give it to me again
after you get it back?
Why? Will you not accept it?
I will retrieve it
and place it in your hand.
This thing has unbelievable powers.
It is a relief we did not know.
You are in for a shock once I get it back.
What kind of powers? Show me.
The Crown Prince
foamed in the mouth and fainted.
It was terrifying.
That makes sense. It was from Jinyowon.
It could be a lethal weapon.
Hello, Assistant Gwanju.
The leader of Songrim returned
to watch the cremation for himself.
What will you do this time around?
I am only here to observe.
This is the last time
I will ever see Master Kang.
It is my duty to see him off.
You have seen a soul shifter before,
so you will recognize the blue mark.
Check and see if Master Kang's body
had been used for soul shifting.
Even if we find out
that he has shifted souls,
we will not know
whose body he has shifted into.
There is something you must do
to help us find that out.
I know that you have
already mastered Chisu.
I did not hide it on purpose.
I am not scolding you.
What I am about to ask you to do
is quite dangerous
and might suck away your energy.
Only those
who have mastered Chisu can do it.
A soul shifter runs wild
once their energy is lost.
The body is still warm.
Pour your energy into him.
And make him run wild.
My lord…
What is it?
He is…
I will collect his bones, so step aside.
This is a soul shifter
who has been petrified after running wild.
Now that we have solid evidence
of sorcery being involved,
can Songrim take over?
Seeing how you are not disturbed
and even tried to hide it,
you must have already known about this.
You already knew
that this was a soul shifter
who had run wild.
Judging by your skills,
I believe Master Kang's soul
is within that body.
Then that body's original soul
must be dead alongside your body.
Cut that nonsense!
You are running wild
after having lost blood and energy.
The more you use your skills,
the faster you will become petrified.
You better stop.
You should stop here.
- Do not kill him!
- Kill him.
A soul shifter who is running wild
is dangerous.
Thankfully, Cheonbugwan got rid of him.
Since you have helped us,
we will let Songrim take credit for this.
- My lord.
- Yes?
Since you said we could take credit,
we will take the body and examine it.
Be my guest.
I closed his gate of energy
to prevent more energy from seeping out.
We need to revive him and make him talk.
Will it be possible?
He is pretty much a breathing stone.
Yet you want him to speak?
This will not be easy.
Are you worried
that he may still be alive?
Even so, they will not succeed.
Perhaps it is possible
with the help of the ice stone.
But that is their only bet.
Are you saying he can be revived
with the ice stone?
That is correct.
And you are in possession of that stone?
You do not need to know that.
Get the assassins ready.
I will find a way
even if it means shifting the soul
of a Jeongjingak mage.
- Hey, Beom.
- What?
Let us go.
THE ART OF HYEONGONG
PRESSING THE HEAD OF A LEOPARD STANCE
DIRECT SENDING STANCE, CAULDRON STANCE
Yul.
Uk.
Are you going to train?
Yes.
And you?
I just slashed…
A soul shifter.
Master Kang who had passed away yesterday
was a soul shifter.
Really?
But how did you know that?
If they hide their blue mark,
they can easily blend in
with other people.
But once they run wild,
there is no turning back.
They will start to petrify
as their energy seeps out.
They can prevent that
by feeding on others' energy.
But once they do that,
they will no longer be humans,
but monsters.
Monsters?
And it is our duty to protect this world…
From such monsters.
We can also protect
the monsters from this world.
Once we keep them in check,
the world will be at peace.
Everyone had high hopes for you
ever since you were little,
so you think
you need to do something grand.
But I was told
to sit still all my life.
I will follow
my heart.
Jin Mu let Songrim find out
something critical.
What if Songrim suspects
the palace as well?
The Royal Palace…
Is not a place he can just barge into
like he did at Daegangtongun.
If he does, I will be in danger.
Ever since Gil-ju died,
I was not able to feed on energy.
I am afraid I will run wild.
Could you share some of the power
of the ice stone with me?
What did you say?
The only person who can serve you
despite knowing your true face…
Is only me, is it not?
Shaman.
You little…
I told you never to address me like that.
Would you like
to be petrified this instant?
I know you cannot do that.
I am the only one in this palace
who knows that you are Shaman Choi,
despite residing in the Queen's body.
If I die,
you will bring your sibling here
from Jinyowon?
Furthermore,
the real Queen is residing in your body.
Should I not visit her from time to time?
Right?
It is getting difficult for me
to live in this body.
Tell Jin Mu
to shift my soul
into someone else's body once again,
Your Highness.
I understand.
You may leave.
Why are you here?
I will let you beat me.
Then it will all be over.
I forfeit.
Hey, Uk!
You wanted to go before me.
And you won.
Dang-go was willing to let you beat him.
How could you refuse?
I did not know
you were this proud of yourself.
You gave me this signal
and told me not to fight him.
When did I?
I only looked at you out of relief.
Then you should have signaled me.
Like this.
I did.
How could I understand that?
Had I known, I would have just done it.
You only have one chance left.
What will you do?
What, are you blaming me?
Why are you getting mad at me
when you gave that jade to him?
Are you seriously
pointing fingers right now?
How childish.
Childish? Do you want me
to show you what real childishness is?
I quit.
Should I keep this up?
Mages have been guarding
Sejukwon since last night.
The soul shifter's body must be in there.
If it was a body, they would have
kept it in the secret room.
Why would they take it to Sejukwon,
which is for the living?
I came by because I was curious
about what happened to the body.
Please wait. I will inform our leader.
I heard the leader was here at Sejukwon,
so I came to see him.
No one is allowed
to enter Sejukwon at the moment.
Then I will meet
with Young Master Jang first.
Please tell the leader that I am here.
Jin Mu is here
to check if the soul shifter
has really died or not.
Tell him to leave
since we are still investigating.
Yes, my lord. However,
someone else is here to see you.
Tell them to leave.
No one is allowed anywhere near Sejukwon.
Yes, my lord.
I will tell Maidservant Kim
to leave as well.
What?
Maidservant Kim?
I will tell her
that the leader cannot meet anyone.
Hold on.
She can be an exception.
It has been a long time, Maidservant Kim.
I stayed at Gwanju Jang Gang's residence
when I served him,
and you made me
countless delicious dishes.
You ate so much
that your rice bowl was exceptionally big.
Do you remember?
You had a huge brass bowl.
Back in the day, I was always hungry.
You must have made
something scrumptious once again.
Yes, I have. I made these snacks myself.
Honey biscuits.
I used to love them back in the day.
Yes, indeed.
Every time I gave some to you
to give to the Gwanju,
you would stash a few in your pockets.
I did that because I was only allowed
to eat once he finished.
In any case, I benefited a lot
from the Gwanju while following him.
I had a chance to taste
such delicious treats
and learn a special spell.
Does it not taste sweeter
if you eat it in secret?
That is exactly why
things that taste sweet are dangerous.
Once you have a taste of it,
you desire it at all costs.
You fail to distinguish
what you can have
and what you cannot.
You are hurting my feelings
by not letting me have any.
Goodness, do not be so stingy with food.
The Gwanju loved this snack.
How about his son?
Young Master Uk loves
honey biscuits as well.
Then shall we share this with him?
I have many stories
to tell him about his father.
You and Uk have nothing to talk about.
You may leave.
He just wants a biscuit.
Do not be so heartless.
You are not letting me share
the good memories with him.
But then again,
you must not want me
to touch what is yours.
Wait.
Here. This was actually
for our young master,
but you can have it instead.
Maidservant Kim.
Do not give that to him.
If I truly wanted to have some,
I would have easily stolen a few of them.
But I will let you win.
It had been a while since we last met.
I am truly sad to say goodbye.
Jin Mu used to take revenge
if he was scolded for eating something.
They were just honey biscuits.
You should have let him have them.
I just did not want him to eat
what you worked so hard to make.
Sit down.
We have not seen each other in a while.
Let us chat over some tea.
Is something wrong?
You seem quite testy.
Do not worry.
Once I have your honey biscuits,
I will feel better.
Mu-deok.
I need you to run an errand.
An errand? What is it?
Go to Cheonbugwan.
This just does not feel right,
so I need to send this over.
Sure.
Is something going on at Sejukwon?
I do not know the details.
But I think it is related
to last night's incident at Daegangtongun.
I heard Cheonbugwan
and Songrim had a fight.
Where is Yul?
I have not seen him since last night.
He must be doing something for the leader.
Really?
I just slashed…
A soul shifter.
We must strengthen Songrim's boundaries.
You are forbidden
from leaving Songrim for the time being.
Those who have mastered Ryusu and more
shall go to Sejukwon
and follow Sang-ho's orders.
- Yes, my lord.
Jang Uk.
You will stay here.
Everyone except for Uk
will follow Sang-ho and go to Sejukwon.
- Yes, my lord.
My lord.
Why am I not going?
You are exempt
since we do not need you there.
Is there something dangerous there?
Is it a soul shifter?
It is none of your concern.
Do not be curious about it.
Why are you keeping me in the dark
when I am also a mage here?
You are excluded from everything.
If you are bored of being alone,
you may leave Songrim.
Go back to your home
and do whatever makes you comfortable.
Yes, my lord.
Thank you for worrying about my comfort.
Mu-deok.
Let us go to Chwiseonru
and have something tasty.
All the mages were headed to Sejukwon.
Why are you not there?
I was told to stay out of it
and that I did not need
to concern myself with the matter.
- Let us go.
- Maidservant Kim gave me an errand to do.
Sure. Let us go together. Where to?
Cheonbugwan.
Let us go.
I heard that you told her
to shift you into another body.
Will you do that?
Then let me shift souls with that girl
who will enter Jinyowon as Jin Bu-yeon.
I have been a eunuch for a while,
so I do not mind a woman's body.
I would like to shift my soul
into a powerful body like the Shaman has.
"Shaman."
She was offended by how you reminded her
that she was a shaman dealing
with trifling affairs like divinations.
I was only stating a fact.
I was also reminded today of how I used
to beg for food and steal snacks.
They were indeed facts,
but I was still unhappy to hear them.
Jin Mu wanted a honey biscuit
while visiting Songrim,
but Park Jin did not let him have any.
Maidservant Kim was worried
he would hold a grudge,
so she wanted me to deliver this.
Are you saying they were childish enough
to fight over some food?
Our leader has a cheap way
of tormenting others.
Why was he so picky about a honey biscuit?
You are right. He was cheap.
Here, at Cheonbugwan,
we have records of all the constellations.
I will tell the Assistant Gwanju
that this was from the Jang family.
Please tell him that
it was from Maidservant Kim.
Tell him that we use a lot of oil
in our honey biscuits
and that he should have them
with green tea.
Yes, Young Master Jang.
We also use a lot of honey
for our honey biscuits.
He should store them in a cool place
or they will become sticky.
- Yes, Young Master Jang.
- Since we have brought that,
- can I take a look inside?
- Yes...
- Sorry?
- Thank you. It will not take long.
Let us go.
But…
I have always wanted to visit.
Despite my father being the Gwanju,
I never got to visit.
Gosh, what is that?
You have been here, right?
Your father was
a constellation recorder mage.
Did you come here for me?
You could have asked
someone else to run the errand.
Was it not
because you wanted to come here?
My father brought me here often
when I was little.
He even showed me the plate
that was recorded the day I was born.
He was a considerate father.
Come to think of it,
I believe he recorded the constellation
on the day you were born.
Is that so?
The constellation of the day I was born
must be somewhere here.
You had promised to shift my soul.
But rather, you are making me run wild.
You are no longer needed.
You will turn into a stone now.
You have gone insane.
Once night draws in, the mages will come.
Let us watch them
record the constellations.
I heard it is a magnificent view.
I would love that, but it will be
troublesome if we get caught.
Let us just go home.
Eunuch Kim has run wild.
No one must find out
that he is a soul shifter.
He is still in Cheonbugwan.
We must find him before morning comes.
Yes, my lord.
I know you are here.
Do not cause any more problems
and just come out.
I will give you what you want.
Come on out.
- Come on out!
- I will.
- Jang Uk.
- Yes.
Why are you here?
I am sorry. I was running an errand
and decided to take a look around.
An errand?
I heard you really wanted
our honey biscuits.
Honey biscuits?
She saw you were sad that
you did not have any honey biscuits,
so Maidservant Kim told me
to send you some.
Thank you. Tell her I said thank you.
What?
I thought you would be upset
that I came in here without asking.
Are you not mad?
You only came here to give me
the honey biscuits. You may go.
What a relief. To be honest…
I have company.
Mu-deok, come out. He is not mad.
She is my maid.
I am Mu-deok,
his maid.
You were here as well.
I thought you would be furious.
I am truly grateful for your hospitality.
Please enjoy the snacks.
Let us know if you want more.
Thank you.
Let us go.
He is a royal eunuch.
What is wrong with him?
He is a soul shifter.
Look. He is running wild.
I cannot believe a soul shifter
was inside the palace.
It was probably
his doing.
I know you are here.
Do not cause
any more problems and just come out.
I will give you what you want.
Come on out!
I will.
Run.
There is a door behind us.
Why will you not let us leave?
I do not think it is right to let a mage
who has barged in here leave so easily.
You will be in a tight spot
if I disappeared from Cheonbugwan.
I never said I would harm you.
Your body will still be around.
Uk.
You are within a barrier that I have made.
Do not worry.
You will be unscathed
as long as you sit still.
Wait there for now.
Mu-deok, was it?
So you were the maid
who always stuck by his side
and caused a nuisance.
There is a human here.
Come and replenish your energy.
After that,
I will let you shift souls
with a young master as you wished.
Did that wench Shaman Choi
tell you to kill me?
I need your help.
If you do not trust me,
I will stay outside.
Feed on her as you please.
I need to get out of here.
Master, help me once again.
Give your hesitant pupil confidence.
Jang Uk.
Mu-deok.
Mu-deok!
I…
I just fed on his energy.
Am I…
Running wild?
- Mu-deok.
- Do not come near me.
No, you are fine.
You are all right.
- You will be fine.
- No.
Do not touch me.
If I am truly running wild,
then you must not touch me.
Otherwise, your energy will be stolen
and you will die.
There was a loud noise coming from
the Constellation Recording room.
Come on out!
Are you angry that we turned
your friend here into stone?
You will never be able
to leave this place.
Are you saying that a member
of the Cho family is in this household?
What if her spirit
is indeed lingering by Uk?
If I had not left you
there in the mountains…
You would not have to suffer this fate.
You said you have bet your life?
This time, place yourself for the bet.
I will definitely win tomorrow.
I only need those
who will definitely win the duel.
If he is looking for
the ice stone to protect her…
They must not be together.
Everything about you has been exposed.
Subtitle translation by: Soo-ji Kim
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org