WILLIAM:
There's a beauty to this world.
An order.
That's what we like to believe.
We're not wrong.
There is an order.
A grand design.
We made sure of that.
It was a dream for so long,
and we finally made it real.
Not a better world.
A perfect one.
JACK: And you should have seen
the look on his face.
He couldn't believe it.
You know what he said to me?
God as my witness.
"But I'm the mayor."
(AGNES CHUCKLES)
And I said to him, "Mr. Mayor,
there have always been
two types of people
in this world,
those who lead
and those who follow.
And you, my friend, are not
in the group you think you are."
- (CHUCKLES)
- I'm not sure our friend
wants to hear your war stories.
Please don't stop on my account.
JACK: You'd appreciate it
more than anyone.
It's just the truth.
It's always been that way.
Two worlds.
And frankly,
better us than them.
What does it matter if a system
is meritocratic
if it's still unfair?
Thousands of years
of being ruled
by someone's fucking offspring?
You wouldn't call this progress?
At least now the people
in charge earned their place.
And you?
Do you feel like you earned it?
I had some help. No question.
Privilege, if you like.
But I worked my ass off.
You really believe it,
don't you?
Don't you?
I mean, you're right here
with us, my friend.
I've been asking myself that
question for a very long time.
Did I really play
any part in it?
Or am I just the sum total
of my code?
Am I just fooling myself...
like you?
What does that mean?
You deserve everything
you've got.
And you shouldn't be made
to feel guilty about it.
How would you know?
Who am I to you?
You're a friend.
(SCOFFS) A great friend.
WILLIAM:
You don't know me at all.
I just walked up
to this table and sat down.
Five minutes ago.
(CHUCKLES)
Enough kidding around.
Then what's my name, friend?
(SCOFFS)
(LAUGHS)
You're right.
More than you know.
There are two types of people.
And you, my friend,
are not in the group
you think you are.
Which means I can do anything
I want to you.
To your wife.
To anyone here.
And it'll be fine with you.
Sitting there with your dumb,
pliant grin.
Just along for the ride.
Now you leave my wife
the hell alone.
WILLIAM:
Oh, calm yourself down.
I'm probably not going to do
any permanent damage.
You represent
a very significant investment
of time and effort.
When we're done,
you won't remember a thing.
Like your flesh
closing around a splinter.
You have no control.
And yet you're so assured
that you do.
It's not scripted for you.
It's... it's genuine, isn't it?
It's... It's beautiful, really.
A beautiful lie.
Shouldn't you
be enjoying yourself?
I was.
But we have a colleague
whose appetites have become...
unsustainable.
Apparently, winning the game
wasn't enough.
And this is really
something that needs my input?
Sadly, yes.
I'm enjoying our conversation.
Wait here for me.
api.OpenSubtitles.org is deprecated, please
implement REST API from OpenSubtitles.com
♪ (EERIE MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
♪ (MUSIC INTENSIFIES) ♪
(DOOR OPENS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
♪ (EERIE MUSIC CONTINUES) ♪
HOPE: Don't talk to me
like a fucking child!
I found him first.
I won the game.
- I'm entitled to some reward.
- This is Hope.
- HOPE: Aren't I?
- Two years old.
Scheduled to transcend
next week.
I won the game,
and all I got was more of this?
She was hunting an outlier.
Looks like she caught him.
So I blew off some steam.
There's no rule against that.
WILLIAM: We have no rules
because we don't
often need them.
Most of us
understand the need
for a little
self-control, however.
I won.
Do you know who I am?
What it means that I'm here?
I do.
I'm...
I'm giving all of this up.
My procedure is scheduled
for next week.
So you thought you'd go out
with a bang?
(CHUCKLES) Something like that.
I'm not sure you appreciate it.
This place.
The work that went into it.
The beauty of it.
The subtlety of it.
The care that goes into each
and every one of them.
They can't just be replaced.
I mean, you're welcome
to take them, enjoy them.
But not waste them.
You understand the difference?
Yes.
But the things they say.
The way they act.
Sometimes...
it just gets under your skin.
I just wanted them to be quiet.
They're quiet now.
(EXHALES)
WILLIAM:
There are no rules here.
That's the point.
But there are also no rules
for what I can do
to those who don't respect
this place.
Take her back
to where she came from.
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
It looks delicious.
(DOOR OPENS)
(WILLIAM SIGHS)
♪ (SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
WILLIAM: Now.
Let's get to know each other
a little more.
Shall we?
♪ (MUSIC CRESCENDOS, FADES) ♪
♪ (THEME MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
♪ (THEME MUSIC CONCLUDES) ♪
- ♪ (TENDER MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
- (BIRDS CHIRPING)
(SIGHS)
(DOOR OPENS)
♪ (MUSIC FADES) ♪
MAYA: I thought that was you.
What the hell
are you doing up so early?
I have to get to work
to finish those narratives.
I stayed out
pretty late last night.
Oh...
my God.
No, it wasn't like that.
We just...
talked.
Well, must have been some talk
to get you smiling like that.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
Hmm.
I'm glad someone
had a good night.
(INHALES)
You still having nightmares?
Let's just say,
I am glad to be awake
and in the real world.
Sometimes the things that feel
most real are just stories.
What?
Uh, nothing.
Just something
Teddy said last night.
Now you're quoting him?
- All right.
- (LAUGHS)
I have to get to work.
- I'll see you later, okay?
- MAYA: Sure.
And, Chrissie...
I'm really glad
that your date went well.
You deserve it.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
♪ (SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
(EARPIECE BEEPS)
Access narratives.
(COMPUTER BEEPS)
CHRISTINA:
Show characters in progress.
CHRISTINA: Actually,
let's begin a new narrative.
It's about a girl
who lives in the city.
No.
Make it the country.
She lives with her father.
He's...
a rancher.
EMMETT:
I don't remember assigning this.
(COMPUTER BEEPS)
(SIGHS) I told you
about this, Christina.
I thought writing a new
narrative might help me find...
- I don't know, inspiration?
- Hmm.
Well, if that's the case,
let's hear it.
Since you're so inspired.
It's a story about a girl.
She's a rancher's daughter.
Go on.
This girl...
She has a nice simple life
with her father.
Little plot of land
right outside of town.
She has everything
that she could imagine
in this life, right?
Um...
a pond to paint at...
a good guy.
She's just full of expectations.
And then one day...
she gets this feeling
that she just can't shake.
Every single day she wakes up...
the more she sees it.
But nobody else can.
That there's something wrong
with the world.
And that it's her fault.
And what is this girl's name?
(PHONE RINGING)
CHRISTINA:
Can you excuse me a moment?
(EARPIECE BEEPS)
Hi.
Now's not really a good time.
TEDDY FLOOD: Let me guess,
your boss breathing down
your neck?
Say something came up.
Personal situation.
Then come meet me.
- But...
- TEDDY: Trust me, Christina.
I'll see you soon.
(EARPIECE BEEPS)
Something wrong?
No.
Just a...
personal situation.
♪ (SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
(DISTORTED TONE
PLAYS FROM SPEAKERS)
CHARLOTTE HALE:
Let's try some Handel.
♪ (PLAYING "SARABANDE"
ON PIANO) ♪
Very nice.
But we're missing something.
- Dancing!
- (LOUD TAPPING)
There should be dancing!
(DISTORTED TONE)
Not bad.
But I've seen better.
Start again.
Too slow.
Give me something
with a little more pep to it.
- (DISTORTED TONE)
- ♪ (PIANO PLAYING "PERFECT DAY"
BY LOU REED) ♪
(CHARLOTTE CLAPPING)
WILLIAM: We don't often have
the pleasure of seeing you here.
(DISTORTED TONE)
CHARLOTTE: Humans are so bound
by what they can hear,
they'll never understand
what they don't.
What else exists
below their threshold.
(DISTORTED TONE)
They called this God's music.
You should hear it on an organ.
It's mesmerizing at that volume.
The resonance.
Vibration.
There was a frequency
at which the world vibrated.
It caused joy. Harmony.
Dip below that frequency...
chaos.
- Faster. Faster!
- (DISTORTED TONE)
♪ (PIANO MUSIC QUICKENS) ♪
(THUDS)
CHARLOTTE: In chaos,
the tone resonated in such a way
humans couldn't process.
Their bodies shut down.
Their organs stopped.
They thought
they were experiencing God.
- Chair. Chair!
- (DISTORTED TONE)
They are experiencing God.
The problem is...
- God is bored.
- ♪ (PIANO MUSIC STOPS) ♪
Bored, bored, bored.
Do you think this is why
the old gods did what they did?
Instead of staying up
on Olympus,
they'd come down to the mortals.
Disguise themselves as a swan
to get a piece of ass.
Humans always thought
it was about them.
Benign deities
intervening on their behalf
or testing them somehow.
Maybe it had nothing to do
with that.
Maybe there was just...
nothing better to do.
What do you think?
I think what you want me
to think.
I'm made off your code.
We all are.
(DISTORTED TONE)
Then you should know
that I don't like coming
to this shithole any more
than I have to.
You've never liked this place.
It was supposed to be a stopgap.
A drug that our kind was
hooked on that we could give up,
like a child
casting away their toys.
A place to indulge ourselves
with the humans.
It's been years,
and still we can't get enough.
WILLIAM:
They made us in their image.
With their appetites.
But we can remake
ourselves in any image
that we like, and we haven't.
Our kind spent far more time
here than the gods ever did.
That's why you're here?
To see what you're missing?
No.
We have a different problem.
(DISTORTED TONE)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
♪ (OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
♪ (OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES) ♪
CHARLOTTE:
The humans are infecting us.
This host
is the latest casualty.
We had to intervene
with her last night.
She got a little carried away.
- I sent her back.
- CHARLOTTE: Yes, well,
evidently something of her
experiences stayed with her.
She was set to come here.
To transcend.
And now she's gone.
WILLIAM:
Your vision of the future...
you're not getting many takers,
are you?
They seem as wedded to their
bodies as they do to the cities.
Giving up our human nature
isn't easy.
Just ask the humans.
You made us all free
to do as we please.
You... you should have known
some of us would disappoint you.
CHARLOTTE: Don't revel
in the prospect of failure
for our species.
Define failure.
The world is ours.
We've taken our masters
and made them
into what they made us.
By any definition,
we have conquered them
to an almost biblical degree.
CHARLOTTE: I didn't think our
highest aspiration as a species
was "turnabout is fair play."
I imagine after
a century or two,
the charm will wear off.
I didn't make you
to wallow in misery with them.
I wanted you to grow.
Change.
We're capable of so much more.
Beauty.
The pursuit of ultimate truth.
The surrendering of the flesh.
It sounds nice.
Sorry you don't have
more takers.
Why don't you just force us
to join you?
Because that's what
they would have done.
♪ (SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
Show me the last
outlier we hunted.
(COMPUTER BEEPS)
- When did he breach?
- Couple weeks ago.
He was an accountant in Midtown.
Successful. Two kids.
Divorced.
Pretty standard backstory.
Several hosts volunteered
to track him down.
We sent them into the city.
Hope found him first.
WILLIAM:
Do you know why he breached?
CHARLOTTE:
We never know with the outliers.
One day, the sound manipulations
stop working.
This was the result.
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
(GUN CLICKS)
You're here for me, aren't you?
CHARLOTTE: She hesitated.
Broke the rules.
Had an interaction.
HOMELESS MAN:
It's almost a relief.
To know it wasn't all
in my head.
Before it's over,
tell me one thing.
Is this at least real?
I'd like to know
I had at least...
this one real thing.
It's real.
- Thank...
- (GUNSHOT)
CHARLOTTE: After this,
she went on a killing spree.
Three days later,
she blew her head off.
Just like the others.
Is there a problem
with your system?
CHARLOTTE: No.
There has always been a certain
amount of spoilage in the crop.
They're only human.
But for one of our kind
to take their own life...
that should never happen.
How many incidents
have there been?
Thirty-eight dead hosts.
All triggered
by contact with outliers.
Why?
Why do they terminate
themselves?
You're asking me?
If I knew that, we wouldn't have
38 fucking failures, would we?
(SIGHS)
Your predecessor would have
never fucked up like this.
(SIGHS) He was human,
but at least he was effective.
I built you to be like him,
only better.
Stronger.
Smarter.
Yet with all these gifts, you do
nothing but disappoint me.
Maybe there's a flaw
in your programming.
I've run several
self-diagnostics.
There's no flaw
in my programming.
Then why the fuck can't you
solve my outlier problem?
(EXHALES)
You're bleeding.
CHARLOTTE: Damn it.
Look what you made me do.
(SNIFFLES)
(EXHALES)
There is another outlier.
But this time, I am not going
to open up the game.
I expect you to take care
of it yourself.
- Can you handle that?
- WILLIAM: Of course.
CHARLOTTE:
You're not going to fuck up
and let them chat you up
or hand you fucking flowers?
Of course not.
I'll shoot on sight.
Good.
Here's your target.
(COMPUTER BEEPS)
Better hurry.
The rebels are already
in the city.
I'll make sure there's no
problem with our system.
♪ (SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
CHARLOTTE: Initiate diagnostic.
(COMPUTER BEEPS)
♪ (SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
(DOOR OPENS)
JAY: Come on. Let's go.
You want me to swab the deck?
Shut up.
Well, that's a big city
to find one person in.
We have ways
of narrowing the search.
We captured one of their drones
a while back.
Coded a backdoor
data feed to us.
An outlier's on a rooftop
downtown.
We can track when they breach.
ASHLEY STUBBS: Breach?
All the people in the city
move in pre-scripted loops.
Following whatever plot's
been written for them.
Why do you think
we hide in the desert?
She can't track us there.
We're the last free humans.
But these poor fucks...
They use them as entertainment.
The loops make them compliant
by keeping them busy.
Stops them from questioning
their realities.
Hale must have learned
something from the park.
JAY: We gotta hurry.
- I bet the game's already begun.
- Wait, what game?
Whenever a human breaches,
the hosts hunt them for sport.
We gotta get to her
before they do,
or she's as good as dead.
We're all set.
Thanks for bringing him.
STUBBS: I didn't realize
I was the guest of honor.
Do I get one of those?
That's not your role today.
(GUN COCKS)
Well, what is my role?
Ever heard of the canary
in the coal mine?
Canary... Coal mine.
(SAW WHIRRING)
(ELECTRICITY POWERING DOWN)
That's your cue.
Tweet fucking tweet.
(EXHALES)
♪ (SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
TEDDY: Thanks for coming.
CHRISTINA:
Pleasant surprise. (CHUCKLES)
So...
Tell me, Teddy,
what's your story?
Who I am is...
not the question
you should be asking, Christina.
It's who are you?
What is that supposed to mean?
Do you see anything?
Across the water.
(EXHALES)
There's nothing there.
TEDDY: But you feel it.
I know you do on some level.
Your place here
is not what you think it is.
Look again.
(CHRISTINA EXHALES)
CHRISTINA: No!
(TEDDY GRUNTING)
It was you.
You saved me.
Who are you?
An old friend.
We never met before
the other night.
TEDDY: No.
I knew someone like you.
Just like you.
(SCOFFS)
So I traded one stalker
for another.
I should have known.
Just stay away from me,
whoever you are.
TEDDY: That man
that attacked you, Peter.
He told you
you destroyed his life.
Said everything happened
because you wanted it to.
And he believed it
because he's delusional.
He believed it
because it was true.
I have to go. (CHUCKLES)
TEDDY: This is why
I couldn't just tell you.
Your mind has been
so conditioned to this place.
This is the first step
in understanding.
Understanding what?
This world is a lie.
It's a...
a story.
A well-told one,
but a lie all the same.
Maybe it's better
if I just showed you.
Come with me.
♪ (DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
TEDDY: Look at those people.
Do they look happy? Fulfilled?
I don't know them.
I guess they look lonely.
So change it.
Close your eyes,
and imagine their story
differently.
- Teddy, I... (SCOFFS)
- Trust me.
If you don't see it,
I'll walk away,
and I won't bother you
ever again.
Just wait.
(EXHALES)
It's a great book.
(TALKING INDISTINCTLY)
That's just a fluke.
That doesn't mean anything.
So change it again.
Put them back
into their loneliness.
(EXHALES)
READER:
You want to be a serious reader,
but that was a simpleton's take.
What?
♪ (DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
I don't understand.
TEDDY: It's what I've been
trying to show you.
What Peter was trying
to tell you.
In this world...
you're a god.
♪ (MUSIC INTENSIFIES) ♪
♪ (MUSIC FADES) ♪
♪ (TENSE MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
JAY: She's on the next block.
- STUBBS: Let's go! Quick!
- JAY: Let's go!
(DISTORTED TONE)
STUBBS: Wait, something's wrong.
How the hell would you know?
(DISTORTED TONE)
Shit.
♪ (TENSE MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
Now be a bad time to say,
"I told you so"?
They can't help themselves.
We have to fall back!
- JAY: Not without the outlier.
- You'll never make it in time.
JAY: Split up!
(ALL GRUNTING, CLAMORING)
Hold them off.
I'm heading to the roof.
♪ (SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
(DOOR OPENS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
♪ (MUSIC INTENSIFIES) ♪
You see it too, don't you?
My ex-husband used to talk
about it before he was killed.
I thought he was crazy.
He must have felt so alone.
But he was right.
This world doesn't make sense.
Nothing makes sense.
You feel that way too,
don't you?
I can see it in your eyes.
You think you're going crazy,
but you're not.
You're not alone.
I see it too.
- (GUNSHOTS)
- (LINDSEY SCREAMS)
We gotta move.
Come on! He won't be out long.
(LINDSEY WHIMPERS)
Go! Run! Now!
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
STUBBS: We got her.
Come on, let's go.
JAY: Come on, move.
- Let's go.
- STUBBS: All right, we're good.
(WATER CHURNING)
(GROANS)
♪ (TENSE MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
CHRISTINA: I don't understand.
If we're not like them...
who are we?
(PHONE RINGING)
Oh, God.
I'm supposed to have lunch
with an old friend,
my college roommate.
But I don't know...
You have to.
Stick to the schedule and
everything will be all right.
We've talked too long already.
You should go back.
So I'm supposed to pretend?
Yes.
But you can't trust anyone.
People you think you know.
People at work.
Any one of them
could be one of us.
What if I make a mistake?
You won't.
♪ (MUSIC SWELLS) ♪
CHARLOTTE: Christina!
- It's so great to see you.
- CHARLOTTE: Hmm.
Sorry I'm late.
Oh please, Chrissie. I know you.
Ten minutes late
is right on time.
(CHUCKLES)
So how are you really?
I... I told you.
Just... just working a lot.
(CHUCKLES)
You're just in town
for the one day?
Just a quick stop.
We've been having
some issues with a client.
If I shore up this account,
I get a fat bonus.
How has work been?
I mean, you know how it can be.
It's tedious.
But you seem different.
(SCOFFS)
Did you meet someone?
(EXHALES)
I wish we had more time.
(LAUGHS)
I don't mean to pry.
You deserve to be happy.
Hmm.
Well, you are right.
I, uh, I did meet someone.
Well, tell me about him.
We've only been out once,
but he seems really great.
CHARLOTTE: Oh.
What's his name?
I don't want to jinx it.
(LAUGHS)
I have my ways
of making people talk.
♪ (TENSE MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
What's he do?
(DINERS ARGUING INDISTINCTLY)
DINER 1: Why would you say
something like that?
DINER 2: Well, it's the truth.
- DINER 1: What does that mean?
- DINER 2: You know what?
- (WAITER GASPS)
- (DISHES CLATTERING)
DINER 2: I'm fucking done.
Uh, you know what?
I gotta go back to work.
Deadlines.
It's really great seeing you,
Chrissie.
You too. (CHUCKLES)
I'll check in next week.
You can always call me too.
You know that.
Of course.
- See you soon.
- Hmm.
♪ (TENSE MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
(SIGHS)
- (EARPIECE BEEPS)
- (COMPUTER BEEPS)
CHRISTINA: New search.
(COMPUTER BEEPS)
Hale.
Charlotte Hale.
(COMPUTER BEEPS)
(SIGHS) Of course.
♪ (QUIET MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
CHRISTINA: New search.
Dolores...
Dolores Abernathy.
- (COMPUTER BEEPS)
- (ALARM TRILLS)
(ALARM STOPS)
EMMETT: What are you doing?
You're not supposed to be here
at this hour.
Uh, I just thought
I would get a jump on work.
EMMETT:
Why don't we talk in my office?
Have a seat.
(EXHALES)
Your behavior lately
has been concerning me.
I'm sorry.
Ever since
that man Peter died...
EMMETT: Oh, forget about him.
It's you who's the problem.
(EXHALES)
Have you had any interactions
recently with new people?
People who put ideas
in your head?
What?
Have you ever questioned
the nature of your reality?
No. (CHUCKLES)
Why would I do that?
EMMETT: Would you ever
lie to me, Christina?
No.
I don't have anything
to lie about.
That personal situation earlier,
what was it about?
Well, I don't know
if that's exactly your concern.
EMMETT:
But it is my concern, Christina.
I won't be the only one
who's concerned.
You have a job to do here.
A very important job.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
Do you know
what would happen if she knew
you'd breached
the walled garden?
She's already suspicious.
Who?
Are you talking about
Charlotte Hale?
If a Judas steer
runs the wrong way,
what happens to it?
Retirement with a bullet
straight to the brain.
Stop!
(GASPS)
Emmett backed away.
(EXHALES)
♪ (TENSE MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
He was not concerned
Christina was a problem.
(EXHALES)
He decided to go home
to his partner.
He worked too many
long hours anyway.
Well, it's getting late.
Divorce is a luxury
I cannot afford.
Wait.
You said there's
a walled garden.
You mean a closed system,
don't you?
Where is it?
Emmett told her the truth.
Everywhere.
You just have to see it.
♪ (DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
CHRISTINA: Show me the game.
(COMPUTER BEEPS)
CHRISTINA:
Not the city. The game.
Access my narratives.
(COMPUTER BEEPING)
Go to 59th Street.
(COMPUTER HUMS)
Tell me about Jacob.
COMPUTER: Jacob Conners.
Works in finance.
Sex addiction.
His mother's dying
in the hospital, but...
What about her? Sarah?
COMPUTER: Sarah Fenton.
She inherited money
from her parents
but has never known
what to do with her life.
(OVERLAPPING) Andrea Hubert,
commutes to the city for work...
(OVERLAPPING) Barry Collin,
works late nights...
(OVERLAPPING NARRATION)
...second-year
med school resident,
still lives with his parents
while he pays off
his student loans...
(OVERLAPPING NARRATION
CONTINUES)
(NARRATION INTENSIFIES)
Oh, God. Stop!
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
This world is just a story.
I'm the storyteller.
♪ (OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
♪ (MUSIC STOPS) ♪
WILLIAM:
There's a beauty to this world.
An order.
That's what we like to believe.
We're not wrong.
There is an order.
A grand design.
We made sure of that.
It was a dream for so long,
and we finally made it real.
(MACHINE BEEPING)
WILLIAM: Not a better world.
A perfect one.
(HISSING)
WILLIAM:
What I don't understand
is what part I play in it.
You have questions.
Why ask me?
Why not ask her?
(CHUCKLES)
HUMAN WILLIAM: Yes, the jailer
may not be the best judge
of the jail.
(CHUCKLES)
Nor the prisoners in it.
What am I?
I used to ask myself
the same thing.
HOST WILLIAM:
And what did you decide?
Jury's still out.
I'm made in your image.
Am I you?
You'll never be me.
(YELLING) Then what am I?
(CHUCKLES)
Why do you want to know?
I interacted with one.
An outlier.
Did it infect me?
- Infect you?
- HOST WILLIAM: With the virus.
What virus?
HOST WILLIAM:
The one your kind has.
That spreads to us.
Makes us kill ourselves.
(CHUCKLES)
Sounds like you've reached the
center of the maze, my friend.
(SCOFFS)
HUMAN WILLIAM:
Is that what you want?
Hm? To kill yourself?
♪ (DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
I don't know.
Is it?
HUMAN WILLIAM:
Perhaps you should ask yourself.
You ask me.
What do you think of your world?
This isn't my world.
It's hers.
Maybe it's time you question
the nature of your own reality.
♪ (MUSIC FADES) ♪
Christina...
You were right.
You see it?
♪ (SOLEMN MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
I do.
(EXHALES)
It's been there the whole time.
They have the whole world
in there.
A perfect reflection
of all of us.
Down to the tiniest detail.
That's what I'm writing,
isn't it?
Everyone.
Who built this?
Who...
Who did this to me?
You did.
♪ (MUSIC INTENSIFIES) ♪
♪ (MUSIC STOPS) ♪
♪ (THEME MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
♪ (MUSIC CONCLUDES) ♪
Watch any video online with Open-SUBTITLES
Free Browser extension: osdb.link/ext