- [Cell doors clanging]
- BRAITHWAITE: Hey! You!
I'm onto you.
I know all about you.
REYNOLDS:
What's all this for?
We was done last week.
Why us again?
JACKSON:
Quit moaning, Harry.
You. Out.
Move!
WOLTON: Sorry, Mr. Jackson.
Just saying hello.
OFFICER: Right, that's it.
Get this lot packed up.
Get sorted.
WOLTON: What have you
got with you, then?
Any money?
Phone cards?
Have you got stuff
you can trade, have you?
BRINKLEY: Bastards.
OFFICER:
Right, Brinkley, shut it.
[Helicopter blades whirring]
Come on, that's it!
Come on!
[Indistinct shouting]
Why didn't you stop them?!
["Only You" playing]
ENJOY ALL VOD IN HIGH QUALITY @ 4KVOD.TV
GET LIVE TV,MOVIES,SHOWS IN ONE PACKAGE
MAN ON RADIO: We have
an abandoned stolen vehicle.
Driver identified
as Stanley Field.
That's "S" Sierra, "F" Foxtrot.
Stanley Field, escaped prisoner.
Do you have sighting? Repeat,
do you have sighting? Over.
MAN #2:
Yes, we have a sighting.
He's out in the open,
left of your patrol car. Over.
Suspect could be armed.
Stanley Field is an escapee
from Barfield Prison. Over.
MAN #2:
We have heat source.
A figure running
left of the patrol cars.
He's down!
Down!
Keep moving to your left.
Yes! Got him.
Got him.
Recommendation 10
from Judge Shuman's report...
The evidence of unnecessary
and excessive use of...
[Dogs barking]
Get those dogs off me!
Get them off me!
Will have contacts for 14 hour
per day out of cell periods!
Abolition of segregation
and hospitalization
for prisoners deemed at risk
or subversive!
Recommendation 27...
Better quality education!
Let him go! Let him at me!
I'll bite his eyes out!
Let him at me!
Stanley Field was arrested
whilst attempting
to visit his family.
Well, we got one back.
Any money the other one's
sunning himself in Spain.
Thank Christ it didn't get out
that Webster absconded as well.
I don't know how she did that.
Didn't even make
the local press.
I know.
We've got two coming in
this morning,
one a real hard bastard.
You got space.
Hang on, we've got half the wing
under construction.
[Indistinct conversations]
Oh, scrambled eggs and
brick dust by the look of them.
Here, Walter.
I couldn't borrow your radio,
could I?
Only I got a visit today,
and I want to record a program.
Educational.
For me degree.
Okay.
I'll have your bacon.
All right, I'm going.
You wasn't in such a hurry
to nab them
when they took off
in the helicopter, was you?
♪ Oh, tie a yellow ribbon
'round the big prize dick ♪
- [Man bellowing]
- [Dogs barking]
Aaah!
Let him at me!
♪ Hey, hey ♪
♪ Hey, hey, hey ♪
♪ Knock-knock-knocking
on heaven's door ♪
I'll pluck his eyes out!
Let him at me!
I don't know where you want to
put them... C Wing or D Wing?
Um...
Well, we've two spare pads
in C Wing, haven't we?
We don't.
They're starting the plumbing
and fixtures a cell at a time.
There's a bit of space
in D Wing,
in one of the bigger cells.
Maybe you could put in
another bunk.
Is Mavis in yet?
Uh, no.
Moira is.
I think we should put
the young bloke,
Anthony John Kelly, in D Wing,
and this old lag, Norman Jones,
put him in C Wing
where we can keep an eye on him.
He's a right animal.
[Mid-tempo rock music playing]
[Jackhammer pounding]
This radio.
According to Simpkins' list
of personal belongings,
he doesn't have one... a radio.
It's Walter Brinkley's.
Take it out, then.
He's probably nicked it.
MAN #1:
Hey, it shouldn't be allowed.
MAN #2: Space cadet.
Pad four.
MAN #1: Hey, Mr. Morgan, sir.
Mr. Morgan, sir.
Not again.
You did his pad last week.
What's all this about?
We was done last week.
Why us again?
Quit moaning, Harry.
You got a new padmate
coming in. You know the rules.
Right, that's it.
Get this lot packed up.
Get sorted.
They're putting
another bloke in there.
Shit.
We'll just have to
put it off, then.
But I'm gonna have that nonce.
Hey!
I'm onto you.
Onto you!
I know about you.
I often double up
the new inmates,
especially the younger ones
without any experience
or previous record.
BUNNY: Yes, but I don't know
why you're telling me this.
Mr. Bunny, I am
simply informing you,
as per instructions from HQ.
Well, then is it possible
to put in a third
in one of the larger cells?
Yes.
Yes, it can accommodate three.
Well, for now.
Well, then, Miss Hewitt,
I think we have no alternative.
[Speaking indistinctly]
Yes.
Thank you very much, Mr. Bunny.
[Sighs]
I could throttle him.
Moira, since that
helicopter escape,
he's behaving like
a demented ferret.
Well, we certainly have
made the headlines
the last few weeks.
Well, Princess Diana'll love us.
[Chuckles]
Okay.
[Telephone ringing]
Has Mavis arrived yet,
or is she planning
on becoming part-time?
OFFICER:
One variety pack of cereal.
One transistor radio.
JONES:
Recommendation 37!
Life-sentence prisoners
should come into line
with Europe and Ireland
and be given
Christmas home leave
after spending a fixed time!
OFFICER: One comb.
[Hawks]
Dear God, do you ever clean it?
OFFICER #2: £4.25.
OFFICER #1:
One cassette tape, empty.
OFFICER #2:
One pair black leather shoes.
OFFICER #1:
One plastic lion.
[Growls]
Prisoner 590.
Mr. Simpkins.
You'll be placed on report
for having unauthorized property
in your possession.
You're bloody joking,
aren't you?
I was lent the radio.
He lent me that radio!
Did that prick Walter
say I nicked it?!
Shut it!
Your mate Brinkley's on report
for lending it to you.
You're nuts.
You mean, tight-assed bastard!
I only wanted it
to record a program!
Aye, what's all that about?
He doesn't usually
get het up like that.
I just found Walter Brinkley's
radio in his cell.
He's on report for lending it.
Hey, take it easy.
I mean...
Well, it's against
the regulations.
- [Bell ringing]
- Yes.
Oh, you do what you have to.
Workshop's open.
Look, I'm just doing
my bloody job.
Yes.
Now we've got a new inmate
coming on the wing.
Get 48 ready for occupation.
The landings are as before,
and identical to C, D, the VP
and seg wings
running at present.
Gymnasium's in the same area...
When the prisons go private,
they'll be headhunting.
The first to go
where there's a detached unit.
Hall, Neagle.
Lithgow, Stubbs, Abbott.
If you could just
hold the chitchat.
This is the SSU
maximum-security unit.
It's different
from a control unit.
Play me cards right,
you think I'll get a room?
The men in SSU, Mr. Morgan,
never leave.
I want my radio.
That is my radio
you took out of Barry's pad!
Well, you can't have it!
You give me back my radio now,
or I'll smash
your frigging face in!
Get out.
Get out of this office!
You despot bastard!
[Grunting]
Oh!
Oh! Oh!
I screwed your mother,
you dirty, dirty little bastard.
Oh!
I want my radio!
[Indistinct shouting]
The roof is made
of very tough Perspex.
It is fire, bullet,
and bombproof.
Exercise yard all covered
in protective meshing.
It'll make our lives
a lot easier.
Mm. Yeah.
You mean you approve this?
LYONS:
Too damn right.
Anyone who works with the real
animals would go for this.
Our problems always
come with the maniacs
with no hope of release.
Bastards who threaten our lives,
'cause they don't give a shit
about their own.
Best place for them.
If you'd been paying attention,
Mr. Morgan,
everything in this unit
is built to contain
not necessarily
the most hardened criminals,
but the high-risk prisoners...
Mafia, terrorists.
Those who can afford
a helicopter?
[Both laugh]
You may well laugh,
but it's close to the truth.
[Knock on door]
Um, any detail you believe
should be incorporated
into Barfield,
now's the time to tell me,
so think about it
and report back to me.
[Bell ringing]
Open this door, you shithead!
Quieten down, Walter.
I'm not opening up.
Well, I'll tell you
what I'm gonna do, you dickhead!
I'm gonna heat up cooking oil
and throw it over that pig face
of yours, you hear me?!
Oh!
I want my radio!
You hear me?!
I'll take him apart with me...
I want my radio!
Now, Walter,
come out of your cell.
Step out.
Piss off!
That's it, Walter.
Walk out,
or you will be dragged out.
Now, it is up to you.
[Breathing heavily]
All right!
You bastards!
All right.
Bastards!
Fuck.
Right, Norman.
Get your kit sorted away
if you want any lunch.
Little palace, isn't it?
JONES: Hmm.
Go left.
MAN:
What's your name?
Right, lad, unpack,
get your kit sorted,
and don't overlap
anybody else's area.
You're on lunch break coming up.
You bunking in here, then?
What's your name?
- Anthony.
- Got any burns?
- Smokes.
- No, I don't, I'm sorry.
Any magazines?
What you got with you, then?
Any money?
Phone cards?
Have you got stuff you can
trade with, then, have you?
Oi, you... out.
Move!
Sorry, Mr. Jackson.
Only saying hello.
We don't do cell association
here at Barfield.
Keep your nose clean.
Get it?
Good.
[Door locks]
The existence of evil is proof
of the existence of God.
If the world consisted
only of goodness
and righteousness...
there would be no need for God.
For the world itself
would be God.
God is because evil is...
and that means that God is
because freedom is.
Then you tuck in
the ends real tight,
just like the army.
- Were you in the army?
- No.
Harry's ex-RAF.
Hey, leave him alone.
He's got personal problems.
His wife's given him
the [Clicks tongue]
I'm doing five for GBH.
He's a lifer.
Fucking bitch.
So, what did you
get up to, then?
Fraud.
Building society.
I was gonna pay it back.
I just needed...
Hope it weren't
the Abbey National.
I'm in that.
[Laughs]
Heh heh.
What books you got, then?
Anything with a bit of...
[Laughs]
Tea's up.
You all right, mate?
[Laughs]
Need some gear, Colin.
MAN: Oh, yes, yes!
Come here! Come out!
Who are you looking at,
you dirty old nonce?
Come on!
Come on, let me... you.
Come on, Arnie.
It's starting to rain.
- Yes, come on!
- What's that about?
You know Arnie. Sees a bare ass,
he thinks it's his birthday.
HEWITT: I meant him.
OFFICER:
Oh, uh, sorry, ma'am.
Apparently Brinkley
has refused to get dressed.
Is this Anthony Kelly?
Yes, ma'am.
This is the governor.
I'm just taking him up
for his medical, ma'am.
I'll try and get
to see you later, all right?
Come on.
Afternoon. Afternoon.
Has Norman Jones
had his medical yet?
Governor for cell 48.
He's just got back.
We got behind with that
bloody Walter Brinkley.
Can I have a word to you
about young Malahide?
Maybe try him out
in the VP Wing.
And I wouldn't mind having
Jumbo Jackson back on C Wing.
What's the problem
with Malahide?
He's very young,
still attached to the rule book.
Got to bend them slightly.
No need to go out of your way
for aggravation,
if you understand?
I'm not sure that I do,
Mr. Morgan.
Norman, governor to see you.
- Hello, Governor.
- Whiskers.
- How are you today?
- Fine, thank you. How are you?
MORGAN:
This is the governor, Norman.
Miss Hewitt.
Stand up.
Everything all right?
I asked you
a question, Mr. Jones.
You'll have a meeting
with a prison
probation officer tomorrow.
Are there any questions
you'd like to ask me?
Then I won't hold up
your tea break.
[Door closes]
Aah!
[Indistinct talking]
I know he's a nonce.
I know it.
I don't care what he says
he's in for,
I know he's bent.
Got any doughnuts left, mate?
BRAITHWAITE: He's a nonce.
Hey, mate,
got anything with jam in it?
- Have my bread.
- It's good stuff.
Snoopy got it in this afternoon.
Cheers.
Cheers, mate.
- Oh! I'm sorry.
- [Liquid splashes]
Oh, here.
Let me.
[Groans]
Nonce, nonce.
Scumbag.
FOSTER: Piece of shit.
We're gonna have some fun
with that nonce.
How you doing, Jumbo?
Nothing new, Victor.
Now go on, move it.
Oh, "Mr. Jackson" to you.
If you want your tea break, son,
you'd better go and move it.
You probably need
a new starter motor.
Probably need
a lot more than that.
- Thanks.
- Okay.
Oh, um, could you give me
two minutes tomorrow
just for a chat?
- Sure.
- Thanks.
- Night.
Can I have a word?
Um, you've got a Norman Jones.
Don't know his number offhand.
He arrived today.
What about him?
Well, physically he's very fit,
but mentally,
diagnosed paranoid schizophrenic
from his records.
- Did you know?
- Mm-hmm.
Well, he's refused
his medication,
Largactil, and I can't
give it to him by force.
Thought you should know.
It's in my report.
Okay.
What about Anthony Kelly?
Frightened.
I meant physically.
So did I.
He's very frightened.
Otherwise he's okay.
- Thanks. Night.
- Good night.
FOSTER: Snoopy's boy
said it was good stuff.
Come in today.
Weren't kidding.
[Coughs]
Ooh.
- Want a toke?
- No, thanks.
OFFICER: Lights out.
Lights out on the wing.
[Laughing]
[Laughing] It's good gear.
[Both laughing]
[Whistles]
- Oh. Hi.
- Hi.
- Can I be of assistance?
- Um, I don't know.
To be honest,
I was only just passing,
and I've not really given it
much thought.
Um, do you do parts exchange?
Uh, mm-hmm.
I was thinking about 5,000
and whatever you'd give me
for my car.
Right, well, we've...
We've got a lot more vehicles
behind the showroom.
Do you... Do you do
a lot of driving
or you just want a local
runabout for the kids, hmm?
[Men laughing]
It's a lot more than you said
you wanted to spend, so...
I like the color of the seats.
Trouble is
I get terrible static.
Look you can test-drive
any of them.
Maybe have a think about it,
come back tomorrow.
See, I need something
a bit substantial
with good leg room, obviously.
See, this one's got
really big mileage.
Yeah, well, if it hadn't,
it'd be more expensive.
It's a lot more
on your original price.
Well, I think you've
sat in them all.
Um, best would be
to see how it handles.
I can arrange a test drive.
Let me try the gray one again.
How much for my car did you say?
Well, the book says 1,300,
but, um...
See? Oh.
That one's not for sale.
[Car alarm blares]
[Men laughing]
It's mine.
Bloody hell.
Jump leads
would have been cheaper.
Morning.
- Morning.
If she were a bloke,
you know what that would be
a substitute for, don't you?
You said last night
you wanted a word.
Yes.
- [Metal clinking]
- Thanks.
[Metal clinking]
But I can refuse
to work with the VPs.
You don't have to
if you don't want to,
but in my experience
it's much better
if all the prison officers
know all the prison inmates.
But I can refuse.
You can, but would you
mind telling me why?
They just make my skin crawl.
Sex offenders?
How do you feel about
the mentally retarded?
The other vulnerable men?
Some of them are on the VP Wing
because they're in debt
to other inmates.
How do you feel about them?
A VP wing does not only
contain sex offenders.
I just can't deal with them,
and the union says
I don't have to.
Look, the wife and I
have just had a little girl.
Now HIV and AIDS inmates
are in there, so...
All right.
Thank you, Mr. Malahide.
I'll let you know my decision.
MAN: Whoo!
Who's a pretty girl, then?
- All right there, lover.
- Oh, lovely!
- Give us some of that.
- Give us a kiss.
- Nice ass.
- Lovely ass!
I'd like to see
around all the wings,
estimate how many more months
we're gonna need.
Morning, Governor.
Got to be very diplomatic
about it, though.
That boy in training
for the marathon?
- What's going on?
- Miss Hewitt's orders.
He's the lad that absconded
from his dental appointment.
I wasn't informed about this.
Right, Walter, out.
Take a shower
and then eat your dinner.
No way.
Until I get my radio back,
I'm on hunger strike.
You tell that bitch governor
I'll starve to death
unless I get my radio!
I spoke to Mr. Malahide
this morning,
and he won't go the VP Wing,
so I've moved him
over to D Wing,
and you've got Jackson
as his replacement.
Um, tip-off, Mr. Lyons...
You'll probably be having
the area manager
and the operationals director
wanting to look over the wings.
Okay.
[Beeps]
Hello.
Mavis, since Mr. Andrews
and Mr. Bunny are here,
could you show them
into my office, please?
Yeah, sure.
Car insurance. Shocking prices.
Costs a fortune.
You wanted me to shop around.
Mavis, did you know
or have any prior warning
that they were coming?
No.
Show them in, Mavis.
Mr. Andrews and Mr. Bunny
from prison services HQ.
- Good afternoon, Miss Hewitt.
- Good afternoon.
We're not interrupting anything?
No, no, please, Take a seat.
- Thank you.
- Oh, uh, could he stay?
Of course.
Please.
ANDREWS: Miss Hewitt.
You at no time informed
the authorities that last month,
the same day that two men
escaped by helicopter,
there was also a third escapee.
Um, someone Webster?
He came back voluntarily.
He's now due for release.
He lost 21 days remission.
Both officers concerned
were placed on report,
as was Webster.
We're obviously aware
of how difficult it must be
to run Barfield
under these conditions,
which is the reason
that I'm here...
To consider if Barfield
should remain in operation
during the rebuilding.
It's now highly questionable.
Right, area manager's
in with the governor
and they might just do
an impromptu walkabout.
Shit!
You're not gonna believe this,
but that prat Walter Brinkley
is on a hunger strike,
till he gets his
frigging radio returned.
This is down to you, mate.
Six month at Pentonville
didn't teach you much, did it?
No, no, you told me to take
that radio off Brinkley.
- This isn't down to me.
- It's down to prison rules.
If they can't obey them,
they get what they get,
so anyone starts
even heavy breathing,
you come down on them.
We've got to look
tight as a nut,
'cause the word is they could be
closing this place down,
and I for one
don't fancy detached duties
Christ knows where.
Poor old Smedley's
stuck on the Isle of Wight.
- Come on.
- [Sighs]
Uh, second, Malahide.
If you've got any kit down here,
get it packed up.
You're going on D Wing.
- Why am I being moved?
- Governor's orders. Go on, son.
Oh!
This is beautiful.
Are you on for a game of pool?
No, got to
get this bitch sorted out.
[Coughs]
It's got a hell of a kick.
You get it off Snoopy again?
Here, Anthony.
Have a drag.
You smoking them French fags
again, Colin?
[Coughing]
[Laughter]
It's okay.
They ignore it.
They all know we use it.
Keeps us quiet.
Keeps us happy.
Keeps us.
My God.
I'm reeling.
Go on, have a drag.
♪ Oh, hallelujah,
come on, get happy ♪
♪ Forget your troubles
and wear a smile ♪
[Chuckles]
Take a good lungful.
It's good and it's cheap.
Are you going onto the landing?
Yeah.
You play pool, do you?
No.
- Chess?
- No.
Poker?
Rummy? Five-card stud?
No.
Well, I sincerely hope you wank,
or it's gonna be a very boring
18 months in here, sunshine.
Hey, come on.
Pass it on.
Bloody hell.
[Laughs]
Given the time,
I would like to tour the prison
before association ends.
Is there
a good local restaurant?
I'll arrange a table.
Mr. Marshall, would you...
Yes.
What's your reaction
to the new plan for Barfield?
More specifically,
the proposed
special secure unit.
Well, I think
if we have criminals
that require
a 24-hour surveillance,
we need a more
sophisticated method
of housing and controlling them.
Staff approved of the plan too?
Yes, without question.
Total approval.
Apart from Miss Hewitt.
She seemed to be
the only one against it.
Gentlemen.
You're, uh, you're being moved
to C Wing.
JACKSON: Why?
Don't ask me.
Governor's orders.
The area manager's doing
an impromptu walkabout.
- You mean on this landing?
- Yeah.
JACKSON: Well, you'd better
check out cell 29, mate.
They've got wacky baccy
lit up in there.
OFFICER: Christ.
Being shafted, are we?
Survive? It's a bit tough
on the other wing, is it?
Just lay off me, fellas.
[Indistinct shouting]
We'd better get that sorted.
The only time they don't
fight over the channels
is when "Baywatch" is on.
Back in, son.
You know what this is about,
don't you?
Nah.
You want to tell me,
you cocksucker.
You know you're bunking up
with a nonce?
You know that?
Oh, he's a nonce.
FOSTER:
No, I'm bloody not.
Come on!
Steven, you know me.
Tell this piece of crap
to push off.
I seen it on reports.
He was a VP, wasn't it?
Aye, he's a nonce.
What proof you got?
Look, I ain't no ruddy nonce.
Okay, let's prove it.
We'll hold
a kangaroo court right here.
Harry, you can be judge.
[Chuckles]
You, defense counsel.
And you, what's your name?
Kelly.
[Clears throat] Anthony.
Right, Anthony.
You're his solicitor.
Hey!
Stay on your billet, shitface.
Sit down.
I'd say this court's
now in session.
What are you, Victor?
Oh, I'm the hangman.
Book a table would you?
Make sure it's the best.
If not the best, then at least
the most expensive.
Has Moira gone?
Period pains.
I said she could go.
Could you relay that
I've gone home early to change?
I'm sure Mr. Marshall will take
full advantage of my absence.
Just as I feel sure
that you will inform him of it.
Mavis...
You're privy to a lot of
very personal information
regarding myself
and some inmates.
I think
you need to make a decision
whose side you're on.
If you can't keep yourself
from gossiping,
for want of a better word,
then I shall consider you
a security risk.
Do you understand
what I'm saying?
So it's a table for three, then?
Exactly, Mavis.
MAVIS: Are you covered?
Yes. Mr. Marshall can take over
as night duty governor.
I meant your car insurance.
Oh, shit.
I didn't look.
[Sighs]
Do I need to take out
a bank loan?
Whatever, Mavis. Please just
keep it to yourself.
Moira's very competent.
Don't struggle, nonce.
You'd be cuffed in court, right?
Judge, am I right?
[Groans]
[Knocks on door]
Some of them prefer
to remain in their cells
during the association.
Get in, you...
But cell doors must remain open.
Miss Hewitt's orders.
She also withdrew
all prisoners' cell keys.
That almost caused another riot.
REYNOLDS: Good evening,
Mr. Marshall, sir.
Just give it a minute.
He's on the toilet.
Safer out here.
He stinks the place up.
I've asked to be moved, sir.
Unhygienic, three of us
in a cell for two.
Good evening, Mr. Marshall.
Evening, Gov.
Evening, sir.
What are you
on trial for, Colin?
Please answer the court.
What are you on trial for?
Oh.
[Coughs]
Noncing.
[Laughs]
Your Honor.
What do you say to that, jury?
Come on, Anthony,
give us a drag.
As the judge,
I'd like to hear
what evidence you've got.
So far I am not satisfied.
There is still reasonable doubt.
[Laughs]
BRAITHWAITE:
It's obvious, isn't it?
He's a nonce.
And as such,
I sentence him to death.
And I happen to have handy...
[Laughs]
I feel sick.
Let me leave.
BRAITHWAITE: So...
Sentence will now
be carried out.
- Let's have him up here.
- REYNOLDS: Get up, Colin.
BRAITHWAITE:
Give him a hand, Anthony.
Come on, come on.
That's it.
There we go.
Over the top.
Good, nonce.
That's good.
REYNOLDS: Joke's over!
Cut him loose!
But I need to know now
exactly where I stand.
It's obvious to me I have
either been placed at Barfield
just to act as a caretaker
during the rebuilding process,
or...
I think that is a, um...
Correct assumption.
Well, if I've almost 18 months,
then I intend to use that time
to establish strong relations
with my staff.
And if you decide
to close it down,
you'll have 88 men to rehouse.
Um...
Mm...
Just the fruit salad, please.
More cream.
Maybe just a little slice
of the chocolate log.
- Just a taste.
- [Pager beeps]
ANDREWS:
I'll have the strawberry
with the chestnut cream.
Excuse me.
Um, where's your phone?
Across there, madam.
[Engine starts]
Dr. Thomas.
We have an emergency
at Barfield.
Sorry to interrupt your evening.
The rope was tied
to an air vent.
Anyway, we've got the cell
cordoned off.
The prisoners
are down the block.
How the hell did this happen?
Well, he wasn't raped or beaten.
Strangulation was
the cause of death,
but the coroner's report
will give more details.
[Sighs]
You okay?
[Scoffs]
Colin Foster
was hanged in cell 29.
Four prisoners witnessed it.
One of them was Anthony Kelly.
No, I am not okay.
Can you stay down here, Doctor?
Inspector Dunes
is interviewing the prisoners,
and he'll need to talk to you.
He'll also want to see Malahide.
Ma'am.
- Yes, boss.
- Malahide?
Yes, poor bugger found him.
He's pretty shook up.
Police want to see you,
Reynolds.
Hey, let's go.
He was dead
when we got to the cell.
- They couldn't revive him.
- How involved was Anthony Kelly?
Well, apparently he had
a spliff in his hand.
A joint.
I'd only just taken Andrews and
the bloody area manager 'round.
It happened like ten minutes
after they walked out.
- They passed the cell?
- Yeah, I was with them.
Well, that lets me off the hook.
I don't know about you, Gary.
Good night.
- Breakfast.
- Here's your breakfast, Walter.
I'm not eating.
Take it away.
If you say so.
Get undressed.
Be ready for showers.
Governor wants to see you.
No frigging way.
You want me to shower,
you've got to undress me.
Strip him.
Scares the pants off of me,
and I don't mind admitting it.
- Right. Let's sort the bastard.
- Aye.
MARSHALL: Want us to get nasty?
Is that what you're after? Hmm?
He won't talk.
Won't speak to anybody.
Stand up, Jones.
Aah!
Right. You want to play it
that way, do you?
I can't get started.
You've got two seconds
to straighten out, son.
I can't get started!
If you want it, son,
come and get it.
[Laughs]
I'm very sorry.
I really am unable
to discuss the incident
or to give you
any further details.
MAN: But can we see him,
help him in any way?
Anthony has been segregated,
and he will require
legal representation.
Tell him we love him
and we'll do anything we can.
- Thank you very much.
- I'll tell him personally.
Thank you very much.
- Thank you, Mr. Kelly.
- Goodbye.
[Knock on door]
Oh, um, just hold him outside.
We're still waiting
for Mr. Malahide.
We've still not be able to trace
the dead man's mother.
Is she his only relative?
No, no, I'm also trying
to contact her sister.
Also, Howard Webster's
due to be released.
You wanted to see him
before he went.
Oh, God, yes.
Mr. Brinkley, do you understand
that you've been put on report
and why?
[Knock on door]
- Come in, Mr. Malahide.
- BRINKLEY: Yes, ma'am.
Charges are lending an item
to an unauthorized person.
My radio.
But as Barry
was needing it for his exam...
Do you plead guilty
or not guilty to the charge?
Guilty.
But with mitigations.
Would you explain your actions?
Well, yes, I've been
trying to explain.
You see, Barry Simpkins
is doing
his Open University exam,
and he wanted to record
a program,
so he asked if he could
borrow my radio.
So that's how it all came about,
and that is the entire truth.
[Jackhammer pounding]
I have created because I think
I have been unjustly punished,
but that said, I apologize
and promise never to do
such a terrible thing again.
If I get my radio back,
I will never lend it
to nobody, never again.
Would you read
his wing report, please?
Governor.
Brinkley is currently serving
a seven-year sentence.
He's been placed on report
a previous 245 times
spaced over six years.
For what reasons?
Mostly for fighting
with other inmates.
[Sighs]
Mr. Brinkley, I do not think
that being put on report
245 times
is anything to smile about.
Your punishment will be
the confiscation of your radio
for four months.
You'll also be charged £3.50.
- You fascist bitch!
- Get him out.
I'd rather die than let
you bastards keep my radio!
It's mine! That radio's
my personal property!
You shit governor!
Nasty bitch!
I'll kill you!
I'm very sorry, Miss Hewitt.
You know, James,
sometimes it is necessary
to bend the rules,
just slightly.
I meant about Colin Foster.
Ah, well, um, yes,
we're all very sorry
about that, but... thank you.
Um, Howard Webster's
still waiting.
[Sighs]
Good luck.
Don't want see you back, okay?
Well, I hope I don't
see you again
unless it's on TV
breaking a track record.
Have you someone meeting you?
My wife and my mother
are already waiting.
Well, I won't hold things up.
Good luck, Howard.
Thank you.
Governor to see you, Kelly.
BRINKLEY: Oi!
You tell that bull dyke
I'm on hunger strike!
Could you shut him up, please?
BRINKLEY: I'll kill her!
- I'll kill her!
- Shut up!
Her brothers, sisters!
I'll burn her house down.
I'll fix the brakes on her car.
Screw you, nasty bitch!
Tell him if he starts eating,
and eating properly,
so that he's
no further problem to us,
he can have his radio back.
Shut it now, Walter!
Shut up!
I will starve to death,
and that Hitler bitch
will be brought to justice.
They had no right
to take my private property.
I explained to her, but...
Anthony, I've spoken
to your parents.
OFFICER: Shut it, Walter.
You can have your radio back.
- All you've got to do is eat.
- Anthony, would you look at me?
BRINKLEY: I don't believe you!
It's a con!
You told them?
Of course.
They had to be informed.
I won't believe it until I have
my own radio in my own hands!
Tell Sandra?
I suppose
I'll have to tell Sandra.
I don't want her upset.
She's my girlfriend.
Fiancée.
They'll be here tomorrow
if you need anything.
- Cigarettes?
- No.
No, I don't smoke, thank you.
So you don't want anything?
What's gonna happen to me?
That'll be for the courts
to decide.
But I didn't do anything.
Then you've
nothing to worry about.
BRINKLEY: It's a con!
You bastards!
I want it in writing!
I won't eat again till I have
my own radio in my own...
MAVIS: And if you think
that's bad enough,
Walter Brinkley is now demanding
fish and chips and mushy peas.
Oh, I will kill him!
I will strangle him!
Shh!
What?!
[Whispering] Colin Foster's
mother.
Oh, shit.
- Does she know he's dead?
- Mm-hmm.
I'm so very sorry,
Mrs. Foster.
There will be a full-scale
inquiry into the tragedy,
which, sadly, makes it
very difficult for me
to give you any details.
I was at my sister's.
It's such a long way
to come each month,
so I break the journey.
That's why I wasn't at home.
Was it his asthma?
He's always suffered with it,
since he was a toddler.
No, um, Mrs. Foster,
it wasn't asthma.
I know you weren't on duty
at the time of the hanging,
and since both myself
and the operational director
were viewing the prison,
the responsibility
is equally shared.
But you do understand,
as governor in charge,
the overall responsibility
is yours.
Yes, I understand.
All four prisoners will remain
segregated at Barfield
until the trial,
which could be anything
up to six months.
So we remain open, then, do we?
OFFICER: Governor's here
to see you, Brinkley.
Well, I've eaten
my dinner last night.
I asked for kippers
for breakfast this morning.
Good.
You can return to C Wing,
and I don't want to hear
another word about this radio.
- Now, is that understood?
- Yes, Governor.
Thank you very much for
being fair and square with me.
Move him out.
BRINKLEY: I've won!
I beat them!
I've won!
Radio!
Mine!
I've won!
It's me!
[Mid-tempo music playing]
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/agzwv
Help other users to choose the best subtitles