- [Cell doors clanging]
- BRAITHWAITE: Hey! You!
I'm onto you.
I know all about you.
REYNOLDS:
What's all this for?
We was done last week.
Why us again?
JACKSON:
Quit moaning, Harry.
You. Out.
Move!
WOLTON: Sorry, Mr. Jackson.
Just saying hello.
OFFICER: Right, that's it.
Get this lot packed up.
Get sorted.
WOLTON: What have you
got with you, then?
Any money?
Phone cards?
Have you got stuff
you can trade, have you?
BRINKLEY: Bastards.
OFFICER:
Right, Brinkley, shut it.
Move.
["Only You" plays]
Watch any video online with Open-SUBTITLES
Free Browser extension: osdb.link/ext
Come through.
Morning, Mr. Maynard.
Is your sister
out of hospital yet?
- Yes, sir. Thank you, sir.
- Keep moving.
Good luck, Mr. Maynard.
Hope it goes all right.
Jackson to control.
Prisoner walking.
We're at gate two.
Is the exit clear?
Over.
You have clearance.
Thank you.
Move through.
[Horn honks]
[Doorbell rings]
Blimey.
They really meant it when
they said they'd send me a car.
Huh! Very impressive.
Thank you very much.
[Metal detector whining]
[Chirping]
[Chirping stops]
Handmade for me, all this.
You can tell the man
by the cut of his jib.
Silk.
Second only to
a young woman's skin.
Governor's orders, he's to be
cuffed at all times,
even inside the wagon,
Mr. Jackson.
Yes, sir.
Hair.
You hand him over
to security at...
Is it fake, is it?
You tell me.
I will tell you, Maynard.
Your kind make me sick
to my stomach.
It's easy to act big inside,
but all you really are
is a cheap thief.
Your money stinks.
Like roses, when you got it.
This is all
you can take out with you.
WOMAN: A little bit more,
please.
Yeah, yeah.
Get to her first.
Yeah.
You got the sides?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, okay, okay.
Are you ready?
- MAN: Stand by.
- You okay? Almost there.
MAN:
Five, four, three, two...
[Fanfare plays]
Good morning.
Last week it was announced
by the prison authorities
that the new governor of the
riot-torn prison Barfield
was to be Helen Hewitt.
Miss Hewitt has joined us
in the studio today.
- Good morning to you, Helen.
- Morning.
At 33, you are
the youngest woman governor
in charge of
an all-male category B prison.
Yes, that's correct.
And as if that weren't
enough of a challenge,
you'll also be overseeing
the government's plans
for the refurbishment
of Barfield.
Yes, I am.
Now, the press believe
that your appointment
may have been
a publicity stunt...
I do not believe
that my appointment
was in any way
a publicity-seeking campaign
by the prison services.
Also joining us this morning
is Sarah Smith.
Sarah, you feel very differently
about criminals, don't you?
Eight years ago,
I was raped and mugged
only a few yards
from my own home.
I sustained injuries to my spine
and have been unable to walk
any distance since.
My house was recently burgled,
although the police doubted
if the two crimes
were connected.
I was unable to deal
with the terror that he had...
the man who raped me,
had come back.
There was a reason for that,
wasn't there?
Yes, he threatened me.
He said he knew where I lived
and he would always
be able to find me.
And you connected the burglary
with the rapist?
Yes, I did.
You see, by that time
he'd already been released
from his prison.
WOMAN:
And how did this make you feel?
Angry. Very angry!
I live with a life sentence,
not him.
I just want to know
that he's locked up
and unable to hurt
and abuse another woman.
Miss Hewitt, do you believe
that more government support
is given to the criminal
than to the victim?
Every victim
has a right to justice.
Of course they do.
But that is not my job.
That is the job
of the law courts.
My job is to ensure that the
perpetrators are rehabilitated
so that when they leave prison,
they are no longer
a threat to society.
SMITH:
But it doesn't work.
The man who raped me
raped another woman
six months after his release.
Well, considering the cost
to keep a prisoner
in luxury today,
it's not surprising...
Why doesn't the government
spend more money on the victims
and not the criminals?
The main costs are
to ensure total security,
so that a prisoner cannot escape
and endanger the public.
I-I do understand
and feel for the victims,
such as Miss Smith,
and of course,
they should be cared for,
but there are
at this present time
over 50,000 men in prison.
We cannot operate
a "lock them up
and throw away the key" regime,
which achieves
absolutely nothing.
We must at all costs
rehabilitate them
so that they do not reoffend.
Sarah, did you receive
any compensation?
£2,500.
It's a very small amount
in comparison
with the estimated £40 million
worth of damage done
during the recent riots
at Barfield.
Surely if the intention
was to rehabilitate
the men held there,
then it failed.
The comfort, or the
softly, softly" approach...
I've no intention of applying
a soft approach
to my term as governor.
In today's paper
it was announced
that Barfield has been allocated
£60 million for the rebuild.
Surely this is
an astronomical amount of money.
I have not been informed
as to the exact amount
to be allocated to Barfield.
Really?
It was in The Independent today.
Perhaps this is an indication
of mismanagement.
Sadly, yet again, the victims
of crime seem to be the losers.
Was anyone at Barfield informed?
MAN: Yes. There was
e-mail notification.
How could it possibly
get leaked to the press
without prior consultation
with me?
I can't say, but it must
have come from HQ.
I would like to see those plans.
Yes, I know you
are my area manager,
but don't you think that since
I am the governor in charge,
I may possibly have
some suggestions?
I'll arrange it.
As you're in London,
say, half an hour?
That's absolutely fine.
I'll be there.
Has anyone from Barfield
been shown these designs?
I really wouldn't know.
I'm just the architect.
Well, it would make sense
to ask people working there
for their input, wouldn't it?
Well, I have only had dealings
with the prison authorities.
The new priority
is to be the plumbing.
Stainless steel toilets
and wash basins to each cell.
These men spend 12 hours a day
inside these cells.
They also eat
all of their meals in there.
It is totally insanitary.
What's this?
A proposed football pitch.
AstroTurf.
AstroTurf?
Well, no wonder
it's costing 60 million.
This a swimming pool, is it?
This is proposed to be built
inside the new larger perimeter,
and is a complete secure unit.
Is it an SSU or a control unit?
A sort of prison
within the prison.
[Cellphone rings]
You mean a secure unit,
Mr. Greenleaves.
In America,
it is nicknamed the "cage,"
but from your design,
it resembles
a four-star YMCA hostel.
- Yes.
- Miss Hewitt?
- Speaking.
- [Speaking indistinctly]
No, I don't care
what his solicitor says.
I want Maynard cuffed to an
officer throughout that hearing.
MAN: Without more time
we were unable
to accommodate your request.
What the hell
am I paying you two for?
There's no way they can freeze
those accounts, is there?
Mr. Maynard, it's gone
beyond that stage.
- You're being charged.
- I'm a declared bankrupt.
They can charge me
with what the hell they like.
How much? Hey?
Now, come on, you two.
How much
are they trying to get me for?
It's not just the Inland Revenue
and value added tax.
Transporting anything
is a very costly business.
Well, there must be a way
to salvage the original plan.
I don't care what it costs.
Now, look, this building here
is under construction.
And this one too.
Now, are you telling me
that there's no way
to get access to this area?
We might get 'round it,
but it will cost.
WOMAN: Mr. Maynard is solicited
to court two.
- Are they ready for the hearing?
- Yes, sir.
Oh!
Trying to clean me out.
Let's go.
There's no way that we can, uh,
get rid of these for
the hearing, is there, you know?
I mean, they know
I've been nicked, you know?
No need to overplay your hand,
you know,
and lose the sympathy vote,
is there?
How much?
Five grand? Ten?
No? 20?
Final offer... 30 large.
[Chuckles]
Just joking.
Can you do it?
I'm gonna have to find
one hell of a pilot.
- Mr. Morgan...
- Later, son.
You must be the new lad
from Pentonville.
I'm the senior officer
on C Wing.
- Russell Morgan.
- James Malahide. Jimmy.
So, what made you sign up, then?
I was in the services.
Couldn't settle into civvies.
My wife's just had a baby.
Ah, 14 years 3 Para, me.
A period is one hour,
9:30 to 10:30.
We keep them coming.
Unless it rains.
Good morning, Stanley.
Your governor coming back then,
is he?
Why, yours not?
Did you see her
on TV this morning?
Not exactly what you'd call
"Baywatch" material, is she?
[Laughs]
That's Edward Maynard's runner.
Carries all his messages
backwards and forwards,
sort of like a ferret.
Other chap is Harry Reynolds,
lifer.
Cigarette?
You know who I am.
Ex-RAF, aren't you?
Mr. Maynard needs some advice.
Do you reckon Maynard
will come back?
Yeah.
These big mothers
look after Maynard.
Day off for them today.
- Mr. Morgan.
- I said later, son.
That's Roddy Marsh.
He ate his grandmother,
didn't he?
Aye.
He's a vegetarian now.
- There's the nonces!
- Perverts!
[Indistinct shouting]
Perverts!
Come on, old man!
Pervert!
What's your problem?
You've got a pad thief,
Mr. Morgan, on C Wing.
All right, son.
We'll settle it.
Go on, then.
You watch your step, Marky.
Good morning, Governor!
Big breakfast go all right,
then, did it?
[Chuckles]
- What's with that guy?
- Oh, he's harmless enough.
Just keeps on
getting over the wall.
We've got to keep him
in the sheltered area
till he learns some sense.
Don't they have those stripes
in Pentonville, then?
Oh, yeah. Just never
seen them used, that's all.
Oh, you don't see them
used much these days.
Bloody prison watchdogs reckon
they're too humiliating.
Yeah, but I was told that
there'd be no loss
of me privileges,
just 21 days punishment.
Hang about.
You're doing four years, right?
- Yeah.
- You lost 21 days.
So you're telling me you're
going out on your old date?
Yeah, man.
But what about you doing chokey
for head-butting that screw?
You get 21 days, right?
Yeah, they just said
me time went on pause.
Well, if your time went on
pause, when did it start again?
When I got back to me pad.
No way.
You got 21 days extra.
They got to be doubled.
You sure about that?
How long would he have?
I don't know.
Piss off!
There's money in this for you.
Get it sent to your wife.
You sure it'd take 20 minutes
before the scream went up?
Night the riot went down,
40 minutes.
I'd go for it.
[Coughs]
- What's happened to you?
- It's my wisdom tooth.
It's been throbbing all night,
and now it's started bleeding.
All right, let's have a look.
Come on, open up.
Which one?
All right, Howard,
we'll get it fixed.
Go on, son.
Scarper.
Now, look, if you're right,
and you say your time
did not go on pause,
and you say none of your
privileges were taken away,
you should be entitled to them.
Yeah.
But they usually put them
at the end of your EDR.
So if you got three months,
well, where did they put them?
Frigging push me!
I don't know.
Piss off.
What you've got to do
is ask them to explain.
Ask the S.O.
Mr. Morgan, can I have a word?
Inside, Brian.
Go on.
So, now you've met some of
the players, what do you think?
Okay.
I think I can handle it.
Mr. Morgan, there's something
going down... big.
- I think it's a delivery.
- Bugger off, son.
Welcome to Barfield.
C Wing S.O.
has made a dental appointment
for prisoner Howard Webster,
4:00 this afternoon.
Anything you need.
Thought you were very good
this morning.
I didn't.
Oh, Mavis, um, was there any
kind of press release from HQ?
I'll check the fax machine.
Everything okay?
You missed your rounds
this morning.
Mr. Lyons isn't here, but I've
shown young Malahide the ropes.
Big of aggro going down, and...
Oh, he's the, um,
the new officer?
Yep. I think
he'll settle in all right.
Mm-hmm.
Prisoner 435, Jack Bulmer,
has complained
that he has lost phone cards,
two one-ounce packets
of tobacco,
a Game Boy, four games,
a Sony Walkman, and some tapes.
I also got a good informant
on the wing.
He seems to think
something's coming in.
Like what?
Dixons opening a branch?
Anyway, I put it in my report.
Lad sometime makes stuff up.
Mr. Marshall coming back, is he?
I've not been informed by HQ.
But then, I wasn't privy
to the press release
about the refurbishment costs
either.
Is that true? They're gonna
spend 60 million on this place?
I really have no idea.
It was in The Independent.
We recorded
the breakfast show in the club.
I bet you did, Mr. Morgan.
I had five phone cards.
And Mark, next pad,
he asked me if he can borrow
one of my phone cards.
I tell him no because I know
he won't pay me for it.
Right?
I come back from association
last night,
and my pad's been cleaned out.
And this morning, on exercise,
I heard a rumor
that somebody in D Wing
has been offered one,
and someone in this
wing's been offered one too.
It's really got me down,
Miss Hewitt.
I mean, that Game Boy's worth
at least 15 phone cards.
All right, Jack.
I'll see what I can do.
But you know it's against
prison regulations
to do these trade-offs.
Okay?
[Sighs]
Now, Webster.
You've made him
a 4:00 p.m. dental appointment.
MORGAN: That's right.
- Morning, Gov.
- Morning.
- Uh, morning.
What time's Dr. Thomas due?
2:00.
But Webster needs a dentist.
I think we should have a new
arrangement with the doctor.
I mean, as things
stand at the moment,
if the inmates want to see him,
they have to wait until 2:00.
So?
It clashes
with their visiting times.
If they have to see the doc,
then they miss their visit,
and they won't miss their visit.
Okay. Point taken.
Thank you.
I'd like to see Mr. Andrews
as soon as possible, please.
WOMAN:
Can I take a message?
No, I'd like to
speak to him personally.
- I'll check his diary.
- Thank you.
Dr. Thomas is here.
Oh, good.
Show him in.
Oh, and Mavis, was there
anything from the press office?
- It's the governor.
- ANDREWS: Miss Hewitt.
I'd like you to use the inserts
on the cuffs for Webster.
Uh, let me check.
- Who?
- Howard Webster, Prisoner 533.
He has a dental appointment
this afternoon.
- Secure?
- Yes, secure.
Well, he's already
absconded twice, so...
Thank you.
Dr. Thomas,
I told you she's waiting.
See you in a minute.
Don't get involved.
He's got a shocking reputation.
- As what?
- A ladies man.
Belongs to the same golf club
as me husband.
Different one every weekend,
and not golfing partners.
Did we get a fax from a HQ?
Well, I do have
quite a busy practice,
but there's four of us,
so yeah, I should be able to.
HEWITT: Good.
It's just that if the men
have an appointment
at the same time as their visit,
then either
they don't get their visit
or they don't
get their appointment.
DR. THOMAS: Yeah, yeah.
You can leave it with me.
- [Knocks]
- HEWITT: Thanks.
I thought I put it on your desk.
It's only the press release from
the article in The Independent.
Could you give me two minutes?
Uh, actually, I'm sorry,
I can't.
I should go on my duty.
Oh, well, don't let me detain.
Okay. And I'll sort out
those duty periods.
It was faxed in late, and, um,
we had the 6:00 TV call.
I mean, you couldn't have
seen it anyway.
In future, Mavis, anything
that comes in for me from HQ,
anything at all,
you get it to me.
I looked a total prat
this morning.
Sorry.
It's headquarters,
Mr. Andrews' secretary.
Are you free for dinner?
No, I'm sorry.
But I didn't say which night?
How about Tuesday or Thursday?
No.
Now excuse me.
Well, Saturday night, then?
[Clears throat]
Mr. Andrews can see you this
afternoon, Miss Hewitt. 3:00.
Oh, bugger it!
Now I have to go back into town.
I'm sorry, do you want me
to change it?
No!
[Up-tempo rock music playing]
[Indistinct conversations]
They gave me this with dates on.
- And?
- They said it explains it.
- Does it?
- No.
Somebody gonna do something
about my stolen property?!
Jack, be a good lad.
Come get your dinner.
Back in your cell.
Mr. Malahide.
Get lockup started.
- Mavis, Miss Hewitt in?
- MAVIS: He's reinstated.
- What?
- Gary Marshall.
Well, could you ask
Mr. Marshall,
as soon as he comes in,
to come down to C Wing.
I think we may have a problem.
Good news, lads.
Gary's back.
Afternoon, Governor.
I was just coming in to see you.
Saw you on TV this morning.
Very good.
You didn't see the article
in The Independent, then?
I'm going to HQ.
I'll see you later.
Any problems?
Nothing I can't handle,
thank you, Gary.
Hey, Gary.
Good to see you back.
Yeah. I don't think her ladyship
feels the same.
[Horn honking]
Well, you can wiggle
out of that, can't you?
So, not taking any chances.
- How's that?
- It's too tight.
That's the way we like it.
Cab here, is it?
Clock ticking,
ready and waiting.
Now, you're on trust, Webster.
So don't mess us about.
Be a bit difficult unless
we want to quickstep together.
HEWITT: Back off!
Did you hear?
I said back this vehicle off.
Are you complete...
Move this back!
[Shouting indistinctly]
Christ's sake!
Is there anyone
with half a brain around here?!
[Laughs]
I'd better give her a hand.
She's wedged in.
Would you move this back?
Will you use
a bit of bloody common sense?
It went all over my car!
Would you get these
bloody vehicles out of here?!
This is a secur...
Look at this!
It's a security risk.
I do not want the contractual
vehicles using this entrance.
They use the back exit,
where it is safe.
No exit must...
This must not be blocked.
- [Engine cranking]
- [Truck horn honks]
Shit.
Yes!
[Cranking continues]
What was that about not
blocking the drive, Miss Hewitt?
HEWITT: [Laughing] I bet those
bastards are taping this.
What's this?
Maynard's back.
["Only You" plays]
Am I glad to be back here.
He doesn't look a happy man.
You have any trouble?
I never left the bastard's side.
[Laughs]
How much did they take off him?
Don't know exactly,
but they stung him
for about two million VAT.
Oh, you're kidding.
Listed about
80 different companies.
I tell you, I've never heard
anything like it.
Confident about
one thing, though.
I reckon he's trying
to set something up.
Governor did too.
She was dead edgy about it.
Ho!
MAN:
Welcome back, mate.
[Indistinct talking
and cheering]
I hear you might be having
your stay with us extended.
Don't bet on it.
- Nice day.
- Yeah.
Forecast said
it was gonna be nice.
Hey, I think I'll do a spot
of fishing this weekend.
What's he in for?
Shooting a cab driver in the
back of the head for being nosy.
MORGAN ON P.A.: Get a move on.
Have your white slips ready
to be checked at the gate.
Please put the cue and balls
back in the lockers
and get in line.
We'd have come out
if you hadn't been reinstated.
Welcome back.
Get those two
off the pool table,
and more important,
lock up the gear.
OFFICER:
Okay, Mr. Morgan.
You up to speed?
Yeah, well, I heard about
Roddy Marsh's tip-off.
Delivery?
Ah, might be nothing, but he
reckons something's brewing.
I'll have a word with security.
I also heard that Jack Bulmer
wants to shove a cue
up someone's ass.
Oh, he says that prick
Mark Lewis nicked all his gear,
but I don't want to
spin Lewis' pad on spec.
Mm.
What's she doing about it?
Bugger all.
I'll have a word
with that bastard Maynard.
Oh, shit.
Never mind, partner.
[Laughs]
Good game, was it?
Yes, man.
You know me.
I always deliver.
You know I got 21 days
down the block, right?
- Come here.
- Yes, Mr. Maynard, sir.
Help the lads with their balls.
There's a good chap.
I shall be making
a few calls today,
so make sure there's no one
on the dog and bone.
FIELD: Righto, gov.
Two cues and a triangle.
Roddy.
Give the man him balls.
Gwan now, Roddy!
[Laughs]
Well, looks like they've brought
us both back, doesn't it?
I want a word.
- Get them in line.
- Sir.
Don't mess me about, Maynard.
I know you've got a finger
in everything on this wing.
What do you know
about this Jack Bulmer business?
What's this?
You think I'm a grass?
I know everyone on this wing
is licking your ass.
So if you want to
keep it this way...
Have you got a visit?
I might not just find
a record of it.
Who's the pad thief?
Oi. Over here.
You've got just 10 seconds.
I want the pad thief.
You're worried
the old shvartza's
gonna top himself, ain't you?
Just the Game Boy.
With me?
OFFICER: Come on.
Visiting time.
Those with passes
start to line up.
You owe me.
Check out Mark Lewis.
OFFICER: Visiting time.
Lockup!
Any prisoners without a visitors
pass, back in your cells.
I need to explain this
to me girlfriend,
about the 21 days.
Shut up.
Mr. Morgan, I thought...
You haven't got
a visitor, Roddy.
Get back in your cell.
Now!
Yeah, Mark Lewis.
We are gonna have to
sort that bastard.
He is not running this nick.
From what I've heard,
nor is she.
We'll wait till she gets back,
let her play at being governor.
OFFICER:
Back to your cells.
[Indistinct conversations]
My stereo,
my Game Boy, five phone cards.
It's destroyed me, man.
Five phone cards,
my Game Boy, and my stereo.
I told her.
I told the new governor.
Five phone cards,
my stereo, my Game Boy.
Is that his baby?
[Indistinct conversation]
See, I reckoned I'd be out,
right?
I mean,
nobody said nothing to me
about attaching
an extra 21 days.
Plus another 21 days.
I don't understand it.
Because if I'd done it,
then why add it?
See what I mean?
Out of order.
So, can you arrange it?
Is there any other open area?
No.
And there isn't much time.
When you go out,
you have a good look.
And you'd better not
come in again.
I'll call you.
I'm flush with phone cards.
He's not gonna be sick
in my cab, is he?
You're not gonna
be sick now, are you?
Excuse me.
Can you tell me where the...
MAN ON RADIO: For £1,000,
you have 30 seconds
to answer
this two-part question.
Who was the singer,
and in which year was it a hit?
- [Instrumental music playing]
- Clock starts now, Elaine.
ELAINE:
Um, oh, it's, uh... Matt!
Uh, uh, Matt... Matt Monro!
Matt Monro!
- MAN: Now the year.
- And, uh...
Year was...
Year I went on holiday...
MAN:
Five seconds left.
And...
ELAINE: 1964.
Webster, you bloody idiot!
To make this area
into a prison within a prison
is to my mind a step backwards.
But this type of unit
has proved very successful
in the United States.
Your prison will be the first...
My prison?!
And yet not one person
from Barfield, including myself,
has been asked
for their opinion.
Well, this is still
under discussion, Miss Hewitt.
My priority is rehabilitation.
Yes, you made that
reasonably clear
this morning on television.
I would have made it
a damn sight clearer
had I been privy to the fact
that Barfield had already been
allocated 60 million.
Barfield will be the most
secure prison in England.
Phone cards.
They have already become
prison currency,
so I would withdraw them.
The inmates could be planning
a riot, an escape, anything.
It is a blatant security risk.
[Up-tempo rock music playing]
Can I make a phone call?
No. You'll have to wait
while it's free.
Just like everybody else.
I was only being polite.
Prick.
Sorry, Mr. Maynard.
Didn't know
you needed to make a call.
Bastard.
Mean bastard.
Webster's done a runner.
See, I would have thought
that withdrawing all currency,
you know, phone cards and so on,
would create
a veritable time bomb.
No, no, no.
Boredom is the bomb.
Some of these bored men have
very short, dangerous fuses.
If we allow
that short, dangerous fuse
to allow a criminal's dominance,
then all we are doing
is creating
a more dangerous criminal.
[Telephone rings]
And every time
that criminal reoffends,
it is proof
that our present system
is failing both us and them.
Excuse me.
Yes, hello. Helen Hewitt.
Howard Webster absconded.
You authorized a dental
appointment this afternoon.
Fine.
The police are on their way
to his family now.
Uh, just keep me informed.
As soon as I've finished here,
I'll be straight back.
Everything all right?
Fine.
One of the prisoners
has a dental problem.
[Bob Marley's "Three Little
Birds" playing]
♪ Don't worry ♪
♪ About a thing ♪
♪ 'Cause every little thing ♪
♪ Gonna be all right ♪
♪ Singing don't worry ♪
♪ About a thing ♪
♪ 'Cause every little thing ♪
♪ Gonna be all right ♪
Evening, Gov.
This is our wing governor,
Mr. Lyons.
This is the new boy... Malahide.
James.
Ah, you've had a blinder
on your first day, haven't you?
Bloody Webster. She should
never have let him out.
Aye.
MAN: In this
high-rise office block...
[Indistinct conversations]
♪ ...with pain ♪
♪ You talk to me of sunsh... ♪
- Back off me, man.
- [Speaks indistinctly]
Look, I need a little bit
more time, all right?
I've got some gear coming in,
so just wait a sec.
MAYNARD: Who else have you been
opening your yapping trap to?
FIELD: I was only
trying to help, Mr. Maynard.
Is it on, then?
Good evening, Mr. Lyons.
Had a day off, have we?
I wonder if there's any chance
of getting Channel 4
or maybe BBC Two
on the old telly there.
♪ ...gonna be all right ♪
BULMER: Pad thief!
Thief! Thief!
- MAYNARD: Oh, for God's sake.
- Thief!
[Indistinct shouting]
FIELD: Don't get involved,
Mr. Maynard!
I'm not,
but you bloody well better
because they can stop exercise!
Shit!
Now break it up!
- [Indistinct shouting]
- [Alarm ringing]
♪ Three little birds ♪
♪ Pitch by my doorstep ♪
♪ Singing sweet songs ♪
♪ Of melodies pure and true ♪
♪ Saying... ♪
[Tires screech]
[Gasps]
Shit!
[Horn blaring]
Webster?
Sorry about this, miss.
Keep your hands
on the bonnet, Webster.
Stay right where you are.
Just do as I tell you.
[Thunder rumbles]
Stay where you are.
Hello? Hello?
Yeah.
This is the governor.
Put me through to security.
Now!
Hands on the bonnet, Webster!
Yeah, um,
I'm about five or six miles
north of Barfield
on the main lane.
Call a search, get somebody
to me as fast as you can.
I've got Webster with me.
They'll be here in two minutes!
Stand up!
I'm gonna pass you my coat.
Keep your hands
where I can see them.
Get in the car, Webster.
Put your hands on the dashboard
where I can see them.
He looked as sick as a dog.
And I thought
he'd had an injection.
So the toothache wasn't real?
Well, the dentist said
he had an infection in his gums.
I didn't put the slips
inside the cuffs.
It's down to me, nobody else.
I haven't lost one in 20 years.
[Knock on door]
Governor's
just contacted security.
She's with Webster
just outside Barfield.
What?
Done it again, haven't I?
I don't think what you've done
is anything to joke about.
It's bloody stupid.
How many more months
are you intent on putting
on your original sentence?
Why did you do it?
Do you have marital problems?
No.
I wasn't running home.
Girlfriend?
No.
I don't want to talk about it.
Well, you're gonna
have to talk about it...
To me,
to the probation department,
to the prison authorities.
Do you understand
what you have done?
You have absconded, Howard,
whilst in custody
for the third time.
I was going back in
like I'd done before.
I wasn't staying out.
I don't understand.
You escape
and then you come back.
It doesn't make sense.
Who were you running to?
Where were you going?
Nowhere.
Look at me, Howard.
Look at me.
Do you think I'm stupid?
Do you think
I believe this crap?
Running to nowhere?
Yeah! Running.
That's it.
- You wouldn't understand.
- Understand what?
Webster!
Don't! Webster!
Webster! Webster!
I can't run in the yard.
Few paces, got to stop.
Few paces, stop.
I can't run in the yard!
I had my chance, so I took it.
I was going crazy.
You escaped just to run?
Are you serious?
To run.
No one understands.
Come on, boy. They'll be here
any minute. Now's your chance.
Come on! Talk to me!
My dad was a great athlete.
He was my coach.
And then he got sick,
and he just
used to concentrate on me.
He pushed and he pushed at me
like I would be everything
that he couldn't be.
Well, the trials
for the county came up.
And he wouldn't leave me alone.
I was in the starting block,
I heard the gun go off,
but I couldn't move.
I just froze.
I think I nicked my first car
to get back at him.
Well, I got back at him,
all right.
He died the first day
I was sent down.
[Siren wailing]
Here, this is your coat.
You'd better take it.
I don't want
any trouble for you.
Howard, would you give me
your word not to abscond again
if I arrange for the yard
to be clear for you
so that you can exercise?
You all right, ma'am?
Come on, son.
Move it.
Prisoner secure.
Returning to base. Over.
MAN: How is he?
What's going on?
MAN #2: What's going on?
Is it Webster? Is he back?
Oi, Webster!
[Indistinct talking]
This is gonna create.
- I told her he shouldn't go.
- [Punches thudding]
Shut up, all of you!
- [Punch thuds]
- [Coughs]
[Up-tempo disco music playing]
Oh, Officer Malahide.
Welcome to Barfield.
Thank you, Governor.
Um, did Mark Lewis
have a Game Boy
on his
personal possessions list?
Uh, no.
No, he didn't.
Mr. Malahide,
it is very important
that every prisoner's
cell belongings
are checked on a regular basis.
If an item is not on the list,
one, it is against the rules,
two, the prisoner
must be put on report,
and three, if this
had been checked,
it would have saved us
a hell of a lot of aggravation.
[Music continues playing]
Good morning, Mr. Snooper.
What do you know about this?
Did Mark Lewis offer...
Could you turn that off, please?
[Music stops]
Nothing.
I never seen it before, miss.
Is it Jack Bulmer's Game Boy?
I don't know.
Does it have "Jack"
printed on the side?
Can you see that?
Now, were you offered this?
Were you going to
buy this, Mr. Snooper?
I've never seen it before, miss.
You know, Mr. Snooper,
you've only got,
what, another 18 months?
Jack Bulmer's got 11 years.
I know.
He's a lifer.
I know he is.
Then you must know that
with that amount of time,
you don't want to
create any trouble.
You don't get a parole.
You just want to do your time
and create
as little fuss as possible.
Look, I feel really sorry
for Jack, Miss,
but I don't know nothing
about no Game Boy.
So Mark Lewis
never offered you this?
No.
Can I ask you something, miss?
Every morning
they bring me scrambled egg.
I don't like scrambled eggs.
[Music resumes]
- Morning, Miss Hewitt.
- HEWITT: Morning.
It's a bit, uh,
early for your rounds, isn't it?
Morning.
Excuse me, Miss Hewitt.
Uh, because of
what happened yesterday...
That, uh, little fracas
that we had during, uh,
association...
That won't mean that we don't
get any exercise, will it?
HEWITT: Thank you.
Well, if you weren't involved in
the, um, fracas as you call it,
then, no, you'll get
your usual exercise period.
Oh, good.
It's just that,
well, it's just a lovely day.
I'd hate to miss it.
Mr. Maynard.
Officer Malahide.
Could you ask Governor Lyons
to step into my office
this afternoon, please?
- Certainly, Gov.
- Thank you.
- Excuse me. Can I have a word?
- Yes.
- Morning.
Webster absconded.
You put him back on the wing.
You know my feelings about that.
Then you give this.
This is bloody stupid.
Why.
Because it's like he's getting
a perk for legging it.
No, that's not a perk.
That is a punishment.
Why? Why are you laying yourself
on the line like this, hmm?
[Sighs] Because I gave Webster
my word,
and in this place, that is
of the utmost importance.
Fine. I'll tell the S.O.
on the wing.
No, I'll tell him.
And, Gary,
I want prisoner Mark Lewis
transferred out of Barfield.
We'll do a trade-off
if necessary,
but I want him out of here.
Are you decent, Webster?
Has he had breakfast?
Could you wait outside, please?
What happened?
Slipped on the stairs, miss.
Do you wish to make a complaint
against anyone?
No.
You will lose your privileges
for a month,
and 21 days will be
added onto your sentence.
Yes, miss.
Thank you, miss.
You will also lose the privilege
of exercising
with the other inmates.
You'll be exercised in the yard,
alone, though under supervision,
and for at least three quarters
of an hour a day.
Punishment?
Don't let me down.
Stop tugging at me.
You're driving me nuts.
Is it going down?
I've done everything for you.
- I'm with you, aren't I?
- Shut up.
Well, come on!
Give it to me straight.
I told you yesterday!
You get an extra three months,
you prat!
Three months?
Bastard!
[Laughs]
I heard Webster come back
with the gov.
He got out to give her a fuck.
That's what I was told.
Yeah.
He's running a bit of a risk,
isn't he?
I'm going to be moved, aren't I?
I know.
You accused Mark Lewis
of stealing certain items.
Are these the belongings
that were stolen from your cell?
He did it at 6:45
on Tuesday's association.
I know because
I went to make a phone call.
But nobody actually saw him
entering your cell,
so how can you be sure?
Because he wanted
some Sellotape.
I said he could get it.
I saw him going in
as I went down the landing.
But you didn't actually see
your things in Mark Lewis' cell.
The next day at lunch, I'm told
by someone that Oswald Snooper
was offered a Game Boy
by Mark Lewis,
so it had to be him.
So you took the law
into your own hands.
I never touched
one of the bosses, ma'am.
I never touched one of them.
I will take that
into consideration,
and your previous good behavior,
and the fact
that you were provoked.
But I cannot condone
such violence,
so obviously
you will be punished.
But you will get your belongings
returned to you eventually.
You put me back on the wing
with him, and he'll kill me.
Mark Lewis will be transferred
from Barfield.
I owe you, Miss Hewitt.
And as I'm down here,
no one will know.
Rumor is there's going to be
a delivery.
They're wrong.
It's a collection.
[Helicopter blades whirring]
Oh, my God.
It's a helicopter.
Get the alarms on!
Don't move yet.
[Wagner's
"Ride of the Valkyries" plays]
[Alarm blares]
[Indistinct shouting]
Stay back,
else it'll cut you to ribbons!
MORGAN: Stop standing
bloody around and get inside!
That's it!
Come on!
Holy shit!
Beautiful!
Yes!
[Alarm blaring]
No, not this time, old son.
Hey! Hey!
Oh, no, no, no.
["Only You" plays]
Why didn't you stop them?
[Men singing indistinctly]
Yes, man!
♪ O-Only you ♪
We've got your car out.
Good luck.
MAN: Miss Hewitt!
Miss Hewitt!
Can you tell us, have there been
any further developments?
She's got some bottle,
I'll give her that.
I just hope
her bloody car starts.
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/agzwx
Help other users to choose the best subtitles