ENJOY ALL VOD IN HIGH QUALITY @ 4KVOD.TV
GET LIVE TV,MOVIES,SHOWS IN ONE PACKAGE
FAMILY MOTTO
A HARMONIOUS FAMILY WITH LOVE
THE YOO'S FRUIT SHOP
I…
I remember.
You'll know how flustered
I am by your actions
once you get your memories back.
I'm sure she wanted
to slap my shameless face.
It's amazing…
that she held back all her life.
I felt like my life was already over
when I was 22.
I prayed to God
to give me a reason to live.
And right then,
she appeared in front of me like fate.
I promise I'll work harder
and move to a better place.
Guys, Dad's home.
Dad, did you drive safely today?
I sure did.
-Welcome home.
-Where's your mother?
-Bedroom.
The bedroom?
You're home.
Ms. Sook, did you cry?
No.
Did the kids give you a hard time?
Actually…
I was reading and…
You cried while reading? Like a kid?
You made fun of me
when I cried during a movie.
The kids are home.
I wanted her to be happy as I was
and love me as much as I loved her.
THE BRIDGES OF MADISON COUNTY
Eun-hee.
What did I do wrong
to make her leave?
I promised that if she came back,
I would only live
as the father of our children.
He said this was
the day he proposed to you
and held your hand for the first time,
and this photo was taken
to remember it forever.
Mom.
Dad said it wrong,
right?
You said you already
had Eun-joo at the time.
She cannot be premature.
Eun-joo was born later than her due date.
Did you…
say it wrong?
I have no idea
what you're talking about.
Your father's memories
are not all there yet.
Want to take some jangjorim?
You like to have my stir-fried anchovies
and jangjorim with beer.
Mom.
I've always been curious…
Why did you
leave the house with only Eun-joo?
Why didn't you take me with you?
At that time…
I was younger than your current age.
I didn't know
what I had to do…
Mom.
That's not what I'm asking you.
Since then,
I thought you'd leave again,
so I started walking
on eggshells around you,
so you would take me with you next time.
I want to know if there was another reason
other than you hating me.
I feel bad
for being mean to Eun-joo all my life.
Yes.
After I returned,
I realized that I broke your heart.
You used to laugh a lot
and remain confident even
when you were in trouble,
but you started walking on eggshells
and looked around
to see where I am…
It's my fault.
I remembered what Dad said
at Eun-joo's wedding.
What's wrong with you?
Why do you keep making that angry face?
I'm not angry.
Is it because I'm not graceful
as his family?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I don't fit as Eun-joo's father.
I…
I now understand
what Dad was talking about.
No…
Your father and I were going to
keep it to ourselves, and…
No…
Yes.
All secrets are revealed eventually.
Who knew that your father
would become 22 years old again…
and bring that up.
Take that photo to him.
I'm sick of your father being immature.
It's not his fault.
I figured it out.
Should I just act like
I don't know about it?
Eun-joo is still my sister.
That doesn’t change.
Nothing has to change.
No matter how things go,
your father is your sister's real father.
We have to admit that.
If he wasn't, I wouldn't have been
with him until now.
Eun-joo has to know the truth.
Don't let her hear it
from someone else, Mom.
You must…
tell her.
You…
I'm home.
What is it this time?
Are you two fighting?
We need to get along, please.
Gosh, such a mess!
You…
Did you hear the conversation just now?
No.
What conversation?
You…
-Don't you have anything to say to me?
-I don't.
Sit.
Since you confessed your feelings for me,
I must answer it.
I got estranged from my parents
when I got into medical school,
and I don't have any friends
to share my secrets with.
You were my only family and friend.
I mean this.
I am going to start working
at the clinic tomorrow.
Take as much time as you need.
Start over.
Meet a man too.
I wanted to talk about it lightly today.
You need a child, a husband, and love.
That's what a true family is.
But that won't be possible with me.
You don't need to be
so meticulous and plan my future.
I can take care of my matters.
I tried to be your friend,
but it's not working.
I can't forgive you easily, either.
But…
If I just forget about it,
it doesn't seem that serious.
Because I know everything now.
There's no need to be anxious
about not knowing the reason.
Wait until I figure out what I want.
You've been making decisions
all by yourself until now.
Don't rush me.
That's the fair way to do it.
Yes.
Do as you wish.
The CEO is going to
reschedule the meeting.
Vice CEO went on vacation.
He came a long time ago,
and he goes on vacation now?
Are they going to get married
and start a family?
Chan-hyuk. Eun-hee found out about it.
About what?
About Eun-joo.
I don't know how,
but I heard her talking about
Eun-joo with Mom.
What did she say to you?
She doesn't know that I know.
Are you sure Eun-hee
doesn't know that you know?
I'm sure she doesn't.
I'm 100% sure she'll ask me.
What should I say?
Let's just be honest
and tell her that we know.
By the way…
I told her not to call you.
Do you think she will?
Why?
It seemed wrong for her
to come to the office
when you were ignoring her calls.
She's dating someone
so I said to keep a distance.
Does Eun-hee have to keep a distance
from me if she's dating someone?
And why should Eun-hee hear
such a thing from her younger brother?
Is it because you work at my company
and you might feel uncomfortable?
You're not thinking straight.
That's purely between me and Eun-hee.
It's not your business.
Are you being punished?
Hurry up and follow me.
Leave him be.
He's been staying up all night
almost every day recently.
I know.
Why does he get so many messages?
He's Mr. Popular in the matchmaking world.
What does that mean?
Calling back to a message
means you're old.
Hello, this is Golden Goose Media.
Can I check the Director's schedule
for today, please?
Would it be possible to
pull the appointment forward?
A meeting with a publishing company?
I see.
Okay.
HIRING A BARISTA
I think the owner
stepped out for a moment.
Do you want the usual?
I'll take it to go.
Okay.
I'm quitting my job here soon.
Are you taking it to go because of me?
I'll get out of your sight soon,
so don't worry.
1 P.M., P&F BOOKS
4 P.M., GOLDEN GOOSE MEDIA
JULY 15, 2:06 P.M.
MEDITATION CENTER
-Hi, Chan-pal.
-Hi.
-A meeting with the Director?
-Yes.
You're scheduled for 4 p.m.
Yes, that's right.
I'm too early.
What should I do by myself?
Can you kill time with me?
Yes.
Let's go.
Did you run here?
No, I was just out there…
Actually…
I tried to call you a few times last week.
In the middle of the night.
Then why didn't you call me?
Because I said we shouldn't
be in contact for a while?
It's not like I have to listen to you.
Then why didn't you call?
Well, just because…
Is Ji-woo working hard?
Yes.
Ji-woo said you're family to him.
Me too.
Ji-woo used to lie often
when he was young.
I couldn't take it anymore,
so I hypnotized him.
I told him that lying is very bad,
but it's okay if he shakes
his leg while lying.
That he won't be punished.
Shake your leg every time you lie.
Shake your leg…
You're more like a gangster than a sister.
Chan-hyuk.
You told me
Ji-woo was troubled
about something, right?
Ji-woo told you, didn't he?
You know what it is, right?
What a big coward.
What's with that face, when you know it?
Yes.
Ji-woo knows…
and I know, because Ji-woo
asked me for counseling.
I'm not a private safe. I'm a family safe.
How did he find it out?
He's not even that keen.
He heard it
when your father was at the hospital.
Still, you're always quicker
than me for everything.
You really must be a brother to him.
That was when you just made up
with Eun-joo.
Ji-woo will never tell.
-Mom.
-Eun-joo, let's go.
Let's go, hurry.
Are you looking for anywhere specific?
That cafe from earlier had a great vibe.
Some places changed,
and some places are still the same.
I don't know.
You said you have something to say.
Where are you going? We can just…
I am going to tell you about the past.
I was wondering
where I should tell to you,
and then, I recalled the neighborhood
I lived in when I was young.
This is the first time
you're telling me this.
It must be around here.
In our yard,
we had a few persimmon trees.
In autumn, the persimmon trees bent,
and came down to the alley.
Your grandmother watched it
with a broomstick in her hand.
Whenever a hungry child
tried to steal a persimmon
she hit the child with the broomstick.
My mom was so…
harsh and greedy.
I hated that.
Whenever you said
I'm cold
and harsh
I recalled my mom.
I only said it once or twice…
I said it when I was furious. Why do you…
I get told I'm cold and harsh
way more often.
Mom.
I've never seen you like this.
I'm worried.
What is it?
What is it you want to say?
It's okay.
Tell me everything.
Let's go.
I've always been
on Mom's side all the time,
but right now, I hate her a bit.
"Were Dad and I just a joke to Mom?"
I get ridiculous thoughts like that.
So?
Will you always be
on your father's side now?
I'm not going to take sides anymore.
I'm just going to be on my side.
What use is a family at this age?
I…
I heard about the Director's
appointment with you,
so I came here early on purpose.
So I could run into you
like a coincidence.
What's with those eyes?
What?
I think I overreacted last time.
We're friends and when I said we shouldn't
contact each other for a while…
It seems too childish.
I heard the news from Ji-woo.
I got worried about you and Eun-joo,
so I rushed over here.
You look kind of
disappointed.
Kind of? Do you think it's "kind of?"
I'm totally disappointed.
My heart totally fluttered when you said
you came early to see me.
I thought of dating you from today.
Happy now? Is that what
you wanted to hear?
Oh.
I have something to tell you
about your father.
I don't know how things are now,
but at the time,
when an unmarried female
college student got pregnant,
it brought shame to the family.
The whole family was in chaos,
and the older brothers were even angrier.
They told me to abort you
and go into a Buddhist temple
and hide there forever.
It was my life,
and it was my baby.
I…
I chose you.
At the time,
an unmarried female student
who got pregnant
had nowhere to go.
The 22-year-old female student
who wanted to protect her baby,
though she was ignored
by her family and the father of the baby,
she became a family
with a 22-year-old man in love
who'd been watching her for a long time.
Eun-joo.
Say something.
What can I say?
I never imagined I'd hear such a story.
I tried to cover it up forever.
If your father didn't have an accident,
I would've done that…
I'm not a kid or a teenager
going through puberty.
I guess it's a good thing to hear it now.
Age doesn't matter with things like this.
Do I have to
ask about my biological father and so on?
No, you don’t need to.
I never even thought about him, either.
Why?
That's a bit sad.
Did you love him at least?
Was I born
ruining your life?
No, that's not true.
I…
I loved you.
I never regretted giving birth to you.
Thank you
for not giving up on me, Mom.
I…
I told Mom to tell her directly.
So I haven't called my mom
and my sister for a week.
Me,
my family,
and that family
are all being too cruel
to Kim Eun-joo, don't you think?
I…
learned something from you.
Though I always see my family
and know them so well,
I still have to put effort.
You try your best for your family.
That's what I liked about you.
You try your best for others too.
And Jong-pal and my twenties grew
and developed thanks to your nosiness.
I mean it.
You're a decent person.
You don't need to
blame yourself for everything.
-Get going.
-Okay, bye.
So you had to give up…
on a lot of things
in your life because of me.
I never gave up on anything.
Do you know how happy…
I was in that small room because of you?
Your father
loved you so much.
He even drove all night home
just to see you for a moment.
That was all real.
Was I actually lovely?
I'm not really sure.
You were.
If it wasn't for that,
I wouldn't have been
with your father until now.
He's not my father.
"Your biological father." "Your father."
I'm just a bit confused.
You must be tired.
You should go home and rest.
Give me some time to think.
I'll get going first.
My dearest Geon-hee.
You look lovely.
Where's Uncle?
Now, here.
-It's okay.
-No.
The baby is tired.
Geon-hee, you grabbed so many items.
Isn’t this a scam?
Why grab everything?
I thought babies were
supposed to grab just one.
In the future, storytelling will be
more important in the world.
If he becomes a baseball player,
then he can say he grabbed a baseball.
If he becomes an idol,
he grabbed a microphone.
We should be able to prove it.
Natural-born talent is important.
Whatever. Where's Shin Saimdang?
Money is the most important,
but it’s not here.
You're a snob.
You're such a snob.
In this story,
I'll be the money-crazy one.
Because it's my profession.
But I'll do it later.
Geon-hee is very tired.
Let's take a break.
Okay.
-Let's shoot the source.
-Okay.
Let's take a break
and do it one more time.
-Okay.
-Sure.
-Let's go mainly with colors.
-Okay.
Hey, Park Chan-hyuk.
I heard you saw Eun-hee.
Yes.
I feel so refreshed
because you two met up.
Those wretched lunatics.
I told her to come,
but Eun-hee was acting so busy.
Hey, remember
the girlfriend's letter contest
when you were in the army?
Eun-hee acted like your girlfriend
and wrote an erotic letter.
It wasn't erotic.
It was erotic.
"Whenever you take a photo,
your chin is so…"
"Your fingers touching the camera are so…"
Stop that.
Why did this Item Grabbing
turn into an alumni reunion?
That erotic letter unanimously
won the grand prize,
and he got five days of stand-down.
They begged for Eun-hee's photo.
Hey, didn't Eun-hee
send you Eun-joo's photo?
Didn't you keep
Eun-joo's photo in your wallet
as evidence during your service?
That's what the photo was used for.
-Did you see that too?
-No.
You got really tangled with my family.
Hey, that idiot Jong-pal was jealous
of Eun-hee's letter and didn't shut up.
That small-minded,
shallow anteater-like bastard.
Honey, I am the most generous man
in the world.
My dear husband,
that's worthy of jealousy.
That letter wasn't something
you could just sit and write.
It means Eun-hee peeped at this bastard
on his chin line and fingers
every time he took photos.
I said, stop it.
Seriously.
Eun-hee should be a writer,
not working at a publishing company.
And she should've dated you
instead of that bastard Jong-pal.
-Where's Geon-hee?
-Sleeping.
-Good.
-He's just like you.
He keeps eating and sleeping
endlessly.
Honey, let's take photos.
-Please take a few for us.
-Okay.
Smile.
Who's there? You might get
hurt walking around here.
Young-sik.
You're Young-sik, right?
Dad.
Someone said
my wife was seen around here,
so I came here.
You can't even remember me,
so I couldn't tell you,
and people say I ran away, but…
I'm going to go back
as soon as I find her.
Why are you kneeling?
Dad.
Why is life so hard?
It is just so hard.
Your child might wake up.
A father shouldn't cry
in front of his child.
Ha-ra was a bit sick.
I'm sorry I couldn't call you.
Is she okay now?
Yes.
I'm okay.
You should've at least texted me.
You answered the call
about a serious fight at night
and didn't call back.
And you didn't come to work
for a week, so I was worried.
Glad to see that nothing happened.
I was about to go.
You were worried
so why couldn't you call me first?
You're not curious?
Why don't you ask me anything?
What did you two do the whole week?
Why did you stop Ha-ra
when she asked to break up
three years ago?
Why do you want to break up with her now,
when you stopped her then?
What's the point of knowing these?
Is asking every single thing,
forcing the other to answer,
and being emotional dating?
I don't want to be
in such an immature relationship
at my age.
We're closed for today.
Didn't Eun-joo come today?
She stopped by during the day.
I'm quitting this place soon.
So stop tricking people
and live a good life.
And you need to trick people
when necessary.
You don't need to be honest
to those who hurt you and are rude to you.
EUN-JOO
The caller cannot be reached.
Please record your message…
When you're finished recording…
I worked late all week.
When I think about it now,
I've been waiting for you.
One day, two days, three days…
As time went by,
actually, I felt more comfortable.
Being out of reach for one week.
That's plenty to end our relationship.
Because it's your fault.
Felt like there was no fault in me.
I felt relieved.
I am sorry as well.
It seems like I'm using your hardship
as a reason to end this.
Just so I can come to you, I…
I spent a week that was harder
than I expected.
I thought you would understand me
because I trusted you.
I'm glad that you didn't call me secretly
by leaving someone sick behind,
and I'm glad that you're polite
to the end even when you're breaking up.
I really do think so.
Don't talk anymore for today.
You waited for me. That's all I need.
I'm sorry.
I am done.
I won't do this anymore.
TAE-HYUNG
Yes, Tae-hyung.
Eun-joo is out of reach.
She's not home at this hour.
Do you know anything about it?
No.
Didn't she tell you
she's going to see Mom?
She didn't.
Can you call your mother
and ask her, please?
Okay, I'll call you back.
They're like two kids raising a baby.
Go home. I'll clean it up.
This is not something for you to do.
You act like you're a generous CEO.
We ate it too.
So you can't clean everything alone.
Don't worry about it. Go home.
I'll do it. My hands are the fastest.
Go home, now. Go home.
-It's okay. Go home.
-Bye.
DID MY SISTER CALL YOU BY ANY CHANCE?
When did you come?
You should've called me when you came.
Did you wait for a long time?
Tae-hyung called me.
You sent Mom alone.
I heard you told Mom to tell me herself.
You said being alone is like poison
and you pushed Mom
into such an occasion?
I don't know that much about it.
And I wondered if I would be of any help.
To be honest, I still
don't know the specifics.
I thought letting you know first
was the right thing to do.
What use is knowing the specifics?
Why would I be curious about
those who were never by my side?
So I can find my biological father
and break into tears?
Remember what you always said?
We're nothing alike.
You were right about that.
I guess I'm a lot like my real father.
Stop talking like that.
Nothing changes for me.
You're my sister,
and I'm your younger sister.
Nothing changes.
Our relationship changed.
How can it not change?
Did you think about Mom's life?
Because of the time period,
she lived with a man she doesn't love
but she can't do it anymore.
I learned the reason why she endured.
-So how can it not change?
-Dad loved Mom!
We saw the 22-year-old Dad.
We saw his genuine expression.
That was a long time ago.
I'm sure Mom hated
that expression even more.
Dad threw things when he got angry,
scared Mom, and made her
give up on everything!
Do you think that's love?
-That's violence.
-Hey!
Don't exaggerate! Dad isn't violent.
You said you look up to Dad's life
as he worked all his life.
You said Mom was selfish
for looking down on Dad's healthiness!
Weren't you the one who talked back to Mom
when Dad was looked down on by her?
Because I didn't know.
I didn't know…
that I was Mom's weakness.
Dad used that weakness.
He didn't use it.
That's not true.
You were a real daughter to Dad!
You are his real daughter.
I'm not his real daughter.
Real daughter? Fake daughter?
That's ridiculous.
You know…
You must be happy
seeing only what you want
and interpreting things your way.
Yes.
I keep myself low
and only see things I want to see.
It's better than being arrogant like you
and not seeing what's below you!
Yes.
I was too arrogant…
to see my husband, right?
You're right.
I have nothing to say.
Family members know the weak point
that others can't see so well.
They can always strike
a hard blow whenever they want.
I must've gone crazy! Damn it.
Let's go.
I made my sister cry.
It felt like my heart
was shattering into pieces.
Eun-joo.
Eun-joo. No.
Eun-joo!
"FAMILY MOTTO
A HARMONIOUS FAMILY WITH LOVE"
MOM
Aren't you asleep?
What about you?
I'm not. That's why I picked up.
Eun-hee.
I…
feel a bit anxious.
Why?
What?
Today…
I went to see Eun-joo…
and
told her all about it.
And Eun-joo…
Eun-joo's…
facial expression was…
Eun-hee.
You…
Go and see your sister.
Okay.
Mom.
Yes?
Ji-woo knows about it too.
He heard it
when Dad was leaving the hospital.
She's going to sleep for a while.
You can go home now.
Eun-joo…
did this before too.
She suddenly couldn't breathe, and…
Hyperventilation can happen due to stress.
I learned about her condition,
so I'll check on her tomorrow
and take care of her for a while.
For a while…
Does that mean
until you break up with her?
Yes.
Eun-hee.
Did anything else happen to Eun-joo?
No.
Nothing else happened.
She's eating well and getting better.
Yes.
She is getting better.
Hi.
Yes.
We're going to talk for a moment,
so wait if you want.
You can go first.
Okay then, bye.
How did you find out about this place?
I remember everything.
I've tailed you before.
I did it more than once.
Tailed me?
I saw you two
getting in the car, looking happy,
in front of the fruit shop.
When?
Was it around this time last year?
I wanted to run it over with my truck.
Are you nuts?
Yes, I was nuts.
I, a pathetic loser, went
totally nuts in my life.
Why did you let me be all this time?
You should've ended us
and found someone better.
Come here.
Sang-sik.
I've only heard about you,
and this is my first time seeing you.
You're handsome.
I'm sorry to come here
all of a sudden when you're resting.
I should've bought some fruit,
but I brought nothing…
Anything is fine,
but you don't need to buy fruit.
When I was at the fruit shop,
you never came,
but my husband said he saw you there.
Honey.
Oh.
Gosh.
Sang-sik…
you are quite shy.
Did you have to embarrass me like that?
Why are we like this?
Is it all because of me?
Well,
even if it's all because of me,
couldn't you have told me
about this and that?
What if I do?
Did you even listen?
What can I tell you
when you don't listen?
That's good.
You tell me first.
Tell me when you started
hating listening to me.
I'm not here to fight.
I am not here today for this. Seriously.
I have a last favor to ask.
I have something to tell you
and our kids.
PUBLISHING PLAN
When were you planning to submit this?
The cover of the meditation book
and its photos.
PHOTO BY
PARK CHAN-HYUK & GOLDEN GOOSE MEDIA
Mr. Park Chan-hyuk,
the CEO of Golden Goose.
You know that he's my friend, right?
I hope you don't get the wrong idea,
but the photos are great.
It's nothing like using connections
or making corrupt requests.
The author recommended it too.
He and the company don't know yet.
So, are you on your way to tell him?
No.
Today I have a family meeting.
Okay. You can go.
Where's Tae-hyung?
He's busy.
Okay.
I came because you asked.
Today's the last time.
I'm not going to do
any more family meetings.
Why are you here?
Just so you know, this is my room.
Just so you know, this was my room.
Let's go together.
Chan-hyuk has been on matchmaking dates.
-Matchmaking?
-Yes.
He's Mr. Popular.
His phone is buzzing all the time.
Let's go.
-You're home
-You're home.
You're home.
My eldest daughter.
I'm here.
Come in.
Come on in.
-Who else is coming?
-I don't know.
We're all family.
So I thought we should
at least know each other's faces.
Mom.
Subtitle translation by: Hae-lim Lee
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/ah6xd
Help other users to choose the best subtitles