Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
FAMILY MOTTO
A HARMONIOUS FAMILY WITH LOVE
I SHARED THE PROMOTIONAL MATERIALS.
THANK YOU FOR EVERYTHING.
I also had a great time.
I wish you good luck!
That soulless encouragement is habitual.
Thistle, stay happy.
Stay happy…
Is it too abstract?
THISTLE, STAY HAPPY
Whatever. Just send it.
E-MAIL SENT SUCCESSFULLY
MOM
Seriously…
Yes, sir.
Yes, I'll be there before 9:00.
MOM
What's wrong with her?
The caller cannot be reached.
Please leave a message…
You have received a call from Mom.
Jeez, this old woman…
Ms. Lee Jin-sook, good morning.
Why weren't you picking up?
Don't call me in the morning.
I'm busy getting ready for work.
"Don't call me in the morning."
"Or during a meeting."
"Or when I'm eating lunch."
"Or when working late."
Then when should I call you?
You should call me back
if you missed my call!
Do you think I called you
because I'm bored?
I call much less than other moms.
I will never call you again!
Hasn't her menopause passed already?
Why is she always yelling at me?
Why are you yelling at her?
Got any aged kimchi?
That's the last aged kimchi
we have from two years ago.
If you need more,
mix the kimchi from last year.
But you don't like mixing them.
Jeez.
Forget it.
Tell the kids today.
Don't play dumb with me.
Do as you wish.
Okay. Fine.
Dad, which mountain
are you going to today?
-Mountains are all the same.
-Have a safe trip.
What?
I'm working part-time
and about to get hired full-time.
I can't stand on my own feet.
Mom, I can see you burning
with rage from behind.
Who was it?
Who made you angry? Who did it?
Call Eun-hee and tell her
to come home in the evening.
I have something to say.
Eun-hee seemed to be
working late recently.
Tell her to come anyway.
Say she's not family if she doesn't come.
Jeez.
YOUNGER DAUGHTER
-The caller cannot be reached…
-So you're upset, right?
What? Is something going on at home?
Why?
Both you and Mom have been
calling like crazy since morning.
Was Mom talking to you
on the phone earlier?
Yes. You heard it too, right?
She was yelling at me on my way to work.
Whatever. Mom says
to come home in the evening.
I'm busy.
She said you should come,
regardless of the time!
She said you're not family if you don't!
It looks like she has something to say.
Just come. She's never been like this.
Do you not know what's going on?
No, not at all.
-Is Eun-joo coming too?
-I don't know.
Mom, see you in the evening.
LOVE
YOON TAE-HYUNG FAMILY MEDICINE CLINIC
We'll return after listening to
"Mozart's Concerto
for Flute and Harp, Movement 3."
I told you to take it to the cleaners.
I have it washed
at the laundromat and I just pick it up.
The laundromat is the best place
to read books.
I have nothing to do either.
You're writing something every day.
I'm looking forward to it.
Goodness.
I told you I'm not writing anything.
But I heard about it.
About what?
From who?
You heard it from Hyo-seok, right?
I'm just having fun alone
using my computer at the cafe.
Hyo-seok?
You call a cafe part-timer
near your house by his name?
He's a kid.
You're not jealous, are you?
Barista Ahn is not a kid, is he?
Hello.
-Hi.
Right. Mom's coming today.
I'm having dinner with her today.
Okay. See you at the cafe.
-Bye.
-Goodbye.
How could I see it as jealousy
and ask him about it?
TEAM LEADER KIM EUN-HEE
THREE MINUTES LATE
Seriously.
If I didn't send the email
and the emoticon in the car,
I wouldn't have been late.
-Good morning.
-Hi.
-Yes, hello.
Small things can build up
to something big.
Even if you're a few minutes late,
the fine is still the same.
I don't want to have a get-together
with the fine you paid.
Thank you for your
kind words this morning.
Darn it!
Good morning.
-Darn it.
-Goodness.
What a lunatic.
Our CEO's explosive disorder
is going on too long.
The US headquarters is sending a Vice CEO.
He's younger than CEO Jung,
but I heard he's super competent.
That rumor about him aiming
to take CEO Jung's place.
Anyway, frowning won't change your life.
You'll just get more wrinkles, right?
Wrinkles.
I like your quote today.
All right, let's work.
-Rolling.
-It's light.
I've been so curious about it.
-Popular people these days…
-Cut!
Is it just me
or is she not pulling it off?
She's…
a bit bland.
Is that my fault?
I know things are tough right now,
but can we use an actress?
No, we have no money.
Act like you're talking to us.
Just do as you wish.
-Just do it. You can do it.
-Ready.
Rolling. Action!
Put on your basic makeup!
I'll open it.
My second older sister
might come home this evening
and I'm going to tell her I work here.
-Don’t. I'll tell her.
-What?
-Do you keep in touch with my sister?
-No.
Even if we haven't been in touch,
we're still friends on chat.
Social media notifies me on her birthday.
-I can contact her whenever I want to.
-I see.
If you didn't want to contact her
for a long time, then don't.
How long has it been?
Five by number of years, four by duration.
Have I been counting that?
Yes, it's nice.
It must've cost a lot to build.
My goodness.
Gosh, my knee.
-Hello.
Ma'am, this place
is so serene and beautiful.
There would be no problem
meditating in a place like this.
-I brought some materials as references.
-Okay.
Who's doing the meditation
experience tomorrow?
Yes, I will do it.
I'll be 29 soon,
and that age brings bad luck, so I must--
This is not the place to relieve bad luck.
-Okay.
-The promotional filming team
is coming tomorrow too,
so the meditation will be very difficult.
That experience will also
help you understand the book.
Okay.
Eun-joo has become more minimalistic.
It's nice though because it's big.
I'm sure nothing lasts in this house.
This doesn't look like a house
for a person to live in.
Here's a freshly brewed coffee delivery.
-I don't drink coffee.
-What?
Didn't you start drinking it?
I'll drink it.
But how did you know?
You said you're going to hold back
every time I brewed coffee.
But you declared you'll eat
whatever you want
starting today.
So I carefully brewed it with new beans.
It's good.
It's really good.
I quit this for years?
I really am stubborn.
You knew I'd come, right?
You brought this to lend it to me, right?
Return it within a month.
I don't like people
who never return my books.
Yes, ma'am.
Did you tell him
that we meet here sometimes?
To Dr. Yoon?
Dr. Yoon?
Isn't that what everyone calls him?
Right.
Did you tell Dr. Yoon?
Was this place…
supposed to be a secret between us?
Was the laundromat such a secretive place?
Yes.
You're here.
Why is a doctor's wife always at
the laundromat or cleaning the hospital?
What's in your head to say
ridiculous words like "doctor's wife"
without thinking through?
-You need to think.
-Sure, whatever.
Why did you make kimchi all of a sudden?
Tae-hyung loves fresh kimchi.
-What about the laundry?
-It takes a while.
Youngest.
Go get your sister's laundry.
Me?
How can I bring it?
I don't know what's in her laundry.
Of course, you do.
It'll be nothing but hospital bed sheets,
nurse uniforms, and doctor's gowns.
Go get it now.
She said it takes a while.
Well, do I get some pocket money for this?
Get going.
-Do you two sleep in separate rooms?
-Yes.
Why?
It's what people do now.
How can you get pregnant
in separate rooms?
You'll be 40 soon.
Living with him alone
can be fun in its own way.
-Start seeing a doctor again.
-No.
Tae-hyung agrees with me.
If neither of us wants it,
then it's right to stop.
A married couple must have a child.
-Without a child…
-Stop it.
Is that the only thing you care about?
Without a child, there's no married love.
You and Dad have three kids, but what's
so great about your married love?
Is staying together because of your kids
that great of married love?
You always say things so harshly.
Eun-joo.
It's the laundromat right below, right?
Didn't I bring it back perfectly?
Is Dad still only hiking these days?
Well…
His work is on and off,
so he just spends more time hiking.
His thighs got muscular like a horse.
He's going to the Himalayas next year.
Isn't he going too far?
He can go if he wants to.
Eun-joo.
I work part-time at Chan-hyuk's company.
-Who?
-Don’t you know Chan-hyuk?
You know…
He used to come to our house
with Jong-min back in university.
You mean that goofy guy?
Is Chan-hyuk goofy?
It seems like Chan-hyuk liked you.
You…
You're dumb and slow-witted.
-What did I do?
-That's enough. Stop it.
Anyway,
Eun-hee and Chan-hyuk
haven't been in touch for five years.
So?
You and Eun-hee
became estranged at that time.
Five years?
Time flies.
So ten years won't take long.
So make up with Eun-hee and--
Why do you care?
That's between them.
But it's uncomfortable for us.
You're assembling a family meeting
but you have to see them separately.
Family meeting?
Let's talk when Tae-hyung comes.
One iced Americano for him
and I'd like my usual.
I'll bring them to you.
He looks young. Is he the owner?
He works part-time in the evening.
Do you come here often?
In the evenings usually?
Who's Mom talking to on the phone?
Are you changing the subject?
What?
We're family,
but I just can't understand you or Mom.
Look.
Mom's smiling brightly.
What?
You're right.
Do you want anything?
No, thanks. I can't sleep
when I drink coffee in the evening.
Ma'am, I made chamomile tea for you.
It has no caffeine.
Tae-hyung.
Tae-hyung?
-Hello.
-We had dinner.
I had dinner, too.
-Have you been well?
-Yes.
What do you want to drink?
The roasted coffee beans
today are Ethiopian.
Doctor Yoon, you don't like bitter coffee.
Taste Ms. Kim's coffee before you decide.
Yes, it's okay.
Hello?
Anybody home?
Gosh, this smell.
It smells like rotten dog food.
The lights are on.
He said this room was his now,
but turned it into a storage room.
Is there any fruit wine?
THE YOO'S THAT STUDY FRUITS AND VEGETABLES
VOLUNTEER COORDINATION
Mom?
Who are you?
I heard there's no one home.
Stop there for now! Don't move.
Who are you?
Good grief. I'm from the realtor's office.
Your mother put this house up for sale.
You didn't know?
Call your mother.
-My mom put the house up for sale?
-Yes.
Mom, is the house for sale?
They said it isn't easy
to sell a house nowadays.
Did someone come?
Let them see the house.
Why did you suddenly
put the house up for sale?
Mom?
What do you mean
you put the house up for sale?
Did Dad mess up again?
Did he cause big trouble?
I'm going to part ways with your father.
What?
You mean you're getting a divorce?
Eun-joo, what do you mean divorce?
-Don't overreact.
-She wants to split up.
That means divorce.
It's not a divorce.
They call it graduation from marriage.
I'm going to do that.
I see.
Graduation from marriage?
Do you think my decision is funny?
Does Dad know?
Is your Dad the one you're worried about?
Because he's involved, too.
At any rate, both of you are doing it.
So talk to him first
-before consulting us.
-Yes.
I consulted him and he agreed,
so we don't need your opinions.
If you don't need our opinions,
why did you assemble a family meeting?
Tae-hyung, even if you feel uncomfortable,
you're family too, so I thought
you should hear it together.
Yes.
Your father told me to sell the house,
take half of the money, and move out.
What's Dad going to do?
It's not my problem.
He told me to tell all of you
and went hiking.
How irresponsible.
It means he doesn't want it.
Dad doesn't want to
graduate from marriage.
Do you think I decided this
over a few days?
Have you thought of
how much I would've contemplated?
I can't do it if your Dad says no?
Let's say you split the house in half
and live on your own.
How will you support yourself every month?
Did Dad say he'll give you
half of the living expenses too?
-Stop that!
Stop sighing.
Mom, you'll be 60 soon.
-People live up to 100 nowadays.
-Don't worry.
I can support myself.
Whether I wash the dishes
or work at a supermarket, I can manage.
I won't ask any of you for money.
You stayed home all your life.
How will you manage?
Why can't I? What do you know about me?
Why do you keep getting angry?
Can't I even ask?
Should I just say yes?
Lower your voice.
Yes.
Just say "Okay, I got it"
for once for things like this.
Eun-hee is home, so I'm leaving.
Tae-hyung, finish your coffee and come.
Where…
-Where should I go?
-You figure it out.
Why did Mom call Eun-hee?
She'll just say, "Mom, do as you wish."
"I'm always on your side."
Go after her.
-Got it?
-Hey.
-Jeez.
-Just shake it off, okay?
Graduation from marriage is sugarcoating.
It's just kissing his butt
when he made money
and abandoning him after retirement!
-You're right.
-Right.
Goodness, what are you saying?
If you say such things these days,
you'll become marriage graduate buddies.
Are you guys still talking
about my graduation from marriage?
Stop it already.
It's all because of you, Oppa.
Our poor Sang-sik oppa.
What are you going to do?
I never expected your wife to do that.
By the way, does that mean
we can't have your wife's kimchi anymore?
-You little…
-Goodness.
I can bring kimchi.
Oppa?
Straighten your shoulders.
What's wrong with my shoulders?
Hey. What's graduation from marriage?
It's graduating from marriage.
That means you can get into a new school!
-Right!
-You can do that.
That's right, Oppa.
You can go to a new school.
Why are you calling everyone oppa?
I don't drink alcohol
Help yourselves.
Cheers!
Mom, do as you wish.
I agree with everything you do.
I'm on your side.
The symbolic area of Havana,
the port city, is Malecon.
I'm leaving.
It's surrounded by the water.
It's always filled with people
as you can take walks, fish,
and even enjoy dates with your partner.
The entire area,
including the Habana Vieja,
is a UNESCO World Heritage…
-You drove here.
-I'm calling a designated driver.
Mom is graduating,
so I must drink as her daughter.
I'm planning to drink a lot.
Hey, Ji-woo.
There must've been signs.
Did Mom and Dad have a big fight recently?
Not at all.
Whenever Dad's home, the house is silent.
When Dad's not home,
there's the sound of the TV,
Mom sings,
and she even chats
with her friends over the phone.
But whenever Dad's home,
it's total silence.
They're both silent.
What did Eun-joo say to Mom?
If you're so curious, call her.
I'm not. I'm sure she only said
harsh and realistic things.
"Did Dad agree?"
"Will he share the house?"
"How will you support yourself?"
"What can you do?"
Amazing.
Eun-joo also guessed
what you would say 100% right.
"I'm always on Mom's side."
"Mom, do as you wish."
You guys know each other so well.
Why don't you see her?
Know what?
Eun-joo knows nothing about me.
Go buy alcohol.
I charge double.
Double, okay?
Okay.
Yoon Seo-young.
I told you to quit if you get caught
sleeping here one more time.
I'm not going to sleep here.
I was about to go home.
Really? Then go home.
Okay.
I really was about to go home.
Why look at someone else's photos?
I was curious about what photos
our CEO took back in university.
Go home.
Why are you here at this time?
To monitor me?
I have to revise the editing.
-I have to pull an all-nighter.
-Again?
They pay us so little,
yet they're so tyrannical.
-I'll help you.
-Go. You're distracting me.
Get out of here.
I guess I should just go home.
EUN-JOO
You take care of Mom.
I'll take care of Dad.
Take care of what?
"We're their children,
so we should tell them
to think twice about it."
"Should we just be democratic
and agree with the divorce
just because they talked about it
and he agreed?"
This is tiring.
It's not a divorce.
It's graduation from marriage.
What kind of lunatic
made such an expression?
A word called "separation" already exists.
"It's not complicated enough
to make a new expression for it, right?"
Kim Eun-joo.
Gosh. Okay.
All right.
Call her.
There's no need to.
She doesn't call me, either.
Why am I so frustrated?
I'm going to bed.
Gosh.
Are you ready?
MEDITATION CENTER
I don't want to do this.
Why not?
I don't want to reflect on myself.
My life has been so problematic.
Then…
-Don't meditate.
-Okay.
Just sit there.
As an employee of a publishing company,
you should know
everything about the author.
Yes.
One, as you breathe in,
and two, as you breathe out.
Some days…
were as long as life.
Take out the memory
of that day,
which you've been keeping.
MARCH 10, 2016
The longest day of my life.
It was that day.
Mom.
Did you get up at this hour because of me?
I must be getting old.
I can't sleep at dawn.
What about Dad?
I knew Mom was crying, but I ignored it.
So that's when…
Mom was preparing for a divorce.
Did Dad blow up and throw his lunch again?
Water's dripping. Go dry your hair.
When did I take off the ring?
It was over for us a long time ago.
I'm leaving!
-Have a slice of bread before you go.
-I'm late.
You didn't move a muscle
the whole weekend,
I'm proud you woke up.
Good rest made me more tired.
My back feels stiff.
You only rest on weekends
and you're busy at work.
Do you even see Jong-min?
That's how long-term couples are.
-You should set a wedding date soon, then.
-Mom.
Don't nag at someone
who's on her way to work.
You…
This is the only time I can talk to you.
Jeez, you're exaggerating.
Do you contact your sister?
Ask her when she's going to quit her job.
This isn't the Joseon Dynasty.
You're free to call a married daughter.
Why worry about the in-laws?
A doctor family isn't a big deal.
She said she'll have a baby,
so I don't understand
why she's still working.
If you're that curious, call her.
Don't say "Eun-joo this and that" to me.
Bye.
Give me Dad's lunch. I'll eat it.
Even money can't buy this lunch.
He's so spoiled and pampered.
I'm leaving.
-Be careful.
-Okay.
Did you call me?
Yes, I'm Kim Eun-hee.
You…
I mean, me…
Were you expecting
that a moment like this would come?
Look…
We didn’t expect you to come alone.
Jong-min has been calling me,
but I didn't answer his calls.
You're nothing but a cheater
and you dared to come here with Jong-min?
Cheater?
What do you mean?
Hye-soo has been
dating Jong-min for three years.
So those two knew about me already.
And they shook me
by saying I was the cheater.
Well, I've been dating him for nine years.
Both of our families know each other well.
That makes no sense.
We've been seeing each other
every weekend for three years.
Jong-min and I were really estranged.
We were just a couple
who's been dating for a long time.
I went to Jong-min's house
quite often as well
and I didn't sense any trace of you.
You went to Jong-min's house?
-Jong-min doesn't live alone.
-Chan-hyuk knows me, too.
Chan-hyuk knows you, too?
He's Jong-min's friend who lives with him,
so of course, he does.
We ate together a few times, too.
I also went on a trip
with Jong-min this past weekend.
A trip?
JONG-MIN
3 MISSED CALLS
It has to be rice.
No noodles.
Excuse me.
I'll eat separately today.
Why all of a sudden?
Eun-joo.
My sister is here.
Okay.
What's wrong?
Eun-joo…
I don't know what happened, but don't cry.
People are watching.
You didn’t eat at all.
Leave it here, please.
Why did you come to me?
You should go to Jong-min.
I don't know.
Jong-pal keeps calling me,
but I didn't answer the calls.
I can't answer them right now.
Are you going to break up?
I'm not sure about that either.
If you're not sure and won't break up,
why are you crying?
I told you
something's weird about you two.
Never mind.
What's the point of saying this now?
I'm sure you knew it already.
But you ignored it so you would feel okay.
Confrontation is always
the most difficult for you.
You just got a job, so you were tired.
You wanted to rest on weekends,
so you talked over the phone
and that was it.
If you've been dating for nine years,
either get married or break up.
It's not something to cry about.
Eat your food.
I didn't like him from the beginning.
Nothing's clear about him.
He told small, unnecessary lies.
He always pretended to know
all the books and movies
when he could've just said he didn't know.
I really hated that. No one said anything.
It's not important,
but he was so serious about it.
And he acts sociable,
but he kissed up and kicked down.
This situation doesn't surprise me at all.
You should've told me nine years ago.
I've been telling you all this time.
You just never listened.
I shouldn't have come to see you.
I'm such an idiot
to see you on a day like this.
You brat.
I don't even expect you to comfort me.
Can't you just
be there for me
when you're my older sister?
You're out of line.
Don't take it out on me.
I'm sorry.
It's all my fault.
I dated a jerk
and came to see you for nothing!
I'm sorry for everything!
You…
You're so sick.
I never want to see you again.
I didn’t know that you
had a miscarriage at the time.
You were having a hard time too.
I really didn’t know.
You never say anything.
You make us hear about your news
from other people.
Hey.
Jong-min told me to step outside
because you're coming.
I'm here to see you.
What?
Me?
You're the worst, you jerk.
You're not even a friend!
What are you saying all of a sudden?
I heard you knew everything.
That woman said she knows you.
She said the three of you
ate and drank together!
What the…
Come inside and talk.
When she said that,
I was more angry at you than him.
What a great friendship you guys have.
Am I not your friend?
You must've thought I was a joke,
laughing around so cluelessly.
Your habit is coming back.
You're blaming the wrong person.
You coward. Let's get this straight.
Have we seen each other lately?
Did I ever get the chance
to see you as a joke?
-You never came here!
-Hey.
What's wrong with you guys?
-I see.
-Go stay outside.
So you never had the chance.
I feel so sorry for not coming here
because I was busy, you bastard.
Couldn’t you make time to tell me?
I didn't know what to tell you!
You shouldn't be involved.
What's wrong with you guys?
We'll talk it out, okay? I'm sorry.
Because you didn't know what to say?
You didn't care enough to do so.
You don't care about others.
You're just an irresponsible jerk!
He said he was going to tell you
when it was time, so what can I say?
And let's get this straight.
Do you think a long-term relationship
is a vested right protected by law?
Is there a privilege in it?
He was fed up, so he dated another girl.
What was I supposed to say?
Hey, watch your mouth!
Watch what? You punk!
Hey, you two are done.
Even I'm fed up.
Nine years? Did you think it was some
great love because it surprised people?
Both of you are cowards
and you guys just put up
with each other for more than five years.
Yes, okay.
We, the two cowards will break up today,
so please get out.
As of today,
I'm done with you too.
-You're out.
-Okay.
Thank you for telling me politely
even if it's been a long time.
I feel much better too.
On that day, I couldn't make out
what was okay to lose
and what I had to keep and protect
for the long term.
Get rid of everything that comes to mind.
Memories are saved as images.
Take out the images of the past
that you kept hidden
and hadn't taken out.
Keep taking them out
and keep getting rid of them.
Now open your eyes.
That's it for today.
Thank you for your cooperation
with filming.
It's six o'clock.
You said to tell you when it's six.
Right.
5:50 P.M.
-Let's talk for ten minutes.
-Okay.
Looks like you have something to say.
There's this regular customer I like.
She suddenly started to
drink coffee, which she quit,
and she drank wine and had a hangover.
And it looks like she started working.
What does this all mean?
That's my privacy.
I have an important call to make.
Okay.
Removing the back of the truck
seems a bit funny.
Isn't this an expensive car?
It's all debt.
I won't charge you for riding it,
so just buy me a meal. Nothing's free.
Yes, my older daughter.
Dad, isn't it dinnertime?
Yes.
When are you coming to Seoul?
Why?
So I can see you.
You're busy. Why do you need to see me?
Did your mother say something?
-Yes.
-Don't mind it.
I'm going to do
what your mother wants to do.
Let's meet and talk first.
I have to go to Ulsan
to load the truck and return to Incheon.
And load the truck again there.
I'm a bit busy.
I'll go to Incheon.
Call me when you come.
It'll be just a moment, Dad.
Okay.
Dad, make sure to eat.
-And drive safely.
-Okay.
-Eun-joo.
-Yes?
You know…
Live happily
and lovingly with Tae-hyung.
Don't focus too much
on having a baby and just…
live happily
and joyfully together.
Okay.
MUNMAE SERVICE CENTER
Thank you for choosing us
as the publisher for the meditation book.
-Please read it.
-Okay.
We'll read it carefully and thoroughly.
Thank you.
Let's go.
Eun-hee.
I didn’t expect to see you here.
I know, right? Why are you here?
Right.
This is the Golden Goose Media Team.
Shooting Director Kim Young-ho.
-Hi.
-Hi, I'm Kim Eun-hee.
This is the producer.
-I'm Yoon Seo-young.
-Hi, I'm Kim Eun-hee.
I saw you while shooting
and you have amazing concentration.
By the way, I never agreed to be filmed.
We can remove you from the video.
Long time no see.
Young-ho, return the shooting devices,
and you two can go home.
What about you?
Do you have plans after this?
Me?
I don't.
Let's have dinner.
We have something to talk about.
Okay.
-Are we dismissed, then?
-Bye.
Stop being flirtatious.
The way you talk
gets more and more out of control.
-Are you still being flirtatious?
-"Still?"
You were popular
because you were exceptionally kind
to female friends.
Don't talk about the past.
I hate that alumni reunion vibe.
You guys aren't having a fling, are you?
Focus on work at the company.
Don't do anything stupid.
What?
Don't you remember?
When I told you
Jong-pal and I were dating, you said,
"Just study at school.
Don't do anything stupid."
I really hate that alumni reunion vibe.
You got old, too.
That was a long time ago.
I like it. I'm going to do it more.
I feel like I'm suddenly getting younger.
What should we eat?
Thanks.
For what?
For asking a friend who let her
anger out on you and cut ties with you
to eat together.
And acting like nothing happened.
Thank you.
Maybe it's the meditation?
It works so well.
Let's eat soup and rice.
I'm in.
Time for soup and rice.
Hey.
President.
Yes.
You're always working hard.
We must go to the peak.
Yes.
That guy named Hong is nothing but talk.
How could he have made
8,000,000 won last month?
That lunatic.
Leave him out.
No need to call him.
Just send him a message.
Yes.
All right.
Gosh.
We need to talk.
Why?
Is something wrong?
Yes.
There's something wrong.
Who?
Eun-joo?
Eun-hee?
Ji-woo? Who is it?
Us.
Us?
No, me.
What is it?
I want to put an end to this.
What?
Put an end to what?
There's a thing called
graduation from marriage nowadays.
It means to graduate from marriage.
Because divorce is complicated.
It's about not seeing each other
and living separately.
It seems like a wise thing to do.
We should graduate from marriage too.
Can you see this?
It's rock-hard because it's been
cramped all my life.
I've worked so hard
and there's less work nowadays,
so I'm going hiking.
I know.
And I also know how hard that job is.
I also know that you've
worked hard and diligently all your life,
and raised three kids well by doing so.
So I…
I've been doing great until now.
-You were happy when I made money.
-Money…
It's not about money!
I get why you won't divorce me.
You hate living with me,
but you want me to make money.
If so…
Let's get a divorce.
I won't ask for money.
Let's sell this apartment and split it.
Did you buy this house?
Yes.
I bought it.
You don't want to split this either?
How many times do I come home in a month?
Graduation from marriage?
That's ridiculous.
Just don't look at me when I come home.
I hate it.
I hate it so much
when you're home.
I can't breathe.
I hate it when you walk.
I hate it
when you take
health supplements all by yourself.
I hate it when you talk
on the phone and say vulgar things.
I hate it when you
take your clothes off and do cupping,
and I hate seeing
those cupping marks on you.
If you hate it so much, get out!
You said you hate it!
Get out!
You get out.
Graduation or divorce, do as you wish.
Sell the house.
Split it in half or you keep all of it.
Do as you wish.
The vibe of this place is…
What was the name of the restaurant
in front of our school?
A White House…
A White House, right?
You're doing this on purpose because
I said I hate the reunion vibe, right?
What can we talk about
when we met after five years?
Shall we talk about politics or mukbang?
We can talk about BTS.
We're taking a bottle of soju.
Okay.
-One is enough.
-You're not drinking?
You're the one not drinking.
You drove here.
How did you know?
Weren't you spinning
the car key in your hand earlier?
Such keen eyes.
We're just going to eat and say goodbye,
so it's a waste to call a driver.
Ji-woo has been working for me
since he was discharged from the army.
If Ji-woo wants it too,
I'm going to hire him full-time.
Hire him full-time? What can he even do?
He's a good worker.
He's nice and sociable.
Small companies make
advertisements for social media,
and they pay us very little
but are very tyrannical.
But Ji-woo knows how to
deal with them sensibly.
You're going to take the precious
youngest son of a family and make him
flatter people and kiss their butts?
Considering how much
I would be paying him,
you think I hired him to flatter people?
He's only a little boy in your family.
He's an adult everywhere else.
That face.
Do you still use the silence tactic
when you're on the defensive?
I don’t.
Why didn't Ji-woo tell me?
I told him not to tell you at first
and he never did.
He said he was going to soon.
Why did you tell him not to tell me?
Because you misunderstand easily.
Misunderstand what?
"What's his scheme in hiring my brother?"
"Is it because he won't complain
because they know each other already?"
I meditated but I still get angry.
So you remember me
as a total loser, right?
People say I'm generous.
I have a good personality!
Yes, you do have a good personality.
Meditation shows your personality.
You really are gullible.
You follow instructions so well.
You were crying so sadly.
I saw myself from the past.
You were there too.
I took that memory out
and I was so immature.
I thought the age of 30
was quite mature at the time,
but I was immature.
I knew nothing.
I'm still immature.
About that day…
I'm sorry.
I guess you were the only one
I could get angry at comfortably.
I couldn't remember
what I was going to say to Jong-pal.
But I got…
so angry at you.
I guess I trusted you more.
I'm sorry.
It took me too long to apologize.
Drink up.
Eat up.
-Bye.
-Thanks.
Let's keep in touch.
Well, sure.
What's with that reaction?
So you actually meant it?
Would we even need to keep in touch?
You've been so harsh since you were young.
Fine, you jerk. Take care.
Go on.
Why are you standing there all sappy?
Let's take a trip down memory lane
to the early 2000s.
"Coincidence" by Baby V.O.X.
It was too serious
To call it a coincidence
We had to ignore each other
Like we didn't know each other
The changed looks
Different lovers…
At the moment my eyes met yours
I tried so hard
Acting like I'm totally fine
But when I saw that flustered look
On your face…
Seriously.
What do you want to drink?
Do you have beer?
I don't like spending money on coffee.
You don't have to.
Give me a cup of herbal tea
with no caffeine.
Okay.
Did you just talk casually to him?
You said you'll never see me again
and you randomly come
after years without even a call?
I called Tae-hyung.
He told me that you're here.
He was happy to hear we were meeting.
He told me to just go as a surprise.
Did you talk to Mom?
No.
I'm just here to see you today.
Then say something.
I'm sorry, Eun-joo.
I was wrong.
I apologize.
If you know, then it's okay.
I had no idea what you were going through.
Because you don't talk about those things
and endure them on your own.
If I knew, I wouldn't have done that.
I'm thankful that you apologized first,
but what happened on that day
has nothing to do with you
knowing about my situation or not.
When things happen, you say,
"How could Jong-min do this to me?"
"How could you do this to me?"
And then you get exhausted
and say, "Let's stop it."
That's such an immature thing to do.
Anyone can do that to you.
You're not special.
Yes.
I'm not special.
Your facial expression says,
"She's lecturing again even after years."
I'm not.
I feel like I'm home.
I'm not your home.
Right.
You hate vague expressions, right?
You're not home. You're just my sister.
All right.
Why did I take so many photos
that I wouldn't even look at later?
TEAM MANAGER KIM EUN-HEE
BEGIN WORK
I got here first!
-Hi.
What's going on?
What's with your fashion today?
Why do you look even tackier
when you dress up?
Why are all of you here so early?
It's the same reason why you dressed up.
Me?
I just got up earlier today than usual.
Then I guess everyone got up early.
They were either nervous or excited
because the Vice CEO
is coming from the headquarters.
So it's today.
Don't act like you don't know.
Didn't you get dressed
like this for a get-together
posing as a welcoming ceremony
at a fancy place?
He's here.
Everyone.
The Vice CEO is here from the US.
Stay seated. You got seats in the evening.
Why get together in a place like this?
I crave beer and soju today.
Have you ever mixed spirits and wine?
That thing is incredible.
Sounds awful.
I guess rich people are different.
-Yes.
-Why do you mix those expensive things?
Because I'm rich. Why?
-Look at all the alcohol.
-It's all alcohol.
This place is insane.
Kim Eun-hee.
Eun-hee.
Hey.
Go on in first.
-Does she know him?
-Yes.
That jerk wasted Eun-hee's 20s.
Look at him ignoring me.
By the way, why did he
ignore me but call Eun-hee?
How are you doing?
Fine.
It’s my wedding anniversary today.
My wife wanted to skip dinner
and have some wine.
But I got here too early.
You must be enjoying your life.
Do you still keep in touch with Chan-hyuk?
Yes.
I had a drink with him yesterday as well.
I see.
So you two still see each other.
Give me Chan-hyuk's number.
Ms. Kim.
FATHER
The caller cannot be reached.
Please leave a message…
Hi.
Mom, what are you doing?
Cleaning.
I can understand
why you live without things.
Throwing things away
does make me feel better.
Mom.
Dad's not answering.
That's how he is all the time.
But he keeps his dinnertime
like clockwork.
I'm sure he has a reason
why he can't answer it.
I have to take out the recyclable wastes.
Okay.
KIM SANG-SIK
CHILBO DRIVER REST STOP
Goodness.
What?
Why is Sang-sik's truck here at this hour?
That's weird. He's the most diligent man.
Eun-hee?
-Are you awake?
-Is something wrong?
I heard Chan-hyuk stays at his office.
He does.
Where's his office?
Why?
I have something to say to him.
It's nothing.
But send me his address right now.
At this hour?
What are you doing?
How did you find this place?
What's wrong?
Are you not packing a lunch box today?
Today is the weekend,
loved by office workers.
You got a call.
Hello?
Yes.
Hi.
What?
No, he doesn't call
that much when he's working.
Yes.
Who is it?
The caller cannot be reached.
Please leave a message…
Mom.
It's the Ulsan factory.
Your father is neither calling
nor answering
and hasn't come to get the load.
Your father is not one to do that.
What if he had an accident?
What is it?
I don’t know why I came to see you.
You’re the only one I can tell this to.
I met…
Jong-min yesterday.
I…
made a mistake.
Mom.
Where is it at?
There really was
a medicine bottle in his truck.
He's been identified.
My body and face are so weird right now.
Ms. Jin-sook?
-Did you say 1982?
So Dad is living in a time
when he and Mom were super romantic?
Ms. Sook, did you kiss me?
And didn't Eun-joo's style change a lot?
We communicated so well.
You don't want to forget it, do you?
Subtitle translation by: Hae-lim Lee
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/ah22q
Help other users to choose the best subtitles