Hey! You!
I'm onto you.
I know all about you.
I'm sick to death
with people talking about me
behind my back.
I'm gonna write to
the home secretary about this.
Lockup!
There's deals
going down all the time.
Every day.
Every night.
What's a fax machine?
Put that bastard
on the wing, and I'll kill him.
Bastards.
Put it down!
Now!
Fall in on the wing!
Wake up! Wake up!
Come on, now, wake up!
Wake up!
Fall in on the wing!
No!
Shut up!
Shut your mouth!
- What's your name?
- Help me, please! Help me!
- What's your name?!
- Officer Smedley.
Your first name, shithead.
What's your name?
- What's your name?!
- Peter. Peter Smedley.
Right, Peter.
I want you to get me
10 grand, cash.
Used notes.
And I want a car.
Stay where you are!
Anybody moves,
I'll cut her throat.
You know my name, do you?
Do you know who I am?
Johnny Franks!
All right, Johnny.
Just don't hurt her.
Don't you Johnny me,
you two-faced piece of shit!
Please, please, please.
You've got 15 minutes.
Go on!
Get me what I want.
I can't get that much money
in 15 minutes, Mr. Franks.
For every five minutes,
she loses a finger.
- No, no! Please!
- You hear me?!
Help! Please!
What you waiting for?
You've got 15 minutes
to do what I want.
I mean it.
I'll chop off her fingers.
- No! Please!
- And then her hands!
Get the armed response group.
Shoot him.
Give it 20 minutes.
We'll do a round.
I'll give you the lowdown
who's got to be monitored
throughout the night.
- You off, then?
- Yes.
Oh, listen, you ain't met
the new lad, have you?
This is the dep, Gary Marshall.
Jason Hully.
How you going?
- Russell, got a minute, please?
- Yeah.
Excuse me.
What are you after?
Udding's got the flu
as well as Michaels and Norton.
It's leaving us short-staffed
at the healthcare center.
- No.
- Oh, come on, Russ.
I need an S.O. on duty.
We've got three new arrivals
coming in early.
Please.
I've got to be out of here
by lunchtime.
I am taking Nora to homecare.
We are in the middle of
decorating, and you owe me.
If I go straight to the hospital
from here,
I have been on
18 hours straight.
Earn enough
to pay for the decorator?
- Good.
- Git.
- Oh, Russell?
- Yeah?
It's our turn
for the jungle man.
He's being transferred
back to us.
Oh, you bastard.
He's one of
your new admittances.
No way.
We're getting the cage
ready for him.
- Oh, no!
- Time's up, you bastards!
I'm gonna rape her.
You hear me?
I'm gonna rape the bitch!
So who is the jungle man, then?
Name's Victor Braithwaite.
Changed it by deed poll
to Tarzan.
- You're joking.
- No, I'm not joking, son.
He's a bloody nightmare.
Settle down, now.
I'm coming out.
ENJOY ALL VOD IN HIGH QUALITY @ 4KVOD.TV
GET LIVE TV,MOVIES,SHOWS IN ONE PACKAGE
Shoot! Shoot!
Oh, bloody hell.
No!
Congratu-bloody-lations.
You just shot the governor.
Okay, everybody.
Coffee break.
And then we'll meet up
back in classroom 4B.
- All right?
- She was good, wasn't she?
You were a bit rough.
You wanted it
to look good, didn't you?
Well, I think you were
rather enjoying yourself.
Do it differently
in the U.S., do they?
Yes, they do, actually,
Dr. Williams.
You should sit in
on one my lectures.
You might learn something.
- Oh, yeah?
- Joke. Just a joke.
He needs to
keep the neck raised,
and get him X-rayed, will you?
Oh, and, uh,
get rid of that contraption.
- Hey, Doc.
- Morning, Doc.
Here you are. Haven't had
a chance to look at 'em yet.
Falla.
Doc... Denny, Dougherty.
Where do you want this one?
Uh, that cubicle
will be fine over there.
Dougherty?
Let's have a look.
Falla, hurry it up.
Doctor is gonna examine you.
Come on, Falla,
get your bunk made up.
You ready for this one, Doc?
Just a moment.
I'm gonna be a little while yet.
You are not that sick.
And that should not be here.
Any discomfort there?
Doc, I need to
get back on the wing.
Be as right as rain
in a couple of days, mate.
Right.
Who's next?
Prisoner 457.
George Falla.
Oh, I... I wouldn't mind
a cup of coffee.
Sure thing.
Cup of coffee for the doctor,
please.
I've just had confirmation
to stand by for delivery
of transportee prisoner...
Tarzan?
Got S.O. Russell Morgan
standing in,
but I'm still a man short,
and Russell's been on all night.
- Where is the governor?
- Try the staff room.
She ran Barfield for about 18
months during the refurbishment,
until she got the old...
Then I heard she went to America
to do some research
or something.
She weren't high enough rank
to run it.
Prison services gave her
a cushy research job
traveling 'round America.
Hey, Curtis, is it true
she was sacked from Barfield?
Hello again.
Right, for those of you
I haven't officially met before,
my name is Helen Hewitt,
I'm a governor two.
I've been working for almost
two years in the United States
studying their category A prison
regimes,
their hostage
and siege procedures.
And for your information
Miss, um, Stapleton,
I was not sacked from Barfield.
I was at the time
only a governor three,
and I'm sure
you're aware of the fact
that in order to run
a category A prison,
you must be a governor two.
I wanted to fill the governor in
on the jungle man,
Victor Braithwaite.
I thought he was dead.
Tried everywhere. Couldn't find
the governor anywhere.
I've got
a list of transfers here.
Unbelievable.
Do you know, since 1994,
Tarzan has been in Wakefield,
Strangeways,
Barfield, Walton,
Winson Green, Lincoln,
Bullingdon, Full Sutton,
and Durham.
Now, that's not all.
He's even been back
to Strangeways, Frankland,
back to High Down,
Winson Green again,
Lincoln...
Poor bastards have had him
three times already this year...
Frankland
he only lasted eight days,
and Bullingdon he lasted 10.
If Tarzan
carries on like this any more,
he'll spend more time traveling
than he does
in the bloody nicks.
He'll just go
straight to the block, then.
And chop his head off, yeah.
Yeah?
Speaking.
What?
Where's Williams?
Where can I contact him?
Newgate House.
Shit. Okay.
Tarzan arrived?
Find Governor Keller ASAP,
and contact Dr. Williams.
- Wife had the baby?
- Get him back here.
Mrs. Gill, get me the records of
a new inmate that arrived today,
George Falla.
I'll contact HQ, the press
office, and the police.
We have a hostage situation.
Why are you doing this, George?
Tell us what you want.
Come on, George, stop
pratting about and talk to me.
Who's out there?
Who's there?!
- George, calm down.
- What's happening?
George.
Open that door
a fraction, and he hangs.
I've got a rope attached
to the door, and I'll hang him!
Yeah, I'll hang him!
George.
Be reasonable, George.
I won't talk to anyone
but the frigging governor!
I want my mother.
I want a blow-up rubber doll.
I want the governor
to blow it up!
Shitface.
Nobody listens to me.
Nobody pays any attention to me.
Now they will.
Right, Chiswick,
what's going on?
He wants the governor,
he wants his mother,
and you ain't gonna
believe this, sir,
but he wants
a blow-up rubber doll.
What? What is this,
some sort of bloody wind-up?
I don't know.
Try and talk to him,
he jabs it through the door
with a broken bottle.
How did he get a bottle?
He's had some medication. He's
got inflammation of the bowels.
Here's his medical report.
Right, I want
all the corridors cleared.
Get everybody out now!
Vacate the cells
either side of him.
We don't want him to hear
what's going on, do we?
Right, Doc,
anyone spoken to Russell?
No, we can't.
Well, we haven't got his records
in the office.
What's the bastard in for?
We don't know. All we've got is
the last prison doc's reports.
- Who's out there?!
- Calm down.
Who's out there?!
Who's there?!
Right, I want all these screens
in a line across there,
mask off the end
of the whole of the wing.
Hey, find out
Morgan's blood group.
What else is on his medical?
Is he mental?
You shouldn't even be
in this area.
Is he suffering from...
He'll suffer
if I get hold of him.
George, you're not
listening to me.
I want my mother!
George, you've got to calm down!
I want a blow-up rubber dolly!
Where are the ruddy negotiators?
It makes sense to me
if I act as go-between.
Sick!
They've been poisoning me.
I know.
Look, George, I'm a decent man.
- A fair man.
- Trying to give me drugs.
Talk to me.
What have you done
to Officer Morgan?
George!
I am not sick in the head!
Three basic rules.
One, protection of life.
Two, negotiation.
Three, no concessions.
Do you know,
in the past five years
there have been 80 hostage
incidents in British prisons.
In 60 of those incidents,
it was a prisoner taken hostage.
The rest were prison staff.
75% of them used barricades.
What about weapons?
80% had weapons present.
To date we have no record
of firearms being used.
In only two of those incidents,
there resulted serious injury
to the hostage,
which means a high proportion
were resolved
with no injury to either party.
Luckily Officer Jackson
wasn't on duty.
So no fatalities?
There's always a first time.
Never, ever believe
that a hostage situation
cannot spiral into tragedy.
I've got everything I need
in here.
Got smokes.
I got weapons!
I want my mother!
Come on, George.
I'm the prison doctor.
Do you need any medication?
I want to talk to the governor
about visitation rights!
- No panic.
- About ruddy time.
- How's Mr. Morgan?
- What the hell is he doing?!
Falla was sick.
He was trying to find out
how bad.
- There was nobody else.
- What?
Because we haven't got a bloody
negotiator down here yet!
How's Mr. Morgan?
- Where the hell have you been?
- Sorry, I was playing squash.
Who's been handling it?
- Doc Harris.
- Just stay calm.
You're gonna need
some medication.
I've seen your medical records.
I'm gonna kill him.
I'm gonna kill him!
Hey, hey!
All right, lads.
No, don't want to
leave my name, mate,
because I'm calling
from Barfield Prison.
Yeah, I've got a big story.
And all I want
is a little request for my wife.
Could you hurry it up,
or my card's gonna run out.
Step back!
He's got me phone card.
He said he'd be a minute.
He's been three minutes already.
He's on his way.
Yeah, but I need the card.
I want to phone me Auntie Betty.
- You, you...
- It's his card he's using.
Hello?
Okay, listen.
I want it played three times.
Yeah. Three.
For Cheryl Smith.
Roy Orbison... "It's Over."
Okay?
Right, there's an officer.
He's been held hostage
since 9:00 this morning.
He's a senior officer,
name of Russell Morgan.
What? I don't know.
He's a new inmate, that's all.
But he's armed,
and he's very, very dangerous.
How? Well, he's got
his bloody head in a noose...
Hello? Hello?
Shit.
Bang out of order.
Got me card, Brian!
Come on, Smith.
On your way.
- He needs to phone his auntie.
- Got to phone me auntie.
- Here.
- Your card's run out.
Oh, you bastard.
I told you I needed that.
Now you owe me, Smith.
I want another card.
Shut it, four eyes.
You'll get paid off.
Oh, four eyes, is it?
Pack it in, youse two.
Pack it in!
Mellowing out. All right.
Later. Later.
I'm getting tired of waiting.
Bastard!
Is my mother coming in or not?
Hey!
Who's out there?
Why they bloody sent him
to us...
Bastards!
Gary, I can't leave
the command post.
Can you go and check
at reception
for that nutter
calling himself Tarzan?
He's scheduled any minute now.
Anyone contacted Morgan's wife?
He's not even supposed to be
on duty, you know?
I'll sort it.
Just treat us as if we were
second-degree citizens.
I know my rights.
This is a protest.
This is a protest!
It is imperative
that you never give in
to the demands of the prisoner.
The aim is to
keep the perpetrator talking.
Keep his attention drawn to you,
listening to you,
arguing with you.
Talking to him, not at him.
And if a hostage screams
that she's being raped,
don't dismiss it.
Ah, yes, but what if he is
chopping fingers off?
Well, he said he will.
Doesn't necessarily mean
he'll carry it through.
But it's a good point,
Mr. Jackson.
So it's also important
that you get on hand
all information
regarding the perpetrator.
What is his crime?
Has he done this before?
Has he a history of violence?
Is he a violent man?
Is he on medication?
Does he have a history
of mental illness?
The negotiator must get to know
the perpetrator.
And he'll have on hand,
to feed him advice
on how to handle him,
the prison psychologist.
What about providing food?
No concessions.
If the perpetrator
asks for food, drug it.
Drug him up.
When he keels over, walk in.
What if he gives the food
to the hostage?
Makes him drink it,
makes him eat him, waits?
He'll know,
he'll become very angry,
and he won't trust
the negotiator,
and they must trust each other.
Okay, that's lunch, everybody.
And then straight back, and
we'll pick up where we left off.
I want a blow-up rubber dolly!
I want my mother!
Oh, come on, George.
Can we see Mr. Morgan?
I want to see my mother!
I'm gonna start
messing with him!
I mean it.
I mean it!
I'm gonna start cutting him!
Williams isn't here,
the doctor's having kittens
trying to talk the nutter down,
and here comes
the biggest nutter of all time.
Said something
about needing a blanket.
What's that about?
Well, they transport him naked.
Have you not met
this character yet?
You're in
for a show and a half, son.
The money it costs
shuttling Tarzan around,
they could have built
his own private wing.
This one's sane.
We've got it on paper.
He's got a new gig by the way.
Spits like a llama.
Here for me, are you?!
Aaaaaah!
Quick!
Wrap him in this.
Hurry up!
Stop wasting time.
Oh! Dirty bastard!
Get him in here.
Drop him.
Wrap him in it.
Oh, no need for that.
- And take him away!
- Show's over.
Come on, let's go.
Good to see you again,
Mr. Marshall.
Likewise.
Is Mr. Jackson
not rejoining us?
No, he's been recalled
to Barfield.
Oh. Pity.
Okay.
The security
of our modern prison cells
means that access or exit
via the windows is impossible.
Same with the doors.
Well, with effective removal
of doors, under a minute.
In the States, they've got it
down to three seconds.
Now, you can't see
inside the cell,
so it could be booby-trapped.
Any suggestions?
Nothing from you,
Miss Stapleton?
Sorry, ma'am.
Can you come to the phone?
It's HQ.
They said it's very urgent.
Come on, George.
It's after 4:00.
This has gone on long enough.
Ah!
Now, you saw that.
Could have broken my nose.
Instead it's given me
a headache.
I've got a headache!
This had gone on
long enough, George.
You've pissed your pants.
If they open that door,
I'll pull your chair away.
Then your neck'll break.
You know what happens
when you get strangled?
All your bodily functions
happen.
Pblt!
Yo, Smith.
You owe me, mate.
One phone card.
Piss off.
It's not my fault it ran out.
Course it is, man.
You used it.
Now, you'd better get me
another one.
- Are you threatening me?
- Well, I might be.
Yeah?
Just do it.
Eugene!
It's him!
See, I was right!
Tarzan!
It's me... Brian!
Tarzan! It's me!
Stop pushing, Smith! Why do you
need to frigging push?
Well, you can't see now,
can you?
Tarzan, it's me... Brian!
Told you he was me mate!
See that?
It's me... Brian!
There you are.
I told you I knew him, didn't I?
He's my mate.
Tarzan!
It's Brian!
Get off him, Buffy!
Buffy, get off him.
Do you hear me?!
I want the local radio station.
What's the waveband?!
Do you know?
Oh.
Sorry.
- Officer held at knifepoint.
- Past the Classic FM.
That's Russell's voice.
He's talking to him.
The gag's off.
Just turn the dial
past the Classic FM.
That's what I do.
Do you know why I'm doing this?
'Cause no one pays me
any attention!
Nobody pays me...
any attention.
I will, George.
I'll listen to you.
You got me here, so talk to me.
I will listen to you.
Ah, no!
- Oh, God.
- Russell?
You talk to them...
Are you all right?
And you're dead.
George, what's going on there?
Okay.
You see?
I have been poisoned.
And I know who is doing it,
but they refuse to listen to me.
Oh!
It's arsenic.
You've got inflammation of
the bowel, that's all, George.
No, I have not!
That's what they said
my dad had.
He died in agony, my dad.
Thank you, Mr. Andrews.
HQ are sending us an experienced
hostage negotiator
and replacement
for Dr. Williams.
- Be with us shortly.
- Shortly?
Oh, well, that's great.
In the meantime,
Falla's screaming blue murder
about being fed arsenic.
He thinks
someone's poisoned him.
Let me have a go.
If anyone goes down
on that wing, it'll be me.
I've been doing the negotiating
training, Gary.
That's what I've been doing.
As HOC, Gary, you go down.
It's a complete breach
of the rules.
Hmm. Been more than a few
breaches already, Governor.
Got a frigging hostage,
have you?
You might just get another one
when I get out.
Dickhead.
Hey, I'll snatch
the ruddy governor.
Yeah, yeah.
I'm gonna write to
the home secretary about this.
I need me glasses.
I can't see without me glasses.
I'm due out
in a frigging few weeks.
I mean, as if I'd do anything.
I mean, I never touched nobody.
This isn't fair.
It's not fair.
- This is your fault, Eugene!
- Bollocks!
- It's your fault!
- Oi! Stop gassing!
- In your cell.
- You're an Uncle Tom.
I have an exam to do.
What about me education program?
Hey, Chiswick!
I've got a one-on-one tomorrow!
You just lost it.
Where's my rubber dolly?!
Hey?!
I need to know
his family history,
his entire prison records,
and his medical records.
At all costs,
whoever who is negotiating
with the perpetrator at Barfield
must in no way
give in to his demands.
Could you hold on a second?
Yes, ma'am.
At Barfield Prison,
and we hope and we pray for...
Does Governor Keller know
that there is a live broadcast
going on?
- I'm not sure.
- I've just heard it.
♪ Whisper secrets to the wind ♪
♪ Through ♪
♪ We're through ♪
♪ It's over ♪
And if you could let them
have that straightaway, please.
Governor.
Miss Hewitt.
Thanks.
You can leave us.
Nice to see you again.
HQ have supplied me
with the background details,
but I'll need to see
George Falla's report.
Good heavens.
What an improvement.
Very impressive.
How's Morgan coping?
He is
a very experienced officer.
But then, you know him.
He was here when you, um...
Did my caretaking job.
Yes.
He was also taken hostage
by a prisoner Norman Jones.
So he'll know the routine.
He's held in the healthcare
center, Miss Hewitt.
In this cell here.
Falla says,
but we can't be sure,
that the door is rigged
to hang Morgan if opened.
Mm.
Well, the door opens inwards,
but we'll have to
take his word for it.
Where on earth did he find
a possible half of a mop?
The mop was left in the cell.
Yeah, we're really
short-staffed after...
Does Falla have a radio
in his cell?
I beg your pardon?
Well, you know they're talking
about the hostage on-air?
What?
Nobody knows
about this situation,
with it being
in the healthcare center.
Well, they obviously do.
The last thing we need
is the local radio wide boy
making a meal of it,
so I suggest you contact them.
If you're ready,
you should go down.
They'll need a break.
Oh, no, I, um...
I won't interact with Falla.
I'll just give my advice on how
to handle the perpetrator.
He wants a blow-up rubber doll.
Mm-hmm.
And to see you blowing it up.
Well, let's see what I can do,
shall we?
After you, Miss Hewitt.
Yes, you were.
After me.
Miss Helen Hewitt.
This is, uh, HOC.
- Gary Marshall.
- Miss Hewitt.
Uh, give us five minutes, lads.
He's been in there since 9:00
this morning, Miss Hewitt.
Do you think we ought to, uh...
I'm here
to do the thinking, Gary.
You shouldn't even be here.
I'm not on duty.
- How's Morgan?
- He's taken the gag off him.
Why don't you piss off?!
Is the doctor the main person
that Falla's
been interacting with?
He was.
But he's exhausted,
and the prison negotiator
didn't do too well.
And then Falla
became hysterical,
said he was being poisoned,
and Governor Keller
let Jackson have a go.
Have a go?
Can you get Russell out of there
or not?
That's what I'm here for.
Bloody marvelous.
Look, Gary, you obviously
find this very hard to take,
but you have got to trust me.
Come on, George.
You need treatment
to take your pain away.
And I suggest
you get Officer Jackson
away from the perpetrator now.
One minute you say you're not
gonna hurt Officer Morgan,
and the next you say
you're gonna kill him.
Well, how do you think
that makes us feel, eh?
Eh?
Do you know what you're doing?
Yes, I do.
I'm gonna have to use you, Gary.
If you and HQ will agree to it.
- Mm-hmm.
- Okay.
I will not die in agony.
No way.
I'd rather be shot.
I am not going through it.
Give in, George.
You need help
to take the pain away.
Right now as
we speak, in Barfield Prison,
a senior officer is being
held hostage at knifepoint.
Mad, bad,
and dangerous prisoner.
For the second time tonight.
This is for you.
♪ It's over ♪
It's a sign.
That is a sign!
It's over!
It's all over!
♪ It's over ♪
Is it?!
You listen to me!
I am asking you to not make
a further broadcast.
No, I do not want to go on-air.
What I want is your cooperation.
There is a man's life at risk.
Do you understand that?
Thank you.
Bloody radio station.
Give me the okay
when Marshall's wired.
All right, everybody,
this is Miss Helen Hewitt,
who will be the negotiator.
Hello.
Yeah?
Gary?
Gary? Hi.
Stand by.
Game commences.
George, turn the radio off
and listen to what
I've got to tell you.
♪ It breaks your heart... ♪
We've got
the medical reports here
from the tests you had done
at your last prison.
I've got cancer.
No, you haven't.
With the right treatment,
you'll be fit and well
within a couple of weeks.
Really play this one, Gary.
Tell him no way has he got
the same thing as his father.
Keep him steady.
He does not have
the same disease as his father.
George, it's not hereditary.
Look, you don't have the same
disease as your father.
Your father
had a-a terminal illness.
You've not got the same thing.
You have not got cancer.
Sorry I can't give you
a break, Gary.
You've got to keep him talking,
and we've not heard anything
from Russell.
Let him see
that you're still there.
We have a long way to go.
What do you know about my dad?
What was that, George?
Your dad?
He was wrongly diagnosed,
George.
Not in his intestines,
but in his stomach.
He had a tumor, not in his
intestines, in his stomach.
We talked to your mother, and
she didn't want you to know.
We talked to your mum.
She was told,
but she didn't want your dad
to know how ill he was.
Tell him it's not hereditary.
And, George,
it's not hereditary.
We've still had no word
from Russell,
but let's not think the worse.
No, his mother's
very, very worried about him.
She wants to come
and talk to him about it.
We can arrange that for him.
That's no problem.
His mother's name is Stella.
Stella.
Now, use her name as much...
As much as...
Could I please have some quiet?!
Now, Mr. Marshall
is very, very tired.
If I lose concentration,
a man could die in there.
Sorry, Gary.
George...
Now, Stella would explain to you
why she didn't want you to know.
We've talked to Stella, and now
Stella will explain it to you.
You were young, you were scared.
She protected you.
Heavy on the protect, Gary.
She thought you were special.
George, your mother,
she... she wanted to...
She didn't want to frighten you.
She wanted to protect you.
Now she's very upset
about this situation.
We can get her to talk
all this over with you, George,
but you've got to agree
to releasing Mr. Morgan.
George?
Speak to me, George.
Come on.
George?
To releasing Mr. Morgan.
George,
it makes sense, doesn't it?
Are you still there,
Mr. Marshall?
Yeah, I'm here, George.
- Are you still there?
- Yes, I'm here, George.
Tell him the prisoner
he thought was poisoning him...
That prisoner that you thought
was poisoning you...
We've had his cell stripped,
and we couldn't find anything.
He would not have done that
to you.
He swears that, uh, he never
put anything in your food.
He says he wouldn't do that
to you.
We want to make sure that you
have the right treatment.
Tea, two sugars.
I wouldn't mind a cup myself.
We're only trying
to help you, George.
We want you
to get the right treatment,
so that it proves that what
we've been trying to tell you
is the truth.
Tell him that it makes sense.
It all makes sense, George.
Come on, there's a good boy.
I'm getting very tired.
Gary, give him five minutes
to think about it.
You drink your tea.
I need a pee.
Okay.
Excuse me.
Gary?
- Okay.
- You okay to start again?
You're doing really well, Gary,
so just hang in there.
Don't take that literally.
Do you think that's true?
What was that, George?
About my mother.
About Stella.
Do you?!
Well...
You were only young.
Makes sense
not wanting to scare you.
Nobody wants
their dad to die, George.
Do you think I'll be okay?
All I needed...
was for somebody
to explain all this to me.
This is what
I've been asking for!
Shit.
What are they gonna do to me?
Oh, you can trust Gary.
Mr. Marshall.
You can trust him, George.
You still there, Gary?!
Yeah, I'm here.
- Mr. Marshall!
- Yes, I'm here, George.
What will they do to me
if I come out?
Keep him steady, Gary.
Ask him what he wants
if he comes out, and if it's
a bloody rubber dolly,
we're back to square one.
Did you hear me?!
What'll they do to me
if I come out?
Now he's on the line,
so reel him in gently.
Don't unnerve him.
He's worried about what's gonna
happen to him if he comes out,
so, nice, lots of flannel.
We know he didn't
hurt Officer Morgan,
and he's a sick man.
Everything's going to be taken
into consideration.
- George, are you there?
- We know he's not a well man.
George, look,
you're not a well man.
But until this problem
come along,
you were a good prisoner,
and all this will be
taken into consideration.
All right,
you're gonna go on report,
but you haven't hurt
Officer Morgan.
In fact you took care of him,
didn't you?
- Mm?
- Yeah.
Even gave him some
Of course you did.
So really all this...
All this was, was a protest,
right, George?
That's... That's exactly
what this is about, Gary.
That's right.
You come out.
I'll be here.
I'll tell you what, George.
If you come out, I'll make sure
it'll just be me here.
Unless you want to name
anyone else.
No.
Just you, Gary.
Just you and the doc.
Okay, George.
Just me and the doctor
will be out here.
Get the doctor on standby.
This is gonna take
a couple of minutes to arrange.
All right?
- Doctor?
- Mm?
Wake up.
You've been ordered on standby.
Okay.
- Want a cup of tea?
- No, no, I'm all right.
Keep everybody back, Gary.
Don't let him see
any other officers.
I think we have
the end game in sight.
George?
- George, are you there?
- Yeah.
I'll tell you what I'm gonna do.
When it's safe for me to open
this door,
I'm gonna unlock it,
and I'm gonna let you come out
when you're ready.
But you've got to let me know
when it's safe.
All right?
Yeah.
Gary?
Yeah?
- It's safe, is it?
- Yeah, unlock the door.
Good boy.
Come out
whenever you're ready, George.
When you're ready, George.
Come on, George.
It's only me and the doc,
like I said.
Come on, son.
He's out.
Is... Is he out, Gary?
Come on, son.
George, come on.
We've sorted all this out now,
haven't we?
I haven't let you down yet.
Told you the truth
all the way through.
There's a good chap.
Come on.
You'll look after me?
Guaranteed, George.
I'll personally see to it that
you get to discuss all this
with the governor himself.
Can't be fairer than that, son.
Come on.
Nobody here, look.
Just the doctor and me.
Hmm?
Was I telling the truth or not?
Look.
Have a look.
No one here.
Doctor and me.
It's only him and me.
Come on, George.
You're there now, look.
You've done it.
Come on.
There's a good fella.
That's it now.
We'll go and see the governor
and get all this
straightened out and finished.
Just put your hands out, George,
so it can be seen that we've
done this all by the book, yeah?
You know the routine, you know?
Come on.
Arms out.
We need him well clear
of the cell
before anybody moves in on him.
Good lad.
There's a good lad.
All right?
It was... It was just a protest.
That's all it was, Gary.
I know that, George.
Come on.
It's all right now, mate.
- Yes.
- Yes!
End game.
Well done, Gary.
Take in the counselors
and the care team.
Russell.
Come on.
Look at me, son.
Hey.
It's Gary.
Open your eyes.
Hey.
Good lad.
Can you stand?
Try it.
Come on.
Try it for me.
Mm?
Would you like to see
the doctor now, Mr. Morgan?
No.
Um, I don't know.
I'm just a bit stiff.
I know.
W-Was that?
Yes, it was.
Come on.
We've got to get you up, son.
I could do with a stiff drink.
That's the both of us.
My God,
you took your bloody time.
Come on.
Got worried about lunchtime.
Easy. Easy.
Did you call Nora?
- Yeah.
- Oh, she'll have been worried.
Done it.
Why don't I call the doc,
let him give you
and quick look-over?
I don't want a bloody doctor.
But if I don't take a leak,
I will have a burst bladder.
Come on, then.
We'll go together.
Come on.
Give me a hand, eh?
- Ready?
- Mm.
Come on, then.
Get up here.
Easy.
You all right?
Aye.
Come on, then.
You can do it.
Hold it a minute.
Wait there.
Here.
Put that 'round you.
Go on.
You're on your own.
Easy.
I'm with you, Russell.
I'm right behind you.
Thanks.
Thanks, everybody.
I'm gonna have to
go to the toilet.
It's been a long day.
Gary!
Yes, Miss Hewitt.
You were very, very good.
Congratulations.
Thanks.
You should take a few days off.
Negotiations really
take it out of you,
especially when you've been
in on it from the start.
You work in the training college
full-time now?
Yeah.
When you left the debriefing,
there was a lot of bad feeling
about how things were run today.
Some of us have got grave doubts
at how Keller
handled the situation.
Barfield could be up for grabs.
Oof.
A lot of water under the bridge
since I was here, Gary.
I don't know
whether I'd want to come back.
Besides, I doubt
they'd even have me.
Good night.
Good night, Miss Hewitt.
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/agzye
Help other users to choose the best subtitles