General, the princess's convoy
has entered our realm.
Prepare to receive them.
Prepare to receive them!
General Meng Yi of Qin
welcomes Your Highness.
May it please Her Highness.
His Imperial Majesty decrees...
that Princess Ok Soo
shall be Concubine Li of Qin,
for our nations' mutual
peace and harmony.
This is what Princess Ok Soo
was ordered to do.
My orders are to bring back
Princess Ok Soo.
Whoever interferes shall die!
Her Royal Highness
is now Concubine Li of Qin.
Whoever dares to go against this order
is an enemy of our state!
They leave us no alternative.
Prepare to attack.
Ready defenses.
Ready defenses!
Hurry! Protect the Princess!
Hurry! Get away from this place!
Please come back with me.
You are already my betrothed.
I cannot go back with you.
I cannot abide you
marrying the moribund emperor.
It's a surrender
of our sovereignty to Qin!
I was forced into this decision.
Please understand.
You are a general!
How can you taint my honor?
Come!
My mission is to protect the princess.
Draw your sword.
Let's both fulfill
our missions.
Protect the princess.
Save her!
Run!
Your Highness!
28 Feb 2005
I have had the same dream
for months now.
This time, I'm an ancient general
leading a vast army...
to rescue...
some sort of princess.
I fell off a cliff...
Hello? William?
You're back in Hong Kong?
Great! Come on over!
Talk about being at sea!
Why are you living on a barge?
The research budget
was cut in half last year.
With the project unfinished,
I had to sell the flat.
So, I moved here with my study.
It's not so bad!
Pretty roomy here.
So why are you back suddenly?
You didn't like the United States?
I came to solve your financial problems.
I want you to do something for me.
Hi, William! This must be Dr. Chan.
Just call me Jack.
I'm Maggie. Welcome to our
Anti-Gravity Research Project.
- Anti-Gravity?
- This is my lab. Check it out.
Let's ask Dr. Smith
to give a little demonstration.
These are very expensive experiments.
Quite impractical,
and unusable on living subjects
as no living creature
can survive such speed.
I don't understand.
You're a physicist,
I'm an archaeologist.
How can I help you?
I'm seeking a breakthrough
in the field of mysterious phenomena.
Remember that paper you wrote?
Over 2,000 years ago,
there was a tiny kingdom south of Dasar
whose king became immortal after death.
His coffin floated in mid-air.
Your paper inspired me.
It's just a myth.
I can even lend you comic books
about this.
Lots of things are called myths
prior to empirical verification.
Wireless telephony
was a myth 150 years ago.
So was the airplane,
and landing on the moon!
Even 50 years ago,
computer and digital technology
were a myth.
Many people are competing
to develop this technology.
If I succeed,
I'll change human history.
This technology could be vital
to our lives,
to surface and air transportation,
even inter-galactic travel!
I know you've always wanted
to do something great.
No one's ever entered
this ancient tomb before.
But my work is archaeology,
and I have my ethic.
I do research, not raid tombs.
You still can't forget
that incident, after all these years?
There are things you never forget.
We haven't played in ages.
How's your game?
Jack!
Don't you practice anymore?
Of course I do, but I just
never shot from this angle before.
- So why shoot?
- Because you passed it to me.
Don't worry about it.
Come on.
That Maggie is your girlfriend?
No. She represents my sponsor.
By the way, what happened to Monica?
Monica? Forget her.
I've been dreaming about a princess.
Her name's Ok Soo.
I called out her name in my sleep.
How do you think Monica took it?
Now, back to business.
Jack, you've never been
a stickler for rules.
You've always trusted your instincts.
Instincts helped you
unravel the Dead Sea Scrolls forgery...
Jack, hey...
Jack!
Do as your instincts tell you.
I want to prove it's not a myth,
but something real.
You're my best friend.
I trust you won't let me
face danger alone.
Ever tried hitting a golf shot like this?
Jack!
- What's with you?
- I think I've got heat stroke.
Almost there. Come on!
Don't lie to me now.
You should exercise more regularly.
I do! Three hours of golf each day,
two hours of tennis...
And another dozen hours a day
playing video games.
You'll go blind in no time.
If you're so fit, why don't you carry me?
You can walk. Hurry Up.
We won't get in if we're late!
Jack, that's the holy man who can fly?
Yes. Let's go over there.
He really can fly...
Get up. Follow me.
Hey, up, up.
- Hurry.
- Give me a hand.
Grab hold of my leg!
- You've got strong legs.
- Let go!
Wow! Nice stone carvings!
You have no idea
how many stories they tell.
I didn't come this far
on my last expedition.
Jack!
The stone coffin's floating here.
- Zoom in and see if it's suspended.
- I'm working on it already.
Jack,
there's a sword beside the coffin.
I can see it.
I think the inscription
records his deeds.
"Mission to Qin"?
"This prince once brought treasures
and women to Qin.
The Qin Emperor gifted him
one of his concubines,
but he picked the emperor's favorite.
The emperor reneged
and gave him her painting instead,
as well as the Qin Star Gem in apology.
The prince even fought against
Qin's greatest warrior,
exchanging swords with him."
- Hey! Don't!
- What?
Jack!
- Are you all right?
- What did you just move?
I've never seen stones like these.
I want some for research.
I told you not to steal anything!
I was going to return it afterwards.
It almost cost me my life!
How come the coffin fell
as soon as I pulled it out?
His Majesty requested me
to paint a portrait of Concubine Li
as a gift to the Prince of Dasar.
If she won't smile, how can I paint?
I've not seen her smile since she arrived.
General Meng!
Excellent!
That's the smile!
Jack!
Stop dreaming!
I hear footsteps!
- Quick! Lift it up!
- Why don't you ask them to help?
Jack!
Help me!
Come on! Let go!
Hey.
Who are you?
Why come and desecrate our sacred temple?
What do you gain by this?
I just came in to look for something,
I didn't mean to wreck the coffin.
It was an accident.
Sorry.
Are you all right?
I was apologizing.
How was I to know?
I was trying to help.
- Let's go.
- Wait.
I told you not to steal.
It's for protection.
Let's go, Jack!
- I took the painting for you as well.
- What?
Run.
- Jack!
- Wait.
Get up. Let's go.
Jack!
Didn't you say you had backup?
All I see are monkeys!
You get on board first.
Jack!
It is too dangerous,
we have to leave now!
Come on! Jack!
Fly a bit lower!
No! We are hit! Let's go!
Jack! Jack!
Jack!
Thank God!
Concubine Li!
Your Highness,
forgive my lapse in your protection.
Halt!
Lay down your sword!
or I'll kill her!
Don't!
If only one can live,
I'd rather it be you.
Drop it!
General!
- General Meng Yi!
- Don't help me.
I'm beneath your station.
Why do you
risk your life for me?
A blade is forged
to drink the blood of enemies.
I am like a blade,
destined to fight for His Majesty,
and die for my country.
You are now Concubine Li of Qin.
Protecting you is my duty.
Your Highness has suffered a fright.
With you beside me,
I'm not afraid of anything.
We cannot stay here.
We must leave quickly.
Meng Yi...
General Meng Yi!
General, come in.
Meng Yi...
Meng Yi? General Meng Yi?
You promised to protect me.
You can't die!
Meng Yi?
Meng Yi? Meng Yi...
I have nothing
left in this world.
Not even a relative.
Please don't abandon me!
I have nothing left but you.
Please don't leave me alone!
General Meng Yi.
Over here, quickly.
This is the first time
I've felt so free.
No courtly rites and regulations.
What a beautiful feeling.
This is the first time
I've seen Your Highness smile.
- Why don't you look at me?
- Your humble servant does not dare.
Don't say such things.
Don't take away this feeling.
I'll stop calling you general.
How's that, Meng Yi?
I want to dance.
Shall I dance for you?
No, Your Highness. You mustn't.
In this world, only the emperor
himself may watch.
This is a dance
for you alone.
Please, Your Highness.
We have reached the Great Wall.
This is entirely our realm.
Our capital, Xianyang
is just over the hill.
You are now safe, Concubine Li.
I have finally
accomplished my mission.
No!
I don't want to go to Xianyang.
Take me away.
Take me anywhere.
I only want to be with you.
I don't want to marry the emperor.
Why did we struggle to stay alive,
just to become slaves to destiny?
When will we ever...
be free?
Not until the day we die?
Ok Soo... Concubine Li...
Your Highness, please calm down.
Don't forget
your own mission.
You must live for the sake
of your people.
Only with life is there hope.
Promise me,
you will live!
You would have me live
in such agony?
Very well.
Very well. I promise you.
I'll live for you.
You! Freeze!
I'm levitating!
Mid-air coffee.
Maggie!
Don't!
Hello?
Jack. Our project has succeeded.
Well, almost!
What? It's a meteorite?
- Outside our solar system?
- That's right.
We must now find the rest of them.
Where's the painting from the coffin?
It's here with me.
I'm going to Xian. Meet me there.
Bring the painting with you.
- Okay.
- Good. See you soon.
I'm coming with you.
I believe it was forged
some time during the Qin dynasty,
This type of scale-like surface material
is found only in Qin-dynasty artifacts.
Looking at the design and decorations,
I'd say it belonged to a Qin general.
This is a national treasure.
Be careful.
Wait. What are you doing?
The sword is ours!
Jack has bequeathed it to our museum.
Our foundation financed this project.
Anything found
should belong to the foundation.
How can you donate the sword
to the museum?
The sword's a grade one national relic.
It belongs to all of humanity.
It's only right we return it to a museum
where it can be seeing by everybody.
Anyway, what's key to the project
are the meteorites.
These two artifacts
have nothing to do with them.
Before my experiments
draw a conclusion,
anything may prove
to be a critical link.
How can you prejudge it
by saying otherwise?
My experiments will benefit all mankind.
Artifacts are old, dead things.
They have no life, no future!
What science is concerned with
is precisely the future!
Fine, if that's what you say,
then how come these
2,000 year-old artifacts
are so important to you?
I risked my life for that sword!
That was me.
Okay! In that case,
when I find the meteorites,
- you'll still give them away?
- Yes.
As long as it's someone else's artifacts,
I'll return them.
No one can plunder relics
from someone else's country
and put them in their own museums.
They call it "safe-keeping,"
but it's theft.
It's despicable behavior.
So, what are we going to do now?
What can I do?
William.
Do you want to meet your sponsor
for these last ten years?
Of course.
But he doesn't want to see me.
I'll bring you to him now.
- Right now?
- Come with me.
I'll return these relics
to Dasar for you.
Thank you.
Professor Koo?
It's you?
It's been years since I was a professor.
Mr. Koo, you've been
funding my work
all these years?
That's right.
I had my eye on you
even before you graduated.
Maggie, cancel my contract
with the foundation.
I won't accept sponsorship
from a tomb-raiding "archaeologist."
And you and Jack
weren't raiding tombs in Dasar?
I've unearthed many treasures
in my lifetime.
But the best ones I found
are you and Jack.
- Don't you hate him?
- No.
Even if he has hurt me deeply.
So what do you want from me?
Stay with Jack.
Follow him.
Enlighten him.
He'll make you
the world's greatest scientist.
Isn't that your life's dream?
"The 36th year of the emperor's reign.
A star fell on the eastern province,
and turned to stone on Earth."
RECORDS OF THE GRAND HISTORIAN
"The meteorite was engraved..."
"...with a curse on the emperor.
So the emperor tried to kill everyone
around him...
to keep the secret
of the meteorite intact."
Look! General Nangong's returned!
Out of the way!
Report to the general at once!
How is my father?
How is His Majesty?
Report!
General Nangong has returned
with important intelligence.
Well,
how is His Majesty?
His Majesty's...
General,
the Immortal Pill is ready.
On his way back,
General Xu was ambushed by rebels.
Prepare the troops for departure.
Yes, sir.
- Fresh horses!
- Yes sir!
If word gets out,
your whole clan will be executed!
Your servant wouldn't dare!
Please tell the Chancellor
I don't know anything.
I'll never tell!
Father had too many
people around him.
I fear for our plans.
The concubines are ready
to be entombed with him.
Your Majesty, the Immortal Pill is ready,
but was taken in a rebel ambush.
Your servant begs leave
to go retrieve it forthwith!
General Meng,
your duty is His Majesty's safety.
You should stay.
The situation is most urgent!
I await His Majesty's orders.
His Majesty commands you
to retrieve the pill.
- As ordered!
- Wait.
His Majesty has few troops
in his entourage.
If you go all out for the pill,
and the rebels strike,
I fear for His Majesty's safety.
In that case,
I'll only take the Light Cavalry.
I won't tell.
His Majesty still needs treatment.
Let me try once more.
General Meng Yi!
Farewell, Your Highness.
You must come back.
The pill can save His Majesty's life,
and therefore yours too.
Know that my heart
is yours forever.
I await your return.
Attention, soldiers of the Meng clan!
Those with aged parents are excused!
The only sons are excused!
Husbands and fathers are excused!
Those who are excused, guard the camp!
The rest of you, mount!
General!
How many years
have we shared our honor?
Why can we not
live and die together now?
I, Nangong Yan swears to follow you
even unto death!
We swear to follow the General!
I have orders from the Chancellor
to take the pill.
Failure to hand it over
is disobedience, Xu Gui!
I can only give the Pill
to General Meng.
I won't give to anyone else!
The Chancellor bears
His Majesty's word.
Obey right now!
Or die!
Prepare to attack!
Defenses!
Ready archers!
Fire!
Charge!
Attack!
Zhao Kuang, His Majesty orders!
Yield at once!
You dare fake
an Imperial Decree?
General Meng?
Leave no one alive!
General Zhao!
General Meng comes
with an Imperial Decree!
Why do you disobey?
Your disobedience in the field
will be punished! Attack!
Soldiers at the back!
No one moves without my orders!
Attack!
Xu Gui!
- General Meng!
- Meng Jie?
The Chancellor wants you dead.
Behind my troops is the only way out.
General, there's no time.
You go with Meng Jie.
I'll hold them off.
Go!
After them!
Out of the way!
My bow!
Everyone out of the way!
Out of the way!
Go! Hurry!
Go!
Black Wind!
Archers, ready!
Fire!
General!
Take the pill and go!
- General!
- The pill must reach the emperor!
Protect Concubine Li!
Farewell, my General.
Go!
Black Wind,
you have done your duty.
Jack.
I am sorry. You were right.
Those relics should be returned.
I made you something.
I hope you like it.
I looked up the geographical data
within 500 miles of Xian.
You once told me your dreams
of waterfalls and tunnels.
I hope this will help.
How far is this waterfall
from Mount Li?
About 200 kilometers.
Sensors indicate a huge cave
behind the waterfall.
There were rainstorms one year,
and the cave never reappeared.
- Thank you.
- Good-bye.
Jack, there's a cave behind the waterfall,
with a huge opening just behind it.
That's right.
A dozen years ago,
there was a drought.
The water dried up.
The cave behind the waterfall appeared,
and a foolhardy villager climbed in.
Then it started to rain,
and the water quickly concealed
the entrance again.
The villager was never seen again.
What do you plan to do?
I'm going into the waterfall.
- How?
- Get flushed in.
You crazy?
That's very dangerous!
You don't even know
if your dream is real.
Sure! I don't know
whether it's real or not,
or who the person in the dream
is to me.
But I can feel her love.
So you're saying,
unless you unravel this dream,
you'll never be at peace?
What a blessed place!
Wind, water,
all the elements are in place.
Jack, only you
could've brought me here.
William, do you copy?
Loud and clear, Jack.
I can see you.
I'll contact you as soon as I'm in.
- But if...
- No ifs and buts.
I'll be waiting to hear from you.
I'll be in touch.
Don't worry.
Whether it's brain or brawn,
he's your superior.
Jack, what's happening?
Jack!
Are you all right?
My ass hurts.
William, I see an opening
with man-made designs.
Like the sketches you drew?
I'll see if I can get inside.
I will call you later.
Get ready to begin.
Now.
Meng Yi.
You've finally returned.
I am your Ok Soo.
You've finally come.
Ok Soo...
is it really you?
You were really waiting for me.
Am I dreaming?
I promised I'd live for you!
I've kept my word.
You kept yours too.
You've really returned.
Jack!
Jack, thank you!
Without you,
this secret would have been buried
for another eternity.
This place is exactly
like Jack's dream.
I can't explain it scientifically.
There are many things in this world
that science can't explain.
This cave stays warm the year round.
It's shut off from the world,
but air flows freely.
They made massive constructions
at Mount Li,
but dug a 100-mile tunnel
to build the mausoleum here.
Brilliant!
A masterstroke of deception.
But where's the entrance
to the mausoleum?
Release me
♪ Jie kai wo ♪
From the mysterious wait
♪ Zui shen mi de deng dai ♪
Stars are falling, wind is blowing
♪ Xing xing zhui luo feng zai chui dong ♪
Finally holding you again
♪ Zhong yu zai jiang ni yong ru huai zhong ♪
Two trembling hearts
♪ Liang ke xin chan dou ♪
Trust me
♪ Xiang xin wo ♪
My heart remains unchanged
♪ Bu bian de zhen xin ♪
I promised to wait a thousand years
♪ Quan nian deng dai you wo cheng nuo ♪
No matter how many bitter cold winters
♪ Wu lun jing guo duo shao de han dong ♪
I would never let go
♪ Wo jue bu fang shuo ♪
Now hold my hands
♪ Iye nae sonul japgo ♪
And close your eyes
♪ Nunulkamayo ♪
Remember the days when we're in love
♪ Uri saranghetton nalto sengkaghepayo ♪
We love each other so much
♪ Uri nomu sarangheso ♪
That we are in so much pain
♪ Apossonneyo ♪
We cannot tell each other "I love you"...
♪ Soro saranghandan malto moshaess-eossneyo... ♪
Your Highness! Beware!
Stop, General Nangong!
He's Meng Yi! General Meng!
Impossible!
He can't be General Meng!
No warrior is General Meng's match!
How can he be him?
He really is General Meng!
There's no mistake!
You really are the General.
Greetings to the General!
Sir, I have followed your order
to protect Concubine Li
- pending your return.
- Good.
Mr. Koo...
Great work, Mr. Koo!
You've discovered the secret
of levitation.
Weightlessness carries serious dangers.
If we lose traction
and float off,
we'll be adrift forever,
and turn into living fossils.
Hold on!
After I left you that day,
I returned with the Pill.
His Majesty was barely alive,
but Zhao Gao doubted the Pill's veracity.
He ordered me
to personally test it.
Chancellor Li said
it was our honor
to test the pill for the emperor,
and forced me to take it too.
And so, those
who wanted to live didn't,
and those who wished to die
can never do so.
General, what happened that day
after I left?
That day, after I gave you the Pill...
Black Wind,
you have done your duty.
Fighting...
by your side...
today...
has been my greatest honor in life.
I take my leave.
Halt!
Attack!
Surrender, General!
No!
Never!
I won't believe it.
If General Meng fell in battle...
then who are you?
I am...
Everything is as I expected.
Life after death...
Troops in an eternal vigil...
I've found you at last!
Who would have thought
the Qin Emperor would use the meteorite
to create a weightless world?
General, did you bring troops?
No.
Wait for me here.
Be careful.
Who dares to trespass the mausoleum?
A Qin-dynasty man?
Immortal?
Jack!
Are you all right?
William!
You conned me from day one.
You've been working for him!
- I... I...
- Jack, I told you before.
Greed is human nature,
and desire for knowledge
drives us.
I merely made use of William's greed
and your desire for knowledge.
And now my life's work
is complete!
When you turned me in,
I told myself...
One day, you'll make it up to me.
Jack, all I want is to take some stuff
back for experiments.
My discoveries will benefit the world.
I'll become the greatest scientist
of the century!
No one can take anything from here.
This is a part of history.
It should stay buried forever!
Without you,
I couldn't have solved this maze
in several lifetimes!
Professor!
Scoundrel!
How dare you defile the mausoleum?
The penalty is death!
Nangong Yan! Careful!
Don't shoot.
I want him alive.
Take care of Ok Soo.
Where's the Immortality Pill?
Tell me.
Halt!
General Nangong!
WHEN THE DRAGON PEARL MOVES,
ANNIHILATION ENSUES
Pull me in.
Quick, give me a hand.
General Nangong!
Concubine Li! Run!
Run!
Give me your hand! Quick!
Use your legs.
Right, your legs.
Pull me in.
A Qin-dynasty deputy imperial general!
Tell me!
Where's the Immortality Pill?
Where's the Qin Emperor's sarcophagus?
It must be in the Celestial Palace.
Take me there! Take me there!
Stay where you are!
Don't you dare try
to steal anything
or take her away!
That depends on
whether you can stop me.
Don't worry.
I won't let anyone hurt you.
Jack! Help me!
Ok Soo, I'll take you
away from here.
Let's go.
Jack!
William!
- William!
- Help me!
Hang on to me!
I only do scientific research.
I'm no tomb raider.
Jack...
you must get out no matter what,
and finish my research.
Jack.
Jack, are we still friends?
Jack?
You really aren't Meng Yi.
No, I'm not.
Whether I'm Meng Yi or not
doesn't matter.
What matters is that
we leave here now!
You're not Meng Yi.
I'm not leaving.
I'll await Meng Yi's return.
Ok Soo, hurry! There's no time!
No. He's not dead.
I'll wait for him.
Ok Soo!
At last! Immortality!
General Zhao!
General Meng comes
with an Imperial Decree!
Why do you disobey?
The emperor is dead now,
and you have to...
From now on,
we will never...
Oh, no!
That last line... the last line!
From now on,
we will never separate again.
You've been lying to me!
From beginning to end,
from today onwards...
You have been
speaking Cantonese style Mandarin
from beginning to end.