Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
FAMILY MOTTO
A HARMONIOUS FAMILY WITH LOVE
Come slowly.
You might fall.
I have to go home today.
To celebrate Dad's return home.
It won't be long.
Let's drink something.
You have something to tell me, right?
On Eun-joo's wedding day,
I saw some facial expressions
and realized that there are things
that can't be expressed in photos.
The facial expressions
of your mother and father.
Eun-joo was the star of the day,
but I was observing them
and taking their photos.
My mom and dad?
Yes.
Actually, I recently saw
that my mom has a photo of my dad.
It was unexpected, so I was surprised.
This?
Why is this photo on your phone?
I like this photo.
So I told Ji-woo to give it to them.
Why?
You've always said that your parents
live together because of the kids,
and they hate each other.
But I…
didn't feel that at Eun-joo's wedding.
Then…
what did you feel?
Well…
It's complicated.
"I know how you've been living
to be standing here today."
"Only I know."
Those eyes.
Those eyes deeper than love.
I'm sure they didn't hate each other
or stay together because of the kids.
Send me this photo too.
But why are you
bringing that up all of a sudden?
I don't know.
I think your mother is very wise.
Whatever your mother says today,
listen to her.
Okay.
But I guess I do know a lot about you.
I don't think you're
telling me everything.
There must be a reason, right?
All right.
I have to go.
Let's go.
How can holding hands
be this heart-fluttering?
You won't say that
if you're actually fluttered.
I think you're in friend mode.
Chan-hyuk, I'll be good to you.
I love it.
How do you feel?
Did you calm yourself down?
A bit.
When someone approaches you
and says, "I know what's troubling you,
I know what you want,"
don't hold onto them.
There's no such thing.
You might've started it
with affectionate love,
but I'm sure you know how you feel.
You held on because she was easy.
Did you think you could just leave?
No.
I regretted it after writing that too.
I also thought I could just leave.
Without even knowing
how scary those words are.
I got divorced.
Thinking about it,
there were things
I didn't tell you, like this.
I think it was because
you are the youngest.
Let's start sharing things from now on.
We both made a mistake
and let's not repeat these mistakes.
Since Eun-hee has arrived, I'm going too.
Buy a cake before you come.
Being unable to take things easily
is a good change too.
Mom, I'm here.
Mom.
It's a gift.
It's the same one I gave my sisters.
Mom, I'll put it on for you.
No, thanks.
Follow me.
Mom, light the candles on the cake.
For Dad's return home.
Don't do that.
What is family?
What is a family…
to you?
I'm asking because I really don't know.
You guys don't know either?
Or…
have you never thought about it?
When you…
cut ties with Eun-joo,
I was wondering, "What happened?"
"Is her heart filled with hard feelings?"
I was worried sick alone for years.
Did you know?
When you…
announced your divorce
without consulting me
about it,
I just accepted it.
And It's still breaking my heart.
Did you know?
You…
Do you…
Do you even know…
what you have done?
Mom…
Get out.
Your mom…
will have nothing to do with you anymore.
I'm going to make her.
Didn't you hear me?
Get out!
Don't do that.
I can't kick him out.
I know
because I've been kicked out.
I know how scary that is,
so I can never do that.
I will not kick you out,
so answer me at least.
Do you know…
what you have done…
to me?
Mom, I'm sorry.
Even if someone rented
that room for one or two years,
I'm sure that someone
wouldn't have left like you did.
You…
Why did you do that?
Mom.
Dad.
I'm sure…
he doesn't really know what he did wrong.
He must've left with the thought
of going to a foreign country
with no one else there
to live freely.
It means that we were a burden to him.
When all of my family immigrated overseas,
I had nowhere to go when things were hard.
"Mom, Dad."
"Things are so hard for me."
"I can't live."
I had no one to hold onto or vent to.
It was so miserable…
I cried a lot at the time.
But you…
Did you want to fly to a place
with no family
and live freely
all by yourself?
Mom also had her mom
and her family.
I forgot about that.
Go bring the cake.
Your father got discharged
after a big surgery,
so congratulate him.
Mom.
I'm so sorry.
I'm really sorry.
I will never do that again.
Please forgive me.
Mom, I really am sorry.
How can he do that?
You've never done that, huh?
Because I don't do anything wrong.
You're disgusting.
I'm sorry.
Mom, I'm so sorry.
I can’t live without you.
All right.
I'm going to be born
the youngest in my next life.
Dad, blow out the candles.
Dad, blow out the candles, come on.
Welcome home!
Yay!
Welcome home, Dad.
Mom.
The gift.
Mom, I'll put it on for you.
How pretty.
We shouldn't have covered it up so easily.
That was the problem every time.
Her anger isn't going to
melt away that easily,
so let's comfort her in our own ways.
Bye.
I brought my car key.
Eun-joo, I'll take you.
Did you bring your car?
Come on, it'd be uncomfortable
for him to go back in now.
He's giving them time
to have a conversation.
Are you dating someone?
Seriously.
I'm too old to be asked
if I'm dating someone or not.
Stop asking me that, okay?
I think I saw this moment before.
Eun-joo, I'll take you.
He wasn't just the youngest
who doesn’t think much.
He's old enough too.
He should know
how serious his actions were.
You're here alone?
Ji-woo isn’t coming.
Ms. Lee Jin-sook's generosity
is at another level,
so he didn't get kicked out.
You.
You knew that my mom knew, right?
How did you know?
I…
met your mother.
You met my mom?
You met her alone?
She asked me
if Ji-woo did go on a business trip,
and I couldn't lie to her.
All mothers in the world
know everything about their children.
I forgot about that old divine truth.
She didn't really ask me to keep a secret,
but I decided not to tell anyone
until she told everyone.
So you came to see me
to tell me to listen to her?
Then what can I do?
I hate keeping secrets from you.
At that moment…
I was on your mother's side.
I love you.
The words I've been keeping
for a long time
almost popped out.
Why are you…
looking at me with those eyes?
Well…
You always…
At all times…
You keep secrets so well.
You're everyone's private safe.
No. You're suddenly
blushing and acting weird.
I'm blushing?
What could it be?
Are you okay?
Me?
Why would I be?
Mr. Kim Sang-sik.
I'm so scared
whenever you call me that now.
Don't get angry.
Do you think I lost it?
Why would I get angry at you now?
I decided to sell Lucky.
How did you know about Lucky?
I guess you completely forgot…
that you used to call me Lucky
when I was pregnant
with Eun-joo.
No.
That's not what I'm saying.
You can't drive anymore.
But if you keep on being
stubborn and continue driving,
I can’t stop you.
No one can stop your stubbornness.
All right.
I'll quit driving.
Earlier on…
even when my heart was breaking,
I was concerned about our kids and you.
Why were you concerned about me?
I guess that's how
I've been living my life.
I've never thought this but today,
I disliked my kids.
My goodness.
How can a mother
dislike her kids?
My heart sunk.
Gosh.
You idiot.
You absolute idiot.
The problem is it's not over.
I was going to reveal everything today,
but I just left.
Chills ran down my spine.
It's not over?
Is your family an onion?
It just keeps peeling.
It's not one hundred percent true.
If Mom finds out that Ji-woo
was conned and lost money…
"Ji-woo worked so hard
to save up that money,
and what have you been doing
when he was being conned?"
If she finds out the true reason
for Eun-joo's divorce…
"Fraudulent marriage?"
"Eun-hee, lead the way!"
"How dare they
do that to my precious daughter!"
"This is a crime!"
"Why didn't you tell me?"
I'll be the one to take all the blame.
I love you.
What's with your face?
What?
It's red right here.
Here?
I'm fine.
-Hi.
-Patent Attorney Kim.
Hi.
Good morning.
Excuse me. I'm getting off too.
-Don't you need to go up a floor?
-I have business with Attorney Kim.
Attorney Kim.
It's not ready yet,
but you came early.
Yes.
My sister
told me what she heard at the lounge.
I heard you stood up for me
when people were badmouthing me.
I did?
I heard you took my side
when they talked about my divorce
and changed the subject.
That…
I find it boring to talk about
someone who's not there.
Is that standing up for you?
I don't beat around the bush,
so I’ll tell you directly.
Someone who just got divorced
feels uncomfortable
when defended and treated nicely too.
The most considerate thing to do
is to do nothing.
Divorce is different from a breakup.
Okay, I see.
Well, I…
Right now…
I'm here to receive
the additional delivery charges.
I'm afraid you might complain again
if I pay for that, so…
Okay.
Tell me how much it is.
Yes, this is the receipt
I got after I paid for it.
Here's my bank information.
GARAM BANK, YOO MIN-WOO
Isn't it precise?
I got scolded a lot by you
for not being precise back in the day,
so I'm now more meticulous.
Okay. I'll send you the money right away.
Patent Attorney Kim.
Yes.
Don't you remember that?
I…
I've always been on your side
since we were trainees,
and I've always been nice to you.
But I thought it'd be weirder
if I'm awkward with you
just because you just got divorced,
so I'm being the same,
as I have always been.
So, don't be uncomfortable
with your co-trainee as well.
You said almost the same thing back then
and you apologized later,
saying you made a mistake.
Lucky hasn't been sold yet, huh?
There's a long line of people
wanting to buy it.
But…
You need to stamp the paperwork.
Sang-sik.
You need to quit.
I'm going to quit soon too.
I've learned from seeing you.
Family comes first, not money.
Want to do business together?
With your wife's kimchi,
it would be a big success.
I made her suffer all her life,
and you want me to make her sell kimchi
because I can't drive a truck now?
Why are you yelling?
That scared me.
Still, I was worried about you.
But it's a relief that
the surgery went well.
I'm going to drive a forklift
at the plant,
and get a license for operating
an overhead crane.
What the heck?
So you had plans already?
Your wife
cried a lot
after collecting your things from Lucky.
You should've stopped her.
You let her see all of it?
How can I stop her from doing that?
She cried so much
that her eyes were swollen
by the time she left,
so I was wondering if she could see.
Okay, here we go. Smile.
One, two…
Give me a big smile.
I feel relaxed. It's amazing.
It feels like I'm resting.
Let's…
give it a shot.
"I love you" is such a common expression,
but I didn't say that to the one I love.
Are you going to be alone like this?
My beloved Kyung-ok.
Were you lonely because I was gone?
Beloved? Come on.
You don't like me.
No, that's not true.
I didn't spread rumors
about you and the vice CEO, okay?
That's not something that can be hidden.
The vice CEO's eyes
were sparkling with hearts.
That was a long time ago.
It was my fault.
Forget about it.
I read in a book
that people tend to be nicer
to those they don't really like
and waste more energy on them.
That's what you do.
You always tell your co-workers
that you love them.
I, too, heard that
you love me too many times.
I know, right?
I did that.
And as for you…
You need to stop wasting money.
Stop treating people.
That's the joy of my life.
Don't tell me to stop doing that.
Can you drop me off here?
What?
Thanks.
-He's taking too long.
-What?
Just drive safely.
Hey.
I love you, Park Chan-hyuk.
All the "I love you" that I said
for 35 years can't beat this one.
Now…
Right now…
I love you.
Fast food.
Fast food?
I treasure Ji-woo
like he's my own brother,
and I like Eun-joo and am polite to her
because of…
you.
I forgot to say something important.
About what I said earlier.
I promised myself to tell
the story to the person
that would be by my side forever.
I'll call you.
I have to do it. What are you saying?
It's my turn today.
More.
Turn to the left more.
The angle isn't right.
Isn't there a rear camera?
Driver.
Are you going to kill
the onlooker with frustration or smog?
Hey.
Come in.
Keep going.
Now slowly take your foot off the brake.
Step on it. That's it.
Yes!
Hi.
Look at that.
You said almost the same thing back then
and you apologized later,
saying you made a mistake.
Welcome.
I'll drive fast,
as this is a call from our mother.
They smell so good,
even by putting them in the house.
Aren't you going to make
any yellow plum wine?
Why would I turn these
good things into wine?
Mom.
I need to meet my biological father.
My tummy.
-I'm going to the restroom…
-Stay here.
Don't do that anymore.
Why?
It says "Jirisan Yellow Plums."
on the box.
These grew from yellow plum trees
in Jirisan Mountain.
I shouldn't leave it like
unfinished homework
and find him.
How can I find him?
That's straightforward.
I know where he is.
A straightforward answer.
He was on the TV.
Is he famous?
If you want to go see him, I'll tell you.
Okay.
And…
I'm leaving.
-To where?
-When?
I don't know.
That's what you say the most
whenever I ask you something.
But,
I really don't know.
Why did we think
that Mom's anger would melt away
if we act cute a few times?
Isn't it funny?
Look how it hops
because it grew up with rabbits.
This cat runs like a horse. Cool, right?
When I'm with Eun-joo,
I try to be rational like her.
And when I'm with Eun-hee,
I try to be cute and bubbly.
And it felt like I lost my true self.
I was worried if I'm going to
live as the youngest forever.
So that's why I did that.
I'm really sorry, Mom.
It’s harder if you clean
the house all at once.
It's better to clean
little by little every day.
Why did we think
that Mom's wound can be cured
with a three-night trip?
I JUST ARRIVED
I'LL SEND YOU PHOTOS SO TAKE A LOOK
I can't stand being curious.
I hardly apologize to anyone.
Did I apologize to you
when we were trainees?
Right.
You've been thinking that until now?
Jeez.
It makes me sad that you can't remember.
I guess you really don't remember.
Okay, I'll tell you.
When we were trainees,
I was openly nice to you
and always followed you around.
You told me that you didn't
want to date anyone
and said I was making you uncomfortable.
I was dating back then.
You made the same face back then too.
And then you suddenly turned serious
and said, "I'm sorry
if you misunderstood."
And of course, I said it's okay.
Do you remember?
I don't really remember.
But I think I said it.
But…
I broke up with her.
I was too busy to spend time with her,
and it created misunderstandings.
She was a good person.
She said she wanted to spend
a lot of time with me,
but I couldn't do that.
I was incapable at the time,
so when I was assigned with work,
I was busy meeting the deadline,
so I really envied your capability.
One keeps being sorry,
and the other keeps trying to understand.
That's a sad thing.
When I wasn't sure
whether my feelings were love or guilt,
she broke up with me.
So…
I totally understand
what you're trying to say.
Doing nothing.
Doing nothing until you're at peace.
I'll try my best to do nothing.
I know how disgusting
it feels more than anyone.
Even when I said it's fishy
and asked you
why you're sending her money,
you believed her, right?
I did.
She wasn’t a total stranger.
She was your first love.
But now, I'm angry at myself
for being conned
by something that dumb.
And you regret losing money too, huh?
I did at first,
but now…
I feel like I hurt my family so badly,
so I'm not really regretting losing money.
I feel like I lost my place
as the youngest, who is loved by everyone,
with my own hands.
You know it.
Let's have macarons
as the two troublemaking young ones.
By the way…
Why is Chan-hyuk going out
so much these days?
Don't you smell something from the CEO?
I smell romance from him.
Really? So his blind date was a success?
You're not keen and you're brainless.
Pathetic.
You know…
I really hate it when someone says that.
What did you shoot?
I'm testing my new camera.
-You bought another camera?
-"Another?"
Why do your words feel
slightly aggressive?
I don't say, "You bought another book?"
You think buying books is a waste?
Its price is incomparable to cameras.
You think buying cameras is a waste?
Why would you compare it to book prices?
This is my job.
Is this how we're going back to reality?
You're not letting our Ji-woo
notice our relationship, right?
You mind your own business.
Gosh.
My sister's divorced life,
Ji-woo's learning about life,
and my parent's declaration of moving out.
So I can't announce my relationship now.
I don't like secret dating.
Why? Do you wish to tell everyone
that you're dating Park Chan-hyuk?
As soon as I switched to dating mode,
I learned something new about you.
What is it?
Our sense of humor matched
when we were friends.
But you really need to…
cut back on the dad jokes these days.
Do I…
make a lot of dad jokes?
But I'm not a dad.
Dads have a lot of money.
If I had a lot of money,
I'd buy cameras.
Stop it!
You stop it.
MOM: DADA ART GALLERY
DADA ART GALLERY
Hi.
I'm Kim Eun-joo, the one who called you.
Have a seat.
First…
can I tell you about my situation?
Yes.
I got married when I was almost 50.
My eldest daughter is
a high school senior now.
I believe a family must be
as sturdy as a fortress
until the children reach adulthood.
I'm saying this situation
can make my family suffer.
My mother told me
she didn't hide her pregnancy.
Haven't you ever thought
that this day might come?
I haven't.
I think the significance of relationships
is in time.
Even parents and children
are nothing but a hollow shells
if they don't spend time together.
I learned that
my biological father
is someone else recently.
I don't like having
any unfinished business,
so I had to meet you at least once.
That's all.
Ms. Kim Eun-ji, you and I
do have a similarity.
This is the wisest thing I can do
without letting my family know.
It's Kim Eun-joo.
Please remember my name
correctly at least.
I've never been interested in paintings,
so I'd like to refuse this.
Please be happy
and live a long, healthy life.
At that time, my mom
was the 60-year-old Lee Jin-sook
who chose a life for herself
instead of that of a mother.
Like how she did when she was 22.
I…
want to leave.
Yes.
You should.
I read that…
Buck…
The bucket list you wrote.
Those are things you want to do
before you die.
BE A GRANDMA
WALK ON DULLE TRAIL
Do everything you want to do.
I also…
read your bucket list.
READ MS. SOOK'S POEM
BUY A HOUSE WITH A YARD
TAKE A FAMILY PHOTO
PUT 100 MILLION WON IN MY BANK ACCOUNT
LEARN TO PLAY THE HARMONICA
GO TO A FLOWER FESTIVAL WITH MS. SOOK
Do you think the kids know?
That we have so many things
we want to do at our age.
People live up to 100 years now,
but we're worried about
how to make a living
until we get old
and think about the future.
They must be struggling
on their own day by day,
so how would they know?
It is hard.
Life is hard.
I'm going to leave.
But…
I don't know
where I want to go just yet.
Mom left.
We didn’t really talk about
Mom's absence.
It was amazing not to know anything about
what my mom is doing
for the first time in my life.
It's because you eat anything.
I didn't just eat whatever. I ate bread.
Ji-woo.
-It's so good.
-What's wrong with you?
We missed her,
but the guilt we felt whenever we saw Mom
was slightly lifted.
The feeling of indebtedness
that our daily lives
were the result of sacrificing Mom's time
was also slightly lifted.
We all
spent individual time for ourselves
and kept on finding our true self.
Are you eating well?
Of course. I'm not a kid.
Stop being a cheapskate
and turn on the furnace.
Thanks for worrying about me.
That little…
Hi, Eun-joo.
It's quite cold.
Yes.
-It's fermented already.
-Yes.
-Take your portion later.
-Okay.
Take a lot of it.
How have you been?
-We're fine, Dad.
-Okay.
Ji-woo.
This is for you, Dad.
Mix it with warm water and drink it.
It's good for coughing.
THE SCENE ROUTE
SLEEPLESS NIGHT
Thank you.
I bought this book.
I didn't even sell 100 copies yet,
but I met one of my 100 readers.
Thank you.
I gave it to the employees as a gift too.
You point that out.
Makes me feel intimidated.
There's no monthly salary,
so I get a share,
so you made a great contribution.
But,
it’s clearly a loss
and the fact is I have to quit.
My first project failed too.
Find a topic among the things
you know the best
and think about the most.
Like what?
Are all of your family matters resolved?
There's no end to that, isn't there?
Well.
When I was in the US,
I thought of my family a lot,
but when I'm here, I call them even less.
I think more of my aunt,
who made me feel uncomfortable.
Are you giving me an item?
The item about family…
Isn't that a bit cliche?
I think it would be fun
if a group of writers
write about their experiences.
We Are Family.
Since "we" and "family" are together,
happiness in the family seems forced.
I think you are getting
some ideas already.
Will I be mentioned in the book?
Are you doing fine?
Yes. I'm doing really fine.
"I'm doing really fine."
I like the sound of that.
INDEPENDENT PUBLICATION 2021
My eyeliner is so mismatched today.
You're still pretty, my daughter Ji-soo.
I hate it!
You look pretty.
Mom, are you doing
really fine right now?
You should've called first.
Then I might've not been able
to see a doctor riding a bicycle,
which is something I have never
imagined with you.
Wait for a bit. I'll go get changed.
It's wine.
Thank you.
GOHEUNG HEALTH CENTER
Has it been more than a year?
Yes.
I thought of calling you
a few times, but I couldn't.
I guess I hold grudges
longer than I thought.
You didn't know?
You hold grudges.
Me?
I don't.
You don't know me well.
I know you so well.
I knew you'd suddenly come and see me
without calling me this whole time.
And you did.
You paint?
You?
It's just a hobby.
But I think I'm talented.
Show it to me later.
Would that day come?
Are you seeing anyone?
I have a friend.
I like that he doesn't ask
unnecessary questions.
I guess he doesn't talk much like me.
No.
He doesn't ask unnecessary questions,
but he talks too much.
You guys are alike.
You talk quite a lot too.
Me?
I don’t.
You seriously know me
in the wrong ways about so many things.
When you scold Eun-hee,
and when you point out someone's weakness,
you talk a lot.
-And you talk fast too.
-I talk only when I need to.
I can see their weaknesses,
and it'd be great if they can fix them.
I don't know how others hold back.
I actually take my time to tell it slowly.
It's not easy to do that.
Are Mother and Father well?
Yes.
I contact Eun-hee sometimes.
I know.
I'm sure it'll stop eventually.
I think Eun-hee might
keep on contacting me.
She asked me to let her
live in a room when I build a house.
When will I come to understand her?
Ji-woo doesn’t contact me.
He doesn't think badly about you,
but I'm sure he doesn’t
want to contact you either.
We're family but different.
I've been speaking to you
like when we were married.
And addressed my family
like when we were married too.
That's hard to fix.
Eun-hee told me.
That it's a trace
that we were family once.
I want you to be happy.
Because we were family.
I want you to be happy too.
Like I am right now.
Have a safe trip back.
Bye.
MOM
Yes, Mom.
Me? I'm with Eun-hee.
Okay, good night.
Why are you so shocked?
I hung up.
Hey, did you tell your mother about me?
Of course, I did.
I can’t keep on hiding it.
Want me to go on blind dates again?
Are you done? Did you finish it?
What did she say?
"Okay, good luck."
"Eun-hee? I remember her."
"Be happy with her." The end.
What? How can your mother remember me?
She remembers you
as a loud girl, like now.
Wow, my mom has a good memory.
Didn't you talk to Mom
on the phone while you were drunk
when we were in university?
Wow.
Don't tell my family.
Hey, be nice to your mother.
Be nice to your mother.
I'll be nice too.
I think I missed the call.
Hey, your clothes…
Eun-hee.
-Eun-hee.
-Hi.
Did you eat ramen?
Yes.
Chan-hyuk…
Dating someone…
My brother-in-law?
is accepting another family
with your entire body.
According to my reasoning…
Dad knows where Mom is.
And…
I think Mom
will come back soon.
Where's your evidence?
Dad's been coming home
every day these past few days.
Did he bring his things home?
Things?
I don't know about that…
Well, anyway,
he cleans the house so diligently.
He put flowers in the vase too.
I put those flowers in.
I was such an idiot to believe you.
No, it's true this time.
How was your walk today?
It was good.
But it was a bit tiring.
How's the weather?
it's good.
Want to see it?
Wow.
The sky is so beautiful.
Isn't it great?
The test is coming soon.
Okay.
Well done.
It's late here today,
so I brought the guitar,
but I can't sing for you.
It's okay.
Dad sang to her, playing the guitar.
The trail where lovers walk on
Hand in hand
Our paradise is far ahead
Calls for us
Waving at us
Hi.
Aren't you tired?
I'm good.
Mom.
I missed you to death.
My daughter.
Let me see your face.
You lovely girl.
-I'm lovely?
-Yes.
Hi.
Hi, how have you been?
Good.
You look well.
I'm well.
Mom!
Ji-woo.
No one asked about the time Mom had.
Ji-woo, put this on.
-Goodness.
-Right now?
Yes. And this is for Eun-joo.
Goodness!
And this is for Eun-hee.
And this is for Young-sik.
It's hard for him to put on
and take off shoes since he has a bad leg.
These have no shoelaces,
so they're convenient.
We can keep buying him these shoes.
And these are shirts for children.
I bought them in a bigger size.
-Are they for Yong-gyoo?
-Yes.
Eun-hee, give this to Ji-woo's boss.
Why are you telling me to…
-Isn't the color of the water pretty?
-Yes.
What is this?
Isn't it wonderful?
Yes, it is.
Looks like Mom went to the U.S.
I saw Jeju chocolate too.
I saw jeotgal from Sokcho.
What are you all doing? Come here.
Mom, did you take photos?
Yes.
Were you looking at the photos?
We put on our perfectly-fit clothes
and felt that we were with Mom
at all times during her time,
and we saw Mom's big smile
for the first time,
and that was good enough.
Wow!
Why did you ask me
to have a fling with you when I have time?
That was just
for a social media upload, right?
They only see
what they want to see, anyway.
It won't do any damage.
And your girl might be watching too.
I'm totally fine now.
The only one who knows me completely
is myself.
Seriously…
Please teach me how to
deal with a ridiculous client.
How is the client being ridiculous?
Does he or she psychologically harass you?
Or does he or she call you
all the time and waste your time?
Or maybe not giving you materials
when you need them?
Do all those
have different solutions?
I must know what's making you suffer
the most to solve it first.
If I don't know much, I can't solve it.
What's making me suffer the most…
Every day…
Dreaming about the future
and being anxious about the future
is also my responsibility.
We're going to
a salted mackerel factory this time.
The script you wrote is surely different.
I can clearly see what I have to shoot.
You're making me work for you
because I can't make money, right?
Is this a family business?
I pay you for scriptwriting.
Huh?
Are we family?
Yes, CEO.
But I have a dream too.
Chan-hyuk.
Yes?
You know the most about me.
You know the most about me too.
That tickles. Stop it.
Don’t do it. Seriously.
You…
Slowly.
Careful.
You two met.
-I asked her to come and meet me.
-Okay.
WE ARE FAMILY
How about we go on a family trip?
JI-WOO, EUN-JOO
Dad asked us about a trip.
Why aren't you replying?
I'm busy.
I'll decide after you two reply to him.
I'm not sure.
HOW ABOUT WE GO ON A FAMILY TRIP?
JIN-SOOK
Let's go, just the two of us.
Even someone as complicated as me,
as us…
have a family.
THANK YOU FOR WATCHING
MY UNFAMILIAR FAMILY
Subtitle translation by: Hae-lim Lee
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today