Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
FAMILY MOTTO
A HARMONIOUS FAMILY WITH LOVE
Although I didn't want it,
thank you for today.
It seems like you're okay now,
but when you're home alone…
The emotions will come back.
You should stay at
Eun-hee's house for a while.
I don't know where she lives.
I can take care of myself. Go home now.
Do you have something to say?
I remember the day
I saw you for the first time.
Me?
When was it?
Your father was at the hospital
due to an accident.
I went to Eun-hee's house
often with Jong-min,
because Ji-woo was too young
to stay alone.
Right.
I was working
as a substitute teacher at the time.
You saw me at my house, right?
No, I…
I first saw you at the park
in front of your house.
Let's do rock, paper, scissors.
Loser buys ramyeon.
-Rock, paper--
-Wait.
Gosh.
-Rock, paper, scissors.
Yes!
It's always like this.
You two planned it, right?
Are you two dating?
Are you nuts?
What kind of nonsense is that?
Go.
It's like this all the time.
Someone was crying alone
in a corner of the park.
She looked even lonelier
because it was nightfall.
She was there until I came back
from buying ramyeon.
And that…
was you.
You're back. You haven't eaten yet, right?
-Hi.
Someone who was crying
alone in the park came in
with ice cream in her hand
as if nothing happened.
I don't remember.
I wasn't doing well at that time.
And don't most people cry alone?
If Eun-hee wants to cry,
she calls everyone to let them know.
I seriously don't understand her.
Then you should try it too.
Instead of crying alone.
If you need someone, call me.
I don't think I'll ever do that.
Then
when you're alone…
take a look at the wedding photos I took.
Photographers
get to see and hear
a lot of things at weddings.
In this situation…
What you said makes me flustered.
If there are any feelings
you've covered up,
then I think it'd be good
to take it out for once.
Yes, I might try when I have time.
You can go now.
Did you…
Did you tell Eun-joo directly?
No.
Was she your Goheung trip partner?
Let's go and eat. I'm hungry. Bye.
Okay.
Did you go to Goheung with Chan-hyuk?
What about Eun-hee?
Eun-joo, what is it?
Why did you go there with Chan-hyuk?
-You know where Eun-hee lives, right?
-Yes.
Ms. Sook, give it to me.
Ms. Sook, I'll do it.
What were you doing out?
I was thinking about whether
to buy Korean melons or tangerines.
I only worked one shift today,
from Incheon to Incheon.
I'm going to take the orders
that others avoid taking
from now on.
So I think I won't be able to
come home that often now, and…
I heard graduation from marriage
is living separately--
Did you find the letter I wrote to you?
You see…
I'm looking for it.
How do you find it when it doesn't exist?
I've never put any letters
in the lunch box.
Are you sure your memories are back?
Yes.
I remember everything.
I know that I'm a scoundrel
and a good-for-nothing bastard.
But why do you say
you never wrote me a letter?
I remember everything.
Let's talk at home.
"Mr. Kim Sang-sik, make sure
you chew your food well."
"I'm too shy to say it,
so I'm writing it. I love you."
I memorized the whole thing.
Don't treat me like a fool!
If your memories are back, tell me
why you did that on that day.
Tell me…
why you went to that mountain that night.
Were you really trying to kill yourself?
I said, were you really
trying to kill yourself?
TREATMENT NOTES
WRITE ABOUT HOW YOU FEEL RIGHT NOW
I WANT TO KILL MYSELF
Don't cry.
Ms. Sook.
I'm sorry.
What's gotten into you?
Are you trying to drive me crazy?
Do you think you can make me give up?
No way.
I will never live my life like this again!
Die? Why would I die?
I'm going to live past 100.
And don't sell this house. I tried so hard
to buy this house. Don't sell it.
Don't even try to hold me back
with this wretched house.
I'm not holding you back, so don't worry.
You remember when you were 22 years old?
Do you remember how you neglected our kids
to have an affair
and raise the other child?
Do you remember that?
You didn't have work,
but you didn't come home.
Your salary got cut in half.
Calls were hung up on me,
but you answered them.
You ran out night and day.
Why can't you remember that?
I hate it!
I hate it so much!
How did you hold it back all this time?
How could you bring yourself
to look at my face?
I've been holding back
because of the kids.
I…
I was done a long time ago.
All right.
I will get out of this house
and never show myself
in front of you again,
so you live here.
I promise…
I will never show myself to you…
again.
Right when I thought I fell in love,
I heard another sound
that knocked on my heart.
And I badly wished for that sound
wasn't you.
You were the only one I could tell.
I made a mistake with the new vice CEO.
I think I fell for Mr. Playboy first.
We always go to his house.
We were actually trying
not to leave a trace.
I saw his girlfriend's photo.
If you decided to meet him,
then meet him alone.
Why bring in a woman who's not even there
and make it look like the three
of you are meeting?
Even if I told you so many things,
I really wished that
you wouldn't get to see this moment, ever.
Why do you feel like crap?
Who said I feel like crap?
Look at you.
You eat super fast whenever
you're upset or you feel like crap.
Did you go to Goheung…
just with Ji-woo's oldest sister?
Without Eun-hee?
I mean, didn't Ms. Eun-hee go with you?
Why are you curious about that?
Even an idiot can tell.
I can tell that you are pretending.
I'm curious because I like you.
Yoon Seo-young.
You told my mom you'd be responsible
for me. I heard everything.
How can you interpret it like that?
You know that's not what I meant.
It does.
No one believed me, but you did.
Even my mom thinks I turned
my distinguished ex-boyfriend
into a rapist because I got dumped by him.
That's not true.
Your mother totally believes you.
She doesn't believe me.
She locked me up,
so I would never report him.
She made a mistake
but it was to protect you.
Protect me?
I've heard that far too many times.
I needed someone
who would believe me at the time.
That was you.
I still believe you
and will always be on your side.
That's why I totally fell for you.
Take care of me.
If this goes on, you can't work with me.
I won't work with you.
Right?
Sorry, telling you to take
responsibility was too much.
I'll get going for now.
See you tomorrow.
Hi, I'm Im Geon-joo.
Hi, I'm Kim Eun-joo.
Ms. Kim Eun-joo here is the eldest sister,
and I'm Kim Ji-woo, the youngest.
I see. I'm Im Geon-joo.
Right.
I'll get going now.
I should've called first,
though it's my sister's house.
-It's okay.
-Eun-joo, that's not what this is.
Ji-woo, see you next time.
Okay.
-See you tomorrow.
-Okay, bye.
Bye.
You said all of your romance cells died.
But that was so sweet.
"See you tomorrow."
Gosh, you cute little boy.
I'm so happy to see you.
Go make her sit.
She's looking for something to criticize.
Why did you go to Goheung?
-Me?
-You all went.
Eun-joo, you, and Chan-hyuk.
It's an odd group.
Why are you whispering, you punk?
You're making my ear rot.
I know.
-I know everything.
-What do you know?
I know that
you three went to Goheung together.
The 20 million won deposit
is all you have at your age?
How can you live
after you pay your rent every month?
-Do you have any debt?
-I have installment savings,
and I pay a national pension
as a citizen of Korea.
No need to worry.
If I can't handle it…
I'll go back to Mom and Dad's house.
If so,
you should try to stop Mom and Dad
from graduating from marriage.
It seems the house is going to sell.
If they sell the house at their age,
they can't afford another.
At least stop them from selling the house.
Me?
Do you think Mom would listen to me?
You tell her. She always listens to you.
Why?
You can't say negative things to Mom
because you're always on her side?
So you know.
Here we go again.
I'm leaving.
This is the moment to catch a taxi.
You brat! Just run.
When I was your age,
I memorized the schedules
for the last subway.
When it was time even when I was drunk,
I levitated into the air and got on
the subway. Don't give it to him.
-You're spoiling him.
-Thank you.
-Hey!
-Bye.
Kim Ji-woo!
That little… Damn it.
Was that man from earlier
the one you made a mistake with?
A mistake?
Did that bastard Chan-pal tell you?
You got drunk and told me,
crying like a baby.
Oh.
You're not in a situation
to worry about me.
If you work together,
then separate romance and business.
Don't depend on him.
Don't say, "Do this and that for me."
Date him independently.
Okay.
By the way, what made you
come to my house all of a sudden?
About Tae-hyung…
About the issue between him and me.
Don't act like you know it.
It may take some time.
Well, I can't really
do anything about it.
Chan-hyuk told me
to call him
whenever I need someone to talk to.
If you let me borrow your friend,
I will gratefully use him
whenever I need him.
You should at least say
thank you to Chan-hyuk
for bringing him to that faraway place.
Even friends have to be polite
to each other.
Okay.
Have a safe trip back.
The caller cannot be reached…
CHAN-PAL
Call me please, I'm begging you.
Hi, Kim Eun-hee.
Look at you.
Why did you change your style
all of a sudden?
Are you back to being
a rich family's daughter?
It's not really a change.
I just put on
whatever I found in my closet.
These clothes are obviously new.
Why are you lying?
I reject the interview.
Take photos instead.
-Now, my hip…
-Hi.
Goodness! That scared me.
You didn't seem to know I was watching.
Please continue.
Okay, again.
Ta-da! Now, the foot.
Chan-hyuk, are you ignoring
Eun-hee's calls?
Do you think I'm in a situation
to answer the phone?
Sorry.
Eun-hee keeps calling me
because you're not answering her calls.
Let's get ready. We might be late.
I got scared again
because your truck was here
but I couldn't find you.
Why are you looking at me
with such a sad face?
I left my house.
What?
Slept in the truck again?
I told you to play dumb.
To be frank, it seems like
you're still not completely sane.
Right?
So you need to tell me the truth.
What?
Was I a lunatic?
What are you talking about?
Why would I go there
at night if I wasn't insane?
A psychiatrist's clinic contacted me.
It seemed like I went regularly.
And Ms. Sook said…
I tried to kill myself.
Good grief…
I deserve to die, actually.
She said I had an affair and a kid.
You know about it, don’t you?
Tell me.
All right,
To be honest, you were kind of sneaky.
You didn’t tell me much about you,
while I was telling you everything.
I thought that was a bit unfair.
Don't do that. I really hate that.
To be honest, I haven't
known you for decades.
You were always stuck in the truck
and were writing in a diary.
Read that diary.
A diary?
BANK TRANSACTIONS
THE BRIDGES OF MADISON COUNTY
SANG-SIK, MAKE SURE
YOU CHEW YOUR FOOD WELL
I'M TOO SHY TO SAY IT IN PERSON.
I LOVE YOU.
Please wait.
I'll get you the soup.
Mr. Kim Sang-sik,
make sure you chew your food well.
I'm too shy to say it, so I'm writing it.
I love you.
My goodness.
I didn't know he'd still remember that.
But amazingly enough,
as he recited the letter,
I remembered it, too.
Why was it so difficult
to say "I love you" and end up
being unable to do it?
What do you think of her husband,
who still remembers
the letter she threw away
in the middle of writing it until now?
Thank you.
I'll tell the kids.
Please be well.
The kids are not even interested in us.
You must be busy.
I'm going into a meeting.
Look how pathetic I am.
Why don't you go in first?
We might end up going in together.
That was my intention.
Sure.
We've become estranged these days.
Let's hang out on the weekend.
Do you only have me
to hang out with when you look this good?
I'm giving up a lot to hang out with you.
Oh, my.
Now, before we start the meeting,
if you have any proposals for me to check,
e-mail them to me, please.
I won't be coming here anymore.
I couldn't think of anyplace else.
I can give you only ten minutes.
I'm sorry I couldn't tell you.
I thought it'd be better
if Dr. Yoon told you first.
Your lover stole your money and left you,
and it seems like Dr. Yoon
is responsible for it.
Then should I say sorry, too?
You sound so cold.
When there's someone who thinks
there's no gay person around him or her…
Do you know the reason?
It means he or she isn't trustworthy
enough to tell secrets to.
Should I repent for not being trustworthy?
Do you think you're always the victim?
We have to understand you
because you're a minority?
I don't even ask to be understood.
You must be busy.
You can go now.
You made that money working
all day long and lost it,
why not take the money from Tae-hyung?
You came to this neighborhood
for the money.
Will I care about nothing but
money like you two, after 10 years?
Eun-joo.
Have you ever been in love?
I was curious about the one
he chose by abandoning me.
But he was a married bastard,
deceiving everyone around him.
Dad!
It's so wide and high.
The steering wheel is as big as you are.
Dad.
When you said your memories came back,
did Mom ask you about what happened
in the mountain?
We both didn't say much about it.
Ji-woo only thinks
it was a hiking accident.
So we can't talk about it
when we go to Eun-joo's house
later today.
Dad.
Promise me…
that you'll never do that again.
It was just an accident.
That's why I'm here right now.
It will never happen again.
Okay?
Okay.
I have a favor to ask you, Eun-hee.
Yes, ask your second daughter for favors.
The photo in the living room.
The photo of me and Ms. Sook.
Yes.
I'd like you to bring it, please.
Dad, are you…
I'll explain when we get together later.
I'm sure Ms. Sook hates it.
I want to take care of it.
Please bring…
the photo.
Okay.
Thank you.
"Ms. Sook"?
Still?
Dad.
Tell me about the day you took that photo.
That day…
Dad, you're still 22 years old, right?
That day was October 13, 1982.
Yes.
That photo is much older than I am.
That was the day
I proposed to your mother.
I did this at the coffee shop.
People looked at us,
so Ms. Sook quickly took the ring.
Ms. Sook is shy, you know.
That coffee shop
was the best one at the time.
It played good songs too.
It played Cho Yong-pil's songs.
Dad.
On that day,
I held Ms. Sook's hand…
for the first time.
It was so warm.
Dad.
Are your memories really back?
Yes.
Dad, this is the company I work at.
-Really? It's nice.
-Goodbye.
-Get home safe.
-Okay.
-It's nice.
-It is, isn't it?
This is my father…
-My Dad.
-Hi.
-Dad, this is the vice CEO.
-I'm Im Geon-joo.
Nice to meet you.
You get to meet all of my family.
-Please look after her.
-Don't worry.
Dad, I'll go get my car.
Okay.
Okay, then…
Please take a look around.
Okay.
Patent Attorney Kim?
Hi.
I heard you started working again.
Nice to see you.
I heard you're freelancing.
Yes, I only work
with pharmaceutical companies.
You were the best in taking care of
troublesome cases, right?
Not staying a freelancer forever, right?
Come join us.
We'll treat you as a partner.
Look at me.
The CEO goes to KIPO herself.
So you got calls
from a few places already.
Did Lee Oh-jang call you, too?
-Yes.
-Don't go there.
Mr. Oh from LeeOhJang is gay.
He wore a flower-patterned suit to KIPO.
Does he have to show it?
Come to our office
and check out the atmosphere.
Come and see it, okay?
It feels like everyone
is laughing and talking
behind your back, right?
Don't act like you know everything,
like you're wise and not greedy.
Your face and the way
you talk make me sick.
You…
What did you think when I was
trying so hard to get pregnant?
I detested you.
It was detesting to see
you try so hard to have a family
when you hated them.
You hated your family. But ours is okay?
Did you need an elevation
of social status?
You're a snob.
EUN-JOO
TAE-HYUNG
Hello?
It's me.
Yes.
Forget what I said.
I think I was harsh on purpose.
Hello?
Come and wrap things up.
The clinic…
and us…
Let's wrap everything up.
Let's be friends.
You told me what it means
to be a friend.
Guess which person is referred to as
"Someone who carries your sadness
on his or her back"
in Native American.
A parent?
No.
I don't think they can do that.
It's a friend.
That's how Native Americans
define friends.
Would there really be a friend
who carries my sadness
on his or her back?
You.
TAE-HYUNG
You carry my sadness on your back.
I'll carry your sadness on my back.
Really? This is your first time
coming to this house?
Want to help Eun-joo,
or hang out with Dad?
Dad, when you're here…
You have to go see the terrace.
Really?
Is it true that this is Dad's first time
coming to your house?
I invited him a few times,
but he refused, saying he's busy.
Then he should've never come at all.
No, you stay here.
Don't leave this house. Make it yours.
Dad. Ji-woo.
Time to eat.
Go ahead, Dad.
Okay.
My eldest daughter,
you and I have the same taste in food,
and we have the same eyes.
You're smart, and you can do anything.
Hey.
What's wrong?
You must be so happy.
But then, why don't Ji-woo
and I have double eyelids?
Does that mean we're not your kids?
I get super thick double eyelids
when I'm tired.
Really? Have you ever been tired
in your entire life?
I've never seen
any double eyelids on your eyes.
Is your husband eating dinner out?
He said he was going to be
very late, so I didn't tell him.
Dad, what's your dream?
My dream?
Eating with my eldest daughter,
second daughter,
and youngest like this often.
That's my dream.
Come on, something besides that.
You were 22 years old.
I'm asking
what your dream was at the time.
Oh.
Dream.
My dream…
I never told this to anyone, but…
Competing in the Campus Song Festival.
Even if you are good
at playing the guitar,
playing the harmonica, or singing,
you can't compete
if you aren't in college.
It was a dream. A far-away dream.
So that's why you always listened
to Campus Song Festival songs.
Dad, then can you play the guitar
and the harmonica too?
No, what's the point of learning
when I'm not in college?
Your mother must be eating alone again.
Shall I call her?
No.
I asked you to gather
so I can tell you about it.
I…
left the house.
Don't make such faces.
It's nothing, really.
I'm undereducated and ignorant
compared to you kids,
so I don't know how to put this, but…
Nothing is going to change.
I'll be the only one missing.
So, Ji-woo,
take care of your mother
and listen to her.
The same goes for you two, okay?
I saw your purse and manuscript
on your desk, so I waited.
Glad to see me?
I am glad to see you.
But…
I really have to work.
Tomorrow's my day off,
so I'll work until late.
Yes, relax and work. I'll work, too.
Don't feel burdened.
All right.
Did your father leave?
Yes, there was a place
to park his truck here.
Your father had palms as hard as a rock.
It reminded me of my father.
Now I only have to meet
your mother, right?
Go and do your work.
Okay.
There were two bouquets on that day.
At the wedding photographers
get to see and hear a lot of things.
CHAN-PAL
All right.
Tell me
why you were looking
at your phone all day.
I'll do the counseling.
You always say that.
Well…
My friend is totally ignoring
my texts and calls.
So you did something wrong?
Why do you think so?
I can feel it from how you say it.
"My friend is totally ignoring me,
but I cannot give up."
"Why? Because I did something wrong."
Do you want to apologize?
I don't think it requires an apology.
Your friend gets to decide on that.
Don't just call your friend,
but go visit them to show some effort.
The counseling is over.
Now, as a man.
I don't want to be a man
who's jealous of your friend.
So,
apologize to him and come to me.
Okay, I will.
Whatever.
Who is it?
It's me, Ji-woo.
Hey.
What time is it?
I want this place to be my room,
not my office, until 8:00 a.m.
I don’t like employees
who come to work too early.
I don't like companies
where I have to come to work on weekends.
If you're tired, get more sleep.
What's going on with you?
Chan-hyuk,
I thought about it all night long.
You and I should act like
we don't know Eun-joo's secret.
We've been doing that.
But why all of a sudden?
Our father summoned us
to Eun-joo's house yesterday.
Why all of a sudden?
My Mom and Dad graduated from marriage.
Goodness.
Let's skip that part for now.
Dad was looking at Eun-joo during dinner,
with so much love in his eyes and said,
"My eldest daughter and I
have the same taste in food,
and we have the same eyes."
He was talking like he's her real father.
You should've seen his eyes.
I could see hearts
popping out of his eyes.
It was genuine.
Yes.
The biological DNA provider
isn't that important.
Both of us should forget about it.
What if you heard it wrong?
Yes, I heard it wrong.
Let's wrap it up that way, Chan-hyuk.
-Chan-hyuk.
-What now?
Why do you keep ignoring Eun-hee's calls?
She's harassing me.
The timing isn't right, that's all.
You're ignoring her calls
after the trip to Goheung.
Why did the three of you go to Goheung?
You three went,
and you came back with Eun-joo,
leaving Eun-hee there?
Long ago, you could get punished
for saying the Earth is round.
-All of a sudden?
-Also,
tobacco was believed to be healthy.
Chan-hyuk, be serious.
The truth will eventually
be revealed after some time.
For now, all three of us
will not give you an answer.
And when that's the case
the polite thing to do is to wait
without asking any more questions.
I see.
Okay, I won’t ask anymore.
You really are
the best.
I should've let the world know about it.
It's so sad I couldn't do that.
Eun-hee has a bad taste in men.
I want a guy like you
to be my brother-in-law
-and have a drink with--
-Hey.
What about my opinion?
You don't care at all?
Now, when we film the unboxing,
we need to follow the products.
Divide the screen into three sections
and make sure it's two-thirds filled up.
Okay.
-Okay, ready?
-Yes.
-Now, please begin.
-Okay.
-How's my no makeup face?
-It's pretty.
I mean, it's okay.
EUN-HEE
-CEO, where are you going?
-Don’t make sudden sounds.
Edit it out.
CEO, where are you going?
I'm going to buy lunch and bring it to go.
I'll choose the menu.
Your company must be doing well.
You're busy on weekends too.
That's why I told them I'm getting lunch
for the employees working on the weekends.
You know it's annoying
when the food comes late, right?
What do you want?
This place must have good food.
They have a lot of to-go orders.
Makes me want to drink.
Get to the point.
I really want to know
why you're ignoring my calls and texts.
Because I'm tired.
Are you tired because of work,
something else,
or me?
Of course, it's you.
What's with the "of course" added to it?
They say you should give up
if your heart doesn't flutter.
-Are you treating me like an object?
-It's a metaphor.
The point of that expression
is about getting rid of objects or clothes
you didn’t use for more than a year.
We cut ties for so many years, remember?
It's possible for us to curse and yell,
whenever we feel bad again,
and cut ties again as well.
Once is difficult.
It's easier the next time.
I don’t want to waste
my energy on a relationship
that is so volatile.
But you know, my friend,
think outside the box.
You've been totally ignoring
my calls and texts,
but I didn't get angry.
I'm being really careful and modest.
I came here myself.
Isn't that because you thought
you've been overreacting these days
and repented, right?
Right. I repent my actions very well.
And do you know why I repented so quickly?
It means I don't want
that relationship in which
I can cut ties with you again.
I'm going to keep
seeing you, contacting you,
and be on good terms with you, my friend.
Sir, here's your order
of four hangover soups to go.
Anyway, let's not contact
each other for a while.
For a while?
You asked me to take care of Eun-joo.
It seems that you knowing about it
makes her uncomfortable.
If she needs someone,
she said she's going to contact me,
so let's do that
until Eun-joo settles things down.
Okay, for a while then.
I won't ask either, for a while.
Please take care of
my sister.
By the way, my brother doesn't like
hangover soup.
You bastard who has no respect
for your employees.
Bye.
Are you taking your car out?
-Mom.
-Oh, my goodness.
What brings you here without calling?
Have you eaten?
You asked Eun-hee to call me.
I was thinking about getting
your father checked up one more time,
but since his memories are back,
there's no need to.
It's dusty.
Go inside.
Did Tae-hyung get better?
What?
I heard he's not well.
Yes, he's fine.
Is something going on?
You look terrible.
And you got skinnier.
What if
you're ill?
-Did you go see a doctor?
-No.
That's not what it is.
By the way, you came here
on the day Tae-hyung's clinic
is closing early…
I heard from Dad.
Don't sell the house.
Ji-woo isn't capable of
moving out, either.
All right.
Have you eaten lunch?
I'm hungry. Want to eat with me?
Mom, why didn't you thank me
even once at the time?
What?
When I was working as a temporary teacher
and was tutoring on weekends.
Each day was so long and tiring,
but when I realized it,
it'd been a month already,
and when I realized it
a season had passed.
I don't remember
how I lived my life at the time.
I wasted my days in my twenties like that.
Why are you suddenly…
Why…
Why are you bringing that up?
I'm just curious.
"My daughter, you're doing so much."
"Thank you, my daughter."
I'm asking why you never
said those things to me.
On the day I met Tae-hyung's mother
for the first time,
she held my hand
and thanked me for being
part of her family.
I've been curious since then.
About why you never said that to me.
You were…
particularly cold
to me and Dad.
I never knew
that you were
bottling that up until now.
Yes.
It's all my fault.
I want an answer.
I don't want to blame anyone.
I just want to know why.
Because…
it's too easy to say
so I couldn't say it.
When I saw girls your age
wearing makeup, and pretty clothes,
and walking on the street,
it broke my heart.
At that time, you didn't talk,
smile, or laugh.
You never took a taxi
when you were going to work early
or working late.
You only wore cheap clothes,
and your shoes were worn out.
How could I say thank you?
That's so shameless.
How could I say I'm sorry?
When I couldn't do anything for you.
What use…
do words have
when they're just words?
Mom.
I have something to tell you.
Yes.
Before I got married,
Dad came to my workplace.
-Happy birthday dear Yu-jeong
-Happy birthday to you
Blow out the candles.
Did you make a wish?
JUNE 13, EUN-JOO'S BIRTHDAY
I never cared about her birthday, anyway.
October 13, 1982.
That was the day
I proposed to your mother.
Eun-joo was in Mom's womb at the time.
On that day, I held Miss Sook's hand
for the first time.
Anxiety knocks on my heart again.
November 14…
December 14…
January,
February, March, April, May…
June.
Ms. Kim Eun-hee?
Why tell me the secret
between you two after all this time?
Do you know what I regret?
You wanted to be friends.
Just live here as a friend.
Coy, but not too much.
Should I gift it to you?
Chan-hyuk ignored your calls.
That's a signal
telling you to keep boundaries.
She's your friend, but she knows nothing.
I liked her because I knew nothing.
Young-sik? Why are you looking for him?
He said this was the day
he held your hand for the first time.
I get it now.
Subtitle translation by: Hae-lim Lee
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/ah6xf
Help other users to choose the best subtitles