JEFF PROBST: In just one
week, 16 strangers begin the
adventure of a lifetime when
Survivor: Africa premieres.
Tonight, meet the new Survivors,
see clips from their audition
videos, and catch an exclusive
preview of the first episode.
Also, hear from the people who
know firsthand what this unique
experience is like: the men and
women of Survivor I and II.
They talk straight about their
time on the island and in the
outback, they share their
feelings about each other, and
reveal their personal secrets
for playing the game.
The lesson to new Survivors
is: this game is not about
building huts and catching fish.
It's a game of people playing
against people.
PROBST: All this tonight on
Survivor: Countdown to Africa.
♪ ♪
PROBST: Hello and welcome to
Watch any video online with Open-SUBTITLES
Free Browser extension: osdb.link/ext
Survivor: Countdown to Africa.
Next week, 16 Americans will
learn what it takes to outwit,
outplay, and outlast the
competition in the heart of
Africa.
In the next hour, you'll meet
each of them and see excerpts
from the audition tapes that got
them selected.
Tonight, we offer you an
insiders' guide to Survivor: how
to watch, whom to watch, and
what to watch for, with some
help from the people who know
best that the battle begins...
the very first moment.
You are witnessing 16 Americans
begin an adventure that will
forever change their lives.
I thought I had survival skills.
That counted for nothing.
Don't get on anybody's nerves.
Don't piss anybody off.
Strategy happens the moment
we got off that plane.
You don't need a leader.
And then again you don't want
to be too much of a weak link.
The leaders are the targets.
Here's what we plan on doing.
High tide is that line right
there.
See that line?
Actually, before we build the
shelter, just knock that whole
branch off.
What's the first thing we
need to do?
Let's see what we got first,
before we make any decisions.
Let's see what we got.
Are you guys all done talking?
I think we're off to a bad
start.
This is not a very good move.
This is not how to conduct
yourself on the first day after
a three-hour swim ashore.
Yeah, after seeing Richard up
a tree originally, I couldn't
imagine him surviving this
episode.
Rich is just sitting in the
tree, number one, trying to tell
everybody to talk.
I'm looking up at the tree,
like, "What the hell are you
doing up there?
You should be down here talking
to us."
And what's the point?
He's so separate, and he's up
in the tree and acting so
condescending.
To me, the very wrong way to go
about it.
I'm good to go, survival-wise.
I've got the million-dollar
check written already.
It's that kind of cocky attitude
that makes people really hate
your guts.
Richard really didn't know
what he was talking about.
Anybody could have won the
million at that point.
Richard's doing what he only
knows what to do: sit on his ass
and talk.
Big mouth.
(chuckles)
In my head at the time, all I
thought when I was walking away:
"He's just a lazy fat ass."
Action, man.
Action, Richard.
You don't want to act ahead.
Richard's a very smart man.
I don't think he was really
concerned if, at that point, if
people liked him or not.
He knew he had something to
offer.
He did play a masterful game,
but there was also other factors
involved.
I feel as if luck played a role
in Richard winning.
I can't play armchair
Survivor and say he did the
wrong thing, 'cause he ended up
winning.
You can't just go sit in a tree
now.
If Richard was sitting in a tree
on Survivor II, trust me, he
would have been made short order
of that day.
We need five more of these.
I didn't have any conscious
strategy, other than I knew when
I hit the island that-that I
wanted to build a shelter.
What you'll notice is that
there are people that try and do
things on their own.
There will be people that will
try to be the go-to guy.
I'm gonna keep working.
B.B. builds buildings for a
living, and he built a great
building, but it was in the
wrong location.
If you're a fisherman, that's
your best asset.
Check that out.
If you're a chef or a cook,
that's your best asset.
It is so good!
But you need to be good at it
out there.
That way people want to keep you
around.
You tell me what you're doing
here, and I'll help you.
I promise you, I'll do it quick.
That's the right way to do
it, but we won't have near
enough line.
Anyway, don't stop now.
B.B. probably did work harder
than anybody else, uh...
but I think he was in too much
of a hurry.
We're okay, but none of the
others are down here helping
carry stuff.
I don't think he likes me much.
You can't have lazy people.
You know, you can't do what
you normally do at home out in a
new environment with strangers.
I got to have this
positioned right.
He's used to having people
working underneath him.
He's used to being the one in
charge.
But when you come to the island,
the outback, Africa, you leave
all that behind.
B.B. thought that he could
just work, work, work, work,
work.
You know, I asked Colleen to
straighten this out for me, and
here it is.
It's the only thing she had to
do today.
He had to realize this isn't
corporate world, you know,
you're not our boss.
You're all on a level playing
ground.
You can't just sit here and
tell me what to do and I'm going
to do it, because if I say no,
what are you going to do, fire
me?
You've cut it four times and
it's still too short, right?
Shh...
B.B. gave us enough reason to
vote him out by being bossy and
overbearing.
But I think I was caught up
in my own ego and my own
determination to get this thing
built, and I think I sort of
lost sight of the objective.
B.B. was an ass.
I made a lot of mistakes.
PROBST: B.B., the tribe has
spoken.
First impressions in this
game are everything.
You don't want to separate
yourself at all from your group.
Staying off the radar is the
only way to survive.
If you take a stand as a
leader right off the bat and
people don't like you, you're
screwed.
We got enough rocks here, too.
We could build a pretty decent
shelter just using rocks.
You know, Richard Hatch in
the first Survivor was the
"leader," and I thought coming
into this second one, anybody
that set themselves up to follow
in his footsteps was an instant
target.
It was stupid to do.
Let's just stop for one
second and look at the map and
look at the compass.
See, if we're going southwest,
how are we going to hit the dry
creek bed?
Because that's north!
There's a time to listen,
there's a time to keep your
mouth shut, and there's a time
to talk out there.
She made it very obvious that
she was going to try to take
control and tell people what to
do, and we hadn't even spoken to
each other yet.
She offered herself up.
Debb needed to go immediately.
One individual in the group
is... ordering everybody around.
In the green hat right here,
can you help her get one side of
this undone?
I'm sitting there thinking to
myself, "Debb, you're digging
your own grave here."
And sure enough, when it came to
the first vote, she was the
first one voted off.
It's been a little cold a
couple nights here.
PROBST: The tribe has spoken.
When we come back, the
importance of alliances.
But now let's meet the first
four men and women of Survivor:
Africa.
Silas Gaither, a bartender from
Germantown, Tennessee.
I'm a big family man, and I
want to support my wife and kids
totally.
If she'd like to work, she can
work, though.
I don't mean to, you know...
politically correct here.
PROBST: Carl Bilancione, a
dentist and the father of two
from Winter Springs, Florida.
I'm not your typical dentist.
Most of them are fat and bald-
headed and divorced.
Not me.
I've completed six marathons.
Survivor's easy.
PROBST: Jessie Camacho, a
deputy sheriff from Orlando,
Florida.
Why do I think I'll make the
ultimate Survivor?
I'm a Puerto Rican female... the
heat, the rice, bring it on.
I'm ready to go to work.
See ya!
PROBST: And Tom Buchanan, a
farmer and the father of one,
from Rich Valley, Virginia.
Come on, we're going to
Survivor. Woo-hoo!
Come on, doggies, here we go!
Let's hit the big show, boys!
We're gonna be a star!
PROBST: Whether it's on an
island, in the outback, or deep
in Africa, the game remains the
same: 16 strangers abandoned in
the middle of nowhere, forced to
create a new society.
To succeed, you must not only
survive the elements, but each
other.
Loudmouth, Sue.
Yeah, Sean, get some b...
Grouch, B.B.
Grouch, probably me.
Myself.
Jeff.
That's an easy one.
Jerri.
The grouch would have to be
No idea.
Trouble maker...
Jeff.
Me!
(laughs)
(monkey screeching)
Femme fatale...
Jerri.
What the hell's that?
I hate to admit it.
Femme fatale.
Jerri.
Whiner...
Richard.
Debb.
Sorry, Debb.
Backstabber, Colby.
Tina.
Colby.
Gervase.
Jeff.
Kelly.
Everyone.
(thunder crashes)
PROBST: One of the keys to
competing on Survivor is
understanding alliances: how
they form, when they shift, and
who you can trust.
You can actually win
Survivor without having a
single survival skill if you
have the best friendships.
When you're out there, you
don't have a lot of time to
figure out if this is the person
you want to be your friend.
As soon as I got on the
island, it was, like, "Okay, who
can I team up with here?"
Me and Joel pretty much wanted
to play the game the same way
and win it the same way.
It was, like, "Look, you never
vote for me and I will never
vote for you."
It was that simple, we got to
look out for each other.
Cool, it's a done deal.
The night Joel got voted off,
I cried.
PROBST: The tribe has spoken.
It just hurt so bad, because
that was the last guy on team
Gervase.
I was just in shock.
I'm, like, "What the hell am I
gonna do now?"
The bottom line is, the
people that lasted the longest
are the people that have the
best friendships or the best
alliances.
Colby and I had a very strong
bond.
My only loyalty is to Tina.
There's no other loyalty for me.
We made an alliance that it
would be he and I till the end.
I made one alliance out there
and that... one true alliance.
We're both, you know, really
hardworking.
We're both very outdoorsy.
We just got along.
I thought I could trust her all
the way to the end, because she
was a lot of fun.
She reminded me of, like, a
younger sister.
So, about day five... and I'm not
stupid... Richard approaches me
and corners me.
Okay, so here's the deal.
He gives me his rhetoric why
me and him should align, because
we're both the biggest creeps on
the island, and... and
everybody's not going to like
us, but if we team up together
and go down to the final two,
they're going to have to pick
between one of us idiots.
So I'm, like, okay, I'm going to
bull... him, so I lied my
ass off to Richard.
So then I told Kelly, I said,
"Me and you," I said, "at the
end are just going to burn
Richard's butt, the three of us
against the world."
(chuckling)
Friendships are very
superficial out there, so it's
rare that you build a friendship
that's as deep maybe as Rodger
and Elisabeth.
I think this situation
genuinely happened.
These are two wonderful people.
This is the scene where I
actually gave Elisabeth the rock
to take home to her boyfriend,
Tim.
And I found a little rock out
here about that tall, shaped
like a heart.
He said, "Here you go.
What's that look like?"
And I said, "A heart."
He said, "You take that with
you, give it to your boyfriend
when you get back."
Elisabeth always reminded me
of my daughter out there.
If somebody would have told me
that I would have went out there
and became friends, especially
with a young lady 30 years
younger than me, and best
friends, and still are best
friends, I would have probably
told them that... that they were
crazy.
It matters so much to me that
he's around, so I'm not writing
his name down. Uh-uh.
I will not spell that man's
name.
I didn't come away with the
$1 million.
Uh, I did come away with a
friend for life.
And if I had to choose between
the two, I think I would...
I would take the-the
friendship over the... over the
money.
This served them well.
It definitely did.
The two good people came
together, and they were a power
of one.
There are bound to be fights
in this game.
I mean, you almost can't avoid
them.
All right, who did it?
Who did it?!
Who counted that chicken before
it hatched?!
I'm tired of you and the...
chicken!
(rooster crows)
When it comes to the fighting
thing...
(bell clangs)
every day there's something
that's going to get to you.
Let go of the chicken thing.
It was 110 during the day.
You're hot, you're cold, you're
tired, you're wet.
(thunder crashes)
Do you have some kind of a
problem?
Yeah, I have a problem with
your attitude.
Oh, really?
What the hell is up your butt?
You first have to evaluate
your position in the game.
And you have to choose who
you're going to start a fight
with and who you're not.
I'm not eating mammal.
I'm not eating fowl.
We clashed from the very
beginning, but we were able to
keep a lid on it the whole time.
Right, right.
We kind of... we kind
of... we'd...
Controlled it. Right.
Bite our tongues and just
kind of be, like, okay.
I think that she and I are both
very, like, strong-willed
individuals.
That's all I was saying.
It's a good thing just to break
it up when it's...
You are the defensive one
about the chickens, not me, so
do not yell at me about the
chickens.
I am not getting emotionally
attached.
You can get as emotionally
attached as you want to.
The only reason we said it is
because we care about your
feelings since you are a part of
this tribe.
But don't jump all over me,
sweetheart.
I tried!
But you mumbled!
Look... you...
You mumbled... mumbled under
your breath.
That's it.
Uh-oh, look at Mike.
That was Jeff.
That was Mike.
I would go to Kimmi, and I
would bitch about Alicia.
And I'd go to Alicia and I'd
bitch about Kimmi.
See me walking away?
I helped instigate it.
I was so happy, I walked away
from it just thrilled,
because...
here it was on a silver platter,
exactly what I wanted, and it
was beautiful.
Jeff did it.
He's good at it.
(laughs): He manipulated
everybody.
That was totally not cool.
No I don't think that was good.
I'd like to kill that guy.
Anything that you can do to
cause trouble offers up another
situation that you can take
advantage of in some way.
Here it was.
But don't jump all over me,
sweetheart.
Don't wave your finger in my
face.
I will always wave my finger...
It's the rhythm of the head
and the finger.
That's the trick behind it.
You know? It's not enough to
shake your head, 'cause
that's... whatever.
The finger is, like, "eh."
You know, it's like your teacher
in school does that.
But the head and the finger,
that's... that's big-time.
My vote is for Kimmi.
This really should be Alicia,
but...
Things are falling apart here
at Rattana Beach.
You told me you were going to
align with us, because Colleen
told me that.
That's bull...
People change, actually,
during the game.
Is that a good thing, to change
yourself during the game?
Um, not really.
Well, I don't give a...
because I trust her more than I
trust you. Why?
I'm, like, Kelly's telling
the other team that she's not on
the alliance.
That's bull...
I've been your friend since day
one.
Nope. I'm going fishing.
So now all of a sudden, I'm
two-faced and I... her when
she had approached me and said,
"Hey, Rich and I have formed an
alliance."
It's just, she was accusing me
of doing something that she
herself had done.
You know what I mean?
Like, I just wanted to talk to
her.
I just wanted to talk to her and
clear the air.
That's bull...
Will you talk to me?
No.
I don't have to.
So then I was, like, my friend's
gone, I'm all alone in this
game, and I don't give a...
no more.
So I blew Kelly off.
That little tiff between
Kelly and Sue has been coming
and plays to my advantage.
Absolutely.
Divide and conquer.
(laughs)
It's inevitable that a fight
like this is going to break out
in an alliance.
I mean, every alliance has to
fracture, and that's just the
nature of the game... you play
with fire, you get burned.
PROBST: The tribe has spoken.
Sue, it's time for you to go.
Coming up, the importance of
food, and how fate can change
the game.
Oh, my God!
PROBST: But first, our next
four Survivors.
Clarence Black, a high school
basketball coach from Detroit,
Michigan.
Hours in the gym.
Hours on the court.
Cardiovascular.
Pumping iron.
All-state number one.
PROBST: Teresa Cooper, a
flight attendant and the mother
of two from Jackson, Georgia.
I've got a lot of endurance,
a lot of skills, a lot of
energy.
This is my lucky bullet.
So I'm getting my fire going.
Start rubbing those sticks
together.
PROBST: Kelly Goldsmith, a
behavioral research analyst from
Rancho Santa Fe, California.
This is how much I love
Survivor: I'll wear this
asinine outfit to a bar on a
Sunday night, all for the love
of the show.
PROBST: And Frank Garrison, a
telephone technician and the
father of two with a third on
the way, from Odessa, New York.
I understand you're putting
together a series looking for
some Survivors to be on an
adventure.
Well, I'm just the man you want.
(roars)
PROBST: Anytime you put 16
men and women together in the
wilderness, one topic's sure to
come up.
In real life, people use sex
as a weapon.
Why not translate that to out
there?
I definitely came into the
game thinking to myself that
there might be the option as a
strategy to befriend someone of
the male species.
(laughs): And then... in walks
Colby.
I had a discussion with Colby
regarding chocolate and how
chocolate releases the same
endorphins that sex does.
Peppermint patty!
This fantasy I have about
chocolate and sex definitely
involves him.
Hot fudge dripping all over the
top!
They're driving me nuts.
I can't take it anymore!
I may be a lot of things, but
I ain't no Hershey bar.
(laughs)
It's all about sex when we go
off.
So we like to play together,
not as a romantic situation.
Romance, you know, Jerri and
Colby played a little game back
and forth with one another,
but nothing happened.
And, you know, you're not
bathing, you're not brushing
your teeth.
It's just the thought of getting
intimate like that with somebody
who's nasty and laying in dirt.
It ain't cute.
PROBST: From the beginning to
the end of the Survivor
experience, food plays a huge
role.
Sometimes it's a matter of what
you're willing to eat, sometimes
it's what you can find to eat,
but ultimately, it's how tough
you are when there's almost
nothing to eat.
Survivor: Africa, here's my
advice to you: tell yourself in
the beginning, "I'm going to be
eating things I don't want to
eat.
I'm going to have to be eating
things that I don't normally
think of as food."
It depends on what you got to
eat.
If it's an eyeball, I think I'd
try swallowing it.
I can't see chewing an eyeball.
(laughs)
(cheers, applause, whooping)
I'm not doing it.
That's the only thing going
through my head is, "I'm not
doing this."
I knew everybody on my team
was gonna eat this except for
me, so I had to do it, you know?
And you didn't want to let your
team down.
This is for immunity, so this is
huge right now, and, uh...
I just did it, you know?
And I can't believe I did now.
I mean...
(laughs): I can't believe I just
did that.
I would eat a bucket of bugs
before I'd eat anything that the
Survivor II people ate.
This is horrible.
This is, like, the worst thing
in the whole world, because I
told my tribe mates I would eat
anything except the cow brain.
And wouldn't you know it.
(disgusted groans, yells)
The brain.
Got flies all over it.
If you think it's disgusting,
you got to weigh... weigh it
against getting kicked off the
island.
You got to eat it.
Can't do it.
Sorry.
This was very hard knowing
that you're disappointing
everybody.
Kimmi made a choice, and that
choice you could say cost her a
million dollars.
PROBST: It's time for you to
go.
There's a lot of factors
involved in this game that I
just did not...
expect or... plan for.
You know, the starvation aspect
of it was just horrifying.
I mean, every day I'm
getting weaker instead of
stronger, and that's a bad
thing.
You were just sapped of all
of your energy.
I mean, you have, you can't even
row the raft anymore.
You can't walk up hills anymore.
You know, we're starving.
We haven't eaten in 24 hours and
we had a lot to do and no
energy, none.
Everyone here was just in slow
motion.
If we don't catch our food,
we won't be eating any food.
There's a pig in the water.
A pig?
Yeah.
There is a pig, right over
there!
Oh, God, Mike's going with the
knife.
If you are the food gatherer,
you become quite important.
This is a game called
Survivor, and we're all
starving, and believe you me, if
that pig had gotten anywhere
near me when I was out there, I
would have killed it with my
bare hands.
I wouldn't have even needed a
knife.
It's good, right?
I feel better about my
position now that I've made this
kill.
I think my position in the tribe
has come up a few levels, and...
it's a good feeling.
You just put that on your face?
Yeah, he did, just like that.
We're gonna get strong now.
That was part of the reason
why we kept winning all those
challenges, because we kept
eating.
We heard a rumor that the
other team caught fish with
their spear.
And that does worry me a
little bit, because they are
going to be eating some protein.
We did a competition where
they won a spear, so we knew
they had to be catching
something.
(laughter, excited shouting)
Watch the spear.
My position with the tribe,
it's probably going to increase
as a result of this.
I could eat rice for 17 more
days.
I could eat rice the whole time,
but they're loving the fish and
it seems to make people feel
great.
And I squeeze every ounce of
credit out of it that I can.
(laughs)
They're pretty damn tasty.
Thank you.
You just need to keep me and
I'll provide you with all the
fish you need.
Did that play a role in
Richard staying with us for a
long time?
Absolutely.
And when we would see them at
the next competition, they'd
brag about it.
"We're eating fish."
You know, it's psychological
now.
They're getting into our heads.
"We're eating fish.
What are you guys eating?"
"Uh, rats."
I really didn't want to eat
the rats.
You get, like, 52 grams of
protein off of a ounce of rat.
This is some of the best
stuff... (laughing)
I ever had in my life.
The people on Survivor:
Africa are going to find out,
if you see a tribe figuring out
how to catch food and one tribe
not, you are going to see an
unbelievable advantage both
mentally and physically.
The only way to win this game
is to have a lot of luck.
You know, luck has got to be
smiling upon you that day,
because anything can happen.
Fate plays a big part, luck
plays a big part, you know,
and...
the gods that be can vote you
off, too.
(Mike yells)
Get some water.
You okay?
(yells) >> Oh, my God!
He's burnt, he's burnt pretty
bad, Jerri.
Here's some water.
Get in the water.
The secret to winning this
game is to physically not hurt
yourself so you have to be taken
out.
He passed out and fell in the
fire.
He passed out in the fire.
Stay in the water, stay in
the water.
Oh, my God!
Do you want me to come in
with you, Mike, and swim with
you?
You passed out?
I was blowing on the fire and
the smoke went right in my face,
and I inhaled it...
and I passed out.
(groaning)
Look at these things.
Oh, God. Oh, my God.
Keep your hands in the water.
I can't decide whether I
should keep trying to bend them
or not.
No don't, no, don't.
No, no, Mike, Mike.
(yelling)
Don't even look at it.
It's just going to make you feel
worse.
Was he bent over working on
the fire?
The day that this happened,
it just changed it all.
In a weird sense, I think I gave
up.
(yelling)
Fate plays a huge role in
Survivor.
It doesn't matter how great of a
player you are.
It doesn't matter if you are a
master strategist.
I have no doubt in my mind that
I would not have won had Mike
not fallen in the fire.
Just right before that we'd
been out fishing.
Mike and myself had formed an
alliance, and we had it figured
where it would be Mike and
Elisabeth and myself in the
final three.
And, of course, then Mike comes
right back to camp, and within
ten minutes of being back in
camp he falls in the fire.
There goes the alliance out the
door, and so that was definitely
the turning point for me
personally out there.
It goes to show you that no
matter how well that you plan
things and no matter what your
strategy is out there, you can
never, ever, ever totally be in
control of what happens to you.
I love you guys!
Love you! Bye!
PROBST: Just ahead, staying
strong when you're running on
empty.
But first, four more castaways
from Survivor: Africa.
Kim Johnson, a retired teacher,
the mother of three and
grandmother of two, from
Oyster Bay, New York.
I want to be there, I want to
kick that young butt, I want to
play the game and I want to win
the friggin' million dollars.
And I can do it.
PROBST: Brandon Quinton, a
bartender from Dallas, Texas.
I would be a great contestant.
Nobody would suspect me and I
would totally win the million
dollars.
And look around... I could
totally use it.
PROBST: Diane Ogden, a mail
carrier and the mother of two
from Lincoln, Nebraska.
You know, Diane Ogden, what
you see is what you get.
And you won't be disappointed.
I can hunt, I can cook, I can
fish.
PROBST: And Kim Powers, a
freelance marketer from
Conshohocken, Pennsylvania.
You asked if we had any body
art or tattoos, and I do.
I have a small red rose tattoo.
But you have to put me on the
show to find out where it is.
PROBST: No one comes away
from Survivor without a few
insights into what it takes to
outwit, outplay and outlast the
competition.
The secret to winning
Survivor is...
Be flexible.
The less you stand out, the
less people are noticing the
things you do.
You have to have the best
relationships.
Emotional detachment and
never giving up.
Eat a lot, and have weight to
actually lose.
Be a contributor, but not a
dominator.
(laughs): Lie.
Fake it.
Work hard.
Be low-key.
Definitely have to be in
pretty good physical condition.
Don't piss anybody off.
Don't trust anybody.
Just make sure that you're
true to yourself.
You have to be yourself.
The secret to winning
Survivor is luck.
PROBST: Okay, you've made it.
You're one of the final few.
Here's your reward.
Now that you're feeling at your
very worst, you need to be at
your very best.
Ten more days, and it'll
all be over.
I'll probably never see these
people again.
That's the way I want it.
Lost some weight, I've lost
some muscle, I've lost quite a
hunk of sanity.
There is nothing that's firm
on this body anymore.
Basically, I'm a physical wreck.
Why am I here?
Why am I putting myself through
this?
God, this sucks.
33 days out on an island, and
it's just hitting the fan now.
This is really horrible.
Today is raining, last night
was raining, and I think
tomorrow it will probably be
raining.
You're sick and tired of
being sick and tired.
And at this point, you start
existing rather than living.
Living here day to day, those
are the real challenges.
The environment and the
elements here have probably been
the most dominant player in this
game.
You've got the 17th player here,
and it's the environment.
Oh, boy, here comes the flood.
Our entire campsite was
washed out.
Our rice is gone, our knives
are gone.
We were just sick.
It was just, like, how much more
can we take?
We have no food.
I know, none.
So I just walked the
riverbank and realized that on
the other side, our tin of food
was there.
And, Keith, how do you think
you're going to get it back
across?
Very dangerous thing that he
did here, very dangerous.
Keith was crossing at an
extremely dangerous point.
Keith.
Oh, my God, oh, my God...
They weren't sure he was
going to be able to make it, so
Tina just went and took an
alternate route.
If you can't bring it all,
just bring one plastic bag of it
over or something.
If there was one thing that,
for me personally, that I came
away with, is the fact that the
show is very, very real.
Okay.
Hello, family. Doing good.
I love you guys.
PROBST: Is that a little tear
in your eye?
Yes, sir, it is.
My mom just said, "Hi, baby."
One of the hardest parts
about the whole Survivor
experience is being away from
your family.
That's... that's what I
needed, right there.
There's no emotion that this
game doesn't touch in any way.
The lesson to new Survivors
is, this game of Survivor is not
about building huts and catching
fish, it's a game of people
playing against people.
PROBST: Survivors, ready.
For immunity.
Go!
This immunity challenge is
such a double-edged sword for
me.
PROBST: Immunity.
Sweet!
The moment you lose, you're
going.
PROBST: Give me a big hug!
Baby!
I knew the only way that I
was going to get to day 39 was
with this little thing around my
neck.
And that's the best thing
about this game is...
situations happen every second
of every day, but you have to be
smart enough to see them and
take advantage of it.
PROBST: Somebody who has
played this game for 41 days is
about to be voted out.
It's Keith.
Everybody wonders why Colby
kept me instead of Keith.
You know, they thought that was
a very poor strategic move on
his part.
That decision proves that
this game is not about a million
dollars.
PROBST: Keith, the tribe has
spoken.
Stupid, stupid, stupid.
If he had picked Keith to stay
with him instead of Tina, it
would have been a unanimous
vote, and Colby would be a
millionaire.
Period. End of story.
It meant more to Colby that
our friendship and him sticking
to his word... that meant more to
him than winning a million
dollars.
PROBST: It's now time for our
final vote.
Rodger, we'll start with you.
In the end of this game, the
final two standing, the one that
everyone respects the most is
the one who's going to win.
PROBST: In true Survivor
tradition, it comes down to one
final vote.
I personally felt like Colby
deserved to win and that the
whole jury would feel that way.
I never allowed myself to think,
"Well, Tina, what if?"
(cheers and applause)
And Colby's, like, "Get up,
you won!
Come on, get up, come on."
Our friendship was worth more to
him than money.
That means the world to me.
PROBST: When we come back,
the winner of Survivor: the
Australian Outback, Tina
Wesson, and a look ahead at
Survivor: Africa.
But now let's meet the rest of
our newest Survivors.
Lindsey Richter, an advertising
account executive from Portland,
Oregon.
I think I can.
I know I can. Whoo-whoo! Ha!
PROBST: Linda Spencer, a
career counselor and a mother of
two from Cambridge,
Massachusetts.
My motto: Life, the ultimate
adventure.
I think it's about ten degrees
out here.
I'm very strong-willed.
Most importantly, I get the
game.
I understand the social
politics.
PROBST: Lex Van Den Berghe, a
marketing manager and the father
of two from Santa Cruz,
California.
One, two, three, four!
If I got to go digging in the
dirt with my bare hands, looking
for a worm, I'm going to do it.
PROBST: And Ethan Zohn, a
professional soccer player from
Lexington, Massachusetts.
I love Tina.
I thought she was hot.
(shouts)
PROBST: Joining us now is
Tina Wesson, winner of
Survivor: The Australian
Outback.
Having gone through this once
yourself and having done very
well, and seeing 16 people now
ready to do it again, would you
do it again?
Absolutely not.
PROBST: No.
No, I would not.
But if I did do it again, I
would play the game differently,
even though I won.
PROBST: Why?
Well, I think that if you're
playing the game just to go have
an adventure is one thing.
But now, as the game's
progressing, people are getting
smarter, and so you have to play
the game smarter in order to
win.
PROBST: Well, we talked to
some tribe members to see what
qualities you had that allowed
you to win.
Take a look at this and then
we'll get your reaction.
Okay.
She's a soccer mom.
Who would bet on the soccer mom,
when she is faced with guys who
are literally chiseled from
stone?
(yelling)
I would not have predicted Tina
at all.
She stayed under the radar.
She hasn't, you know, thrown in
your face that she's a tough
woman, but she was.
You're going to try to cross
this current?
You're crazy.
No matter how many men were
out there with Tina, Tina had
the biggest... out there.
Tina has this very sweet,
genteel Southern mother...
You go, girl.
"Everybody just loves me, and
I just love everybody," and you
know, give me a break.
She's brilliant, that's a smart
woman, and she'll chop your head
off in a second.
Maralyn and I have bonded.
We saw her stab several
people in the back, until she
got into the alliance that she
needed to be in to carry her
through.
Tina won the game because she
was everything for everyone.
She was the mother to those that
needed a mother.
Stop it, both of you, or
you're going to time out!
She was the best friend to
someone who needed the best
friend.
She was there for emotional
support.
She was competitive, she was
manipulative, and that's what
you have to be to win this game,
period, bottom line.
But she did it with a smile on
her face.
PROBST: Your reactions... are
they accurate in assessing why
you won?
Well, to some degree, but for
me personally, Jeff, I feel like
winning Survivor takes three
things: a little bit of luck, a
little bit of logistics and
strategy, and not rocking the
boat but just getting along.
PROBST: We always say on the
show, surviving the element,
that's one part of it; surviving
the others is the bigger part.
Absolutely.
PROBST: True for you?
100% true.
PROBST: Let's talk about the
new 16.
You've had a chance to look over
their audition tapes, sort of
assess how you think they're
going to do.
Anybody stand out, maybe people
you like, don't like, who might
do well, who might not do well?
Well, I picked two people who
were game-savvy in their
audition tapes.
I thought that these guys, they
kind of know what's going on.
And that's Clarence Black.
You know, he seems like, you
know, "I'm going to say what I
need to say in order to make
friends."
You know, very strategic.
PROBST: And what's...
what's... why is that important?
Don't people see through that,
figure that out?
Not if they're good at it.
You know, take Richard Hatch,
for instance, you know?
He played everybody on that
show, and they didn't even know
it... till after it was over.
PROBST: Okay.
And that's how Clarence is to
me.
Lindsey Richter: I feel as if
she's just a very intimidating,
Alicia-type person, you know.
She comes across as very strong
physically, and she... it's like
she has this mental knowledge,
you know, "I'm going to go out
there and I'm going to kick
butt."
And she's a strong woman, and I
think she has potential to do
very well.
PROBST: Last tip before we go
for somebody watching this.
Is there anything they should
look for when they're watching
the show, a tip that might help
them figure out...?
Well one thing, Jeff, I'm
going to be looking at is I'm
going to be watching behind the
scenes.
Whenever they show people at
camp, who's sitting next to each
other, whenever they're walking
to challenge together, who's
walking next to each other?
You know, I want to know who's
really friends, who's really
bonding out there.
PROBST: Tina, thanks for your
insight.
And now, a look ahead at
Survivor: Africa.
Next week, an all-new adventure
begins when our 16 strangers are
abandoned in a landscape unlike
any the previous Survivors have
faced.
Diane was the one in charge
of the map, which I would say
was the first issue of our
tribe.
I carry mail, so I just kind
of went at my pace, which is
probably faster than most
people.
I just started my period.
No wonder I have cramps!
Excuse me, Africa, you know,
we're not down at the mall here.
Frank is like a big strong
ex-army guy.
Dude, were not all like you.
Let's do it!
(whooping)
PROBST: Temperatures are
scorching.
Water is scarce.
The water's disgusting, it's
sick.
I mean, I was filling it up.
You get water mixed with crud.
We've got to get water, like,
in the next hour, or we're just
going to be so screwed.
You don't boil your water out
here you end up with anemic
dysentery, which basically has
you puking and crapping your
guts out.
PROBST: The dangers are real.
Always keep two people awake
on the lookout for animals that
hunt at night.
(growling)
PROBST: The stakes have
definitely been raised, but the
game and the social politics
remain the same.
We're pissed off, and we now
need to deal with the situation
where we were starting to build
trust.
The trust has been broken, and
it needs to be built from square
one.
PROBST: Join us next Thursday
night when it all begins with
the premier episode of
Survivor: Africa.
We'll be right back.
PROBST: That's it for
tonight, but we hope you'll be
watching next week when 16
Americans begin a new adventure
on Survivor: Africa.
I'm Jeff Probst.
Good night.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today