The mystery
of Tansen's tanpura begins with...
the curse of the rudrabina?
"Sarod, sitar, flute,
santoor, shehnai...
sarangi, rudrabina."
Nawab Amanat Khan
had gifted each of us a disc.
Is this a clue to finding
Tansen's Raga Sanjivani?
Your singing and your work
has impressed us, Naad.
Your singing is full of mystery.
But it's lifeless.
You have to atone for the sins
of your ancestors, Naad.
Will you accept me as your student?
Of course.
Do you still have your disc?
"In the heart of Rudrapur
lies a Shiva lake
When the discs are aligned
And the notes are played
at twice the pace of time
Raga Sanjivani you shall find."
Was Salamat Uncle
Madanti's descendant?
You're hiding something
this time too.
Mom!
Can you hear me?
Tell me, Bahadur.
Were Salamat and Noor...
murdered?
No matter what it takes...
I will unravel this mystery.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
You...
You're Noor's father, Bahadur?
And all these years...
you kept it a secret?
Lolit.
You and Saaz should leave.
Dangerous...
They are dangerous.
- What if something happens to you...
- What will happen?
What do I have to lose?
Take Saaz and go away from here.
Bahadur.
Stay with us for a few days.
It's not safe for you
to stay alone.
You don't have to worry
about me.
Won't spare them.
I won't spare anyone.
- Bahadur.
- Lolit...
CURSE OF THE RUDRABINA
PART 2
Hey, where's everyone?
- Upstairs.
- Oh.
- All good?
- Yes.
Good morning.
Wow!
Everyone is here, huh.
You?
Why are you here?
To do my duty as a friend.
Lolit might not consider me his friend...
but I consider him a friend.
How can I not stand by him
in times of need?
Your skin should be displayed
in the museum
for rhinos and chameleons to see.
Hmm.
Everyone changes colour,
Pandit Ranjan Ghosh.
You defamed me.
That's how you got the National Music Award
meant for me.
- Now I know...
- Stop talking nonsense, Hemanta.
You?
- You're a disgrace to Anandagarh.
- Hmm.
There's just one problem.
You couldn't prove it in court.
You needed a better plan
to frame me.
- Hemanta.
- Yes?
I'm really not in the mood.
- Please leave.
- Right.
Lolit, I know this was a big loss for you.
But you can't break down, my friend.
Hemanta, whatever I might be...
I'm not a scoundrel like you.
Hmm.
So, I don't need your consolation.
Leave.
You still misunderstand me
for that characterless woman?
Hey, cut the crap.
Why aren't you throwing him out, Dad?
Hemanta, go away!
Just leave.
I better not see you here again.
My goodness!
So, everyone's out to insult me.
Fine.
I'll leave if you want me to.
All of you wronged Rohini.
But all the blame's on me now?
Good.
Great!
Just a minute.
Nawab Amanat Khan had given you
a disc
at your naming ceremony.
Do you have it?
Yes.
Why?
Can I take a look at it?
Just a look?
You can keep it.
I don't need it anymore.
Alap...
who do I have but you?
How can I get the disc?
It's in my bag right now.
Come with me.
He's carrying it with him!
Well, look at that.
You need my help, after all.
Hmm?
Come.
I always carry this with me.
It's a gift from the great guru,
after all.
Here you go.
Someone who can sell
his lover for money...
can never value a precious gift.
I don't buy it.
If you harm my mother again
no one will be able to save you
from me.
Hmmph!
(inaudible)
Good morning, Alap.
Hope you recognise me.
This is the Rudrabhairav.
How long will it take?
Um...
I'll do it.
I'll fix up a date.
Don't worry.
Confirm the show.
Yes.
The job will be done.
Okay.
Show? You're managing shows?
Hey, why are you lying?
I've been noticing you.
- I'm not...
- You haven't even been practising.
Don't avoid me.
Why are you lying?
Wait.
Turn off the lights.
The guards are not there.
- Come with me.
- Okay.
Come along.
Let's go.
Have you checked properly?
Wait.
Let me go first.
- Let's go.
- Come.
This way.
Hurry up.
Fast.
Where are you going?
Don't you dare try this again, Rohini.
Don't forget, your son's life
is in my hands.
Take her back.
- Come on!
- Come.
- Let me go.
- Come on!
- Moti! Moti!
Hey, let me go!
Why are you here, Gopal?
Naad has returned to Anandagarh.
Why are you still here?
I was on my way.
I came here because of the ruckus.
Leave!
And keep a close eye on Naad.
- Go.
- Okay.
Who's putting these ideas
in your head, Moti?
Answer me.
No, it's just that...
She was in pain so...
How dare you?
Who should I punish for this?
You or your son?
Hmm?
Moti?
Punish me.
Hmm.
Alap.
- Hey.
- Hmm?
What's this?
Didn't sleep at all, did you?
I just can't crack this notation.
Even the rare books in your library
couldn't give me a hint.
What do I do now, Shruti?
I know you very well, Alap.
Tell me what's...
You evaded my questions yesterday too.
What are you hiding?
And...
stop avoiding me.
Has something happened
to Rohini Aunty?
Hey, why are you crying?
Alap?
Tell me what happened.
Is Rohini Aunty alright?
Hey...
What...
Moti.
W... Where's Moti?
Tell me.
Where's Moti?
Hey!
Wait!
Listen to me!
Moti...
How could you not tell me
something like this?
You could've at least told me
that Rohini Aunty is in danger.
Don't you trust me at all?
Mom will be fine, right, Shruti?
She'll be fine.
Nothing will happen to her.
We'll crack the notation together.
Hey...
can't we try searching
Grandpa's farmhouse?
Dad was saying
there might be rare books.
We might find something.
I can get the keys
if you want me to.
Okay.
Let's go.
Shruti.
- Don't tell anyone about Mom, please.
- I'll tell everyone.
Obviously I won't.
Come on.
This way.
Oh, sorry.
I can barely see anything.
- Shruti.
- Hmm?
There's nothing much here.
There's another room.
- Ouch!
- Hey! Careful.
A rudrabina.
Did your Grandpa teach
how to play the rudrabina?
I've never heard anything like that.
HAIL GODDESS SARASWATI
Mom's handwriting...
(inaudible)
What are you thinking about?
Look what I found.
There's a pen in the box.
See, it looks so strange.
Wait.
I didn't notice that.
Hey.
Isn't it the same symbol?
Yes, looks like it.
What does it have to do
with my grandpa?
Only one person can answer that.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today