Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
Thank you
It's no coincidence it can't be Supo's own people that there was an accident
He was given fitness, who told that Varkala himself came directly to the signal where the traffic light is installed.
that's the limit
How did you know from the ration behind everyone that tomorrow is helping us, tell about the Bricklane defect
about that photo
in finding out
helps him
What about Vikala's trained girlfriend?
I don't know
I don't think being a member of the x2pro will talk a lot, people say a lot by being deceived
Stop
In the morning, Veer Kala's girlfriends went out to the place, everything was already planned, if it is not included in this, then we have to save.
we only have
Modern report and call mannequin
Main Hospital Jadav
There is a meeting of Marco committee, Lord is tomorrow, not we have to go today
tell them what happened
I won't tell you to lie again to break the rules
go
listen to me wait me i thought about this a lot i can help you
in a coma because of you
please tell the song i won't bother you
Telling Seema Powder Vet that I am thankful for their trust
But I've done my job Unfriend
Giving some kind of letter will not make any difference
You know that it is in your goodness that I do not suffer
you can't think right all friend
i understand
speak your motions now, speak all thoughtfully
i'm totally cool
send me some photos
I have humanity but your work
O all the information with them we will continue our operation Alfred
you're going to be the head of department
Wait for you a new medal and a new rank
Takhatgarh
Ok
Mr. Problems know you better than you Alfred
take this your key was mine
did you hear about him
about what
mean you don't know anything
we are praised yesterday
Our department is best prepared to join net
We have been praised by all the old
thanks to you all friend
tomorrow
we will get certificate of honor from my store
I'll get the salary done now
i said i will take care of you
what does jokes do
So tomorrow I have to go to my head ok ok
very good listen
Alfred I was thinking that this net benefit us a lot
Maybe
we can move on
We are Barbie We are the flowers blooming in this field
we can go too high
It's so funny to hear everything from your mouth
yes but
want to prove it to a liar
that I
I can do a lot other than office
don't you worry all friend
I'll take you too
to be ready
Alfred who is yours
right behind the palm
no nothing just
The work is a bit much and Krishna
Tomorrow you are also in coma
he's probably gonna be like this
His wife's name is Britva
I will go and talk to him maybe he can tell some name
ok king
keep calm
absolutely yes
may not write to you
Today I feel like your feet are going to explode
yes then this is your chance
You can put all the blame on me in front of the committee anyway you deserve it
I'll make everything right and then everything will be fine
NKCV
we'll work with a little patience ok
started out bright
I can't make any Bihar with my own language.
Me
take responsibility for your child
I also want all peace and nothing else
Music March India always follows the command line, much more than that
happened to someone and she
whatever it is for him and you take your work very seriously
Didn't you see mean you don't quit while working
Very good example set for us to ever
guess it wrong a little hasty
he is very good at his job
He is a very good team leader and that too he has a lot of respect I mean nowadays.
high honor fair
whatever happened learned a lot from us
In my thought
image
I Police Outpost Detective
I have a few questions about your husband call elements
yes us
nothing to question
do you know that yesterday
whom they used to meet a lot
Do you have any photos from whom used to get a call that they made friends for nothing
or a group photo with their friends
I don't have
Anshi really don't know anything sorry
Thank you
Which media packet do we get and which service do we need?
you don't understand
Talking internet is a bit fast maybe
Hello Hello
i will handle
what are you doing in my house nice house
fond
Jhansi
painting art expensive cars
friends' wives
Artist is best I told you not to vote
No use of voting day mind public concerned we understand that you
I have done my work, go away you will really be able to abuse it
You have to be the head of department instead of Oscar, we'll take care of it all.
no need to worry we have not started the work
A role model for all of us We do the work Laxman called me what
you give me the language
Alfred will you laugh
and became very happy
I will finish everything by calling refusal ok ok
ok what happened
Yes
We will increase the speed of your internet connection
Your husband is very intelligent today a fast connection is very important sir let us think about it
Now you can go so that everything goes through Security Comment Cameras Door Locks
Will think in Amritsar
list
definitely think
free you say right
Fever asked for a little for us so I return
Chandu's cheap
us our
to neighbors
Charas movie song
I have to go out of work for a while
Where are you going
a long training
but it's good isn't it
For work
tomorrow i will get it almost everyday but good job
Very good
I just wanted to say that when I go I'll be here with some money
so that you go ahead
no problem
how many kids are you carrying
It's not even sure just if I had to go
so you have some kind of problem
Ok
ozone
by yours who was going to give statement against you today
she hanged that darling in her
had come out of the cell only to put a noose around his neck and he
it will be a big test
A Witness Has Died Before It Came Out On Amazon
i'm telling you something is wrong
We have to keep a close watch on how much family we can't do this is not working opportunity
He has questioned that people are investigating his death and I have absolutely no time to talk to him.
Waiting for investigation, was roaming near the house, he was not
If I was with Kapoor, I would have caught me, I would not run away
It may have been
Kal you so much
Be a member of a local organization
I have used them to hide the Russian salad PM and then to suppress the talk at the behest of the Russians in the same group
made her condition worse
If not then there would be such a reason
Then even after this, why are many people roaming near the house, do you know why people are doing this brother?
yes yes ok
how was the winter vacation
Don't ask spoiled the situation
Tate people don't know what will happen to you
Mister Marcopolo You were wrong before the setting was over, I won't leave you
Yes
Ok
walked
yes what
sushant
Do you have to reach the car plus early
ok please go fast in the photo
I support Kalidasa was my responsibility and I had taken the decision.
All done without telling new education
Together with yesterday, I was not given any official permission for this and I used illegitimate methods.
Yesterday the teacher always said that we should follow the rules
At that time I felt that I am behind the enemies of the country and I have to take a quick decision.
Try it a little, tell me what happened
hi kachi sir
chanting police
ok i'll handle so just try to calm down
Now that I think about it, I understand that
A big mistake has been made I believe that it is because of Defense Force Intelligence Crop Production
I promise this kind of behavior will never happen again
hello location powers take back the baby
If nothing happens, then I will go straight to Babu, are you listening, what am I saying, take the child back
Don't play the game immediately, bring the baby back, I'm yours for half an hour, after that I'll leave from you
Don't understand I will go and finish everything myself
Alfred be ready
The command to save money is Asian has forgotten what
talk to me
What happened
In Trouble
in big trouble
he told me
i'm crazy
what do we do
you spy for them
posted me
to me
know what
crazy behind you
but now i can't stop
speaking france
Ok
do bismillah ok go on
And I will tell and send
What should we do now we will go to the minister we will accept your marks or come back
I'm not running away from my responsibilities
I'm just hoping that the committee understands why I violated the rules
what was nepal city
For his unmatched contribution in the process of joining the notes and for the country's
The Secret to Handling 875 Forward Intelligence
you got up on both sides
Because living in the world was all over
jokes bhajan
what you had to do
that you did
we all make mistakes
I accept this
Keeping such tickets hidden is no small task
But first we are human
you stopped it all for me
to save me
Kharnal
can come by 1:00
I'll try to do as much as I can
I will surrender myself to them in Vasudha
we will adjust to you
Bhopal is hidden from Sachin
Central policeman told that he hanged the young man
He was the one to inform the social committee
committed suicide on
do you know what
he had accident news
wait what
Somebody had a recording
Then all the IT of defense was in the hands of Milba.
Then the matter calmed down again and it is also your work with ease, I believe in you, right?
If this committee removes me from my work, then I will hand over everything to you, then I will write it down and when everything
then you can start on your own
I should have handled this matter more carefully. Knew my streets, he was the record of the security politicians.
trying to save holi
i don't know what we are looking for
Good
drama documents
For what I gave from his photo
i drink a little
you will tell me everything
this is the right time to drink
what to ask makrana husband
I thought someone would understand or forgive me
should i be punished for that
America
OK OK
You sit in peace and think about things then we find
don't hear are you gonna fix this thing
tomorrow i'll take you to the first
and tell you everything
Then I will call the same division and it is written that the police will come.
what can we do
new movie
But
you loved me so i thought you were one of them
what do you mean you added me on their behest
Hey no one believes in any tuition of all languages
Vishambar called
Passenger train timings are not at all
asked me to call
did you give money from russia
lady russia
threaten again
like what you always do
I am something in everyone
I will give useless information and nothing else
Some wrote that everyone will go to Bihar later, my connection song there too
lied in his eyes
Fate wishes so many nightmares
now uncle
growing on people so it happened
but you still rain
would really
You can pretend like you've caught me spying
Don't give a fuck I am right then you will always speak your double agent talk yourself
Play Whatever is known, everything is true, truth is such a thing that makes someone's life hell
Whatever had to happen has happened, now we don't think ahead, don't let the answers get spoiled.
i want to be punished
i can understand your language
i will help you
You have got your punishment, now you have to show the spot for the whole life
another way
you remember
you said you don't want to die you have to live
don't fuck girlfriend darling how way wrong right now
When the doer is alive his price
always try how long it takes
But one day you will come back together
Will die when you go home
and heard
now let's
came back
i'm on my way now
I talk
thank you kisli
for life
Photo
The investigation is over and the committee has taken its decision.
and i would like to tell
of this decision
according to you
Removing you from Defense Force Intelligence Department, Landforce Headquarters till further orders
to tell the truth
If not today then tomorrow you can ask the same problem again.
Men feel that they have more freedom in the defense post.
Feels that he can do anything that he can help the country at his convenience.
can be considered according to
Men keep everything as taken program, he is not like us and you
One who has reached this far in spite of adversity and whose mistake may be the last
that we don't deserve here
woman is a good person to mother
place of poetry
And it's not made of work
how do you feel
looks fine
We can do it
you're not a liar, we'll do it all
I knew he had some problem but that's it
had no idea
today you doctor department
someone has to find someone to replace you
How happened now everything will be fine
i don't doubt that
I know how well it must have been so far
All of you can say that the recommendation must have gone to the President.
for someone's job
you get the presidential medal
Then I will merge for your contribution in a week, after that on March 29 I will award you
When will it happen again for this the disappearance of irrigation twitter of first mill
and Bhaskar
Something is fishy
will figure it out
Rest I am thinking that in this matter I also tell them
i trust you
Thanks
light are you
ok google means my room chair can change
I also know so asked Farming
don't want to type it
America date
brother so sorry little forgive me
you should be glad you're alive
After all, nothing can be fixed anyway
worried about the morning
was drinking
wanted to take care of him
participate
i didn't understand
didn't even try
still can't understand
pick up something
let me know if it works
i didn't support him
didn't help him
Maybe if I had supported him, he would
Shoe
you did nothing wrong
finally found peace
alfred i know
that where you disappear till late at night
And why do you stay out of the house so much
i know your baby girl
and i met you
You had taken Jamai to myself.
Beti tut na is not a good mother for your daughter
I want to support you in my stomach
Iran to our teacher
There's no secret left
1 minute
hello i am speaking
Yes
what left where
king details
I didn't feel like I've come to spoil your mood
I talked to our news cop
So
Next HD print is about to be made, just do it for the whole university.
Till then we are after the wrong person
just do it because we really did it wrong
Chikiti Rajnath
you like it too
By the way
I wore it today but its rightful right here is all of you guys
I would like to thank you all for your dedication
Thank you very much friends, now we are members of NATO and this is the most important thing
marble stone
but you will become
How Much Nation Embassy's minority met Valentine's coma
you talk to hide the recorder
You doubted me yet with trouble I never doubted you
pardesi babu pictures
You are my most trusted attraction to you for this madam
we got a little bigger
Watch any video online with Open-SUBTITLES
Free Browser extension: osdb.link/ext