ENJOY ALL VOD IN HIGH QUALITY @ 4KVOD.TV
GET LIVE TV,MOVIES,SHOWS IN ONE PACKAGE
FAMILY MOTTO
A HARMONIOUS FAMILY WITH LOVE
EUN-HEE
Did my sister call you by any chance?
CHAN-PAL
-Are you awake?
-Yes.
I was too busy to check my phone.
Is Eun-joo out of reach?
No, she was home.
Ri-ra and Woo-seok came to take
their baby's first birthday photos.
I see.
Go to sleep.
Chan-hyuk.
Yes?
I…
hate myself.
What can you do? You can't start over.
Just keep living your life.
I'm cheering for you.
Go to sleep.
Ri-ra insisted
that you have to be a writer.
I quit writing.
Remember the fake love letter you wrote
to me when I was in the military?
No.
I absolutely don't.
Go to sleep.
Okay.
MY DEAREST PARK CHAN-HYUK
My dearest Chan-hyuk.
Before you take a photo,
your lips are smiling
but your nervous chin line stays frozen.
I want to embrace
your chin softly with my hands.
She lied way too seriously.
I suddenly remembered it too clearly.
Gosh.
Oh, my gosh.
This is driving me nuts.
You looked so bright
as you took photos everywhere.
And I, at the time tried my best
to capture your image
in my heart.
I'm leaving first.
Okay, good job.
You should go home too.
Hi.
The alley here is confusing.
Wasn't it hard to find?
I found it easily thanks to you.
-Please sit. I'll get the coffee.
-Okay.
-Here.
-Thank you.
I couldn't come empty-handed,
so I brought some photo books.
Thank you.
Eun-hee never gave me such presents
though she works
at the publishing company.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Like I said on the phone,
I'm here regarding the contract.
Yes, by the way…
What contract are you
trying to sign with us?
Ms. Kim Eun-hee postponed
the approval of the photo team.
Is it because
is the photo team our company?
Yes.
We want to write up a contract
with you and your company.
But Ms. Kim Eun-hee never said that to me.
Actually…
We have a different photo team
that works with us.
I see.
I understand what you mean.
Ms. Kim Eun-hee doesn't
mix business with private life, but…
I guess she wanted to support her friend…
You should keep working with
the original team.
But you could've just told me
over the phone.
The author wants your photos, CEO Park.
I also heard you shot
a promotional video too.
It's weird that
Ms. Kim Eun-hee still hasn't
brought the contract.
She was being too strict.
The publishing schedule is tight, so…
Can I give you the contract?
Come in.
Come on in.
-Who else is coming?
-I don't know.
My ball…
Hey, Yong-gyoo.
We're all family.
I thought we should
at least know each other's faces.
Mom.
What is this?
Did you ask me
to call the kids to do this?
It's not what you think.
I have something to tell all of you.
Let's go inside.
Yong-gyoo.
-Can you play alone?
-Yes.
-Stay quiet and draw, okay?
-Okay.
Sit here.
I think I've had
two separate families.
Dad…
Mr. Kim. Don't just do that, and…
You stay quiet.
You should listen to me first too.
After my memories came back,
I thought about it a lot.
I was only going to tell
your Mom and stop there.
But I thought all of you should know
about me, your father.
I committed such a big crime
and have been hiding it
until I reached this age,
making an excuse that it's for my family.
Get up.
We should talk alone later.
How can you do this with our kids?
Don't you feel any shame?
You're so…
You should all get up too.
That's not what it is.
Please listen to me until the end!
If it's what you think it is,
then it would be…
It would be better.
Remember the summer of 1994?
I bought the newest electric fan
after thinking and thinking,
and I was in a hurry to go
to my daughters and caused an accident.
I had so many thoughts
in that short moment.
"The company didn't sign me
up for insurance."
"I don't have any money."
"How can I compensate?"
Young-sik!
That's the first thing that came
to my mind when I hit a child.
It was only a child and his grandma,
so I took him to a hospital
without reporting it.
His grandma thanked me
for taking him to the hospital
and asked me if it was okay since
the medical bill will be high.
I thought it'd be over if he was
discharged from the hospital, but…
Well.
Mr. Kim did everything he could.
He sent me to school, gave me money,
and played soccer with me.
He looked after my grandma.
I truly…
received everything.
All right, let's do this.
Young lady, the jujubes are delicious.
I should've gone to jail.
If I didn't even care for you,
that means I'm a beast.
Why would you go to jail?
Do you know that everyone says
that you're a pushover behind your back?
Please take care of Young-sik.
Don't worry.
-Let's work together.
-Okay.
He found me a job at the plant,
and he even saw me get married
and have my kid.
Even families don't do that.
Didn't you
live in Ulsan at that time?
Mom, did you know?
She didn't.
She saw him for a moment
when we went to Ulsan last time.
I lost my memories,
so I couldn't tell her.
I've been living in Ulsan,
and I came to Incheon.
To find my wife.
Mr. Kim told me to get a place
for the three of us,
but I have a place with my kid.
I don't know why he's saying that
when he has such a nice house.
From now on,
it seems like the three of us
have to live together.
I don't know what the law says, but…
I think I must be responsible
for this for my entire life.
Why?
You said it was 1994?
It happened before I was born.
Why are you still responsible?
What's with you? Let's talk later.
I…
I didn't get to spend much time
with you, Dad.
I've never played ball with you!
Hey.
I'm sorry.
Mr. Kim, you didn't have to…
-You need to stop now.
-Young-sik.
Go down and wait in front of the car.
I'll be down soon.
Okay.
Yong-gyoo, let's go home.
Let's go home.
What's your name?
Kim Yong-gyoo.
I'm five years old.
You're so good at playing
by yourself. What a big boy.
Let's go, Yong-gyoo.
Bye.
Can I do this by tomorrow?
I'll meet Ms. Kim Eun-hee tomorrow.
Then I'll leave it here
so you can read the contract form.
Okay.
That photo is nice.
The location was great.
The weather was good, too.
Eun-hee mentioned you
when she was planning a photo book.
She said you think of Van Gogh's paintings
whenever you take landscape photos.
At the time,
I didn't even know what I was saying.
It's embarrassing.
She told you all sorts of
unnecessary things.
When I was at the US headquarters,
I'd been exchanging emails
with Eun-hee for a long time.
At first, it began with work,
but we began to chat more later on.
Among everyone I know, I'm sure she writes
the most interesting emails and letters.
She does write well.
Since you're her friend,
you should tell her
to write her own things,
instead of making someone else's book.
Well…
That's hard to say even between friends.
I heard you two are old friends,
so I thought it would be okay.
I heard she won an award before.
She bragged about that too?
I guess she does want to write.
She said you were the only friend
who went to the award ceremony with her.
Was I?
I'm sorry.
The only common factor
between us is Eun-hee,
so I guess I talked too much.
That little child
was made fun of for his injured leg.
He couldn't even kick
a soccer ball with his friends.
He was down so I played ball with him
one or two times,
and you're that upset about it?
You're not one to behave like that.
Dad, can't you get some rest now?
You've worked hard enough.
There's a thing called
statute of limitations.
Are you going to be responsible for life?
You're only going to get older.
You're not young. You're old.
You really aged this time.
Ji-woo…
You're heartbroken for me, that's why.
But,
this is the beginning for me.
Want to go hiking with me?
I'm probably faster than you.
Seriously…
I'm leaving first.
You're leaving without
saying goodbye to Dad?
He made his decision.
I heard all about it, so I should go now.
I'll leave without saying bye.
Eun-joo is leaving.
Don't you two…
have anything to say to me?
You don't want to talk
as it was from a long time ago?
No.
Do you think your father's life
is nothing but pathetic?
Dad, you're back.
You even yell in front of
your dear Ms. Sook.
I'll wrap things up
and go see you later.
My smart eldest daughter,
don’t you have anything to say to me?
Is it because you're disappointed in me?
Do as you wish, Dad.
Right?
I should fulfill my duty for life, right?
Your duty was to report it at that time.
And…
you should've told Mom too.
Since you're married,
you should've asked her
to solve it together.
You did it to provide for us?
No, you just thought that
a kid and a grandma were
easy to deal with.
You wanted to bury it
in the cheapest way possible.
Eun-joo is stern. Why did you ask her
to say something?
Take it easy.
You got attached to him
and told him to call you Dad.
I'm sure you didn't expect it
to pile up as debt for life.
Dad…
Why do you take responsibility
for things you can't handle?
Do you think it's easy
to be responsible for someone?
Tell him to take responsibility.
He said he would do it.
It's none of your business.
You're right about everything.
Yes.
Yes, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Eun-joo…
Yong-gyoo, how many floors are there here?
-Five.
-Yong-gyoo, you're good.
Bye, Yong-gyoo.
Eun-joo.
Why are you following me?
It's your job to comfort them.
They're all grown-ups.
I don't need to comfort them.
-I'll drive you.
-No thanks.
Tae-hyung told me to give you a ride.
You live in that expensive apartment,
and you have anemia and malnutrition?
Live a happy life.
It'd be awkward for you to see the kids.
So I'll live in this house.
But instead…
take this with you.
INSTALLMENT SAVINGS ACCOUNT
You said you're looking for a place.
You can't take responsibility
with just words.
Money is scarier than words.
I'll pay it back to Eun-joo
little by little, so you take it.
Please just take it.
Why did you have to bring the kids here
and say such a thing?
You should've consulted me first.
I feel relieved. That's good enough.
I don't know why I didn't have the courage
to say this.
You made me misunderstand all my life
and you feel relieved?
You're going to make
all those years up in one day?
Who told you to make it up?
Just keep on
hating me.
I left something.
Hi.
-Goodbye.
-Okay, goodbye.
Who is it?
Do we have new work?
If you found what you left,
then go home quietly.
Come on, you know it.
I left nothing.
Your phone was ringing
after your blind dates,
so I thought one of them was coming.
Why are you having
such unnecessary thoughts?
You cleaned the office, dressed up,
and brewed coffee.
It calls for the wrong idea.
But…
He's from the publishing company
where Ms. Eun-hee works?
A contract is precious.
Put it down carefully.
I find myself disgusting as well.
I give up.
I know that I'm never the one for you.
It's not because of my past, is it?
Hey, do you see me as such
a loser after you've given up?
That makes me so sad.
I've been seeing you
since you were a baby.
You're just like a little sister to me.
If you're worried, I listen.
When you're in a bad mood, I am too.
All right.
I'll be your little sister.
Go home.
You idiot. You stupid loser.
This is how real siblings talk.
Jeez.
But…
I can somewhat understand Dad.
At that time, insurance was
more difficult to process,
and he couldn't ask anyone for help.
He must've felt lost and scared.
Don't you think about Mom?
He changed and didn't come home…
Never mind.
Let's just try to understand
this separately.
Things will get worse
if we try to convince each other
I have no energy.
I think that's the right thing
to do as well.
But…
When will you tell Dad?
Shall I go with you?
Do you think it’s easy to tell?
I'm not done wrapping things up, either.
I'll take care of it.
I said that to Mom as well.
Earlier on, that punk Ji-woo…
Wow, he was totally rebellious.
-Weren't you shocked?
-He's a grown-up too.
We all treat him like the youngest
so he just lives his life as the youngest.
Let him be, so he can think
and judge things himself.
At least we have memories of the time
when Mom and Dad got along…
But Ji-woo doesn't even have that.
He said he never played ball
with Dad. Leave him be.
I'm leaving.
Wait.
Here.
No way…
Did you forget?
I'm not like you.
Drive safely.
You need to eat well, at least.
Tae-hyung must be out.
I'm not going to see him and leave.
You didn't take the medicine.
I said that you can't ignore
your conditions.
Take care of yourself. You need to focus.
I forgot about the medicine.
I can take care of myself,
so stop being fretful.
Sometimes I think…
if I didn't miscarry at that time,
our child would've been
five years old this year.
I need to stop trying hard
to look like I'm okay.
I can never forgive you.
Why…
Why are you here?
Your vice CEO came
to our office yesterday.
Didn't he tell you?
He didn't.
So he's the type to act cool.
Is it because of the meditation book?
Yes.
Do I have to suffer
because of your office romance?
Why can't you sign
a contract for your friend?
Do you feel uncomfortable?
Let's not do it, then.
Let's go inside.
Ms. Kim Eun-hee.
Please be honest.
Should I stamp the contract or not?
Which are you more comfortable with?
The author likes the photos
and videos taken by the Golden Goose team.
I'd appreciate it if you stamped it.
But sadly, the down payment won't be much,
and you won't make that much of a profit.
I see.
So you couldn’t tell me
or ask me this whole time
because it won’t be much money?
Because of money?
Stop it.
Stop picking a fight.
Hi, you're early.
Yes, I did.
Ms. Kim, you're here early, too.
Yes.
-Would you like some coffee?
-Oh--
No.
It'll be over soon.
I'll finish the contract signing
and go to the printing house.
Okay.
So that's all you need to know.
Good morning.
Would you like some coffee?
I'll do it.
Jeez, I never would've imagined.
My gosh…
Are you stamping
the Declaration of Independence?
Why do you look so serious?
Because a contract is a holy thing.
EUN-JOO
Yes, Eun-joo.
Chan-hyuk, would you like
to meet up if you have time?
Yes, I'm free whenever.
How about this evening?
Yes, sounds good.
Okay.
She wants to see me in the evening.
I know you'll do a good job, but…
She's in the worst condition.
Please look after her.
And for Ji-woo…
Goodness.
You're becoming family.
Jeez.
I'll call you after I meet Eun-joo.
Okay.
That's what you think, Mom.
Mind your own business!
I'm hanging up.
Eat breakfast and take medicine.
Eun-hee gave me this chocolate.
This is…
Eun-hee's sign of withdrawal she gave me.
A sign saying we shouldn't fight anymore.
I'm sure you don’t know, but I like this.
Eun-hee is worried about you.
She doesn't want to fight you anymore.
Cutting ties and avoiding each other…
Once is enough. She doesn't want it again.
So she prepared this,
as she couldn't say it in words.
So…
She could've said it.
Why give me this all of a sudden?
It's like you giving me medicine
after the meal, all of a sudden.
Like us…
Eun-hee and I changed a bit too.
Eun-hee always complained
that Dad only cared about me,
but Dad didn't discriminate against us.
He found kind Eun-hee comfortable, but…
I'm sure he found me uncomfortable.
Because I'm not his real daughter.
What does that mean?
How can you not understand
such a simple sentence?
We need to stop too.
Let's get divorced.
Why didn’t you tell me your emails
with the vice CEO?
I thought there was no use
in telling you that.
That lazy look on your face.
This hardly ever comes out
during a relationship.
Mr. Carless.
Want a ride to the station?
No, thanks. Stop slacking off
and go to the printing house.
I have a place
I want to check out since I'm here.
Where? This is my territory.
Just walk naturally.
The model looks tacky,
so I can't take photos anymore.
Isn't the view great here?
This is the park I love.
You should go to the printing house.
The vice CEO coming to my office
without telling you,
doesn't that mean he's concerned about us?
You call him the vice CEO
for signing a contract?
You have the mind of a businessperson.
I don't think he's Mr. Playboy,
and he seemed to know
your personality well.
It seems like he thinks about you a lot.
Wow, but he couldn't keep a poker face.
How come you two didn't get caught?
Look at you all ladylike
because I'm complimenting your lover.
Are you happy?
I'm not…
That wasn't a pleasant sight.
I had something to tell you,
but now I don't. Bye.
No.
If you don't tell me,
I'll die from curiosity.
What is it? Tell me before you go.
-Eun-hee.
-Yes?
I…
I treasure Ji-woo
like he's my own brother,
and I like Eun-joo
and am polite to her
because of…
you.
Eun-joo and Ji-woo are my friend's sister
and my friend's brother,
and in front of them
you, my friend, are always there.
To me…
my friend is the most important.
Is there a more perfect
confession of friendship than this?
It makes my heart flutter
and makes me sad.
You big liar.
Wow.
You're so keen.
I knew you wouldn't believe me.
Hey, you're always on Eun-joo's side,
you know Ji-woo's secrets more than I do,
treat me like number three,
and what? Friend?
Hey, why would I believe that?
You dumb…
What? What did you just say?
Did you just curse at me?
-I didn't curse.
-I heard it.
I didn't curse.
Shall I buy you a hearing aid?
Wow, Kim Eun-hee just cursed at me.
No.
-Forget it.
-I'm going to be obsessive.
Wow, Kim Eun-hee, you cursed.
Hey, I didn't curse.
-You're so…
-How can I curse at my friend…
Hey.
From getting to work until now,
he's super serious.
Vice CEO.
Do you help
with other team's work like this too?
Like you would go to someone else's office
to give them a contract?
No.
Then from now on…
I refuse any help that is uncomfortable.
Okay, I understand.
I ordered it when I ordered mine.
Well, I don't think this is an occasion
to choose what to drink.
Okay, thank you.
I'm going back to the US.
I'm sure you heard it from Geon-joo.
I wanted to see you before I leave.
Geon-joo and I went on a vacation
for more than a week, right?
I was surprised
that you never called or texted him.
I had his phone the entire time.
Why didn't you call him?
I thought he had a reason
for not being able to call me.
Geon-joo did everything
to stop me three years ago.
I should've ended it then.
I got soft and couldn't end it.
I regret it. I was angry.
So I wanted to harass him
as much as he harassed me.
That took a week.
I read the emails
you two exchanged with each other.
I didn't know I was exchanging
emails with Geon-joo.
Anyway,
Geon-joo stopped me,
but he cheated on me, again.
He had small affairs from time to time.
Oh.
Small affairs.
That's fresh vocabulary.
Do you know that you're a bit funny?
When we meet in the US, let's get along.
He came here to close
and wrap up the Korean branch,
so he's going back to the U.S.
You didn't know about the email,
and that he came here
to close your workplace.
You just had your office romance.
The email was a mistake.
The latter is probably confidential.
It wasn't even that romantic.
We slept together on the last day.
I think it was the warmest
and cuddliest moment
in our relationship.
I felt that all those years
weren't a total waste of time,
and it comforted me.
He couldn't even ask me
to give it back to him.
Give this to Geon-joo.
I don't want to tell him
about our encounter.
You give it to him before you go.
Tell him.
I…
don't want to see him again.
I also…
don't want to get involved.
I have to eat lunch,
so I can't give you all day.
What is it?
We decided to get divorced.
We will solve it logically without causing
any ruckus.
I'll trust you for now.
But…
Divorce is more realistic than marriage.
You never know
what will happen in the future.
Do you think Tae-hyung is refusing
when he can choose differently
like when he went to
medical school for you
and was forced into marrying me?
That's not a choice.
No one can be against Tae-hyung
or persuade him.
Looks like we won't
see each other anymore.
People give tons of advice or curses
when they're not going to
see the other again.
Do they put their bad feelings
in advice or curses?
You go ahead first.
I don't feel good,
so I need to skip lunch today.
Okay.
Do you have anything else to say?
You should eat lunch.
I'm leaving.
Sang-sik, did you get younger?
You're working so hard.
Yes, I got younger.
I am full of energy.
But your face is dirty
and covered in fatigue.
Let's keep an eye out, okay?
I've been told that
I'm money-crazy all my life,
so why keep an eye out?
You remember that?
You go and tell them.
Tell what?
Whenever people criticize you,
I close my mouth and ears.
Tell them I was money-crazy
because I had to provide
for two families all my life.
Your husband is romantic.
He gets jealous,
and he misunderstands too.
Try experiencing it. It's ridiculous.
And you shouldn't say that
since you have the best husband.
I don't really like my husband.
Yes.
No one's 100% perfect.
Though he's so nice to me
it doesn't go away.
When he was a professor,
he never let our kids live freely.
He made them study all night, hit them,
and wouldn't even
let them waste one minute.
Even if we have a grandchild.
Those memories are still so vivid.
You told me your husband
knew nothing but the kids.
I was so envious when I heard that.
He really did.
Don't eat more than three.
Fruits have poison too.
Hi, Eun-joo.
I saw the wedding photos again.
Now, tell me what you saw
and heard that day.
Actually, it was nothing.
Your friends who brought the bouquet
were waiting for me after the wedding,
begging me to send the photos.
Because they were sure
you wouldn't send them.
They gave me an address in London.
So did you send them?
Yes.
I still keep in touch
with them through social media.
You're as nosy as Eun-hee is.
I was their friend for almost 20 years.
They said I'm closer than family, but…
I never told them about my family.
Did I keep too much distance from them?
I think it's kind of my fault.
I feel like you caught
my inferiority and scars
that even my family doesn't know about.
Didn't you tell me to look at my wedding
photos for me to find out about that?
Actually, they contacted me again.
Those two are always curious about you,
so I thought you should contact them.
So I got a bit nosy.
Does my situation look like
I need some friends I haven't
kept in touch with for years?
Yes.
Sometimes friends can do
what your family can't do.
It's delicious.
Eun-hee liked you before.
She keeps her distance
when she likes someone.
She's the middle child.
So she learned that she must be keen,
please people and make them laugh
to keep the family going way too early.
She's used to lowering herself,
so when she sees someone decent,
she thinks he is out of her league
and draws a boundary.
Oh.
That's the part of Eun-hee's personality
only a family would know.
She just looks super optimistic
on the outside.
Anyway, she talked a lot about you
after she got into school,
and then suddenly stopped.
She has to mature and overcome it.
I wonder how her current relationship is.
I was not supposed to be displeased
with Eun-hee anymore.
It's okay, you can do that
with me as much as you want.
Wow.
The taste is different.
Goodbye.
This tastes different too.
Chan-pal. Park Chan-pal.
Your voice sounds seriously ominous.
-What are you doing?
-Want to know?
Then give me 50 cents.
I'm going home after meeting Eun-joo.
Bye.
I worked late all week.
When I think about it now,
I've been waiting for you.
I was going to leave it here and go,
but I was flustered to see you here.
I don't know how I got to play this role.
Ha-ra said she feels uncomfortable
seeing you again.
Thank you.
Do you have any other questions to ask?
No, I don’t.
How dare you…
Why are you here?
Are you tracking me? Are there no secrets?
I tracked you down through your brother.
That brat…
He's been asking me where I am.
Well done.
Chan-pal. Welcome, Chan-pal.
Good to see you.
Chan-pal.
She's the middle child.
So she learned that she must be keen,
please people and make them laugh
to keep the family going.
She's used to lowering herself,
so when she sees someone decent,
she thinks he is out of her league
and draws a boundary.
Chan-pal.
Stop it now, or I'll leave.
Hey, get your own one.
This is a ritual to end my love triangle.
How childish.
So, are you done with that
incoherent love triangle?
Eun-joo doesn't know, does she?
That you sent me her photo
instead of yours in the army.
Hey.
Mr. Kim, we're off now.
No one's here, so you two
have a lovey-dovey moment.
Look in the kitchen
and eat anything you want.
Wait for me.
They laugh at everything.
Mr. Kim Sang-sik.
Don’t frown.
And don’t yell.
I…
I didn’t do anything.
INSTALLMENT SAVINGS ACCOUNT
I told you not to frown.
If you don't take this,
I'm going to think
you have different thoughts.
What thoughts?
I'll assume that you want me
to sell the house
and give half that money to you.
All right.
I'll take this bankbook,
so don't worry about that.
-I'll send you living expenses…
-Living expenses?
Stop being arrogant
and think that you provided for me.
I'm the one who provided for you.
I don't need living expenses.
You think I tried
to graduate from marriage
without a plan?
Don't make an excuse to contact me.
Did you tell Eun-joo?
Hey, that was a long time ago.
You big coward.
I didn’t tell her.
If you're so scared,
Why send me her photo instead of yours?
Since everyone at your base
was looking forward to
your girlfriend's photo,
I was burdened
and Eun-joo is pretty.
That photo of her was
exceptionally pretty.
You also
have lots of decent photos
of you taken by me.
I'm a good photographer.
The first photo of yours I took
was at the literature award
ceremony. Remember?
I remember.
We were…
20 years old at the time.
Goodness.
Perfect timing for the requested song.
After the award ceremony,
we got drunk and walked down
the stone wall of Deoksugung Palace.
Right. It was autumn.
Yellow ginkgo leaves looked like
incandescent lamps.
How long did we walk there
talking about silly things?
I'm sure we walked
about 100,000 steps that day.
Youth is amazing.
If I rank
the most perfect days in my life,
that day would be number one or two.
Wow, what an honor.
I never thought of you as a man,
and you never thought of me as a woman.
We were purely friends.
We giggled,
we got serious,
and we talked about
our dreams and future too.
Actually, on that day…
I picked up a ginkgo leaf
and took it home.
So I can remember it.
So, did you remember it for a long time?
Well…
I'm confessing this to you
for the first time.
I was about to go to school the next day,
and suddenly, I thought of you as a man.
"He'll be there when I go to school."
"No one knows we walked down
the stone wall of Deoksugung Palace
until midnight all by ourselves."
"We have a secret to ourselves."
"What should I do when I see you?"
I was making myself up,
thinking about that.
With my heart fluttering,
I went into the classroom, but…
A secret to ourselves?
You were advertising the photos
from the ceremony and the stone wall
to Jong-pal and other kids.
Wow, I was so embarrassed,
my face turned red,
and I felt like I got caught…
On that day, you…
You were disqualified as a man in my life.
Hey, what is this feeling?
I feel like I've been dumped
even without dating you.
You are
the stone wall of Deoksugung Palace to me.
It's like the memory of autumn
when I was 20.
Yes.
Shall I call you Deoksugung Boy now? Let's
go.
How could you keep
such a big accident a secret from me?
We're graduating from marriage,
so I thought…
it doesn't matter.
But how could you not tell me
about it all your life?
I might die from anger!
Do you…
not have any secrets?
I have no secrets!
On Eun-joo's wedding day…
Eun-joo's father came.
Didn’t you keep in touch
with him all your life?
I met your mother today.
What for?
I needed to wrap things up.
Your mother missed the chance
to apologize to me today.
She won't. Don't waste your energy.
Divorce is between the two of us.
No, it won't be between the two of us.
Wait and see what I'll do from now on.
You said it's a memory,
but why am I about to begin now?
Dad, you know nothing about Ms. Sook.
I'm a family, but I hardly have
any memories of you.
-Eun-joo.
-You said you'd tell me.
I don't think I can forgive myself!
It'd be wrong if Dad
is the only one who doesn't know.
Why do you think CEO is a playboy?
So he told that young lady everything.
Why won't you even look at me?
I'm sorry.
Did you live your life
feeling like you're indebted?
I felt it was so unfair
to the point I wanted to die.
Subtitle translation by: Hae-lim Lee
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org