api.OpenSubtitles.org is deprecated, please
implement REST API from OpenSubtitles.com
if i tell the truth
what you are saying is a bit confusing
i can't tell everything right now
But I have been told and I think the information I have is wrong.
I can reach you, it will be of no use to me
this information can tell me
you are talking about this kind of information
you have about a colleague of mine
Ministry of Defense Tum To Maa Par IT System
But I am talking about marriage, it is waiting for classified foreign intelligence and then print
try to drink sweets
50 kms
your head hurt
i call the doctor
but we should talk about money
Struggle
I like your paint
Tauranga
a little rough
will talk later
If we act carefully no one will know
A senior of Indian Intelligence can tell us about the fund's ration connection and will also meet new many of you.
Jhagaria to Pune Train
then art painter art
Mother knows you all can walk us on this
One has to take care of this
should not know
Mother
Varkala Weekend 45 Keeps Going
Nakhli
stays at the same place
There is a house near the sea in Pirda, what will I tell there?
what did modi do
a romantic part with her romantic partner
Varkala is a happy grandfather in Finland but here he
As soon as he comes, he becomes a playboy, because of this, you will not put pressure on me, otherwise we will put a little pressure on someone and let him
If you meet him near his girlfriend's house, he will keep himself hidden from the bakelight.
Must be at work, just get some rest
If you become, you have sent a message that you will not go to work today.
I have to give a report that I have taken care of everything
B.Com Pinky Lines
today without
We will not lie down nor will we eat anyone, we only want him to see some faces from the old photos.
Hey let me know we just want name real name tell agent name or anything
Was it right that even at that time there was such a relationship with the keeper of the wind, what happened to those Russians today?
What if Bela herself had a relationship with Ration?
Then
we have to do background check
Guided full-scale operation has become Rani Tu Jaa Hai Let's do a little spying with Mamu
Take care of you Arpit. Good morning
Great
So
first day serial
Reports
and then budget proposals i have 1 hour
Ok sir
you should start
look let me tell you clearly
i can't believe you
I have solid proof that you sarpanch must have some reason to implicate me, I have camera recordings.
even knowing you have from the recording
In business you just don't know what I have from the recording
After the arrest he didn't want to give it to anyone because I didn't know who works for whom why were you recording him that I doubt him
had some
I used to work in Kapu's Counterintelligence earlier, so why were you fired?
to keep me
where is it now
i want to check
i demand that
Check the committee in the court because you can't hide like this
Why didn't you tell this to your senior immediately?
arrested me before
i will tell you everything
Ok
what's in the recording
See
Network
I won't be able to help if you don't tell me
If no one gives a camera, then the environment is very easy for us.
In Pirda, what is the matter of an old film's police and processor's lover?
If the type was a companion of reservation, then a little more quiz
Tell in a way that Russia's medicine is very important
Still we Dada can't take the risk
Etah
i am going to work now
I'll be back in a while
After that we will talk and everything will be fine
i'm fine
I came back and told the doctor
what are you doing sonu jodidar
strength coaching
What are you doing
Sikandra Automatic Gram Kya
Vitamin E
Believe in PC Sharma's song
open happiness
I have been implicated behind the style photo in which it is too late isn't it?
yes i remember
Tea pornography was found in your office computer but those people knew her Titanic a few hours ago but can
All of them are running at 4:00 now
Your entire background will be thoroughly checked
His concern is being traced from where he was studying except me.
because i have a recording
And if those people did not listen to me, it misinterpreted my words, then according to me, I will use the recording now.
behind it all
Alfred Banks
yes ok lets start
Lets start
you and the train are fine
observed or not
Has gone to her sister's house with 10 children
we will meet today
work packet case more competition than here
Yes
I am unable to understand
I don't understand how this is done
play house
don't know train
can do it or not
a little factory
Everything will be alright
Problems keep on coming, when it rains, we can sit inside the house on our own, bring raincoats, I said
how is yours
what is going on all is well
i can see how without you
nothing like this coming is committed
Good
There is a madhouse here
Make this partial work of art
Oscar
Yes, yes
where is polay
Rita Flight
is sick someone else has to be kept in his house ok Got it
alfred
little one wants to leave me
he needs t4
you want to go
wants to go
I don't understand reflux
you don't understand
ready to change
I do not know
wanted to ask didn't know
know something
has not been
maybe she has an affair with someone
i don't know i don't understand
Vasundhara will have to handle the work
what
Actually there is a 3:00 presentation in the ministry
and my brain isn't working at all
ok no matter
babu keep the presentation will give
Ok
Sachin speaking
some strange rumors are flying
how are you sleeping
let's talk together
What is the name of a quality child porn specialist?
he has any old recordings of yours
where you can laugh
87 battery
Recording a security camera near him
from Rabu Investigator
Calling for setting up an independent committee
He does not trust the Ministry of Defense and will show that recording to that committee only.
maybe why are you leaving him
The mitigator thinks this tea was fueled by porn stuff
Alfred I could not even understand that I was out of America to escape
All this is the minister's rubbish, he is probably using this story to save himself.
When will the uncle's holiday end, did it in the first condition and how is your government
That's why I would have chosen you after because Defense Force Intelligence was suspecting you.
thought he trapped you okay
It is not a sure thing that what are you talking about in any recording
no such recording
Hi!
come on in
to be honest
I don't know yes but what to do
you come in first
let's talk
Paint TV Colors Tony is coming on Friday, came in last 2 weeks, may come again
ok and found out that Lal's body was mixed by Sethia
ok so we don't have anything else we got it again tomorrow
if he
if nothing works
we will close it
Pucca
Don't forget our favor kids
Yes, yes
speaking lima
keep your mouth shut
I know I should have done it long ago but now I
what should have been done
i am going
Shoe
see i know and trying tomorrow but he
You
I don't even know how many years I have been passing, how difficult it was for me
You do not know what
that I
it's hard to stay together
all satka
she has an affair with someone else
I also know Saurabh's name
I don't know how long he was living stripe life I know
I know you know belly
that i know
Honey
Like Ritesh
British heat is that woman's name
tongue is single mother
i know where she lives
i found out myself
Maybe you with Oscar's troubles
Could still be in the rest of life
You can live with everyone between us
There's a lot more than that
want each other very much in the video
and there's nothing between us
Anything
we have work
Oscar and
It's not that easy Ali
I understand very well but till now my life was meaningless
hey i don't start money in the beginning account
He doesn't have a job, he has a new career
he doesn't rate anything
yes i already did
first i know
i know what happened
i know what can happen
learn
Check and approve the material score
Then enter and register JATA
I will wait for your patient, give me this report as soon as possible
Tomorrow I want to listen carefully to what I am telling you, you are lost somewhere
Where should your attention be?
Please pay attention
where is the station
You have made some plans for the Intelligence Department of Merger
yes chauhan
The boy of making is constantly saying that he has your department
Recording being heard or not
Everyone has been fooled and reprimanded
If he could not show the recording then time is right
sexy
why is this bar coming so early
According to our police data
Veer Kala's boyfriend is leaving tomorrow morning's flight, that place will speak
Vacancy will not be missed
got it
Hi!
pencil color
i want to talk to you
listen listen to me don't listen to me
nothing will happen to you
Nepali language
i will help you
I will go to you but listen to me I have to meet someone first and that is very important
threatening me is working
Deepika's information is born and nothing else and everything from our people
no one does i am compelled i rule sehore
extract information so that we can help
will work together
you're working with us then we'll be able to do ours
i have to call sunday how will it be then everything will be fine i will take you to the doctor
finish everything please
Mr. Mishra
Open Camera
love story
If I kill you, I will not be able to do any harm to you.
chhath puja moon get lost
Yes
Whatever I want to ask you, ask quickly I don't have much time
what is your opinion
I didn't understand
what is your bank in the army
i am a major
Major Ram
defense force intelligence
unofficially
I want to ask you something I want some information
maybe you can help me
I am listening ask what to ask do you like any of this photo
this year
1987 is 1988 when we got Russian
We Protected a Finnish Construction Site in Soviet Times
And for that we with the Russians
the company was formed in it, it was probably his boss and this
I do not remember
what was their name
why do you want to know all this
us on someone
It's true that we need to know
if you could help us
ok come on ok what type of helsinki i don't have
some old paper roads and after years I will also meet an old friend of mine and
Together they will take out any information from those old papers, thank you very much.
This will really help us a lot. Thank you so much.
The handicapped is going to come back on Monday and will also bring some papers along
The face can recognize our fellow
You said you would never study again in the midst of women
skip start thing
Lucky Saxena, can we somehow do this?
similarly
will have to call alexey
i don't want it to hurt any more
there is another problem
quality guy meet park hai he me with classified documents
recorded in the room
If all the cameras were removed or removed, they could have known
is going to give the highest recording to a special committee
For the sake of the son
don't think before it's over
I'll handle everything will be fine
Do not panic
creta car
Sarita's case can also be resolved with humanity
will sleep with it
who am i in the end
what to do with grace
kick you out first
left of her own free will
that's all you need to know
go and go do your packing
Chocolate
hello election result
you even go to the bedroom
brave terrorist attack
you go home we'll clean it all up
never understand you
Goodbye
If there is anyone in Bhind's contact who is crying ahead of it at its beginning, whose reservation is Intellij
had any connection with the GB of Asia
You we have to find out what position those people are in today and where they are if we come to know that there is anyone today
you are near kapu
Reason for investigating official event
If You Involve So Much Then Won't Tell Anyone To Do
But when the truth comes out then everything will be heard
You don't care whether to fire me or give me the work of Radhe by speaking in the defense post
Watch Match Band Expose
i don't understand what is it
aqua suddenly redesigned
pornography a few days ago about this
was talking
When its Hum State Cricket Clearance
If Hoshiyar Singh was not done, he had indicated
that maybe this isn't the right place for him
to hear the story of his grandfather
it was a little weird from the start
never mind
I don't know what is happening nowadays
Social ID is not known
don't know about you
casual
someone is speaking
Talking about the recording, has the hero gone mad?
He doesn't even know what it is, you are so honest and hardworking Kishan.
we're after you
i don't understand anything
i left her
who left
have a drink
being a liar
hey i don't wanna drink at all don't wanna drink a drop
what happened to me
still lying
We've got an agreement I'm going
Chhota will stay in the same house, I will go to the pain in the summer house
you will come to the office from there
I am fine!
I can drive there
ok then i will also have to come to meet you
It is more difficult to be alone than to drink alone
you also need to help me settle
so it can't happen nowadays
No problem
don't you worry
You are the bank and I have nothing
Central Kamal Police said that
they have done dna test
On the jalebi body of that latrine, which was found in the forest, 1 minute of gum was also found from them, in which the DNA of someone who is in our life.
was with
good there
but now
They got the same DNA from somewhere else, that sample was already with them.
not of the machine but of the other person
and which
Matching that mint packet perfectly
and brother dene was taken from that fellow's fingernail
Who has been killed and put in a coma, 1 month ago you call, according to the information, somewhere
had fallen down
All have marks of beatings and ropes around their necks.
arjunda was
still in coma
If from Russian intelligence who among us
hit the lettering then
the same person
you killed it
To be this photo that the police of 7 countries are looking for
Hi!
About pulse bank
i know thank you
Still if something needed to go
then i will come to you
can i get my pinky kiss
and put it on your head in the locker
table in it
he is going to leave soon
a committee also sat
but he has no recording
There is someone in the government who watches too many spy movies
listen a thing
the DNA of that child
after which you did not give
what do you think will come
you are his father
it is proved
Congratulations
Say more
Ankit Kumar
how is it with him
what happened to preeta
now you leave her
I'm leaving work
alfred
Don't be stupid, there was no talk of our calculations, can't send more to the block
Ok
but do you know what's next for you
there is light
It is dark
sexual intercourse
i will support everyone
Ram Chalisa
easy
Sent a gift for you on Seaman Publications Anniversary
whose anniversary
You have an anniversary with Haley
you two are 12 years old
Have you forgotten
We
don't speak
Yes
10th class clap is not coming
eyes will never come
Excavation accident in Helsinki brother died
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/ah2fv
Help other users to choose the best subtitles