Watch any video online with Open-SUBTITLES
Free Browser extension: osdb.link/ext
FAMILY MOTTO
A HARMONIOUS FAMILY WITH LOVE
The time when I was too pathetic…
WRITE 3 PAGES EVERYDAY
…and couldn't meet anyone.
DON'T BE AFRAID.
DON'T CHANGE WHO YOU ARE.
I used to plant a single seed…
and waited for…
the fruit to grow.
EUN-HEE'S
TRASH
EMPTY
DO YOU WANT TO EMPTY THE TRASH?
EMPTY TRASH
After ending my nine-year relationship,
the 30-year-old me,
had nothing to offer to the world.
To change my life, the first thing I did
was move out.
What do you think?
Isn't it spacious?
Yes.
It's nice.
I'm leaving.
Moving out from my family
was too simple,
and the fence keeping the family
was too loose,
so I felt even lonelier.
What is it all of a sudden?
I felt anxious all of a sudden
I couldn't stay home, so I came outside.
Ma'am, we will tell you inside the house.
EUN-JOO
ELDEST DAUGHTER
Yes.
Is Tae-hyung there?
I'm almost near the house.
Tell him to wait.
I heard you're coming to my house,
so I called Eun-joo.
She's almost here.
Then you should go inside.
I'll go in with her when she comes.
Okay.
I didn't tell her yet.
Do you wish to end things here and there
on your own, like doing homework?
You said you'll tell her last time.
I thought it was rude for me
to not visit her once you told her.
I couldn't tell her on that day.
It turned into a somewhat
noisy family occasion.
I'm going to refrain
from being the party pooper from now on.
When I heard you were going with Eun-hee,
I did worry that would happen.
You really were a family.
You know too well.
We were family.
To my family,
you've always been a guest,
but to your family…
I was their family
the moment I stepped into…
that house.
Come in.
Sit comfortably.
Mother.
We…
decided to get divorced.
I'm sorry.
Why?
We can't be together anymore.
Our love for each other has disappeared.
You answer me.
What could be
a more certain reason than that?
We can't love each other
as a man and a woman anymore.
It's meaningless to be together.
I…
I know my daughter.
If you showed that much love,
considering your personality,
it means you liked him very much.
It's the same now.
Coming here as a couple and sitting there.
You can't do that to someone
who doesn't love you anymore.
You.
Is there another woman?
That's not what it is, Mom.
No.
I'm sorry.
If you're sorry, tell me the reason.
I found my family uncomfortable
and hated them,
so I got married to run away from them.
I got the wrong idea
that Eun-joo chose to marry me
for the same reason.
You got married…
because you hated your family?
Is that…
what you mean?
Eun-joo.
Is that what he means?
I still find my family uncomfortable
and can't stand them.
But I learned that
Eun-joo loves and treasures her family.
I hardly knew anything…
about Eun-joo.
I thought we could live
together like friends.
I realized Eun-joo doesn't need a friend,
but someone to love instead.
I wasn't qualified
from the very beginning.
Everything is my fault.
I can’t make Eun-joo
more miserable than she is now,
and I want her to start over,
so we decided to part ways.
I promised myself
that when I become a mother,
I will let my children live freely,
will not discriminate
against my daughters,
and let them do whatever they want to do.
But when it became a reality…
it was hard to do so.
I'm sorry, Mom.
I…
I will try to live my life.
You are capable,
so it would've been easier
for you than for me,
but seeing you two…
parting ways so suddenly and vainly,
it seems like it was my fault
to mention graduation from marriage…
How is it your fault?
Thanks to you…
I'm enduring it so well.
The child whom everyone wanted aborted,
survived so well thanks to her brave mom.
Don't you think…
it's a waste to see that daughter
being forced to live a fake life?
People might think…
you're 20 years old when they see you.
My precious daughter.
No one sees me like that.
It's been a few years
since kids started calling me an old lady.
You don't look old at all.
You…
Want to live with me?
I'm thankful
that you accepted it
more easily than I thought,
but still, that's not right.
Eun-joo.
Your father…
knows that you know.
I told him.
Good.
Would you like me
to tell him about this?
No.
I'll go see him with Eun-hee.
And see how he's doing too.
Mom…
just think about yourself now.
I hardly knew anything
about Eun-joo.
Yes.
We hardly knew anything
about each other.
This…
Wash.
CEO.
There's something you don't
know about Ji-woo.
What?
I saw his social media
and something seemed weird.
You know how I get obsessive
when I'm curious.
I searched everything from social media
to game usernames and found her.
Who?
He said he was dating someone
and that she was a bit far away.
She's his first love
from school or something.
Isn't that a common story
for those who use social media?
Something feels off.
Someone's first love is always
a target to be attacked, right?
It's not like that.
I heard she lives in Toronto,
but nothing seems right.
She has more than 800 friends worldwide.
Is she the UN?
I don't like bad-mouthing people.
If you're curious, go ask Ji-woo yourself.
Why would I ask him?
It has nothing to do with me.
I could've crawled here faster.
The CEO there kept asking me questions,
so I answered them.
He says I'm the only friendly one.
He said you're exceptionally scary.
Then should I smile while I'm working?
You should smile more.
When is your driving test?
Why?
Eun-hee asked me.
She should just ask me if she's curious.
What's the point of asking through you?
I guess she wants to give you…
Taffy to wish you success.
Ms. Kim. We don't need
to do a separate meeting, right?
Why not?
I said I wish to quit this year
during my salary negotiations last year.
And then you said you can't
work at a publishing company
that's obsessed with English study books.
I know I get paid every month
for selling study books.
I never said that. Not even in my dreams.
Do you have a plan?
Yes.
I should've focused on
working in the office!
Listen to your friend!
Learn your lesson!
How did it go?
Chan-hyuk's test is today.
Don't you…
regret what you told me?
I thought about it all night long.
I'm not the type of guy
that says things I might regret.
You must be happy because you're great.
When I heard…
that you took me out of your heart
to see me before you went to sleep,
my heart raced too much to sleep.
As you said,
I took you out to see you in bed.
and it reminded me of myself
when I had cut ties with you.
I went to alumni reunions
where I thought you might come
and went to that bookstore
in Gwanghwamun a lot as well.
But I never ran into you.
I recalled the time I couldn't contact you
but looked for you.
If we ran into each other back then,
we might be wearing a ring
to commemorate our 1000th day.
At that time…
I thought Jong-pal left me
because the 30-year-old me back then
was pathetic, incapable, and didn't
have a good family background.
I wanted to change my life.
Write three pages a day,
which is 100 pages in a month.
Read 100 pages of a book every day.
Only plans.
I only had plans.
You know that kids with bad grades
work hard on their schedules, right?
Well begun is half done.
Half?
I achieve everything in my mind.
I read it before I cleaned
the entire house,
and nothing was finished properly.
I always write the beginning only.
I have no talent.
When I'm at work, I laugh and chat,
worry about my bosses and co-workers,
and make mistakes.
Aren't you self-reflecting
a little too much in front of your friend
who's about to get a government license?
Yes.
I am self-reflecting.
I got to like the ordinary days
a little bit.
This ring has that meaning.
A gift for myself.
Loving myself, starting today.
Even so, my confidence is still low,
so I need to improve it first.
Then I can seriously think about
what you said to me.
Someone who truly has low confidence
can’t say they have low confidence openly
like you just did.
Well, anyway,
I must date you, who decided
to love yourself,
starting today.
Should I get a ring for myself too?
Why are you so straightforward?
Going straight can only make you fail.
I can take it again.
Thanks to you
I think I can be cool about
this place as well.
I think it would hurt less too.
Yes.
Mr. Park Chan-hyuk?
Please get ready.
You must come
the day before the operation,
so we'll call you about the schedule.
If it's benign, then it's the best.
Even if it's malignant,
brain tumors these days
have a high recovery rate.
We will tell you the separate guidelines.
-Let's go.
-Doctor.
Does that mean
the reason my memories got mixed up
wasn't the accident?
The tumor moved a bit,
and it was pressing the part
in charge of memories.
I got my memories back now,
but can I lose them again
if I don't get the surgery?
If the tumor grows a bit bigger
and puts more pressure on the brain,
it can cause trouble with your memory.
Ms. Sook?
Were you shocked
thinking I turned back to 22 again?
I'm sorry.
I…
need to adjust my workload
and clean my truck too, so…
Let's book the surgery after that.
Do what the hospital tells you to do.
They said the surgery isn't difficult.
You didn't drink or smoke.
You even climbed all the mountains
in Korea at least once.
so I'm sure you can overcome that.
I climbed all of them once?
I climbed them at least 12 times.
I didn't even touch alcohol or cigarettes.
I know I shouldn't say this,
but I'm as solid as a rock.
I'm proud of you.
We…
graduated from marriage.
I'll take care of things myself.
You've been chasing me around
with a flower in your hands,
and you say that now?
See? One flower wasn't enough for you.
I should've given you a bouquet.
Mr. Kim Sang-sik.
Don't tell jokes to let it pass.
Think about it in my shoes.
If I'm sick, can you
tell me to take care of things myself?
If you don't want the kids to find out,
get surgery quickly.
Get well and live freely, okay?
Hi.
I made my daughter join
such a horrible family…
Was there someone you know among them?
No.
There wasn't.
It was a stranger.
A total stranger.
Let's go.
No. 3, you passed.
Congratulations.
I promised, right?
I'll help you with practicing.
I will coach you strictly,
so prepare yourself.
Okay.
I saw on social media
that couples have quarrels
when coaching each other with driving.
I guess it's time for us
to start doing that, right?
Can I see that too, please?
Shall I take all of them
out for you, then?
I'm sorry, can you show me
the one on the front…
-This one?
-Yes.
When you're old…
even an appendectomy can be difficult.
Mom.
Why?
Mom, you know how much I love you, right?
Mom.
Tell Dad to come back home.
Get your arms off me.
Did Dad say something?
No.
I need to move out too.
You said you'll never.
Well…
I even have some friends who are married.
I have to be on my own.
What is this?
Young-sik.
Go back to Ulsan.
She might come back
because she misses the kid.
If you don't want to go back,
then let's settle down here.
Please, no.
The sea of Incheon looks terrible.
I'm going to go back to Ulsan.
You show people how you feel
and smile all the time.
But why were you so harsh
to your wife, the mother of your child?
Wait.
How did you know, Dad?
It's because you're just like me.
Your leg.
You're ashamed about it…
so you were afraid she might
run away because of it, right?
I wasn't happy doing that, either.
You must learn how precious your wife is,
so just wait.
I need to…
go someplace now.
Where are you going?
Are you looking for a specific law firm?
There's a floor guide here,
and there's Yoo Min-woo
Patent Law Firm here.
And I'm Yoo Min-woo. Nice to meet you.
CHIEF YOO MIN-WOO
I'm not here for a patent.
-Oh, but still. Take it.
-Okay.
If you need patent counseling, call me.
If anyone looks like they need me,
then introduce them to me.
-Okay.
I heard there's a lounge here.
Which floor is it on?
I'm actually on my way there now.
-Let's go.
-Okay.
What made you want to go to the lounge?
-Well…
-To take a break?
No, that's not why.
Part-timers and employees
aren't too different.
Some things are different like
medical insurance and unemployment
benefits.
Do you not want to be
an official employee here?
That makes me sad.
Come on, that's not why.
I love you so much.
You're confessing your love
during career counseling?
I…
wish to live freely as a freelancer.
Is it because
you like me so much,
and you feel sorry to be paid?
Yes, that's right.
Ask him.
CEO, you don't have tons of money, do you?
Don't try to persuade the kid
-The kid?
-to be an official employee.
I guess he doesn't need
medical insurance and so on.
Maybe he wants to go abroad.
I'll think about it.
Ms. Kim is working again.
Which Ms. Kim?
Ms. Kim Eun-joo. She got divorced.
I'm sure that smart woman
made sure she got alimony.
If so, is she single now?
I guess I must comfort her.
Let's invite her for a drink.
If she's looking for work here and there,
it means she needs money, right?
There are tons of other places
that need true comforting.
Attorney Kim isn't looking for work.
All the firms are competing to hire her.
Yuna Kim and Kim Yeon-Koung,
the sports queens.
She's on the same level.
Yuna Kim retired a long time ago.
A legend never dies.
Patent Attorney Kim isn't really a legend.
-She isn't.
-Now,
the most important thing
is how to win a lawsuit against
a powerful and large conglomerate.
Let's talk about that.
but I think it won't be easy
like how it was last time.
Patent Attorney Kim Eun-joo!
Your sister is here.
-Let's go to the meeting room.
-Okay.
Did you wait long?
No.
Continue with your conversation.
You're Patent Attorney Kim's sister?
I've always wanted to meet you.
We're…
like avatars, you know.
Avatars.
If my sister was a trainee…
It was around ten years ago.
You still remember
what she said back then?
Since then and until now,
all the words Patent Attorney Kim said
are like quotations, so once I hear them,
I can never forget them.
They're arrows, not words.
Anyway,
ten years ago was
when my youth was at its peak.
I was also enjoying my youth
for the joy of passing the exam,
so I wasn’t hard-working
during my trainee days.
But I'm glad I had fun at that time.
Right now, my work controls my life.
If I see anyone
who wants to have this job,
I will stop them at all costs.
I miss that time.
At that time…
I could drink two bottles of soju
with some anchovy broth.
Back then, I could easily drink
three bottles of soju with some kkakdugi.
I could drink four with beef soup.
Five bottles with pickled radish.
Six bottles with red pepper paste.
Was it seven or eight?
I don't quite remember.
Right. My sister hates heavy drinkers.
Right. Your younger sister
is a heavy drinker.
I can't even drink half a bottle nowadays.
It's too much.
No, I don't drink anymore.
I can't drink anymore.
Patent Attorney Kim.
Here…
This realtor's office
is a trustworthy one.
I consulted them to downsize my office,
and I thought you'd be
looking for a new office.
Here, take a look.
I got one.
Right.
You're always on top of things.
Are you starting your own office?
-A chief.
She'll be chief just like me.
So you two were close enough
to talk behind my back
when you were trainees?
He stood up for you
when people were bad-mouthing you.
We're not in that kind of relationship.
His drinking habits reminded me
of you at get-togethers,
so I told him, "You're like my sister."
What was that drinking habit
that reminded you of me?
He made a mistake
and made things complicated.
But he asked me to criticize nicely.
He said he made more mistakes
because I scare him.
Right.
I totally understand how he feels.
He keeps repeating the same mistakes,
so he needs the pain to stop entirely.
I have to point it out.
Pointing things out is painful.
It can't be nice.
That's enough.
My sister, that's your problem.
No one makes mistakes
because they like to make them.
When they realize their mistakes,
it breaks their hearts.
But you pour salt on the wound
without any change
in your facial expression.
That hurts.
Okay, let's stop here.
I'll stop.
What's that ring?
It's not…
from that man who was
in front of your house, is it?
What's with the question?
What's upsetting you this time?
You didn't even see him that much.
What's with the face?
Do as you wish.
-It's not from him. We broke up.
-That's good.
-Eun-joo.
-You broke up with him,
so what's that ring?
You said I'm cowardly.
I wanted to fix that,
so I bought it in order to love myself.
What now? What about it is pathetic?
From what I see
you love yourself enough already.
So why put on a ring
to love yourself more?
Don't say that to others.
They'll say you're immature.
I told someone already.
By the way…
do we have to go so suddenly like this…
We should. Yes.
We should go.
What is this?
What a lovely color.
Dad.
Yong-gyoo!
I came with Eun-joo.
I told Eun-hee not to tell you
because I was afraid you might
feel uncomfortable coming here.
I'm going to move soon.
Mom's heart will break
if she sees you living here.
I'm going to move soon.
They're going back to Ulsan,
and I'm going to move too.
I saw that there are houses equipped
with refrigerators,
washing machines, and air conditioners.
Use the money in the bankbook you took.
You should know
if you thought about it in my shoes.
If you calculate it in terms of
paying off debt to me,
then I must calculate it
starting from my birth.
Yes.
Okay.
I will use that money.
That's enough to get a place tomorrow.
Then get it tomorrow.
Eun-joo.
Try looking for your biological father.
I'm not doing that.
If you're saying that because of me…
No.
I'm sure there's a reason why
Mom didn't look for him all her life.
I'm sure it was purely because of me.
At first…
I thought I couldn't ask for more
if your mother was with me.
But then…
I heard people whispering
that they couldn't understand
why your mother,
who lacks nothing,
married someone like me.
That was when I became a loser.
I suspected that she might
be curious about your father
and that she'd contact him.
That's an incurable disease.
I did something so shameful
I can't even hide from it.
Find your father if you want to.
You have to know everything
and make things clear.
I know your personality.
Is she eating well?
You said you'd leave after drinking water.
Why are you still here?
Did you tell Dad about the divorce?
He says everything's his fault
no matter what the subject is.
I'm afraid he would say
my divorce is his fault too,
so I'm going to tell him later.
Yes, well done.
Don’t make that face. Go.
You know because you live alone too.
Being alone can be good at times.
All right.
By the way, about our Dad,
I never knew he liked
taking photos that much.
I thought he only took flower photos.
I guess we are flowers to him.
Eun-joo.
Don't do that.
A sudden change in a person means death.
Bye.
Hey, Chan-pal!
You should've waited inside.
Why are you standing here?
Did you miss me that much?
I didn't want to waste my money on tea.
That's too practical.
What?
By the way…
why did you come all the way here?
If we can't see each other often,
we should see each other
when there's time.
Wouldn't that make your decision easier?
Hey…
Have you always been so…
This is a bit…
I'm still a bit…
Actually…
I'm here because of Ji-woo.
Oh.
So it's a matter of an employee.
What is it?
Ji-woo doesn't want to be
an official employee.
Why not? It looked like
he's been waiting so long.
Have you heard anything about
Ji-woo's girlfriend?
I only thought of him as the little kid,
but I guess he's old enough
to have a girlfriend.
Did he tell you?
How can he treat his sister like this…
He didn't tell me, either.
It looks like Seo-young knows a bit.
Is it because they're the same generation
and they can understand?
Thinking about it,
the families don't know much
about who's dating who, do they?
Is that so?
He's not a kid.
Let him do what he wants
to do in his life.
Right?
What do you want to eat?
Let's go have something delicious.
What should we eat?
Pyongyang naengmyeon?
Fast food.
Fast food?
What do you want?
How about tteokbokki?
-Fast food?
-Yes.
Kkakdugi.
Anchovies.
Soy sauce boiled beef.
The table isn't colossal.
It can't be too far to reach.
Just eat it as it's set.
-Let's eat.
-Yes.
Thank you for the food.
Here.
CONSENT FOR SURGERY
Read this part, please.
You can suffer death,
paralysis of the entire body,
upper body, or lower body,
loss of hearing and sight,
and loss of memories
as the after-effects of surgery.
Please sign here.
PATIENT OR GUARDIAN
YOON TAE-HYUNG FAMILY MEDICINE CLINIC
Hi.
If it's hard for you to take care of this,
give it to your mother.
That's so like you.
Finishing everything accurately.
Do you even know enough
about me to say that?
Put yourself in my shoes.
You'd understand that I can't forgive you.
Mistakes.
Bad lies.
Fraud.
I'm sick of suffering them
again and again,
so I'm going to focus on my life.
So what I did to you…
was a mistake, a bad lie, and a fraud.
I now understand it clearly.
I'm sorry.
Don't ever
do that again to anyone else.
Don't ever do that again.
MOTHER-IN-LAW
Don't worry too much.
I feel like I can fly,
both physically and mentally.
Are you sure you don't
want to tell the kids?
I'm not going to be
a troublemaking father.
I'll tell them proudly
after I fully recover.
I…
I need to do something.
Okay.
You don't need to come today.
You don't have to
do anything for me today.
Go and do your thing.
I'll be back.
I heard
that you accepted
the attorney's opinion on the alimony.
I don't want to have a lengthy fight.
You wanted me to apologize to you?
Not anymore.
You lost your chance.
I know you're not the type to tell,
but I want you to keep the reason
for the divorce a secret.
You got everything you want,
so now you apologize
and even ask for a favor.
A divorced man.
That can serve as a barrier
to keeping the family from worrying.
To do that for his family…
Tae-hyung went to my parents' house
and kneeled like a sinner.
He said it's all his fault.
He couldn't even lift his head.
I believe…
that you're even more heartbroken
than I am.
Sang-sik had to get a loan to buy it,
but he was extremely happy
after buying this truck.
It has a name too.
A name?
It's Lucky.
Whenever he drove it, he used to say,
"Go, Lucky!"
If we sell it without consulting him…
he's going to kill me.
He looks soft,
but when he gets angry,
he's blinded by his anger.
You know it more than I do.
I'm scarier than him when I get angry.
I'm worried he might say he wants to
drive again when he sees the truck.
Dying on his own is okay,
but I'm afraid he might harm someone.
WEDDING INVITATION
Sang-sik.
That's enough.
The wedding hall is going to explode.
I'm going to write down everyone
who comes to my mind.
About 100 people.
What? Are you starting a political party?
Even if I invite 100 people,
some of them might not be able to come.
I have no relatives.
I need this many people to come.
Yes, Eun-joo.
Dad, you're on your break, right?
I just ate and I'm writing
a list of invitees for the wedding.
How many do you want?
Just 50.
Give me 100.
I need at least 100.
Dad.
The wedding hall is small.
And people these days
only invite closest friends.
Really?
I'll leave room for ten people.
And I'll give you ten invitations.
Okay.
Ten.
What about breakfast?
I'm tired. I'm going to bed.
Eun-joo's wedding invitations are out.
She left some for you.
I'm not inviting anyone.
You can use the ones left for me.
People these days don't invite
that many people to weddings.
Don't make Eun-joo worry.
Our eldest daughter
got skinny with her wedding coming up,
so why would I make her worry?
I can't invite just a few.
So I'm going to let it pass quietly.
But if you don’t invite anyone,
Eun-joo won't feel comfortable.
I'm doing it to make
my daughter feel comfortable.
She won't know if I don't tell her.
So you stay quiet!
The bride is too busy to care
about her father's friends.
WEDDING INVITATION
HANSEONG NEUROPSYCHIATRY DEPARTMENT
MEDICAL NOTE
Happy occasion.
The stir-fried anchovies are delicious.
Sad occasion.
My kids aren't calling me.
Angry occasion.
Myself.
Happy occasion.
Bulgogi.
Sad occasion.
I can't sleep.
Angry occasion.
Myself.
I talked to my eldest daughter
on the phone.
She told me to give out
only ten wedding invitations.
Angry occasion.
Myself.
She hid fruits.
Do you even think it's a waste
for me to eat fruits?
Yes!
I do!
I've been driving all night long,
and you want me to go out
and make money right away?
I want to die.
WRITE ABOUT HOW YOU FEEL RIGHT NOW
I WANT TO DIE
You…
You said you look up
to your father, right?
Because in this world,
social connections and diplomas
mean everything,
but he worked and provided
for his family on this own.
You were never intimidated
when you talked about him.
I saw
him at the hospital.
I didn’t say hi.
We're not in-laws anymore.
But I thought I should tell you at least.
Please think of this as my apology.
If you work as a doctor for a long time,
I can tell if someone has…
a serious illness or not
just by looking at the face.
Were my parents there together?
Yes.
I must keep confidentiality,
so I won't tell you anymore.
It looks like…
they decided not to tell their children.
Parents…
sometimes make decisions like that.
Find out about it in any way possible.
Okay.
Right now.
We're here, so we need to take a photo.
Yes.
-Go stand.
-All right, stand together.
-Eun-hee.
-Yes.
Take one with Eun-joo and me.
Okay, here we go.
You need to smile.
Okay, smile!
One, two, three!
Oh.
What were you doing?
Isn't it obvious? I was at a bank.
I did bank things.
About that girlfriend of yours in Toronto…
When did you start dating her?
She's from the same school.
How…
How did you know she's in Toronto?
I'm not stupid. I can look things up.
Have you been keeping in touch
with her since she went to Toronto?
No, it wasn't like that.
We chatted while gaming
and we really hit it off
so we messaged each other separately.
And it was her.
We were both shocked.
So you ran into her in a game?
Why did you send her money?
Money?
You were at the currency exchange.
Oh. That.
No more questions, please.
Let's respect each other's privacy.
Someone might think he quit working here.
Why is his desk so empty?
Chan-hyuk, I'm at the airport.
I'm sending you a message
before I board the plane.
I'm sorry I couldn't tell you
the biggest decision
in the 26 years of my life.
If you knew about it,
it would've grown into something big.
I think my family
will stop me if I tell them,
so I'm running away now.
I've been planning this for a long time,
but I'm not all that happy.
I thought it'd be freeing
to leave my family,
but if you explain it to my sisters
and comfort them,
I'm sure they will make
Mom and Dad understand.
I'm sorry, Chan-hyuk.
The caller cannot be reached.
Please leave a message after the tone.
When you're finished recording…
What the heck?
What is it?
EUN-HEE
I'M RUNNING AWAY
I'VE BEEN PLANNING THIS FOR A LONG TIME
What…
does this mean?
Let's go to the airport.
He's already on the plane.
He probably went to Toronto.
Seo-young said she'll find a way
to reach him via social media.
Was I…
nothing to Ji-woo?
Am I just a family
he wants to escape from?
What's going to happen to my family?
We seriously knew…
nothing about each other.
Ji-woo is a grown-up.
He can leave anywhere if he wants.
Even if it's family,
if he wants to leave, then he can.
DEPARTMENT: NEUROSURGERY
PATIENT'S NAME: KIM SANG-SIK
DURATION: 8 HOURS AND 41 MINUTES
OPERATING CENTER
The surgery went well.
The location of the tumor was unideal,
so it took a long time.
We tried the best we can.
Let's keep an eye on his recovery.
Now everything depends on the patient.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
It went well.
It went well. That's a relief, right?
Mr. Sang-sik.
-Dad.
-Mr. Sang-sik.
Mr. Sang-sik!
Code Blue for Mr. Kim Sang-sik.
Dad!
Why didn’t they tell us?
I'm sure he couldn't even if he wanted to.
Ji-woo's first love disappeared.
I'm careful with my words
even to my family,
but with you, I feel relaxed.
Do we have to know everything
because we're family?
Then will they not tell us if something
happens because it might burden us?
Ms. Sook
I'm afraid that I might not be able to
return this time.
Subtitle translation by: Hae-lim Lee
Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.