ENJOY ALL VOD IN HIGH QUALITY @ 4KVOD.TV
GET LIVE TV,MOVIES,SHOWS IN ONE PACKAGE
GANG VS. G-MEN
PLANNING: SHIGERU OKADA, TSUNE YABE
SCREENPLAY: SAKAE SAJIMA
PHOTOGRAPHY: YOSHIKAZU YAMAZAWA
SOUND: KOICHI IWATA
LIGHTING: KENZO GINYA
ART DIRECTOR: HIROMU KITAGAWA
MUSIC: KOICHI KAWABE
EDITOR: KAN SUZUKI
ASST. DIRECTOR: MIKIO KOYAMA
PRODUCTION ASST.: EIJI TAKEDA
DEVELOPING：TOEI CHEMICAL INDUSTRY
STARRING
KOJI TSURUTA
TATSUO UMEMIYA
SHINICHI CHIBA
YOSHIKO SAKUMA
TETSURO TAMBA
DIRECTED BY KINJI FUKASAKU
SPECIAL JOINT INVESTIGATION MEETING
Hey, here they come!
Chief! What was
the meeting about?
- What are you investigating?
- Is Tatsumura involved?
There are rumors that Sanritsu
Industries is behind all this.
Isn't its president Tatsumura
the mastermind behind this incident?
Aren't you flooded with complaints about
police ineffectiveness in the case?
They say the authorities are too
cautious, or worse, weak-kneed.
I'll ask you the same question:
What do you guys think?
It's easy to criticize others.
But are you trying to bring back
the old, heavy-handed police power?
It's not as if cautious
investigation is bad.
And that's part of the
difficulty of this job.
It's not you who's been getting your
men killed at every turn, it's me.
Oh, hi.
The press?
Yeah. I got a little excited.
I went to the farewell ceremony
for Detective Sugiyama.
I see. Well.
That's three in a row.
- What a shame.
- Yeah.
And...the meeting?
It's like we've hit a dead end.
We don't have a concrete plan.
All the violent incidents
in this neighborhood
are connected to
Sanritsu Industries.
I'm sure I'm on
the right track,
but I don't know where to start
to catch them by the tail…
We don't have a single clue.
We're helpless. It's our own fault
that the city is calling us weak-kneed.
The three men who died
would turn in their graves.
SANRITSU INDUSTRIES
BUSINESS INFORMATION
CHAIRMAN SAICHI SAKURA
PRESIDENT JŪGO TATSUMURA
I just had an idea.
I heard a rumor on the street.
Tatsumura has recently taken
complete control of the organization.
They say things are getting
awkward with his uncle, Sakura.
Mmm-hmm... So?
If we can crack the organization by
successfully exploiting this opportunity,
we might be able to get some
clues for the investigation.
I see.
But that would require--
Of course.
We can't do it alone.
We really need the help of a man
knowledgeable about the organization.
Mmm-hmm.
A kind of guerrilla operation.
Interesting idea,
but I don't know if there's anybody
who could be that useful.
I actually have a little
bit of an idea about that.
Oh? Who is it?
TOJIMA BROTHERS
Hello!
Coming!
Oh! Old man!
Hi.
Welcome.
- Are you two working together?
- No.
She wouldn't stop asking
me to show her how to fix it.
Boy, you look terrible!
Oh!
Did you have the ceremony yet?
No, not yet.
It seems rather silly
to call it a wedding now, but…
- We'll invite you when we do, Mr. Ogata.
- Sure.
- Please come in.
- Okay.
It looks like two more cars have been
added after not coming here for a while.
But the two drivers are unavailable,
so they're just like decorations now.
- Please have a seat.
- Okay.
Hard-working, kind-hearted…
She'll make a good wife.
Yeah...
I suppose so.
So, what brought
you here today?
Well…
It's kind of hard to say
what I'm asking you to do.
Actually, I just wanted to ask
you to go back to the old you.
- The old me?
- Yes.
A yakuza.
Old man, don't joke
around with me.
I wouldn't joke about
asking you to do this.
Please...
I really need your help!
What's the story?
You want me to be a G-man.
You're no stranger
to Tatsumura.
I would like to ask you to do this.
And let me assure you,
this isn't about saving the
face of the police or anything.
We have to crush that germ-like
organization as soon as possible.
Old man, if you want to talk about that,
please take it up with someone else.
I'm asking because I know
I can count on you.
It's not a job that
just anybody can do.
Don't give me too much credit.
I'm not that respectable.
But--
First of all, I don't want to do
anything that'll open old wounds.
Okay.
Maybe I shouldn't have
asked you to do it.
Why don't you get out
of this business?
I'd be happy to
help you find a job.
It would be my pleasure.
But I'm a man with no education at all
living only for this job
since I was a simple police officer.
The grime sticks and
doesn't seem to come off.
I might have to die to get it clean.
I'm sorry I can't help you.
It's okay.
I'll definitely
attend your wedding.
Yeah.
Bye.
Oh? Is Mr. Ogata
going home already?
- Yes.
- Oh.
What was that about?
It has nothing to do with us.
Yes, this is Tojima
Transport Co.
Huh?
What's up?
It's the usual…
- Hello.
- How's it going?
Are you ready to
accept our protection?
I refuse. I don't want
to be under your care.
Think carefully about it.
Without a driver there wouldn't
be any business, you know.
What?
What did he say this time?
Don't worry about it.
Huh? The car's back.
Oof!
Brother!
- Osamu!
What's wrong?
He said he got
jumped by thugs.
- Thugs?
- Yeah.
- Let's go inside to treat the wound.
- Yes.
So when did you get out?
Today.
I was on my way here.
I was surprised to see that the
truck was marked "Tojima Transport"!
Boss, I'm quitting.
No matter how many lives
I have, it won't be enough.
What are you saying?
The two guys taking a break must
have gone through the same thing I did.
You can't tell us
to fight the yakuza.
Let's do it, bro!
I can help you!
To be honest, I'm disappointed
that you quit the business.
Osamu...
What have you learned
from four years in juvie?
I'm not going to fight.
I'm going now because they're
probably waiting for me.
You're free to quit.
You can take your
salary up to today.
Bro!
I'm disappointed in you, bro.
Where's the brother
that I used to know?
I'm sure he wouldn't just sit back
and let this happen to him!
Idiot! Damn it!
You're not my brother!
Osamu!
Don't talk to your
brother like that.
- Take care of yourself.
- Thank you.
But, you know, don't you
think it's frustrating?
When you're
provoked like that--
It's frustrating, but we'll be out of
business if we take on every fight.
We're not selling fights.
But you were the boss's daughter.
You should understand how I feel.
I've forgotten, you know, the old days.
Both your brother and I.
Suit yourself.
No wonder my brother
became a coward.
His wife's too beautiful
and too decent.
Sassy little thing,
aren't you?
You should look before
you say something weird.
TOJIMA BROTHERS
You see?
This business belongs
to you and your brother.
Damn it.
My brother, he…
Your brother was really looking
forward to you getting out.
You have to understand.
We're half-brothers.
We're not meant to be like
other brothers in the world.
What are you talking about?
I'll throw you a welcome
home party tonight.
What's your favorite thing?
What do you want to eat?
Osamu? Osamu!
Where are you going?
Who was it?
Who did this?
- Mr. Jo.
- Boss!
- This is my car.
- What?
I parked it on the corner
over there, and it's…
That's right.
Why is this happening again?
Shall I take care of this?
Mind your own business.
Leave me alone.
Don't say that.
You need our protection in case
things like this happen. Right?
- That means you guys are--
- Boss!
Anyway, let's go in.
I see…They've even come to
your business for protection money?
If they know the old you, they wouldn't
be able to do something stupid like that.
Well, go ahead.
Sorry. Because of my mess,
even your store is--
No, actually, my business
is being blackmailed, too.
You too, Jo?
Yeah.
In the beginning
they called me to invite me.
When I refused, the thugs came.
I told 'em to look people in the eye
when talking and threw 'em out.
And here we are today.
You didn't report it
to the police, did you?
Yeah, I thought about that.
But if the cops are there all
day long, no customers will come.
They predicted
that much, all right.
Do you know which group
the thugs belonged to?
They belong to the Takeda
family down the street.
I think Sanritsu Industries is the
mastermind behind the protection racket.
I heard that the
Takeda family's boss
became a shareholder of
Sanritsu Industries the other day.
I think that's fishy.
I didn't know that.
A champion, huh?
Well, I'm past my prime if
I'm remembering the old days.
Welcome back!
Oh...
- What happened to your car?
- Uh…
What happened to the drivers?
Well…
Did they all quit?
Yes.
But that's okay.
Hire someone new again.
Maybe I should learn to drive.
What about tomorrow's work?
I turned it down earlier.
I'm sure it's not a good time.
Come on! Tonight is Osamu's
welcome home party.
It's going to be
at my apartment.
- Osamu?
- What's wrong?
I showed those guys from the Takeda
family how strong I got in juvie.
Idiot! What would you do if
something happened to you?
Worry more about yourself
than you do about me!
- Osamu, what happened?
- Ouch!
Captain Fujikawa was
happy that you agreed.
We'll help as much as we can.
But this work is informal.
Yes.
So it's strange when I'm the
one asking you to do this, but
- you take good care of yourself and--
- Old man.
You needn't worry about that.
I'm willing to do it even
if no one asks me to do it.
Well, I feel better now
that you put it that way.
And what about your subordinates?
I want to work in my own way,
so I'm going to get five or six
guys who are used to fighting.
What I'd really like from you
is a car that starts fast.
I've already got it for you.
I've got a good driver too.
- Come with me now.
- Okay.
Why did we stop here?
Well, wait and see.
He'll appear any moment.
Huh?
Matsushima!
Hey, you're caught red-handed.
I haven't done it yet.
You should be glad you haven't.
If you had, you'd be back
eating stinky food in jail.
Sorry.
I'll tell you what, instead, I'm
going to have a little chat with you.
Please, no more lectures--
That's not what I meant.
- I want to show you something.
- Huh?
Whoa!
This engine--
It's like a sports car!
What do you think?
Would you like to drive it?
Oh? You don't mind?
- I'll leave it with you.
- Yeah!
Oh, it's a police motorcycle.
- Should we make a run for it?
- Idiot!
You should stop
for the poor guy.
Are you sure?
Do you know how fast
you were going just now?
Thank you for your work,
but there's a reason for that.
Are you on a case?
Yes, well, something like that.
Sorry about that.
Thank you for your work.
This is great!
Shall we try a little more?
I've had enough of this.
I'll turn it down this time.
I'll introduce you to
a guy you might like. Go!
You damned fool!
What the hell are you doing?
Fuck you, motherfucker!
Come here!
Get the fuck off me!
You son of a bitch!
You ruined a girl's life!
Get the fuck off me!
Get off of me!
- What's going on?
- Oh...
He tricked a runaway
girl and sold her.
Oh.
Well, that's the guy.
He's so hot-blooded that he
sometimes forgets his duties.
But he's a great shot.
I'll introduce you.
- Excuse me.
- Oh!
What are you doing?
- I see, he's fast--
- Drop the gun!
Oh, excuse me.
Mr. Ogata asked me
to test your skills.
Sorry, sorry.
This man is right.
Never trust a person
who has a gun.
By the time you get mad
at their trick, it's too late.
Okay. Old man,
you should explain.
- I have some other ideas.
- Okay.
Ron.
There you go.
- Here, reach!
- Ron!
Little three dragons. Half flash.
You bastard!
You son of a bitch!
Bro!
I don't know what all this is about,
but give him a break.
I'm telling you--
Let's go. Come on.
Man! Thanks for saving me. I guess
it's different when you're a pro.
Don't you have any shame,
cheating a bunch of thugs?
Well, it's like they say,
"Poverty dulls the spirit."
What's up?
I need to borrow your help.
It's work, isn't it?
Is it a safe or is it a--
Neither. Anyway, come
to my house tonight.
If you want the manager,
he ain't here!
The owner changed today.
Go there to collect the debt!
Looks like things are
pretty rough for you.
Boss. You've come
at a good time.
I'm not sure I'd enjoy a
farewell party by myself.
What farewell party?
They're all gone.
How did that happen?
Well...
A series of disturbances
the other night, you know,
bartenders running away,
waitresses being taken…
Even the debt was taken
over by Sanritsu Industries.
The former champion
is no longer in shape!
I'll give them all to that
bastard Tatsumura!
I'll explain later, but I want
you to come to my place tonight.
Hey, sis! My brother's back!
Honey, those people have
come to pick up the truck.
Did you really sell it?
Yeah, we've already
made the deal.
Please take it!
Hey, why are you doing this?
What are we going to do now?
I'm sorry to break it to you,
but I've decided to
go back to my old life.
What?
You'll have to live in the
apartment for a while.
That's the brother I know!
Sorry, but there's a world of men that
women don't understand. Right, bro?
You go live with her.
And get a job.
That's stupid!
Please, please don't do it.
Did you forget what
happened four years ago?
Didn't you almost die trying
to crawl out of the muck?
Don't get desperate just because
things aren't working here.
We can go somewhere
where there are no yakuza.
Please, please don't do it.
I'm sorry, but I've
made up my mind.
This time I'm going
to do it my way.
That's right!
That's right, brother!
But you can't do it alone, bro.
Hey, please, let me do it.
I'll bring my friends
if you want.
Idiot!
I said no, you can't do it.
Pack your bags with her.
I've now given you
the gist of it.
I'd really like some
help from you all.
I just want to assure you that
we're subcontracting for the police.
It's low-pay despite the risk.
I'd like to know if you're
still willing to take it on.
Please don't
hesitate to tell me.
When you say subcontracting for
the police, how will you start?
First I'll pretend to make
a comeback to the yakuza.
Then I'll infiltrate their organization
under the guise of a turf war.
That would mean
we're the Tojima family.
Gentlemen, this is the
perfect role for you.
If you look in the mirror
I think you'll see what I mean.
I don't want to flatter you, but
I'd hardly call you all good citizens.
But it takes a hell of a lot of
guts and horsepower to hit them.
You're all perfect team
members in that regard.
Hey, bro, even though it's police work,
we're putting our lives on the line.
There will be a little
reward, won't there?
I can't guarantee that.
I'm sure you'll
manage it just fine.
But don't forget there's
a policeman next to you.
So let's hear your answer.
Can you guys give me a hand?
Let's show them what we can do!
I'll get Tatsumura back
for his protection racket.
How about you, Matsushima?
Well, I'm being asked
to take care of the car.
I don't see anyone
else qualified.
Goro?
I'll do my best to
save the extra money.
Mr. policeman?
It's my duty so
I'll do whatever--
You scared me!
- Osamu!
- Brother...
Don't treat me like a stranger!
Everyone, I'm his
brother, Osamu Kaji.
We're actually half-siblings.
How many times
have I told you?
I'm not gonna
make you one of us.
Again with that.
I wish you'd trust me.
But a goofball like you
would be the first to get hit.
I can't take care
of a guy like that.
Well, then, brother.
You mean you can't--
You'd be slowing me down.
Give it up.
Fine, then!
I'll do my own thing!
Osamu... Osamu!
He's just like you the way he won't
back out of something once he's said it.
He's a real pain in the ass.
So everything is
okay then, right?
Okay, now let's get to work.
First you'll go out and spread word
that I'm making a comeback.
TOJIMA BROTHERS
♪ That man… ♪
By pistol.
By tommy gun.
♪ That man… ♪
By dynamite.
♪ Everybody, everybody
disappears in a puff of smoke ♪
With water.
♪ When the blood left
on the bed dries up ♪
There, I hear it.
♪ That rhythm ♪
♪ Sing it! ♪
♪ Dance all you want! ♪
♪ Jam session on an
enchanting night ♪
♪ I'm drunk and I'm all alone ♪
May I sit here?
If you don't mind
me sitting with you.
Would you like to
buy me a drink?
In return, you tell me
whose territory this is.
You sure aren't
tight-lipped, are you?
I'll have what he's having.
I hear a retired yakuza named
Tojima is making a comeback.
Well.
I'm sure there will
be an uproar now.
I don't think
Tatsumura will allow it.
But Tojima and Tatsumura
must have been like brothers.
People only think that's true.
They don't get along
with each other very well.
I'm telling you this
for your own good.
If you want to make a living as a
yakuza, it's smarter to join Tatsumura.
Thanks for the advice.
If you want, I can ask
the higher-ups for you.
Did Tatsumura ask you
to scout for the yakuza?
Huh?
You'll have to ask Tatsumura
if you can hire
a guy named Tojima.
Then you're…
Next time you see me,
call me Tojima.
RECREATION CENTER CONSTRUCTION
Who are you?
You almost got yourself killed.
Do you know what's
going on here?
I do, but thanks anyway.
Don't get me wrong.
I'm here to kill you.
Don't move!
Do you recognize this face?
Five years ago…
Five years ago?
In a turf war on the beach,
you shot a guy named Kuroki.
Then you're Kuroki's--
I'm his younger brother.
Now that you remember,
I'm going to kill you.
Wait!
That wasn't supposed
to be a fatal injury.
No respectable doctor
would've treated that wound.
It's no wonder it was fatal.
I made a vow then.
I swore I'd kill you
if I ever saw you!
Are you hurt?
You think you saved me?
That doesn't make up
for my brother!
Wait a minute!
I get how you feel, but
I've got a job I've got to do.
I won't let you stop me.
- Boss, are you hurt?
- I'm fine.
The advertisement worked 100%.
I've already got
a lot of sponsors.
That's the guy.
Him?
A debt is a debt.
I'll wait until
your job is done.
In exchange, I'm not leaving
your side for a while.
I won't let you die
until it's by my hand.
So you're a bodyguard. Well, okay.
He's an old friend of mine.
Try to get along.
Starting tomorrow
we're going to be busy.
SANRITSU INDUSTRIES
Boss, Tojima is here.
What do you want to do?
I thought they'd
be here by now.
Hey.
To what do we owe
this surprise?
It's been a while.
How's your shipping
company doing?
I heard you were happy together
with the previous boss's daughter.
I don't think I can make
a living as an honest man.
I'm going back
to the old Tojima.
I see. That's why you came all
the way out here to say hello.
Shimadzu. Let's celebrate
Tojima's comeback.
Book a welcome home party--
You already threw me
a welcome home party.
A fancy one with lead bullets.
I know it was supposed
to be a fireworks show,
but it was very much your style.
Tojima....
You've become nastier
living as an honest man.
I'm not as bad as you.
You took over this building
in less than four years?
I was hoping you'd tell me
how to make money.
That's the kind of advice one can
only get from a professional.
I wish you'd stop
with the innuendos.
Sanritsu Industries
is a legitimate company.
And we pay our taxes.
If you want, you can
go ask the tax office.
But I hear there's a lot of money to be
made without the tax office knowing.
What do you mean?
For example...
protection rackets.
That sort of work
fits these guys.
Don't move!
What's this?
A raccoon dog's tail?
I'm the one who built all this.
I have some allies,
but also many enemies.
You can never be too careful.
Everyone, leave us.
I think it's time to
cut to the chase.
I'm being extorted, it seems.
No, I just need a little help.
It's a lot of work to make up
for four years of absence.
I'd like to borrow your territory
for a while, for old time's sake.
Sorry, I don't have anything
like that right now.
I have enough to eat running a
theater and a recreation center.
Oh yeah? That's a relief.
Then I'll make my own
territory without reservation.
That's all well and good,
but be careful.
They say once a boxer retires,
he never makes a comeback again.
Jinxes can be broken
someday, you know.
Well, look forward to it.
I see.
Tojima has shown up
so now Tatsumura has
more things to worry about.
That's why he tried to
get rid of him last night.
That was a screw-up,
out of character for Tatsumura.
I'm getting lucky.
It's good to live a long time.
You've pit the two against each
other for your own advantage?
I'm the one who originally created
Sanritsu Industries, after all.
I didn't want to keep it in
Tatsumura's care forever.
So...
Shall we propose the election of a new
president at the next general meeting?
No, I think we'll wait
and see what Tojima does.
- Chairman!
- Hmm?
Mr. Tojima has come
to say hello to you.
Good thing he came now.
Have him come over here.
Mr. Chairman,
it's been a while.
Yeah, a while. I hear you
made a comeback the other day.
Yeah. I'll need
your help again.
Yeah, sure.
But now I'm
practically retired.
But…
I heard a rumor that you'll be returning
as president of Sanritsu once again.
There are too many
irresponsible rumors out there.
I agree.
I was even gossiping
with Tatsumura just now.
With Tatsumura? They say
you had a dispute last night.
That's just another
irresponsible rumor.
But you better be careful.
It's weird saying this
to your face,
I've always preferred you
to Tatsumura.
If you ever need help,
I'm always here for you.
Oh. I'll see you, then.
Well, I'll leave you
alone for today.
This is a fine house
for an old fox's nest.
And they're even planning
to expand the place.
SANRITSU INDUSTRIES
I see. That old man
and Tojima, huh?
I think we can still do
something about it now.
You're something yourself too.
What are you after?
The Sakura family's territory?
Well, if that's on the table.
Okay.
I'll grant you that.
In exchange, get to work.
Eliminate the old man.
Boss.
He's your blood relative.
I don't remember having
an uncle like that.
Murakami.
Take the Kijima brothers.
Mr. Chairman.
These men say that they
came from Tatsumura.
What do they want?
Can't you handle it yourself?
No, I definitely can't.
What are you doing?
Stop it, you!
CHAIRMAN OF SANRITSU
INDUSTRIES MURDERED
Killing anyone who
gets in the way?
But this is too much!
This is exactly how
Tatsumura works.
Now their organization
is strengthened again.
We have to find a
new way to get inside.
Welcome. Can I
get you a drink?
I don't have any money.
Here, let me pay with this.
We're supposed to ask for cash.
Don't be so uptight.
I heard whose
restaurant this is.
Welcome.
Eh?
Are you the one
I need to talk to?
Maybe. We'll see.
Boy, where are you from?
Check the family register.
No comment.
Well?! I want a clear answer!
Come this way.
Here.
The pistol.
Wait here.
MANAGER'S OFFICE
I have someone
we could use.
We heard your story.
- Go home for today.
- What?
We have to check if the gun
has been used in a crime.
If you can't tell by holding it,
then you're an amateur.
What?
That gun isn't loaded.
You're not qualified
to be a bouncer. Move!
Are you the boss?
If you really want to work
here, do as you're told.
Waving that thing around
won't get you anywhere.
Got it?
Got it.
Nice to meet you.
The Takeda family controls
the bar area here.
The bars and cabarets in this area
are the Yoshi family's territory.
Both are backed by
Sanritsu Industries, I'm sure.
Just as I thought.
So what's the connection between
Tatsumura and the owners?
It doesn't seem to be
just protection rackets.
I bet they're into something
more profitable than that.
Okay. This is
their turf, anyway.
Let's provoke them one by one.
Tojima's taking over this bar.
Get lost, goons!
Motherfucker!
Get him!
What the hell, you guys?
The Tojima family's taking
over this place now.
If you want protection
money, we refuse!
What?!
- How did you do?
- Good.
Ah. Now the Takeda
family's stronghold.
Let's all go together.
- What's that?
- I got it from the bar earlier,
but there are some weird
symbols in the purchase column.
Let's check the
next place too.
Go back and tell your boss.
Tojima is taking over
this business for a while.
It'd be interesting to
find a similar ledger.
- Let's check around.
- Yeah.
Somewhere like in here?
This is why amateurs
are no good.
Leave these things
to the professionals.
It's just been
high school so far.
Now comes the college class.
Find anything?
Nothing of value.
It's written the
same way as this.
What could this mean?
I'm sure it has something
to do with their organization.
Six people.
Just six people and they're
raiding turf all over the place.
And what do you want me to do?
I'm truly ashamed.
Actually, I'm going to
take care of this right now.
I just wanted
to let you know.
In that case,
leave him be.
Let him do his
thing for a while.
But that's--
Don't you get it?
What's a couple of
cabarets and bars?
The point is to keep our
organization unnoticed.
Wait and see what they uncover.
SANRITSU INDUSTRIES
- Hey.
- Huh?
So what are they doing?
They're not moving at all.
The car's crying.
We'll let it rest while it can.
What the hell is going on?
He's wearing a Sanritsu badge!
Who are you calling?
Oh, it's you, bro!
Don't scare me!
- I was just about to call you--
- Come here.
What the hell is going on here?
I used my brain a little.
Not many people know that
you and I are brothers, right?
Because we have
different last names.
So I figured it was up to me to
sneak into Tatsumura's place.
I told you that you can't.
It's too late. I'm in.
So you don't want
to hear what I got?
You got something?
Actually, I'm just
about to get it.
Idiot.
You've got me beat.
Well then, brother!
But be careful, you're
talking with the enemy.
If you're as careless as you
were just now, you're dead.
They're totally systematic.
In that organization,
unless you're a real old-timer,
you can’t figure out anything.
It seems so.
I tried to step on his income
streams, but it didn't work so well.
I'm sure he's got some
big source of money.
I'll find it eventually.
See you later, brother.
All right, place your bets!
But think carefully
before betting.
Watch closely!
Here we go.
That one.
You choose this one?
Are you sure this is the one?
Too bad!
I feel bad about
taking from a cop.
Okay, one more time!
We have a visitor.
Hey, stop.
They've been going to bars
and cabarets for a while.
They don't seem to be
collecting laundry.
What are they doing?
Okay, I'll find out.
Give me a hand.
Hey, can I get a light?
Thanks.
Hey, hey! Hey! Hey!
Hey, what do we do?
What do we do?
Good! It's a red light!
You stupid bastard,
you had me worried.
I see.
So the dry cleaner
was a collector.
Yeah.
But where is that
money coming from?
A bag this big with
a bunch of bills in it.
And instead of laundry,
there's a load of whiskey.
A Daihatsu Midget,
whiskey, and wads of cash…
What kind of mystery is this?
We’ll have to poke around more.
Come on.
I went to see Mr. Ogata.
I was hoping to ask
Mr. Ogata to stop you.
And he told me the truth.
You should have just told me.
Am I such an unreliable woman?
No.
This is my problem.
I thought I'd washed my hands of the
business, but they don't respect that.
I had to do it.
To break free.
I understand.
But this is not just about you.
Good luck.
You're doing a good
thing for the world.
But…
Don't overdo it.
♪ When I lie in bed, there's a man ♪
♪ When I drink wine, there are two men ♪
♪ When I walk down the street,
there are three men ♪
♪ They all stare at me, dead ♪
Boss, Tojima is here.
What?
Okay. I'll check it out.
♪ The people who loved me ♪
♪ They all disappear ♪
♪ Little red flowers in the heart
are hickeys made of lead bullets ♪
What's up?
Are you still
scouting for recruits?
Not anymore.
I found a really good warrior.
I think you're in
the wrong place.
Is that so?
I think I read the sign
properly and I came in.
I think the woman
made a mistake too.
Aren't you just a kid?
Don't smoke.
What?
I've got a lead.
I'm counting on it.
Punch me once.
You son of a bitch!
What should we do?
What's he up to?
- Let's go.
- Hold on.
Wait a little longer.
- Check the moonshine.
- Got it.
I'll leave that to you.
Oh, hello! Metropolitan Police?
Listen, I'm at the
"Night Castle" cabaret!
There are drunks rampaging!
Yes! Please come!
- You're saved by the bell.
- It's a draw.
Something extra.
I wonder if it's
just a turf war.
No, it can't be.
Moonshine.
This was the key to
their secret organization.
So, through the bosses of
the amusement quarters
they would get this moonshine
into bars, cabarets, and clubs,
then they paid profit
dividends to the shareholders.
Then this ledger is likely a
record of moonshine sales.
I wonder how much money
they can make on this.
If they put import prices
on such cheap liquor,
they'll make twenty
times as much.
- Twenty times?
- And it's not taxed.
Compared to that, protection
rackets are nothing.
In any case,
we're going to find out where
the moonshine factory is.
Then we can have
them by the throat.
First, let's do all we can
to find the couriers.
Wait a second.
What's that?
They're collecting
empty bottles.
So they finally have a
job that looks like a job.
That's kind of weird.
- What?
- Those two cars behind us.
They've been following
us for a while now.
Here they come!
Hey! That's one gone!
Hey! Here they come again!
Damn it!
That was close. Good job.
Hey, Matsushima, what's wrong?
Oh! Stupid son of a bitch!
Why didn't you tell me sooner?
This car was entrusted to me.
I can't leave it with anyone.
You're stubborn!
What's wrong?
We got shot at while tailing
the bottle collection truck!
Call a doctor!
If it gets in the papers,
they're gonna find out.
It's no time for
talk like that!
Wait. Lay him down over there.
Stay sitting.
Don't just stand there.
Run hot water.
Will it work?
It didn't work out
for my brother.
Because it was close
to his vital organs.
But it's going to
be okay this time.
Come on, bite down!
Harder!
Hey!
He only fainted.
It's done.
So their focus is now
on the organization.
By the looks of it, they're
doing a lot of research.
Maybe he's a rat for the cops.
No way.
No way would the
cops trust a yakuza.
But this needs a
thorough investigation.
If he's willing to go so far,
I have an idea too.
I came here today to talk to
you on behalf of Tatsumura.
So now you're going to join
me and take down Tatsumura?
Tatsumura wants to have
a peaceful talk with you.
I'm gonna use
this for a moment.
Hello.
Hey, it's me. Yeah, I'm
giving him the phone now.
It's Tatsumura.
Hello.
Tojiima? It's me.
I don't have anything to
talk to you about now.
You might not, but I do.
Say, would you like to
hear a pretty woman's voice?
What?
Would you like
to say something?
She doesn't seem to
have anything to say.
But you're not an idiot.
So I'm sure you'll
back off quietly.
Don't give in!
All you've done
will be for nothing!
Akiko!
Don't worry about me!
Don't back off for a second!
Akiko!
Stop!
Got it now?
Back off.
Hello?!
Hello?! Hell--
Damn it!
Looks like we're done here.
Well, I'll leave you to it.
Wait, you son of a bitch!
Boss...
SANRITSU INDUSTRIES
I'm here to see Tatsumura.
Stay out of this, thugs.
Mr. Tojima.
He's waiting for you.
Excuse me, but I'll
hold your things for you.
What's up?
Heh-heh. Well…
- Sis!
- Don't move!
Sorry about last night.
I didn't mean to
make things worse.
I just thought our discussion might
go better with a woman involved.
Well, have a seat.
We're not supposed to sit
down and talk to each other.
I see.
Well, let's hear your
answer right away.
You'll back off,
of course, right?
I'm not backing off yet.
Oh...
I guess we had it all wrong.
We thought you had
a thing for that woman.
So you don't care
what happens to her?
I'd like to ask you
something first.
Do you have the guts to
make a suicide pact with me?
A suicide pact?
Yeah.
You wouldn't have the guts.
Because you have
too many things.
You ruined my business.
And you even kidnapped Akiko.
Thanks to you, I'm really
naked. I have nothing to lose.
Not even my life.
If anything happens to Akiko,
you can be sure I'll kill you.
If you think being surrounded by
guns will stop me, you're wrong.
I swear I'll get it done.
How about it?
Shall I try it right now?
If you don't have the guts,
return Akiko immediately.
Then you can fight me.
Are you so rotten that
you can't even do that?
Boss, I know who the spy is.
Who is it?
It's that bastard Kaji.
He didn't see me and I caught
him trying to save the girl.
I tied him up and threw
him in the basement.
I see…
So he was the cop's dog.
Or was he your dog?
I guess that was a
stupid question to ask.
Let's ask Kaji himself.
Show our guest the way.
So you're a dirty rat and
you had me fooled, too.
I'd like to know
who asked you to do it.
I just felt sorry for the girl,
so I decided to let her go.
I'll make you wish
that you'd talked.
- Idiot!
- Bastard!
Idiot!
It's useless to beat me up.
Useless, huh?
Wait.
That's some nerve you got.
Give me the pistol.
Tatsumura, I have a request.
You're finally
starting to understand.
He was trying to save my girl.
I'm responsible for that.
If you're doing this
for me, don't bother!
I have no connection
whatsoever to you.
Besides, he's not someone
you can negotiate with.
I see.
Sit him up.
Wait.
If you're worried about me,
mind your own business.
I've admired men like you
since I was a kid.
You've been my dream.
Please.
Please don't destroy my dream.
Stop!
Wait.
Finally you're ready
to come clean.
I don't want to die by
the hand of this beast.
Mr. Tojima.
Shoot me with your hand.
Please.
Give me the gun!
This is one hell of a show.
Let me enjoy the spectacle.
Come on! Come on!
He's dead.
That takes care of one of them.
Think the next one
through carefully.
Our guests are leaving.
Politely see them out.
TOJIMA BROTHERS
Damn.
They're all over the place.
Everyone, just hang in there.
But Boss--
If we back off, Osamu
won't rest in peace.
Akiko won't be pleased either.
But with such surveillance!
There's still a way!
We're disbanding today!
What?
The Tojima family
has disbanded?
Yes, I'm sure.
I saw it with my own eyes.
With him still around,
we can't be too careful.
Why don't you get rid of all
the moonshine we have on hand?
Mmm. You'd better get prepared.
I'll have the factory
moved to the Kansai region.
- Shochu with cider.
- Sure.
Hey! How's it going?
What's wrong?
- That's weird.
- What is?
Look. A milk truck
at this hour?
If it's a courier,
it should have an escort.
That's it. I'm sure of it.
But how do we follow it?
Got it! I'll handle it!
Hey! What are you doing?
I'm borrowing it for a while.
Idiot! I'm a cop!
We're gonna lose 'em
if you talk like that!
I'll return it later!
There it goes!
Are you coming or not?
Looks like I have no choice.
I'm with you.
They're slowing down.
It's to see if we're following!
They're changing lanes.
I'm gonna pass!
Okay. Here we go.
Let the boss know right away.
I'll take a good look
at the surroundings.
- Hello?
- Boss!
- Yeah.
- We located the moonshine factory!
What?
It's in the warehouse
district at the harbor!
Come soon!
Everyone is supposed
to meet here!
Okay! I'll be right there!
You.
I told you I'd never
leave your side.
Now you owe me one.
Make sure the debt
won't be irrecoverable.
Great work.
Here's a map of the
area around the factory.
There are entrances and exits
at the front and the back.
Okay, I got it.
Let's split up and go in.
Everybody drop your pistols!
Tojima.
I see you were the cops' dog.
Who stabbed us in the back?
You were too careless.
I'm just trying to learn how to
organize the G-men next time.
Look, here comes the
one you want now.
Goro!
Next time pick someone who's
not greedy for money or women.
So...
Take our guests
to the basement.
This factory is
closed because of you.
If you're going to die, it might as
well be in a place with memories.
In one hour this place
will be nothing but ashes.
Along with all
of you, of course.
Boss. The explosives are ready.
Get ready to leave.
Tojima.
I told you a comeback
was impossible.
Never underestimate
the power of a jinx.
Damn it! You son of a bitch!
Stop pulling!
The debt will be irrecoverable!
Boss.
We have to do something…
You can have your traitor back!
Damn you!
Damn it!
They tricked me!
Brother, I'm sorry!
They bribed me!
I couldn't resist!
I'm sorry!
Forgive me, everyone!
Goro!
Brother!
Hey, everyone hurry up!
Goro!
Damn it!
Let me do it.
I told you...
I told you I'm a pro.
Goro, hey!
Goro!
Shoot it open!
Damn it, we need weapons!
Here.
- What about Tojima?
- Yes, sir!
- Get it done quickly.
- Hey! Come on!
- Where are they?
- Inside! Go!
Go!
Hello? Hello?!
Damn it!
Motherfuckers!
- Are you ready?
- I finally got two cars.
Okay. Let's go!
That way! Huh?
- Hey! The back?
- We're surrounded.
Okay! Head for the gate!
Over there!
Good, good. Where's Tojima?
Go!
Hey! Hold on!
As I thought.
The debt was irrecoverable.
Kuroki!
Damn!
Tatsumura...
Get up!
Get up and move!
Tojima!
Tojima! You did a great job!
- Because of you we--
- Old man...
Three men are dead.
Don't say anything now.
What have we accomplished?
I feel like we've lost
more than we've gained.
I don't think so.
We did the right thing
for the first time.
Yeah. Even the dead
must be happy about that.
Let's send them on their way.
THE END
-== [ www.OpenSubtitles.com ] ==-