api.OpenSubtitles.org is deprecated, please
implement REST API from OpenSubtitles.com
FAMILY MOTTO
A HARMONIOUS FAMILY WITH LOVE
I…
made a mistake.
So you ran into Jong-pal
by coincidence yesterday
and made a mistake?
Does this "mistake" mean
what adults do?
What are you thinking?
Me and Jong-pal? A mistake?
"I met Jong-min yesterday."
"I made a mistake."
That's what you said earlier.
No, I said I ran into Jong-pal
by coincidence yesterday
to explain my emotional state.
And what's that state?
Yesterday was Jong-pal's
wedding anniversary.
I guess that date got stuck in my head.
I hate myself for waking up
and remembering that date.
It's been five years
and what have I been doing in that time?
It was very complicated.
The intro is too long.
There's a time in your life
when a coincidence is really powerful.
You know, the moments
when you run into someone
by coincidence wherever you go.
That's how I am these days.
You, too.
Why did I have to run into him
on his wedding anniversary?
Speed it up.
Give me Chan-hyuk's number.
Ms. Kim.
We can't get started
because you're not coming.
Let's go.
Okay.
Who is he?
The Vice CEO from the US headquarters.
We had a welcoming party yesterday.
So?
I couldn't get myself together
before the meal
because I ran into Jong-pal.
You were just looking
for a reason to drink.
Right.
I found a reason to drink
and I drank a lot.
And…
I made a mistake with the new Vice CEO.
Mom.
You're here.
Hello?
Jin-sook.
It's me, Man-ho.
Are you at Gangseo Police Station?
Yes.
What in the world is going on?
After I talked to you on the phone,
I brought someone from a group chat.
She was the member
who was with Sang-sik until the very end.
Where is it at?
I live in Suwon
and Oppa was on his way there anyway,
so he offered me a ride and I hopped on.
I had dinner with Oppa at the rest stop
and I took the back road home.
Since when has Oppa been out of reach?
You should go to the hospital.
Okay.
Go.
Oh.
You're the doctor son-in-law.
I heard a lot about you from Oppa.
Gosh.
That word "oppa" is stuck to your mouth.
She calls me oppa, too.
Did you part ways
after just having dinner?
Unnie, Oppa has been having a hard time
because of that graduation from marriage.
Why are you bringing that up
at this moment?
Did you…
talk about graduation
from marriage with Oppa?
No, Jin-sook.
Everyone in the club heard about it.
And this graduation from marriage
is kind of your fault.
Our club can't live without
your signature kimchi.
Did my father say anything
about going somewhere else?
I don't know about that.
Should I say this or not?
Unnie, we need to talk alone.
Why are you trying to make things weird?
You have nothing to talk about
with Jin-sook alone.
You know,
one thing I'm sure about Sang-sik
is that he's very gentle.
He never did anything
to make women misunderstand.
You don't know anything, Oppa.
There are things
that the children shouldn't hear.
Let me get this straight.
Because you ran into Jong-pal yesterday,
your emotions got complicated,
so you drank, got drunk,
and slept with the Vice CEO?
I couldn't tell anyone else.
So you needed a trash can.
A trash can?
It was too much to handle alone,
so you wanted to tell someone
about it and empty it out.
Right.
Deal.
I'll be the trash can for you.
So tell me what happened.
Everything.
I'm sure it seemed weird
between me and Jong-pal.
But I liked it because he didn't ask me
about who he is
and what our relationship is.
I'm Im Geon-joo.
Pleased to meet you.
-Pleased to meet you.
You're wonderful.
Paper books never disappear.
Be super positive!
-Be positive!
-Be super positive!
Are you serious?
You'll be 40 soon,
and you still say yes to everything
when you get drunk?
I couldn't help myself feeling good.
So, he saw you feeling good,
he smiled at you, and your heart raced.
Gosh, you're still young.
-Oh, friends forever
-Oh, a happy heart
-Oh, a happy life
-Oh, friends forever
-Oh, a happy heart
The time we spent not seeing each other
must've been longer than we thought.
The Eun-hee I knew…
I would've avoided it.
Saying that he's obviously making a move.
But the me in the present liked it.
It's not complicated.
"He's showing that he likes me."
"He wants to impress me."
I feel like I'm watching
an animal documentary about seduction.
Seduction.
What's the next episode about?
What are we drinking at the music bar?
What?
Makgeolli?
It's super delicious.
But it's a bit expensive.
-Let's go.
-I was
jealous in that short moment.
Actually, it's not exactly jealousy.
Anyway,
I felt all kinds of emotions
at that moment.
That's the power of alcohol.
I'm getting bored now. Speed it up a bit.
Hey, this kind of story
is all about details.
My dad prioritized me
more than his business.
In Africa, he made me
a special space of my own…
My father is a truck driver!
Do you think this is fun?
Is it fun to talk about your father's job
when we're all grown-ups?
When you're at a music bar,
listen to the music.
I'll shut my mouth, okay?
You're drunk.
I have about 5 trillion
and 50 song requests to make.
You go home first.
Okay.
I'm leaving first, Eun-hee.
You eat everything you want to eat.
And charge me for it, okay?
I will…
Eat whatever you want.
-Go!
-Okay?
I'm not going
until I listen to everything.
Go on, shoo, shoo
Beyond the mountains
Finally on the 1982 Campus Song Festival.
Where's Kyung-ok?
I sent her home by taxi.
She wasn't that drunk.
I'm out of breath
from running back in case you left.
You've only been requesting songs
from the Campus Song Festival.
How did you know…
that this song was from
the University Song Festival?
Isn’t it that song?
You requested songs
starting from the first festival, right?
You know all of them?
My father loves them.
"My father is a truck driver!"
That father, right?
You're a good daughter.
You must be close to your father.
Both are incorrect.
My father only loves my older sister.
But he always comes to me
when he has a favor to ask.
"Record Campus Song Festival songs for me
so I can listen to them while driving."
"Sort out the Grand Prize-winning songs."
"Record the songs I like."
And eventually,
I mastered
Campus Song Festival songs, too.
How can he not love such a cute daughter?
I tend to sober up
when I hear cheesy expressions.
Then I'm going to
continue saying cheesy things.
You're really drunk,
so you need to sober up.
Well…
These things happen.
There, are you done?
The trash can has been emptied out,
so forget about it now.
Yes.
But you must be worried.
"What if I run into him
at work on Monday?"
Exactly.
"Should I just quit over the weekend?"
"Should I be cool and ignore him?"
"No, what if he spreads words everywhere?"
You're having fun.
"What if he doesn't even remember it?"
-Stop it.
-Anyway,
don't come up with stories.
Just forget about it.
If it spreads, so what?
Just be embarrassed.
Time goes on.
If something bigger happens,
it'll be forgotten soon.
It's not a mistake.
You don't want to forget it, do you?
My dream library was there.
I thought it was my bookshelf.
We had so many of the same books.
Don't try to sneak away quietly.
Drink all of this tea.
Okay.
We communicated…
so well.
I haven't had a fling
for the past five years.
That's the saddest story
I've heard recently.
There's no need to be sad.
I wasn't even lonely.
"I must be sick of boring relationships."
"I must hate men."
"I must be a master of having fun alone."
I was certain of it.
But,
how could all of that collapse overnight?
That's the most heartwarming story
I've heard recently.
-Congratulations.
-For what?
You can talk to him well,
he has the books you have,
and has a similar soul as you.
To put it simply,
you fell in love.
Would it be okay for Mom to be alone?
I thought that woman was so vulgar,
but she thinks that some stories
shouldn't be heard by the children.
She's a decent person.
Unnie.
There really was
a medicine bottle in Oppa's truck.
Come on.
Don't say such unnecessary things.
How is this an unnecessary thing?
Unnie looks clueless.
You're family but looks like
you know nothing.
What medicine bottle?
He collected sleeping pills in it.
Come on.
He's been saying
that he'll go to the mountains,
take a bottle full of sleeping pills,
and fall asleep to his death.
Oppa, you've heard him saying that
once or twice, right?
Well, Sang-sik…
is so gentle and romantic,
so he was popular among women.
So I thought he was pretending
to be lonely and sad in front of women.
I didn't know it was real.
Yes, Driver Choi.
Did you look into Sang-sik's truck?
Someone called and said
his truck was parked all night long
and something was weird.
So I called them
and told them to open the door,
and the door was unlocked.
He also left his car key,
cell phone, and wallet
next to the driver's seat.
Oh, my.
Right…
Tell them to check
if there's a medicine bottle.
I don't see a medicine bottle.
Check the cargo, too. Search thoroughly.
Let's go. They found your father's truck.
There's a problem.
I had no interest
in relationships for five years
and he managed to seduce me overnight.
He could be a playboy.
Well, I can't do anything about that.
Yes, you can.
I need to learn the mind of a playboy.
-You're a playboy, too.
-Did you just say, "too?"
Right…
Well then…
what is a playboy?
Good.
This is the chance
to learn about the concept.
The concept is not important.
It's very important.
When others, and by that I mean
those around you, say things like
"He's admirable."
"That person is a liar."
"That person is lazy."
Then they really are.
If they say "That person is a player."
then they're a player.
Everyone said that you're a playboy
since you were in school.
You knew that as well.
I must learn about playboys.
I need someone who's
a total playboy from head to toe.
-That's you.
-My goodness.
Ji-woo, you…
I told you not to tell people
where the office is.
Your sister?
She's right here. Why?
Where's your phone?
Phone?
Maybe it's in the car.
She left it in the car.
Do you want me to put her on?
He doesn't sound very good.
Yes, why?
I'm taking off now.
What is it?
I don't know. Dad's out of reach.
Where did I put my car key?
Hey…
Hello.
Oh, hello.
You should greet me too.
Why are you here? It's a holiday today.
To practice editing.
Then practice it.
Yes, this is the rest area
for the truck drivers
behind the Chilbo Driver Rest Stop.
Is this the police station
with jurisdiction?
That's the only mountain you can go to
with your car parked here.
Why would anyone go there at night?
Though it looks low,
it's called Panting Mountain,
because it's full of stiff hills.
Yes, my father's truck is here,
so we want to file
another missing person's report.
Yes, okay.
They said to come to the station.
They can check the CCTV nearby.
Let's go, Mom.
-Thank you.
-Okay.
He got out of the truck,
sat there for about an hour,
and went to the mountain.
We can't see him on video after that,
perhaps because he didn't take
the hiking route.
He's been identified.
Name, Mr. Kim Sang-sik.
June 24th, 1963.
Is there a patient named
Mr. Kim Sang-sik, born in 1963?
Hang on.
Ms. Jin-sook?
Right?
You're Jin-sook, right?
-Dad!
-Dad, are you okay?
-Are you okay?
-Is it Ji-woo?
-Yes.
They found your father
right after he was reported missing.
He's at the hospital now.
He's fine. It's Suwon Hospital 3.
I'll type in the new address.
Nari, navigate me to Suwon Hospital 3!
Navigating to Suwon Hospital 3.
Jeez, is your navigation hearing impaired?
Do you have to yell like that?
If I say it quietly,
it takes me to the wrong place.
Even machines only listen to
those with loud voices.
Hey, aren't you speeding up
out of joy right now?
You took my car key in such a cool way,
so I thought you got a driver's license.
Never drive a car.
That's your life philosophy.
You remember. You keep it in mind, too.
Never drive in a state like this.
You had the car key in your hand
and you kept looking for it.
How can you drive in a such state?
Just take a taxi.
I'll drive safely, you coward.
Are you okay now?
What?
Drop me off at a nearby subway station.
Right, of course.
I didn't realize we came
all the way to Suwon.
What if Seo-young got the wrong idea?
I was out of it earlier,
so I couldn't even say hi properly.
It looked like she brought lunch boxes.
You managed to see that
while you were out of it?
A lunch box on a day off
is the proof of an office romance.
I won't tell Ji-woo.
Even after five years, you're still nosy.
-Bye.
Thanks.
You have to fast until the checkups
are done, so we gave you IV fluids.
Okay.
Dad?
I'm a Dad?
When he arrived at the hospital,
he showed the symptoms of hypothermia.
He showed signs of frostbite
on his fingers and toes,
but he recovered quickly.
How is he right now?
We have to do checkups
to see if there's any organ damage.
By the way…
-It's okay.
-Sir, calm down.
Please calm down.
Sir, what's your name?
I'm Kim Sang-sik.
How old are you?
Me?
You mean my age?
Yes, your age, Mr. Kim Sang-sik.
I am
22 years old.
What?
I'm 22 this year
and I will be a father next year.
I don't know why I'm at a hospital.
My body and face are so weird right now.
Sir, do you know what the date is today?
October 13th.
Do you know what year it is?
It's 19…
It's 1982.
-Did you say 1982?
Yes, that day in 1982
is Mr. Kim Sang-sik's last memory.
I'm sure he's the most
confused person right now,
so don't ask questions
and treat him naturally.
There can be a mix-up
in memories due to shock,
but he'll recover soon.
Ms. Sook.
Mom.
Dad!
Dad, are you okay?
By the way,
if Dad is 22 now,
isn't he younger than me?
By the way,
what day is October 13th, 1982?
It sounds so familiar.
Is it someone's birthday?
It's written on the photo
in the living room.
You always see it,
but you still don't know?
Right. That's crazy.
Thank you.
If you're hungry,
we should go eat
rather than drink milk here.
Why are you smiling?
Because…
you look so beautiful today.
Even more than usual.
I'm sorry.
Sang-sik.
Yes?
Mr. Kim Sang-sik.
I'm listening.
I'm…
I'm pregnant.
They said I'm pregnant.
I thought so
when you ordered milk.
What…
should I do?
Please take it well.
This is the day to remember forever.
Okay, I will.
One, two, three.
Can…
the two of us be alone, please?
Why? What are you going to do?
It's wrong
for a father to not remember his children.
Go somewhere else.
Dad doesn't remember us at all, right?
He can't remember you either?
He adores you.
Think logically.
If his memory is in 1982,
I wasn't born either.
So Dad is living in a time
when he and Mom were super romantic?
How can you tell
such a joke at this moment?
How are you two so natural together?
Are you sure you haven't
seen each other for years?
Was I the only one who was worried?
Did you two meet without telling me?
Customer number 21, your order is ready.
Go get the coffee.
Wait. Weren't you coming with Chan-hyuk?
Go get the coffee, please.
Go.
I heard
you called Ji-woo out of nowhere
and asked where his office is.
Do you still drunk dial people
and make mistakes?
A breathalyzer cell phone that stops you
from calling would win a Nobel Prize.
I remember Chan-hyuk.
But now, he's Ji-woo's boss
before he's your friend.
It's not that kind of company.
Ji-woo calls him by his name.
They're like brothers.
All companies work the same way.
If he pays him, he's the CEO.
If he works at a place that pays,
that's a company.
Is he family with Ji-woo
and friends with you?
Draw your lines clearly.
All right.
I'll never mess things up with Chan-hyuk.
Don't worry.
Don't say "never" that easily.
Eun-joo must be living her life
so comfortably.
Why?
She never hesitates to point out
other people's flaws.
I'm sure she's never stressed.
But you're not other people.
I'm worried about you, that's all.
Is it so hard to say, "Okay?"
Okay.
He's been saying that
he'll go to the mountains,
take a bottle full of sleeping pills,
and fall asleep to his death.
Eat all of it.
Am I sick right now?
It was an accident.
You went hiking and went missing.
I see.
Did I go hiking alone?
I guess so.
Did I go hiking alone…
quite often?
They said if you don't ask questions
and just be natural,
your memories will come back.
Okay.
So I shouldn't ask questions.
So we're…
still awkward with each other
even at this age, right?
Here's the medicine.
Take it after the meal.
Thank you.
Why? Do you need something?
It feels like I'm having a weird dream.
What are the names
of our children?
They're Eun-joo, Eun-hee, and Ji-woo.
Is Eun-joo the eldest?
Yes.
Eun-joo, Eun-hee and Ji-woo.
I want to
meet them properly.
Eun-joo?
I'm Kim Eun-hee, the second daughter.
This is Kim Eun-joo, the eldest daughter.
Kim Ji-woo, the youngest son.
I see.
Eun-joo, my eldest daughter.
Yes.
He only cares for his eldest daughter.
Are you okay?
Should I call a doctor?
Should I?
No.
It's okay.
Dad, should I play the songs
from the 1983 Campus Song Festival?
What?
Campus Song Festival?
It'd be like your first time hearing it.
It must feel like you're time traveling.
Hey, he has to rest.
I think all of you should go home.
It's not that spacious here anyway.
We're leaving.
Get some rest.
Bye, Dad.
Bye.
I'm going home to get Mom's things
she might need at the hospital,
so take Eun-joo home.
Will you pay me for the ride?
What are you going to do
with all that money?
Are you going to move out, too?
I can't move out.
Wait.
Is the graduation from marriage
going to fail like this?
I'm sure she'll take care of it
when Dad recovers.
Mom didn't just say it.
I'm against it.
Eun-joo, you were against it.
Tell them you're against it.
I don't want to hear that word.
If they can't live together,
they should get a divorce.
-Was Tae-hyung here?
-Yes.
Are they not getting along?
It didn't seem so.
Go on.
You might not be able to
get money for the taxi.
-Call me.
-Okay.
I'll drive you safely to your destination.
Why is Eun-hee standing there, zoning out?
Is she dating these days?
I don’t think so.
A few days ago,
she said all her romance cells have died
and she's not lonely either.
I'm going to get delivery food.
What have you been doing
not eating until now?
I brought lunch boxes. It's for two.
Eat this.
How come you didn't eat until now?
I lost my appetite earlier.
Since you came back without eating,
my appetite is suddenly back.
Relax, okay?
And don't make that ridiculous face.
When I think of the effort…
Well, that's clearly bought,
but that's still effort, right?
But if that effort
makes someone uncomfortable,
then they shouldn't take it.
Then should I eat all of this on my own?
CEO.
You put your rent deposit
on this company, right?
You used all your rent deposit at that age
and you feel uncomfortable
living with your parents,
so you're sleeping on the sofa.
I wish Ji-woo and Young-ho
were as sharp-witted as you are.
They think the company
is doing much better now.
So you bought this because you pity me?
Now that makes me feel relieved.
Help yourself.
By the way, why were you two
in the office at that hour?
There was a reason.
Did you sleep with her?
Hey!
I'm fine with you being rude
and talking down to me.
You're good at work and life.
So keep to those two.
Ms. Kim Eun-hee has no feelings for you.
So don't do anything stupid.
Tell me one stupid thing that I've done.
The photos you take show your emotions.
The photo you took of her
showed that you like her.
Have you been doing
stupid things for a long time?
I've been a great photographer
since this time.
Did she look old back then?
She looks the same as now.
Actually, she looks younger now.
You have a long way to go
before you understand my photos.
Don't ever let her see that photo.
If someone was keeping
a photo of me without telling me,
I'll surely misunderstand.
"He's madly in love with me."
She might die from her heart fluttering.
Now that makes me want to test it.
A call from Kyung-ok.
KYUNG-OK
Did you go home safely yesterday?
Are you feeling okay?
Did you relieve your hangover?
You were the one who got drunk.
I never lose my consciousness.
By the way,
that Vice CEO is quite American.
What?
He was so touchy on our way to the taxi.
It was no joke.
And when the taxi came, he tried
to get in with me in the back seat.
I blocked him with my entire body.
Even if he's lonely,
that's a wrong thing to do.
Kyung-ok, I'm driving right now
and the road is so crowded.
Okay, then. See you on Monday.
Bye.
Dad's saying he's 22 years old.
Get it together.
CHATS
NATIONWIDE LARGE TRUCK DRIVERS
Do you remember something?
This thing is incredible.
What's even more incredible is,
I think I know how to use it.
Ms. Sook, do you have
this kind of phone too?
It's 22-9438.
That's your home phone number.
Remember?
Do you know how much I ran here and there
to find phone booths
to call you at 9:00 sharp?
Do you remember it too, Ms. Sook?
I don't remember it at all.
How could you forget?
Whenever I heard your voice,
I thought my heart would explode
and die from happiness.
You forgot about that?
Then,
what happened to the Diamond Game?
The bet was to get 100 points first.
I got 59 and you got 50.
Aren't you acting like you forgot
because you were losing?
I was losing by 59 to 50?
I was so good at the Diamond Game.
See? You remember it, too.
To be honest, I was losing.
I got 50 and you got 59.
Who won?
Did it end boringly with your victory?
The winner was supposed to kiss the loser.
Miss Sook, did you kiss me?
What are you doing?
Why?
-Hi.
Stay seated.
I'll join after ordering coffee.
Did you go somewhere?
How about a strong coffee today?
You drink strong coffee
when you're in a bad mood.
I'm a bit tired. Add an extra shot.
Okay.
Ms. Kim, stay seated. I'll bring it.
It's okay. I'll bring it.
No, I'll bring it.
Because of a newbie,
we have to have coffee get-togethers
even if we get out early on the weekends.
The barista is good-looking.
Just give it to me.
-Here.
-Thank you.
So it's this photo.
Dad was 22 years old at the time?
Neither of them seems like it, right?
Does aged look run in the family?
Mom and I don't look aged.
Maybe Eun-joo looks old
because she takes after Dad.
Did Eun-joo give you money for a taxi?
I got it.
But she told me to drop her off
at a cafe in front of her house
saying she needs strong coffee.
-A cafe in front of her house?
-Yes.
Eun-joo speaks casually
to the part-timer there.
-You know it, too?
-Know what?
Well, you know.
That part-timer is in great shape.
And didn't Eun-joo's style change a lot?
She hated long hair and makeup.
And since when did she
like coffee that much?
Hey!
What are you thinking?
I'm going to tell her.
"Eun-joo, Ji-woo said you fell
for a part-timer who's in a great shape
and you dress up all nice for him!"
Come on. That's not it.
The mystery of DNA.
Your expression looked exactly like Dad's.
Don't just take after
his expressions and grow up, okay?
These two became parents
when they were younger than you.
Eun-joo was in Mom's womb at the time.
I've seen this photo my entire life.
But I never thought
they were in their twenties here.
I know nothing
about Mom and Dad from then.
What about now?
Do you know about them now?
Then do you know?
MOM
CHAN-PAL
Hi, Mom.
While your Dad was unconscious,
the deactivated part of his brain
might've been stimulated
or the active part of his brain
might be asleep temporarily.
He talks and behaves a bit like a child.
You said he's 22.
I was a grown-up when I was 22.
Wait.
What if it's dementia?
Not all brain-related
sickness is dementia.
He won't have any problems
with his daily life.
The body remembers what it can do.
I'm sure he'll drive if he sits in a truck
and know its functions.
-Is your arm going to be okay?
-It's okay.
-Why did he get hurt?
-I don't know.
You act close, but you don't know?
Is something bothering you?
Hey.
Eun-joo.
Dad asked me
to bring the Diamond Game board.
Is he regressing?
Ask Tae-hyung.
Does he have dementia or something?
It's not dementia.
Don't say stupid things
without knowing anything.
If he needs something, bring it to him.
I'm hanging up.
What did I…
What did I do to be scolded like that?
Good grief.
DIAMOND GAME
What is that?
Dad asked me to bring it,
so he can play it.
Diamond Game? All of a sudden?
That's weird.
Is this an early symptom of dementia?
She said it isn't.
She told me not to say stupid things.
I asked Eun-joo and got scolded.
That's who she is.
I'm guessing you have to go back
to the hospital with Mom's clothes.
-What did Chan-hyuk say?
-What?
You were on the phone with him.
Right.
He asked how Dad was doing.
I was the last person
Dad talked to on the phone
before he went on the nighttime hike.
He told me
to live happily and joyfully with you.
Like he knew there would be an accident.
To live happily and joyfully.
I thought about it
and Dad was the only one who never asked,
"Why aren't you having a kid?"
"How's the hospital business going?"
"Are your in-laws nice to you?"
He never asked such questions.
He always just tells me
to live happily and joyfully with you.
He knows that I've been trying hard
to have a baby for years.
But…
I think he also knew I gave up.
I gave up.
I went back to the life of drinking
multiple cups of strong coffee.
Can the two of us really live
happily and joyfully without children?
Ms. Sook, is he bringing
the Diamond Game board?
You're going to play me, right?
Ms. Sook, I'll wipe it.
Stop calling me Ms. Sook.
I see.
I don't call you Ms. Sook anymore?
Then what do I call you here?
I mean, now?
What do I call you now?
Hey.
Eun-joo.
Eun-hee.
Ji-woo!
Hey, you!
Just call me "You."
You…
Then what do you call me?
Here.
You left this.
It's time to eat.
Tell your father to come and eat.
I call you the same.
You.
You…
haven't changed at all.
My dirty, shaggy, and gloomy room
without any proper items
shone brightly after you came.
And our kids shine brightly too,
perhaps because you raised them well.
You…
haven't changed at all.
What is it?
I don't think I left anything behind.
This.
Hey, this is…
Let's go for now.
Where are we going?
That relieves my hangover.
Did Mr. Playboy call you?
Mr. Playboy?
Hey, that's just how I feel.
He doesn't know my number.
-How about you?
-I don't know his either.
Why did you lie to me
and make me come here?
Whether you know his number or not,
don’t call him first.
That's quite a tacky advice
from another Mr. Playboy.
Should I be elusive?
No, it's about being cold and considerate.
Isn't considerate a kind word?
Cold and considerate?
Mr. Playboy and you.
The two of you know nothing
about each other.
-Do we know nothing?
-Then what do you know?
Position, qualification, age, and gender?
Everyone else knows that.
Did you ask before you made out with him?
"Are you a playboy?"
That's just how I feel.
-"Are you married?"
-That's not it for sure.
"Do you have a girlfriend?"
Hey.
Did you make me come here to say all this?
You always gave me advice
whenever I dated someone.
Hey.
Do you need advice too?
No.
When you dated Jong-pal,
you always did what he wanted.
You never told him
what you like and what you don't.
Don't do that this time.
Don't get anxious and start asking him
about what he remembers.
It'll come back naturally.
Just let him relax
and do what he wants to.
Okay, thank you.
It was small back then,
but this is big, so it's easy to see.
You bought this.
Really?
Your mom's coming. Let's play it with her.
Ms. Sook.
Come here.
Ms. Sook…
I think I fell for Mr. Playboy first.
He acknowledged me.
You should've gone in first.
You're the best at our company,
so I must wait for you.
I studied a lot after I was assigned.
I read company newspapers
and studied the employees' tendencies.
And you had the best harmony with me.
The books published under your planning…
were the best.
That made my heart flutter.
When he said the books published
under my planning were the best,
I was so happy I couldn't handle it.
I guess I was lonely
after being single for five years.
I feel bad for myself.
That's how everyone is.
When someone acknowledges you,
that becomes poison.
One time, the lady at the restaurant
in front of my office
gave me tons of kkakdugi
saying, "You like kkakdugi, don't you?"
I was so touched beyond words
and I only went there to eat after that.
Even if it had cockroaches,
I only went to that place.
Are you feeling lonely, too?
Good grief.
TINKERBELL
PLANNED PREGNANCY
90 DAY PLAN
-Mom, are you going to be okay?
-Yes, go on.
Dad's out.
-Bye, Mom.
-Bye.
Rest up. I'll be back tomorrow.
Okay.
I think you should watch this, too.
Ji-woo.
I'll count on you when Dad
leaves the hospital tomorrow, too.
Just go in first.
Yours won't need any more corrections.
-Send it to the company and upload it.
-Okay.
My father is being discharged today,
so can I step out for a while?
You're done. You can go.
Okay.
Mr. Playboy is walking toward me
in the parking lot. What to do?
How was your weekend?
Great.
What about you?
Don't look around with an anxious,
awkward look on your face.
If you care too much,
they'll find out
and you'll look like a loser.
Would you like to have lunch with me?
What?
Don't act like you didn't hear it.
Be honest and clear in conversations.
No, let's have dinner.
Yes, good morning.
Good morning, sir.
This is embarrassing.
What is it?
Who are you texting
so early in the morning?
Kyung-ok, stop acting cute.
It's too early in the morning.
Why? Doesn't my energy
get rid of your Monday blues?
I have important information
about the Vice CEO.
The Vice CEO…
has a fiancée he will marry soon.
What are you doing?
I can’t remember the house
we live in together.
I'm sure you'll remember if you go there.
Do we own that house?
It's under your name.
So I bought a house in Seoul.
What if my memories don't come back
even after I go home?
I'm worried.
The doctor told you to relax
and don't think too hard.
By the way,
I'm asking just in case I make a mistake.
Does our eldest daughter…
know about it?
Eun-joo knows about what?
Are you going somewhere?
Does she know…
that I'm not
her biological father?
You're keeping a secret from me, right?
Tell Eun-joo before I tell her myself.
The fruit shop?
The fruit shop Mr. Yoo?
-He's jealous, too?
-Ms. Sook likes Korean melons?
Ji-woo, which one do you prefer?
Tangerines?
It's not that I like him.
I made a mistake.
You like Mr. Playboy.
You'll know how flustered
I am by your actions
once you get your memories back.
Don't be ridiculous.
You're lying about not remembering, right?
Subtitle translation by: Hae-lim Lee
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/ah22u
Help other users to choose the best subtitles