JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor...
It was down to the final four.
We're in the home stretch,
and emotions are just all over
the map.
PROBST: In which city and
state is Jessie a deputy
sheriff?
At the first of two final
immunity challenges, Kim
Johnson's memory led her to
victory, and Tom was voted out
of the tribe.
The tribe has spoken.
Under a blazing sun, the final
three took part in one last
endurance immunity challenge,
and Kim outlasted Ethan and Lex,
insuring her a place in the
final two.
At Tribal Council, she voted Lex
out of the tribe...
Lex, the tribe has spoken.
Choosing to face the jury
with Ethan by her side.
When the final votes were
tallied, it was Ethan Zohn who
won the title, Sole Survivor.
Tonight, the final adventure
into the private lives of 16
Survivors back from Africa.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
PROBST: Well, Survivor:
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
Africa is over, and 16 more
lives have been changed forever.
Tonight, we go beyond the game
and take you deeper into the
lives of those who have played.
From the unexpected...
I couldn't spell "Clarence."
I put "C.B."
There I am, 46 years old, on
national TV and can't spell.
Whoa, man!
PROBST: to the
revealing...
We've seen quite a bit of
her, you know, more than most
son-in-laws get to see of their
mother-in-law.
PROBST: to the families
they came home to.
I cringe a little when one of
my friends says, "Oh, your son's
really hot!"
PROBST: Every Survivor has a
different way of keeping their
memories of the game alive.
Lex, well, he brought back...
A couple of baboon teeth.
PROBST: And Kelly?
Okay, I stole Clarence's war
paint.
PROBST: But our journey
begins with a man who's picked a
more unusual way to remember his
tribe mates.
And Kim Johnson, where's that
old goat at?
Come here, come here, Kim!
I just put their names on the
cattle.
They have some of their
characteristics.
I'm an animal person, and the
animals out in Africa was
probably one of the greatest
experiences I ever had in my
life.
There I was sitting right in the
middle of Wild Kingdom.
At 45, I thought I'd done some
things and I found out I ain't
done diddley.
This just shows me that there's
more to life then just what's
there around the corner at the
house.
(country tune playing)
I was pretty wild and rusty
in my younger days, and I had a
pretty big reputation before
Survivor come, and this just
added fuel to the flame.
I like all types of music.
I know about one line of every
song.
♪ Honey, baby, mine... ♪
I like music, I like to dance.
The Bluegrass, I grew up with, I
love it.
Tom has always had the
ability to get along with women.
I have never seen him meet a
woman that he can't talk to.
He's like a magnet.
He's witty and he's a bundle of
fun.
Something that makes me feel
vulnerable is spelling.
Clarence Black, he let the team
down.
I couldn't spell "Clarence."
I put "C.B."
There I am, 46 years old on
national TV and can't spell.
And I started a little reading
program, "Reading is the key to
Survival," because of that.
How ya'll doing?
Lookee here.
How'd I get him?
Which one's yours?
Attaboy, you got a lot of
feathers.
I think he realized right
then that he could do something
in our community to really help
to motivate these children to
read.
If I can help one kid be able
to read and spell, if I can help
one kid do better than me,
I'm... I'm glad it embarrassed
me.
Come to daddy, come to daddy.
I'm still not the sharpest tool
in the shed, but I'm still in
the shed, and I'm happy to be
here.
I'm even more happier than I was
before.
Since I've been back from
Africa, the job market's really
tough.
All right, thank you.
Taking all these small jobs and
I walk someone's dog as well,
for cash just because I need it.
I'll take up baby-sitting for
people, moms that I've met at
the gym.
Get off.
You want me to get off?
This was my luxury item that I
was able to bring into Africa
with me and this necklace has a
very special meaning to me.
It was given to me by my
brother.
And I wore it to Tribal Council
every time I went.
It was kind of my security.
I always had my necklace on.
In 1998, my brother was killed
in a very tragic accident.
Lex looks a little bit like my
brother, so every once in a
while, I would kind of get this
quick look of Lex and think, "oh
my gosh," you know, it looks
like him.
And it was just a reminder.
My brother, he really is here
with me.
He's here, making sure I'm okay.
It wasn't just about trying to
win $1 million, and it certainly
wasn't about just being on TV.
To me, it was much more about
the competition between me and
myself.
I have it!
Big Tom nicknamed me "Little
Bit."
He saw me and he thought, "that
little bit of a girl is going to
make it out here in Africa."
People would keep telling me how
small I was, and it really
angered me.
I was out there giving 150% of
everything I had to say, "You
can count on me.
I can handle this.
I'm strong."
I took so much away from the
game, and I learned so much
about myself.
There were moments of every
single day I spent out there
that I thought, "I want to go
home, I don't want to play this
game anymore."
PROBST: Keep going!
Kim, it's not over!
But somehow, some, some way,
I always pushed through that
feeling.
Come on, Powers.
You can do this, Powers.
Come on, one more.
Push.
And went on.
And that's the one thing that
I... I think I'll probably
always remember about playing
the game was that it was tough
and it was hard and I wanted to
give up, and I never did.
And that's the thing that I'll
always draw from.
♪ When you're smiling
When you're smiling
♪ Then the whole world
smiles with you
Smiles with you. ♪
One thing about dentistry
that I really love is that once
I step into this role, and I'm
working on a patient, I don't
think about anything else.
Didn't hurt, did it?
Didn't feel a thing, did ya?
Saw patients all day, worked all
day, jump in the car put the top
down, put some tunes on and
cruise on home.
What do you drive?
You don't want to know what I
drive.
Yes, we do, yes, I do.
No, you don't want to know
what I drive.
Aw, tell me, Doc.
I'm not telling.
The question came up about
what kind of car I drive and
what kind of lifestyle I had.
I already knew that Silas was
trying to put in play, "Here's a
guy who doesn't need the million
dollars."
Doc getting out all his...
all his valuables and all his
money.
Mercedes!
I have one of those.
What else?
What do they say?
"Little boys grow up to be men
with bigger toys."
It's definitely true.
I like my toys.
A Porsche.
You have a Porsche.
I drive a Porsche, pardon me,
you know what I mean.
I've worked my entire life to
get to this level, you know.
I'm not embarrassed of that.
That's the American dream.
That's what defines America.
I feel I epitomize the American
dream in my own right.
12 years old, I remember reading
Disney's autobiography, and he
had a little quote in there that
said, "If you can dream it, you
can do it."
And I live that way.
I dream... I dreamed that I
would be on Survivor no problem.
That experience in Africa
definitely changed me.
Look, I'm the old guy, okay, but
I know what needs to be done.
Every morning... fire, water and
food.
Well, of course, I went to get
the water because if I don't get
it, it's not going to get done.
You think anybody else gets off
their ass to do anything.
They thought they signed up to
go to the Y.M.C.A. and roast
marshmallows and maybe win a
million dollars, they're wrong.
After being out there for, I
guess, two and a half months and
not having family there, it's
changed him a lot, and he's more
willing to listen to people.
My wife said she should have
sent me 20 years ago, made me a
nicer person.
He seems genuinely sweeter,
kinder.
I think he really missed me a
lot, and his actions show it.
Life is fun and you don't
know what tomorrow's going to
bring.
So, go for it.
If you shoot for the stars,
if you miss, you may land
on the moon.
PROBST: When we come back,
Lindsey's darkest hour.
The most embarrassing moment
of my life, by far.
PROBST: And Survivor's most
colorful castaway.
I got my Catholic schoolgirl.
PROBST: Survivor has a way of
making strange bedfellows.
In our next group, one old-
fashioned guy, two strong-willed
women, and someone who clearly
is a different drummer.
One, two, three, four.
My life before Survivor was...
I had a good life, don't get me
wrong.
I spent about ten, 12 years
working in the high-tech
industry, surfing with my
buddies, and going out catching
a good surf.
But I never felt like I was
really cut out for that kind of
ordinary life.
Cool.
I've got some good tattoos.
I've got my devil head, Catholic
schoolgirl, samurai fighting a
snake.
Obviously, my wife and my kids,
huge part of my life.
My very favorite tattoos are the
ones my boys drew for me.
It's actually a drawing of me.
I've got my boy's names: Corbin
Ace Daniel; River's name is
right here.
When I got back from Africa, I
actually celebrated my ten-year
wedding anniversary.
My wife and I both got wedding
anniversary tattoos, you know,
ten years on the dice there.
My wife actually got one as
well, right there.
We're freaks.
I recall coming home, seeing my
wife and kids, being just so
stoked about seeing them.
Of course, my luxury item.
They're these shoes, they have
now taken a special place in my
home.
They'll always hang out with my
Survivor stuff now.
Hey, River, do you remember
these?
Yeah.
You wore these.
You learned to walk in these
shoes.
I know.
Yeah.
Really the only thing that
has ever really been important
to me has been my family and my
friends.
♪ Sleep all day... ♪
I play in a band called Lucky
Dog, with friends of mine for
almost 20 years.
We play here in Santa Cruz...
All original music.
We have such a good time doing
it.
It's always been a huge part of
my life.
(laughing)
Africa is... is nothing like the
states.
You might as well have taken 16
of us and dropped us on Mars or
on the moon.
I didn't anticipate that it was
really going to be quite as
dangerous as it was.
I thought to myself, "We all
know it's going to be tough, but
they're obviously not going to
put us in harm's way.
(roaring)
There aren't going to be any
animals that can pose any kind
of threat to us."
(roaring)
I can hear him breathing.
He's right outside the fence.
(growling)
The drinking water.
We show up, you know, at our
drinking water hole, at the
spring, expecting that it's
going to be something pretty
safe.
This is mud.
I came home pretty sick.
The first three weeks back here
was spent pretty much just doing
a lot of this.
My doctor found no less than
four different parasites and a
couple of different bacteria.
I have to take so many pills,
probably like almost a dozen.
I'm still dealing with the
results of being out there in a
dangerous, hazardous, very real
place.
Almost the first question I'm
always asked by people is, "Did
you have fun and would you do it
again?"
And I had the time of my life
and I would do it again in a
heartbeat.
Being on Survivor, going to
Kenya for seven weeks this
summer was extremely meaningful,
very important to me.
This place can just... can just
fill our spirits!
I don't know if they're spirits
or what.
I just feel very protected in
Africa.
Life is different now for me.
I'm still the same person.
Come here.
Did your mama never hug you?
But there's definitely been a
transformation.
I think I'm calmer.
I think I'm more focused now in
terms of what's really important
in life: family, friends.
Good job, very good job.
I wasn't the least bit
surprised that she wanted to do
Survivor.
I've seen her passions escalate
from race walking to roller
blading to mountain climbing,
now yoga.
When she gets an interest, she
gets very passionate about it.
Once I was diagnosed with
thyroid cancer, when I heard
those words, "You have cancer,"
I felt like my life was spinning
out of control.
It was soon after, very soon
after, that I decided to climb
Mount Rainier.
And each time I take a trip it's
not about reaching the summit.
It's not the destination.
It's about the journey.
So it's really a metaphor for
how I try to live my life.
She always has a positive
attitude and she's always
telling me, "Go for your
dreams."
PROBST: Get them ready.
Keep them down on the ground.
I never went on Survivor for
fortune or fame.
I went because I was looking for
an exciting, interesting and
challenging adventure.
PROBST: Linda!
This show has taught me to
live my dreams, to go for it.
That life is the ultimate
adventure.
If you have a dream, you have a
goal, you have a desire, go for
it!
Woo!
I was at a point in my life I
think where things were getting
a little monotonous, plugging
along, working out, you know,
training on my bike...
flying back and forth to see
my boyfriend.
I hope my boyfriend doesn't wake
up some mornings and think,
"God, what is next to me?"
And I was ready for something,
just something big and exciting
to just, kind of... turn my life
around.
I got me a tick on my ass!
Ow!
Lindsey is who she is.
What you see is what you get.
That kind of sums up her
personality.
Competitive.
Emotional.
I just started to cry because I
felt sad, and we're all stressed
out and...
Intense.
Oh, okay.
Emotional.
( laughing)
Competitive.
Wait, towards me.
Damn it!
I just went back and forth, from
one to another.
Barbie went down in Africa.
I never feel pain.
I'm not one to hide what I'm
feeling.
I just started my period.
No wonder I have cramps!
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, that was a great moment,
wasn't it?
The most embarrassing moment of
my life, by far.
Excuse me, Africa, you know?
We're not down at the mall here,
you know.
Big, big mistake, coming out
of my big, big mouth.
And trust me, when I'm pumped,
you don't want to (bleep) with
me!
(gasping)
I think she said the F-word.
He said, "Nah."
I said, "Are you sure?"
And he said, "Well, no."
She speaks her mind.
She's extremely honest and
truthful and up front with
people.
Don't underestimate me, people!
She's a really fun, fun girl.
And I think that...
You're with me because I'm
fun? That's all?
Oh, my God.
Well, you are sometimes.
Give me a kiss.
I'm very sensitive.
I'm almost too sensitive
sometimes.
This show just... just boosted
me up in maturity a little bit
more.
It wasn't positive seeing some
of the ways I handled
situations.
PROBST: Lindsey, have you
made any mistakes so far?
I'm a walking mistake.
I think I grew a lot from it.
Lindsey, would you go boil
some water for us please?
(laughter)
What you saw on Survivor
was... was me, the real deal.
No, just go!
Just come around the corner.
You know, Frank Garrison is not
going to change, and either you
like me or you don't like me.
It really doesn't weigh heavily
on my mind.
Going to make two huge S's here
on each side.
I was worried that Frank
would come back a different
person.
That it would really affect him
and change him dramatically.
I can't help it if these
little liberal special interest
groups that the media give open
market to...
But Frank is Frank, and
three days after he was back, I
knew he was the same man that he
was when he left.
We're going, bud.
We're going.
Let's go home, guys.
Frank can be the most
charming, sweet and lovable
person, and the biggest jerk in
the next breath.
Let's just get moving along.
(beeping)
Jocelyn Rose up and at them.
Let's go!
Come on, guys.
Frank, we just hit the snooze
button.
My life's philosophy in
general is to get up early in
the morning.
Okay, can I have a kiss?
I love you!
Kiss your wife and children.
See you later, alligator!
Go to work.
Give the man 100%.
He gives you a little bit back.
And come immediately home, and
spend time with the family.
He's a very loving father.
Would you like a cup of coffee?
And a very loving husband.
We found out I was pregnant the
day before we got the call that
he was actually going to Africa.
And when Frank left, there was
something missing in the whole
family dynamic.
What was missing was his
enthusiasm for life, and his
zest for everything that he
does.
Very good.
Straight arrow.
See how nice and straight that
went?
When I think of my dad, I
think of hugging.
I think of sharing, and I think
of being a leader.
Samburu!
The things that were
important to me prior to
Survivor are the same things
that are important to me now:
Providing my family with the
basics of food, shelter and
security, but most importantly,
love.
PROBST: Coming up, we go hot
tubbing with Mama Kim...
and mud-slinging with just about
everybody.
Clarence, I just didn't like
him worth snot.
PROBST: Welcome back.
Well, at the end of every Tribal
Council, the person voted out
has to leave immediately.
Once the tribe has spoken, the
departing Survivor can't.
So we decided to give them a
chance for a parting shot.
Clarence Black.
Oh, Clarence.
Loves to talk about himself.
Like him a lot.
He's my favorite.
I just didn't like him worth
snot.
Kelly Goldsmith, off with her
head.
Woo!
Cut it right off.
Lex, eccentric.
Lex is like a 16 year old
living in a 40 year old's body.
Eh.
Lindsey Richter.
A bit of a whiner.
Emotional.
You're sweet.
You were in over your head,
though, sweetie.
Okay.
Tom.
Yeah.
A dirty, old pervert that I
love.
Good ole...
Country boy.
It's a sickness.
Silas Gaither.
That smile could knock your
socks off.
You love yourself.
Ethan Zohn.
Quiet.
(sighs)
Super sweet guy, shy.
Um...
Mr. Lovable.
Great hair.
Frank.
Frankie.
Hardcore.
Green beret.
Trying to be sensitive here.
Frank and his deer antlers.
Brandon...
in a different world.
Good job, Frank.
Jessie, what a woman.
Me?
Hot.
(laughs)
Kim Johnson.
Wait a minute, let me think
on this one.
Dear God.
Probably be clever.
Honest.
Like my mom, I got along with
her great.
There's nothing more
important to me in my life than
my family.
I've got three kids, all
married; three grandchildren,
one on the way.
It doesn't get much better than
that.
Hello there.
My oldest child is Wendy.
Wendy and her family only live
four miles from me.
Hello, hello!
(laughing)
Yeah.
Our son, Teddy, just got married
two weeks after I got home from
Africa.
My middle child, Kerry, just had
the most beautiful baby boy.
We spend as much time as we can
with them, where they live in
Durango, Colorado.
Growing up was... was tough.
It was really just my mom and
myself.
I was really more the mom.
We had a lot of problems...
Health-wise, money-wise, every-
wise.
I never really had a warm and
loving relationship until my
husband.
Come on, Sierra.
Ted and I met when we were in
college.
He's been my best friend ever
since.
Kim was 19 when we got married.
The way she grew up, it gave her
the resolve to really put her
all into making everything work.
We've really helped keep each
other young.
I probably do look like a
grandmother, but I don't think
most of the time I act like a
grandmother.
When she gets her mind made
up on something, there's just no
stopping her.
At my age, which is 57...
Ouch... my life is... is pretty
much set.
I'm not going to go out in the
street and hang out with a guy
full of tattoos and say, "Hey,
what's your life like?"
Yes!
It was so cool to be able to
spend time with people different
from me.
As far as the thong thing
goes...
Whoa, man!
I didn't go there with the
idea of taking off my pants.
Women in her thong there.
We had people over in our
apartment and then they showed
scenes from next week.
All of a sudden the thong was
out there, and the place went
crazy.
Anything to get this challenge.
We've seen quite a bit of
her, more than most son-in-laws
get to see of their mother-in-
law, so that's... that's been a
big plus, too.
You and the whole town.
Yeah, well, and all our friends.
I came away from this
experience with a reaffirmation
of my ability to do what I want
to do when I want to do it.
It's probably the coolest thing
I've ever done.
Every day, I like to
basically start with a devotion.
"For God so loved the world that
he gave his only son."
I focus on the day ahead and...
and, you know, I read a... a
chapter from the Bible a day,
and it just kind of gets, you
know, my priorities straight and
that sort of thing.
Coming from Tennessee to Los
Angeles was a huge move.
I'm trying to make it as an
actor.
And I try to read a script a
day, and bartending to make ends
meet.
It's a dog-eat-dog world out
there.
This is the green machine.
But, man, I absolutely love it
here.
The beach, man.
The temperature is perfect.
Welcome to sunny California.
The sun's shining bright.
I mean, it's just absolutely
amazing.
You ready to rock?
You know, depending on the day,
I try to knock in a... a good
day of surfing.
It's that carpe diem mentality.
Survivor helped me in the fact
that there's an unpredictability
about it, you know?
PROBST: Silas, Teresa, Frank,
you guys are now members of
Boran.
The switch meant the game for
me.
Smokes.
I never saw that coming.
Right when I got kicked off,
I couldn't sleep for a week!
Just now, I mean, I'm finally
starting to forget and relax and
just, you know, really come down
from it.
You know, it's funny when you're
in Africa, it's a place to,
like, really think about life
and think about the importance
of life and like what we live
for.
If you were going to die
tomorrow, it's relationships,
and the relationship that I have
with God and my family and
friends and loved ones, man.
I mean, that's, to me, that's
the most important thing in
life.
I love proving people wrong.
I think that's my thing.
Men that say that women can't do
the same thing that men can do.
Well, guess what?
I love proving men wrong.
The reason why I love police
work is because it's a job where
you can do something about
society.
My grandpa was a cop in Puerto
Rico, retired 25 years.
I've heard all the stories.
I just fell in love with it.
Now I'm working for the
Sheriff's Department, and I love
it.
She's a good cop, good cop.
Behind the cop, I am probably
the coolest chick you'll ever
know.
No, no, no...
I'm a big kid at heart.
I like to do spontaneous things.
Boxing is a good stress
reliever.
Your only concentration is on
trying to get that person, and
try to hit 'em and knock 'em
out.
(laughs)
It's fun.
My sister was the one that made
me do Survivor.
She's a tough girl.
Survivor in Africa was so
much tougher than I thought it
would be.
I never expected the water
conditions to be so bad.
Throwing up when you have so
little hydration to go around,
it's bad for her, it's bad for
us.
PROBST: Jessie, the tribe has
spoken.
When I was voted off and I
thought, "Wow, you know, I just
disappointed my sister."
Once the show was over, I
actually stayed an extra month
in Africa, and helped out in the
community project, building a
lodge, working with the Masai.
Working with them was excellent.
I mean, it was such a great
experience.
And I don't think I'll ever,
ever, ever forget that.
Brandon was the hottest,
sexiest, smartest guy on
Survivor.
Aah!
I know he didn't look like it.
Sorry.
But Brandon was the bomb.
Uh-huh.
I got a date with Frank!
I may have had my outlandish
moments, but I was secure enough
to be on a hit show, proclaiming
that I was gay, and it didn't
bother me if everybody knew it.
Are you gay?
Uh-huh, I am.
They put me with people that
they suspected would dislike me
for that very reason.
Brandon would be the last
person on earth I would pick.
You know what?
I got along with them all very
well.
Go, Brandon!
I'm not a very good bartender.
And when I first started, I used
to tell people, you didn't come
because you thought I'd make a
good drink.
I always look good.
Brandon's skills as a
bartender sometimes leave a lot
to be desired.
What he serves best is the
attitude.
What do you want?
A drink!
I work in the leather bar...
Big, burly guys, and I'm not
that.
I'm just a little almost-used-
to-be-chicken kind of guy.
I had never gone camping.
First time I ever slept in a
camping situation was my first
night in Africa under those
stars.
Oh, my goodness!
It made me realize that I really
can do anything if I set my mind
to it.
C'mon, dude, let's go!
Brandon always said the
reason he wanted to be on
Survivor was because there was
no one on TV that he felt
portrayed him.
I think he wanted to show
America a gay man in their
middle 20s who's getting out on
his own and finding his way and
coming to grow as a person.
To Brandon!
The Walt Whitman School is
for gay and lesbian teenagers
who have been tormented in their
schools and abused.
How did the other tribe
members feel about you being a
homosexual?
I'm just a normal gay person.
Some of those kids might see me
and maybe take a little
inspiration, and that makes me
feel very good.
Just because I'm gay, don't
assume certain things about me.
You just never know what kind of
person you're dealing with until
you get to know them.
And that's really all I want to
say.
PROBST: When we come back,
she's hard-driving, yet soft.
Are you calling me
schizophrenic?
PROBST: And later, the softer
side of the hard-driving guy who
won it all.
I'm in touch with my feminine
side.
Her fellow Survivors called her
the smartest girl out there.
She says she's just a homebody
with a wild streak learning to
live in L.A.
From the beginning...
Go!
I was out-manned by everybody.
I thought I was going to pass
out.
I felt like I was the worst
athlete there.
I thought I was definitely the
first person voted off.
But the snake pit that is
Survivor...
We cut Kelly off tonight.
We take her out.
Are you sure?
I'm sure.
Made me uniquely prepared to
live in Los Angeles.
My days usually begin with a
workout.
Okay, guys, what do all good
Californians do?
Go to the gym!
Three, two, one, all right.
All right.
By day, I edit.
I'm a behavioral research
analyst.
What I do is very, very detail-
oriented.
I edit books.
I mean, it's interesting to me.
I love academics.
I love research.
But part of me is a big
homebody... crocheting.
It's... it's my weird
introverted habit.
I made this myself, and it's
big.
It's really, actually, if you
look at it, it's not straight.
But don't tell anybody.
I usually actually make pillows.
Oh, I have one of those, too.
Pillows are my favorite.
Well, I can't reach it because
it's on the top shelf, but trust
me that I have a pillow.
I really... I can't sit still.
But then there's this other side
of me.
I hop in my car, drive way too
fast.
I love to cut loose.
I love to, you know, be wild.
And then, you know, I come back.
I love to crochet.
Are you calling me
schizophrenic?
I love baking cookies.
The secret is that I'm just a
big dork at heart.
It's just who I am.
But, yeah, that's me.
Before I left for Survivor,
I was working a lot.
My mom, who's my best friend
and... you know, she was even
saying, "Teresa, I'm telling
you, you're...
You're not spending enough time
with your children.
You're working too much."
Teresa doesn't want to be a
real estate agent.
She wants to be the best real
estate agent, because that's
just the way she is.
She's basically a corporation.
She was gone a long time, 48
days, with no communication.
It was a long time.
I obviously missed her, and the
kids missed her.
I told my husband Brian when
I left and the way I looked at
it was, "I'm not going on a
summer vacation to Africa.
I'm not going on a safari.
I'm going on a business trip."
The objective of the business
trip was to go out there and be
the last one standing of 16
people.
It's just mind over matter.
It's just a matter of saying,
"I'm going to stand up here, and
I'm going to be the last one, no
matter what."
I get really scared every
night because I'm afraid my mom
could get voted off that night
and, like, she could lose a
challenge.
PROBST: Six hours, 20
seconds.
You, my dear, get this.
Thank you.
PROBST: Congratulations.
I kept thinking about my
children.
I kept thinking about Tyler and
Elly.
And I kept thinking about
watching the show with them and
them seeing their mom, one of
the oldest ones, and just
thinking how proud they would
be.
When I was out in Africa, I had
so much time to think about
family and what's really, really
important.
I started making a mental list
in my mind of things I wanted to
change when I got back home.
Reading to the kids more, saying
their prayers with them at
night.
Saying the blessing at the
dinner table every night.
Giving Brian more back rubs.
I might regret saying that.
When I was watching her plane
to come in, she was the one of
the last ones to get off, and
then when she got off, I was the
first one to run up there and
hug her.
It felt great.
As opposed to me just
being... being a mom and a good
friend, hopefully they'll see me
as a role model, and say, "Hey,
Mom, that's pretty cool."
I'm a city kid.
I've grown up in the city.
The city is where I'm from.
Before Survivor, I was a
financial consultant.
Clarence was my stockbroker.
How you doing, Mr. Green?
So we made some investments,
that we was able to turn a
profit and open a business...
I was, I guess, in that rat
race, just like everybody else:
9:00 to 5:00 job.
It just wasn't for me.
In my first trip out of the
country, I'm seeing animals and
I'm seeing a way of life that
I... that I can't even conceive
of.
I could still see him, too.
I don't want to move.
It was just an awesome
experience, and the food was
good, too.
When I see a gazelle now, I
think, like, "Man, you're a good
piece of meat."
(laughter)
Notice how everything
eventually came back to food.
When they said, "I think
Clarence took two cherries," the
first thought was, "Yeah,
Clarence took two cherries."
I want to be a food critic.
I'm going to be called the man's
man's food critic.
All right, we got ourselves some
barbecue, all up in here.
My man doing it up.
We got some mac and cheese,
Greens.
That's a delicacy there, baby.
If there's one thing being on
Survivor's taught me is... be
yourself.
I came back feeling like, "Wow,
man.
I've got to come up with some
new goals."
It made me want to go see more
of these exotic places that are
out there and not just be a city
dweller.
(alarm clock beeping)
My life as a single mom, it's
not a chore, it's not a duty.
It's a way of life for me.
I get ready for work.
I always wear makeup.
It makes me feel like I'm ready
for the day.
That's it!
Just enjoying a little bit of
downtime before going off to the
post office and another hectic
day.
Good morning.
Then I wake my son up.
Got a kiss?
The whole time we were over in
Africa, we couldn't make any
contact with our family.
En guard!
I wanted to just say, "I'm
okay, Alex.
I didn't get eaten up by a
lion."
My safe return!
My home's great.
I love my home.
It's bright, it's fun, it's
happy.
I'm bright and fun and happy,
so...
You feel like you're inside a
box of colors.
And when you go into another
house, you just feel like you're
in a regular box of brown or
white.
I'm real good at my job.
I am real good at carrying mail.
The audience, they didn't get to
know me.
I did not open the can for me.
I opened the can for her.
The bean incident.
That's a lie!
Clarence, that is not.
Diane!
He lied.
He knows he lied.
I think I'm a little more
sensitive than I was before I
left.
I don't take anything for
granted anymore.
I love you, baby.
Good night, Mom.
I love you.
PROBST: Ahead on
Survivor: Back from Africa...
You don't have to be an evil,
back-stabbing person to do well
in this game.
PROBST: What it took to win.
In the end, it was the
professional soccer player and
coach from Lexington,
Massachusetts, who was the sole
Survivor.
He won it with his strength, his
smarts, but mostly by sticking
to his principles.
Before he left for Africa, I
said to him, "Ethan, it's not
that important that you come
home with $1 million, but you
know what you have to come home
with.
You have to come home with your
integrity."
I said to myself, like,
"listen, I'm not going to change
who I am as a person to be on
the show.
I want to come back with my
dignity and self-respect."
When I come home to Lexington,
that's where I grew up, then I
usually make a grand entrance.
(cheers)
That kid's got, you got my hair
back there.
(laughter)
I like that.
Usually I go on and, you know,
see my brother.
He's a chiropractor.
Hi.
Doing okay?
So he gives me a little
adjustment to straighten me out
a bit.
I stop, I see my mom in her
little knitting store.
Hi, Mommy.
Ethan!
I think he's appealing to women.
I mean, I cringe a little when
one of my friends say, "Oh, your
son's really hot!"
I've always liked women.
Maybe because I was brought up
by my mom, I didn't have... I
was sensitive, you know, the
whole sensitive guy thing.
I'm in touch with my feminine
side.
Maybe it's because I doted on
him so much after his father
died.
The biggest tragedy in his life
was when his father died, and he
was just 14 years old.
He got diagnosed with colon
cancer, and I think from the
time he was diagnosed to when he
passed away, it was maybe a
year.
No matter where Ethan went in
the evening, you know, he knew
he had to be home about 10:30,
11:00 to help get his father up
the stairs.
He could be, you know, having
the best time of his life, but
he was home, come 10:30, 11:00.
If my husband woke up in the
middle of the night, I couldn't
lift him or take him where he
needed to go, he'd say, "Okay,
Dad, I'm going to count to
three.
Put your arms around my neck,
and I'll lift you."
And that's what would happen
time and time again.
Having my father pass away
and, kind of, me overcoming
that, you know, I could have...
is definitely, you know, my
first lesson in survival, I
guess, in being a survivor,
because I could have easily, you
know, gone the whole drug route,
drop out of school, you know, be
depressed my whole life.
I feel there was a change in
him after that, a sense of
intensity that I didn't see
before.
I wanted to push forward and
try to succeed and be the best I
could possibly be at everything
that I've done.
Let's go, blue!
Yeah!
You know, I never thought in a
million years that I'd be
playing professional soccer.
It was always a dream of mine.
Easy! Easy!
I played for the United States
Maccabee team, and I went to
Africa.
I went to Zimbabwe, and I was
one of two white people in the
entire league.
Walking into a stadium...
(crowd cheering)
with 50,000 people is just
uplifting.
Every time I step on the field,
every time I put my cleats on, I
just, you know, get that energy,
that buzz that you get when, you
know, it's... you're doing
something you love.
You got it baby, you got it!
PROBST: There it is!
Survivor is a brilliant game.
You're hungry all the time.
You're tired all the time.
You're dirty all the time.
You're thirsty all the time.
And then you have to make
friends with people.
You have to perform in
challenges.
(cheering)
You have to perform in mental
challenges.
You know, you've got to watch
your back.
But you don't have to be an
evil, back-stabbing person to do
well in this game.
You can be a nice, honest,
genuine person and become the
ultimate Survivor.
PROBST: Up next, a look ahead
to the remote Pacific Island
where 16 new Survivors will face
the challenge of a lifetime.
PROBST: Soon, 16 new
strangers will be abandoned in
the middle of the most remote
place on earth, the Marquesas,
part of Tahiti's mystical
islands in the South Pacific.
Thousands of miles from the
nearest continent, it is a lush
and tropical environment and
home to some of the most
dangerous sea life in the world.
And for the first time, these
Survivors will be given no
rations whatsoever.
It is the ultimate challenge.
Outwit, outplay, outlast until
only one remains and emerges as
the sole Survivor.
Well, that's it for tonight.
I'm Jeff Probst.
Thanks for joining us, and we'll
see you next month for Survivor:
Marquesas.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/agzse
Help other users to choose the best subtitles