(vocalising)
Watch any video online with Open-SUBTITLES
Free Browser extension: osdb.link/ext
There's water in the river again!
(crowd cheering)
Master.
Master!
It's a miracle!
There's water in River Domor.
The river which was dry for a hundred years
is filled with water.
Are we free from the curse, Master?
Hmm?
Hmm.
We... we're free?
We're free!
Everyone listen,
we're free from the curse!
(indistinct)
We're free from the curse!
Everyone, listen!
Listen, everyone.
He has brought life
in the dry River Domor.
He's our god.
- Bow down before him.
- W... what's all this.
Please get up.
Get up.
Hey!
Where do you think you're going?
This cheat's days are over.
Say, everyone.
We'll not listen to these nasty people
anymore!
Hey!
Moti!
Mom!
Mom.
Punish that rascal!
Naad!
Kill him!
Master!
(indistinct)
You were the one who taught me
how to sing.
If you would have told me
on the very first day...
that I'll drown in darkness
because of music.
I'd never have taken up music.
Other people's music is so soulful.
But why is our music lifeless?
Why, Master?
What was our fault?
Hear that?
Can you hear them?
The Domors have risen.
The age of the Rudrabhairavs is over.
And the days of the Naads are also over.
You made me a Naad.
Won't you accept my service
for the last time?
Master?
You thought Raga Sanjivani
will make you immortal.
But it killed you.
You're a bigger unfortunate than us.
Mom.
Mom!
Hey, Mom!
- Mom!
- Moti.
Mom.
Rudrabhairav is dead!
The fraud Master is dead, Mom.
You have no more worries.
Open your eyes, Mom.
Please wake up, Mom.
Couldn't learn to love this time.
If I learn it someday...
I'll come back to you.
Don't break my heart then.
Mom.
Cover you ears.
Cover them.
Cover your ears.
Hey, cover your ears, everyone!
Cover them fast!
Cover your ears.
How did Mumtaz die, Bahadur Uncle?
Believe me, Bahadur.
It's true that I came here to kill
Abdul's descendants.
And I know that you and Mumtaz
are his descendants.
But I couldn't kill Mumtaz.
I'm in love with her.
Trust me, Bahadur.
- I don't believe you, rascal.
- You have to.
I would have killed you and Mumtaz by now
if I wanted to.
Bahadur, after coming to Anandagarh
I've realised that hatred...
can destroy everything
in an instant.
But love gives the power
to protect.
I want to live like others.
I want freedom from Rudrabhairav.
I want to save you and Mumtaz.
Need your help for that.
My help?
You have to find a corpse, Bahadur.
- Corpse?
- Yes.
He was Abdul's only son.
He was hiding.
I've learnt that Abdul does not have
anymore children.
Madanti's lineage ends with him.
Please release me now.
Where do you think you're going?
Bring him here.
Alap, he's the root of all problems.
Shame on you!
(indistinct chatter)
There's only one weakness with my son.
In his body there's blood
of a rascal like you.
If only he could purify it
with a raga.
Whore!
Bastard!
Hold the rascal tightly!
Hey!
Take him away.
Let me go!
(indistinct)
Don't cry, Mom.
Don't cry.
I know that you're not a bastard.
I know your parents.
What!
"All who possess the discs are 'udara'.
'Bibadi' is Mumtaz's daughter".
"Bibadi'" is a particular note
which is not used in any raga.
Amanat Khan, while giving the clue
on Raga Sanjivani...
gave discs to everyone
except my mom.
He has given the hint
through this line of the riddle.
Isn't it, Bahadur Uncle?
Amanat Khan left a hint.
Kedar Mishra and Mumtaz's daughter...
His own granddaughter...
did not receive a disc from him.
He did not want his granddaughter
to get into trouble.
If your mom is their only daughter...
- Who am I then?
- Hear him out.
W... what are you saying, Alap?
I'm not saying this, Mom.
It's science.
Ramnidhi Uncle.
Yes?
Gopal told us something
before he died.
In my mobile...
there are some DNA test reports.
Gopal followed Rudrabhairav's orders
and got everyone's DNA samples.
Everyone's DNA matched
with the people of Rudrapur.
Everyone's except Mom's.
You're not an illicit child, Mom.
Kedar Mishra and Mumtaz's real daughter
is not Ma'am.
It's you.
What?
Alap!
Isn't it, Bahadur Uncle?
Bahadur!
Bahadur.
She's like you, sister.
Just like you.
But Master Kedar did not come
to see his daughter.
When will he return?
He said he'll be late.
There's a flood in some village.
Come, sweetie.
- Don't cry, sweetie.
- He has gone to rescue children from there.
Kedar truly loves you, Mumtaz.
Don't suspect him.
Remember, the Ramayana?
Even a dacoit can turn into a sage.
And if someone from Rudrapur
gets to know our identity?
What if he changes his mind in future?
I'm not telling it for myself, Grandpa.
They'll not spare even my daughter.
Hmm.
It's quite possible.
There's only one way out.
Bahadur...
you have to do something.
When he brings the children
he had rescued...
exchange this baby
with one of them.
But this must remain
within the three of us.
You stole my dad.
Your dad will be your's forever.
I give you my word.
I'll always keep it a secret.
Everyone promise me...
that you'll keep it a secret.
Promise me!
What about Raga Sanjivani?
Calm down.
Raga Sanjivani.
That...
That will remain a secret too.
It will remain a secret.
Master told me...
that the raga can bring
the dead back to life.
But it can kill many others.
So, Tansen kept it a secret.
We'll keep it a secret too.
Go, let it drown.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today