FAMILY MOTTO
A HARMONIOUS FAMILY WITH LOVE
-Thank you for the food.
Leave it. I'll do it.
Are you done eating?
You should've just come in to eat with us.
How can I take my share
when you ordered four servings?
Did Ji-woo eat the hangover soup?
He emptied the bowl.
I raised him well.
Get to the point.
You…
went on a trip with your parents
every vacation.
Even after you turned 30.
A photo of you and your parents
on a trip, smiling happily.
I remember it.
So this is why you're so warm-hearted.
You and your parents
are so bright.
I was envious.
You're warm.
It's no use for you to act grumpy.
You're good at comforting
people who are hurt.
That's why I left my sister in your hands.
I have no other intentions.
All right.
I don't think you had
any other intentions, okay?
Please let my sister know this.
Even if she feels betrayed
and angry at her husband,
she shouldn't say hurtful and nasty words.
She shouldn't say something
she doesn't mean.
I'm really worried, that's why.
My sister would be
a serial killer if words could kill.
That's too extreme.
I'm going to tell Eun-joo.
What is it?
Seeing you smile
makes me feel a lot better.
I'm…
going to be friends with you for real.
True friends.
Totally friends.
What's with you?
Oh, friends forever
Do you have to do this
in our neighborhood?
Yes!
I think I can really go now.
I'm leaving, my friend!
Bye!
Seriously…
The feeling of deja vu,
like having the same day before.
My heart is beating for you.
Me laughing so hard,
trying not to get caught.
It always ends with self-hypnotization,
saying "Well done,
you did the right thing,"
then and now.
And my solidified heart
does not break easily.
Since when have you guys been there?
Give me 10,000 won.
Why? Tell me if you need money.
I said it seems like Eun-hee is here,
and he said she's not.
So I won the bet.
Give me 10,000 won!
Why did you give that to her?
Is Eun-hee a stalker?
She even came to the office
for not answering her calls?
Your sister is tenacious, you know.
Chan-hyuk.
I was going to tell Seo-young
to stop calling her
by her name, but I didn't.
Don't hold back. Tell her to stop it.
I'm holding it back
because I know how she feels.
She likes you.
And you know she likes you.
I do.
And I know that she shows it on purpose,
regardless of who's around her.
But do you know why?
Because she likes you. What else is there?
No.
Seo-young is…
Seo-young is tricking herself
into liking me.
-When she actually doesn't.
-Why?
There is a reason.
You will know
if you get close to Seo-young too.
Well, if you're curious, ask her directly.
Come on, Chan-hyuk,
what are you talking about?
Not me. I think of her
as my coworker only. For real.
You're denying it seriously.
I don't pry into employees' privacy.
I have a girlfriend.
Do you think I wouldn't know
if you have a girlfriend?
You're making a ridiculous excuse,
so it means you…
I really do have a girlfriend.
Don’t tell my family.
It's top-secret. I'll tell you later.
One hot Americano, please.
Okay.
Yes.
I arrived.
-Happy birthday dear Yu-jeong
-Happy birthday to you
JUNE 13, EUN-JOO'S BIRTHDAY
I never cared about her birthday, anyway.
November 13…
December 13…
January. February, March, April, May…
June.
Was Kim Eun-joo born prematurely?
No.
I heard Mom was pregnant with her
when the photo was taken.
October 13, 1982.
That was the day
I proposed to your mother.
On that day,
I held Ms. Sook's hand for the first time.
Are Dad's memories
not completely back yet?
Ms. Kim Eun-hee?
Are you here to see Kyung-ok?
Yes.
I'm Jeon Ha-ra,
Kyung-ok's junior from school.
I'm Kim Eun-hee.
How…
You found me at once.
I saw the photo you took with Kyung-ok.
You look much younger than in the photo.
Kyung-ok is always
at least 30 minutes late…
She's coming. Kyung-ok.
Hi, girls.
What the heck?
Did you two become friends already?
We just said hi.
Ms. Eun-hee was here first.
No need to use honorifics.
You two are the same age.
-I'm sorry.
-It's okay.
You have a baby face.
Thank you.
Now, it's time for a proper introduction.
This is Jeon Ha-ra, my junior
from elementary, middle, and high school.
And this is Kim Eun-hee,
my junior from work.
-Say hi.
-Hi.
Ha-ra is my personal stylist
who changed my style.
Did I become your personal stylist?
I knew it.
I could see the touch of a professional.
Eun-hee was so envious of me,
saying my style got so awesome,
so I decided to share my personal stylist.
Aren't you thankful?
I'm so thankful.
Since I came here last, I'll pay.
What would you like to drink?
I drank mine already.
I'd like…
-Kyung-ok, let's order together.
-Shall we? Okay.
Do you have any specific kind
of cake you like?
Anything is fine.
People who say
"anything is fine" isn't fun.
Since I'm the personal stylist today,
I should change your taste in things.
-Let's go, Kyung-ok.
-Yes, let's go.
Before I got married,
Dad came to my workplace.
When he wasn't making
enough for the family…
He said it was a debt to me.
He saved up for seven years
but apologized for not having enough.
INSTALLMENT SAVINGS ACCOUNT
KIM SANG-SIK
He calculated the money
to pay me back every day.
Even if I insisted
I wouldn't take it, it was no use.
He asked me
to keep it a secret.
Why tell the secret
between the two after all this time?
I don't need this money anymore.
I don't want to be compensated
for that time like this.
To think of how Dad spent seven years
to save this money…
It hurts me to look at the bankbook.
Okay.
I get it.
I guess I was shocked
because the amount is so big.
Dad can't keep sleeping in his truck.
At least help him get a place.
I know that
he wasn't a great husband.
But…
You prepared for graduation
from marriage for a long time.
But Dad was suddenly forced to do it,
when he never thought about it, ever.
That's…
shocking enough
to break his body and mind.
You are being
too cruel to him.
Okay, I get it.
But…
I…
really…
want to rest.
Why do I feel so sad?
Is my time
and my life
worth less than a single bankbook?
OCTOBER 13, 1982
Was the change
in Kyung-ok's style good enough
to make you envious?
Of course.
I don't know that much about it,
but she had
this natural sophisticated charm.
You say things in such a complicated way.
What does "natural
sophisticated charm" mean?
Oh.
It means something positive,
like a sudden change in style
can look awkward, but it wasn't like that.
That's because I got a solid foundation.
So it means something positive.
I don't like changing things
too suddenly to show it.
I like natural things.
Right.
Ha-ra totally hates changes.
She's been dating only one man
for nine years.
How about we reveal it now,
so Eun-hee can be shocked?
Come on, why would it be shocking?
It's an obvious story.
Ha-ra…
is our vice CEO's nine-year girlfriend.
You must be so shocked.
Of course, I'm shocked.
It's not an obvious story.
Right. Look at your face.
You're totally shocked, right?
Right.
Eun-hee,
you have trauma
about nine-year relationships.
Change of topic.
Let's finish and go shopping.
What's the trauma?
I'll tell you about that later.
Don't you think we should
change her style, too?
No, thanks. It's hard to make me stylish.
It's not hard.
Feminine beauty, but not too much.
Coy, but not too much.
You act like you don't care,
but you’re obsessed
with the intellectual vibe.
I always try not to overdo it,
but I'm not obsessed.
Okay.
I know a shop
that would totally suit Eun-hee.
Let's go.
Yes, let's go.
Let's use our credit cards
until we get tired of using them.
No, thanks. I wouldn't have come here
if I knew you were going shopping.
I feel uncomfortable then.
Like I got in between you two.
Come with us.
Yes, I'm Kim Eun-hee.
You're nothing but a cheater,
and you dared to come here with Jong-min?
Is the past me and the current me
different in any aspect?
Yes, let's go.
Let's go.
Okay, ready.
Look here, Seo-young.
Shoot the product first.
This is so annoying.
What is it? What happened?
This is so annoying!
That punk…
looked at my social media page
and said I look well.
He said he's glad that I look well.
Didn't you expect this to happen
when you started social media?
I did expect it.
I was prepared for it too.
But he was friends with my mom.
Seriously…
I want to move out of the house.
Think straight.
Your mother isn't the problem.
How do you feel after seeing his comment?
Like a rollercoaster.
It goes up all of a sudden,
I get chills,
and I get angry.
Something like that.
You're doing so well compared to before.
To be honest, these days…
I sometimes forget about it while I work.
Yes.
Even if you can sometimes forget it,
you'll never…
forget that memory.
But…
try forgetting from time to time
for longer periods.
Then you should
think of me as a woman from time to time.
And try doing that for longer periods.
You saying something
like that at a time like this
makes me wonder
if you're actually okay or not.
It's all thanks to you.
In five minutes.
No…
I'll begin in a moment.
Okay.
Didn't feel to go shopping after a while?
Money is something
you're supposed to spend.
One, two, three, four, five.
Oh, my.
Vice CEO.
Looks like he's here for dinner.
Do you mind?
Yes.
I do.
Do you feel uncomfortable?
Yes. You two go ahead.
-Kyung-ok, let's go then.
-Yes.
We need to talk alone.
Come on, say hi at least.
I'm sorry.
No, it's okay.
Let's go.
You two can eat here.
We're only going to talk.
We're not going to eat.
-Let's go.
-Yes.
Let's go to your house.
What the heck?
They can't eat together,
but they can go home together?
I guess she doesn't want
rumors to spread at work.
She held things back,
no matter what I said.
How did you know?
You…
Did you read my emails too?
Actually, I've been dying to
come here today.
I'm so thankful
as they disappeared on their own.
Let's see.
This one.
-Kyung-ok.
-Yes?
Why didn't you tell me
you were bringing your junior with you?
I forgot because I was in a hurry.
Right?
I thought so too.
To be honest, Ha-ra was curious about
female employees in the company.
I guess she wanted to see the women
who were working for her boyfriend.
Hey, but, can't you understand
how she feels?
I could totally understand her.
You know Mr. Choi with a bad temper?
He said that he saw Young-sik walking
here and there at this place.
But Young-sik's leg is not well,
and he's too weak to work here.
He's young.
You also once ran here
and there at a place like this.
And you got hurt.
Young-sik? Why are you looking for him?
Because we have a reason to look for him.
He's the child of this man here.
The child?
He went somewhere else.
Everyone here is a wandering laborer.
If he's on the run like this,
it's obviously about money.
Sang-sik, tell me the truth.
You have money issues with him, right?
Sang-sik, where are you going?
The workers won't like it.
Get out. You're not supposed to be here.
-Get out!
-Okay.
Eun-joo.
Have you been like this
by yourself all this time?
I haven't. I'll go wash my face.
I thought I knew you well.
But I didn't know
you would suffer so much.
It's not because of you.
I saw my Mom.
Did something happen to her?
I showed off for making money
when my father was injured
and my family was struggling.
I said mean things to Mom,
because I hate graduation from marriage.
So it is because of me.
Don't blame yourself.
You put your anger out on your mother.
I hated her cold attitude toward Dad.
She never laughed,
even if something joyful happened.
It was uncomfortable.
I'm like my mom.
I push my family away from me.
You never pushed them away.
Our problem is because of me.
Do you know what I regret?
I regret
letting Eun-hee
sleep at our house that day.
If she didn't know,
I would've tricked everyone.
I would've just told you to live.
I'll act like I don't know.
-It's not so hard, right?
-Eun-joo…
Don't you think it's creepy?
I'm just like your parents, aren't I?
You're different. You just need time.
You wanted to be friends.
Yes.
Just live here as friends.
That'll make things harder.
Let's break up quickly.
Are you being considerate to me?
If so, I will try and experience
how much harder things get for me.
-I can't do it anymore.
-After tricking me for years?
Did you have to tell me
when I was dealing with my parent's issue?
Couldn't you be more considerate?
Tae-hyung, even if you feel uncomfortable,
you're family too, so I thought
you should hear it together.
-Mom, here…
-No, put it in front of Tae-hyung.
It was painful
because your mother and father
treated me like family.
Then you tell them yourself. I can't.
INSTALLMENT SAVINGS ACCOUNT
KIM SANG-SIK
You must be glad that
your life can be calculated accurately.
Not everyone in the world
is skilled like me.
There are those without skills.
Then who should do it for them?
Now, first,
wipe with alcohol.
And dry them,
so they can be attached nicely.
Help me out.
I can't. My hands are tied.
Okay, let's take a break.
Hello?
When are you coming? Did you eat dinner?
I'm still busy. Why?
Right.
Call your father
and ask him to stop by the house.
Hello?
I can't tell Dad to leave
and then come back.
Mom, you call him from now on.
I'm hanging up.
You can't keep sleeping
in the truck forever.
You can find a place with Young-sik.
I can only ask him to live with me
when I remember something.
That wretched memory!
That damn memory!
Sang-sik.
Why?
The guitar in your car.
Play the guitar.
-What?
-You can play the guitar too.
It's just like driving.
Go bring the guitar.
I can play the guitar?
Of course.
When you ate with me and had coffee,
you used to play the guitar
and sing for me.
Man-ho.
-Yes?
-Did I really play the guitar
and sing for you?
Are you sure you're not just saying things
because my memories are on and off, right?
Did I really do that?
Did I?
Sang-sik…
I should get going now.
Sang-sik, it's your wife.
Come on, answer the phone.
What if she changed her mind?
I had an affair and a kid.
I will not interrupt
Ms. Sook's life anymore.
You're like a rat being nice to a cat.
What? A rat?
A rat.
-Hey, you…
-No.
-Come here.
-My leg!
I just can't…
MISSED CALLS
JIN-SOOK
The caller cannot be reached.
Please leave a message…
VICE CEO IM
Hello?
Were you waiting for his call?
Do you think he'd call you
when he's with me?
Hey, Ms. Kim Eun-hee.
Say something!
Do you think I'm doing this
because I have regrets?
I'm just trying to pay back
for what I've suffered.
I asked him to break up three years ago!
-Stop it.
-Do you remember
how much you harassed me at the time?
You should suffer too.
Don't move. Stay still.
She's not young,
not pretty,
looks poor
and has a rotten mind
to have an affair with her boss.
It's embarrassing to be
like this because of her.
Is this your revenge from three years ago?
Then get a girl who measures up.
THISTLE: THIS IS THE SECOND PROPOSAL
THANK YOU FOR THE FEEDBACK.
I'M SENDING YOU THE REVISED PROPOSAL
THE FIRST PLAN WAS FULL OF TYPOS!
JANE, DON'T LEARN KOREAN FROM ME!
I have a friend
who likes Vincent van Gogh.
And he said he recalls landscape paintings
by Van Gogh whenever he takes photos
because he can see the angle
to take the photos.
That's cool.
I want to see your friend's photos.
I want to see them too.
Why can't you see them?
Because I broke his heart
with harsh words.
Like Van Gogh.
If you regret it, apologize.
I'm sure you miss your friend
and want to see the photos he took.
I'm afraid he might not accept
my apology, so I can't.
Thistle, never lose your friend
who's spending your twenties with you.
I said all kinds of things.
Hi.
I've done nothing but study all my life.
So when something happens,
I try to find
the most logical way to solve it.
I don't want to beat around the bushes.
If you want a divorce,
I can take care of the alimony.
Is that a logical way to solve it?
So the reason you came
all the way here on your day off is money?
Did you know?
He said he will put this house
under your name.
I didn't know.
Yes.
I knew it.
You're not a shameless girl.
You're wise and simple, right?
A girl who grew up in a lowly household,
but wise and simple.
My mother-in-law's opinion
of me never changes.
I'd like coffee.
By the way, you really didn't know?
Didn't you think that you two
weren't on the same level?
The marriage wasn't for love, right?
Please stop and go.
We'll talk about it.
You.
I thought you would be able to
handle this marriage.
I chose you.
-Did you forget?
-Mother.
I'm not telling you
to be my daughter-in-law.
I'm just saying
we should make a wiser choice
for everyone.
If you let her be,
then she can live peacefully
by acting like she doesn't know.
Why make things worse?
You two are family.
I'm sick and tired of that word "family."
Eun-joo isn't like you.
She did her best.
She did everything she could.
My conscience can't handle it anymore.
I am going to stop. So give up.
Get up and go.
You should've just come in. Why text me?
Did you get up just now?
I went to bed late.
So why are you here so early?
If it's not a side dish delivery
from Mom, what is it?
Coffee.
Coffee for me too.
You look a bit serious.
Is something wrong?
Eun-hee.
Why?
Yesterday,
did you have to come to the office
just because Chan-hyuk was ignoring you?
What are you talking about?
Did he say something?
No, it's just not pleasant to see.
Even if you're friends, that's not right.
That's not Chan-hyuk's house.
It's his company.
I didn't know
he'd be working on the weekend.
His home would be weird too.
You have a guy. Does Chan-hyuk know?
He does. I told him.
Of course, I can tell him.
Did you think I was making
a move on Chan-hyuk
without telling him that I have a guy?
No, that's not it…
Then?
Chan-hyuk and Seo-young…
They have an unusual relationship.
There's something between them.
You brat. Did you
figure that out just now?
You knew it, and you did that?
Do you…
Do you think men and women
cannot be friends?
Men and women, friends, or whatever.
Chan-hyuk ignored your calls.
He ignored them on purpose.
That's a sign. A sign telling you
to keep the boundaries.
Did you have to ignore that
and barge into the office?
Don't you feel sorry for Chan-hyuk?
You cut ties on your own
and act like you're close to him
on your own.
"Act like I'm close to him?" That's harsh.
You're breaking my heart.
I'm asking you to not cross the line.
He's the CEO of the company I work at.
This is how scary a paycheck is.
All right.
I had something
I had to wrap up yesterday.
I'm sorry.
I won't do that again.
I've been seeing him
since I was in elementary,
and I think of him as my
brother and family.
He's not family. I am your sister.
I raised you. I am your family.
How childish.
You can die from childishness.
Ji-woo, you've grown up.
You're a cheapskate, but you bought
pastries to give me advice.
Let's go. I have to go
to Mom and Dad's house, too.
I'm going to go play games.
And I'll be rebellious for a while.
I only sleep at my house…
Rebellious? Don't even!
You think you're a teenager?
You're being ridiculous, you little kid!
Kid? I told you not to do that!
-Not to do what?
-You're even smaller than me.
-Want to wrestle?
-Come on.
-You little…
-Try me.
GOLDEN GOOSE MEDIA
Why are you here?
I came here to check something.
What's with those nasty eyes of yours?
Because I need
to check something with you.
No one wears a suit
to a blind date these days.
Right, Mom said it's a blind date
to get a fiance.
My mother must be seeing
her friends too often after she retired.
Blind date to get a fiance.
A meeting of a man and a woman
checking looks and attitudes
with the intention of getting married.
Wow, I'm totally shocked.
Does Eun-hee know too?
What's the point?
Doesn't she know that you do everything
your parents tell you to do?
You said you're leaving.
Let me get changed and get some rest.
She's your friend, but she knows nothing.
I know a lot more.
I liked her because she knew nothing.
It's in the past tense.
So that means you liked her before.
It means I like her as a friend
who knows nothing.
I have to go home
and report about my blind date.
I'm leaving.
Wait for me.
Don't be too rebellious
and come home early.
Whatever.
The suit and the camera
don't go well together.
That's a prejudice.
Chan-hyuk.
Why are you here?
To play a game. The Wi-Fi works well here.
How come she didn't say goodbye
before she left?
She's waving.
She's saying goodbye with it.
I'm going in.
Looks so dazzling.
-My friend.
-Something happened again at home?
Why? Should something happen?
You aren't nice enough to Ji-woo
to meet him and give him a ride.
Ji-woo must be going through puberty.
He's being rebellious to Mom and me.
And I'm not a nice sister
who can tolerate him being rebellious.
What are you trying to say?
Why aren't you with Mr. Playboy?
and why are you wandering around,
looking horrible?
I've always looked like this.
Your standard must've gotten
higher because of her.
I'm on my way to see him.
Get off the phone.
Bye.
What’s wrong with my looks? Damn it.
I chose you.
Did you forget?
Then I'll meet with
the pharmaceutical company and see
if your thesis was cited
in the patent document.
Okay.
Want to have dinner?
Do you have time?
Oh.
Yes, I do.
Good.
There's someone we will eat dinner with.
This is Patent Attorney Kim Eun-joo.
This is Yoon Tae-hyung, my student.
I didn’t think the professor would set up
such an occasion.
I didn't know, either.
I thought she was wrapping
things with our team today.
She always said she doesn't like
how the work was done.
She thinks no one is
good at working except for herself.
She's selfish and immature.
I understand the selfishness
and immaturity of someone successful.
It's not harmful, at least.
You just don't need to be hurt
by straightforward words.
What words can hurt?
"I like you because
you don't flatter people."
It's not obvious that you're poor.
She insults me so brightly,
making it sound like a compliment.
You analyzed my mother the best
among all the people I met.
Mother?
You call a cafe employee
near your house by his name?
Are you jealous?
Would there really be a friend
who carries my sadness
on his or her back?
You.
Get some rest.
Is it hard that my parents
treat you like family?
You want to stop
because of your conscience?
That's not the real reason.
You…
find me
burdensome.
Because I like you.
Without realizing it,
little by little,
slowly…
I grew to like you.
I guess that's why I tried so hard.
I realized after saying it.
That was the most useless
and sad confession.
OCTOBER 13, 1982
What am I, a thief?
Why did he ask me to do this?
Over here.
Like this.
But still, it was Dad's favor…
OCTOBER 13, 1982
Jin-sook, over here.
Hi.
Well…
Sang-sik must be out of his mind.
He kept ignoring your calls.
No, I didn't call him more on purpose.
It seems like he's settled down
in a quiet place after work.
Keep going straight.
Miss Sook, did you kiss me?
You haven't changed at all.
Let's graduate from marriage now.
JIN-SOOK
I'm at the plant.
You could've asked Ji-woo
to deliver the message.
Why come all the way here?
He doesn't want to.
He told me to call you directly
if I have something to say.
But you don't answer my calls.
You could've texted me.
I'm sorry for coming here.
If I need anything, I'll buy it.
Don't worry about it.
Don't buy unnecessary things,
and use the money in it for a few days.
Come back home when I call you.
Are you
telling me to come back home?
Yes.
I decided to leave the house.
The kids think I kicked you out,
and they resent me.
It's hard to be at home.
Why would our kids do that?
I broke your heart
and their hearts to graduate
from marriage suddenly,
so I should leave.
Because you're a good father
who worked hard your whole life
to make money.
INSTALLMENT SAVINGS ACCOUNT
Why should I take this?
Why should I take Eun-joo's bankbook?
Just how many secrets
are you keeping from me?
Are there more secrets for me to find out?
Why are you making me
a bad person to our kids?
Then don't take it.
You're graduating from marriage
but also taking our daughter's money?
You're not that kind of person, Ms. Sook.
Don't you remember this bankbook?
You made this bankbook for Eun-joo.
Don't you remember?
INSTALLMENT SAVINGS ACCOUNT
Your memories aren't back, are they?
I remember everything.
I just didn't know she kept it
without using it.
Give it back to Eun-joo.
This is not a place
for someone to roam around freely.
So don’t go anywhere and wait here.
So that's why such a thing happened.
Man-ho!
What?
You don't even take a taxi
because it's expensive.
Don't come all the way here anymore.
Fasten your seat belt.
THE BRIDGES OF MADISON COUNTY
Is this the first edition?
When did you come?
A while ago.
Did you eat?
I ate two servings of a home-cooked meal.
Where have you been at this hour?
You dressed up like a college student.
It's because you love me!
Why did you come here without telling me?
Are you here to fight me too?
"Too?"
Who fought you, Ms. Sook?
Who was it?
That wretched "Ms. Sook."
Ms. Sook!
Eun-joo's birthday is soon.
Did you think I'd forget?
Mom, by any chance…
Was Eun-joo born prematurely?
What are you talking about?
Dad asked me to bring this photo to him,
so I came to get it secretly, but I can't.
This photo…
I think the root grew from this.
I can't pull it out.
This is the best place for it to be.
Stop talking nonsense and take it to him.
Want to take jangjorim?
He said this was
the day he proposed to you
and held your hand for the first time,
and this photo was taken
to remember it forever.
Mom.
Dad said it wrong, right?
You said you were already pregnant
with Eun-joo at the time.
She cannot be premature.
You said Eun-joo was born
later than her due date.
Did you…
say it wrong?
Mom.
Tell me what I'm thinking is wrong.
Please.
You must never…
tell her now.
We shouldn't give any more
burdens to Kim Eun-joo.
She won't be able to handle it.
THE. YOO'S FRUIT SHOP
May 3, 2015.
I gave the bankbook to Eun-joo.
I regret depositing 500,000 won per month
instead of 600,000 won per month.
Ms. Sook.
I feel like I'm still dreaming.
One thing is for sure.
Family is all I have.
Eun-joo's father came.
We should graduate from marriage too.
You just want me to sign up
for life insurance and die, right?
I'm sorry I'm not fit
to be Eun-joo's father.
Do you remember
how you neglected our kids?
Do you remember that?
I…
I remember.
Chan-hyuk.
I…
hate myself.
Since you confessed your feelings for me,
I should give you an answer.
How did you find out about this place?
I've tailed you before.
Is asking every single thing
and being emotional dating?
That's what I liked about you.
To meet you.
I have something to tell you
about your father.
You're my sister
and I'm your younger sister.
Why would I be curious about
those who were never by my side?
Subtitle translation by: Hae-lim Lee