ENJOY ALL VOD IN HIGH QUALITY @ 4KVOD.TV
GET LIVE TV,MOVIES,SHOWS IN ONE PACKAGE
FAMILY MOTTO
A HARMONIOUS FAMILY WITH LOVE
How did you find out about Dad?
Tae-hyung came to my work
saying that I should know about it, too.
When?
Yesterday.
It means Tae-hyung
is taking it seriously too.
Dad had insomnia. It's been quite a while.
He even went night hunting before.
Don't get agitated
without thinking things through.
Then he should've taken the pills,
not collected them.
I looked into it,
and long-distance drivers
and those who work at night
tend to suffer from depression.
A side effect
of antidepressants is suicide.
Isn't it terrifyingly ironic?
Dad might've been taking antidepressants.
Antidepressants. Sleeping pills.
These words…
don't seem to fit Dad.
Why not?
Because dad dropped out of middle school
and worked all his life,
he can't get insomnia and depression?
You think his life was simple?
Why are you being so abrasive?
Why are you getting worse as time passes?
They're having a great time.
They told me to call you over.
I have editing to do.
Okay, I'll tell them that you're busy.
I know you won't enjoy this occasion.
I truly love your wisdom, CEO.
Don't let your guard down
because they're having a good time.
It can change in an instant.
He worries too much.
Have a good weekend. See you on Monday.
TEAM LEADER EUN-HEE
Remember?
Mom only took you
and ran away from the house.
You were absent from school
for a long time too.
I was so happy that you came back home,
but you didn't talk to me for a long time.
You weren't the only one I didn't talk to.
I didn't talk to anyone for a long time.
Why not?
You must be bored.
Not at all. I like to listen.
I cried every night,
but you came home
with wildflowers in your hand.
I came in with wildflowers in my hand?
Memories are so selfish.
It only knows itself.
-That's a fact.
-I don't remember
whether I had wildflowers
or a rock in my hand.
At the time,
I was cold and hungry every day.
But you were wearing new clothes
and a lovely headband,
and eating the food Dad cooked.
I was wearing new clothes
and a lovely headband?
Yes. This is how different
memories can be.
So don't say it's a fact so mindlessly.
Cold and hungry?
That wasn't the war times or anything.
I worried more about school
than being cold and hungry.
When I saw the kids going to school
with neat backpacks,
I envied them.
So, why did Mom take you with her?
She should've taken me.
I've always hated going to school,
since the first day of kindergarten.
I guess Mom didn't want to
make you suffer.
From then until even now,
Mom won't let you and Ji-woo suffer.
If someone hears that,
they might think
I grew up like a princess.
When I was in college,
I worked like crazy, right?
I worked as a contract teacher
and as a private tutor on weekends.
I made as much money
as large corporate employees did.
And as I gave all that money to my family,
I got exhausted.
You should charge that to Ms. Lee Jin-sook
and Mr. Kim Sang-sik.
Why is it me all the time?
I'm saying I made money
and helped pay tuition too.
-You're drunk. Drink some water.
-I'm not drunk!
Eun-hee.
My friend's husband
started to leave the house,
saying he was going to smoke,
buy something to drink,
take out the trash,
and even mow the lawn.
Holding his phone tightly in his hand.
He was cheating on her.
They got divorced.
RUN, FATHER
Are you having an affair again?
It's not an affair.
We broke up.
I said we should take time
to think about it.
Seeing you grabbing your phone once more,
I don't feel like breaking up.
We broke up, and we had time
to wrap things up.
But I guess there's no need to.
Take that photo with you.
I can carry them to your house.
It's okay. You can go from here.
Mr. Yoo, who studies
fruits and vegetables,
please come out.
What are you saying?
This is a real estate office.
Gosh, I'm so sorry.
Where's Mr. Yoo?
Can you take her home?
It will get messier if you're with us.
Just go, quietly.
-Go.
-Mr. Yoo.
Where are you…
Eun-joo, what do you know?
-You know nothing.
-Be quiet.
Mr. Yoo.
"Have a good weekend. See you on Monday."
Yes, you're telling me not to call you
during the weekend, right?
Where do you want to sleep?
-Eun-joo.
-Goodness.
-Hey.
-We were born from the same tree,
but why are we so different?
Why am I not smart and sharp like you?
I said, where do you want to sleep?
I'm so tired.
Why did my Dad do that?
Dad.
Come to Ulsan with me.
It seems like you're bothered,
so let's go meet him.
I am not keeping
any more secrets from you.
Kim Ji-woo. Why aren't you going home
at this late hour?
The subway stopped running.
Is it that late already?
It seems like
you don't want to go home these days.
With the upcoming summer break.
I was thinking hard about
whether or not to go to the military.
And that bastard Jong-pal said
he started dating Eun-hee.
They became a college couple.
It's been a while since
I heard that expression. College couple.
So, you went to serve in the military
because my sister got a boyfriend?
There was a girl named Na-ri.
Na-ri?
Is she your ex-girlfriend?
Na-ri.
I can never forget it.
What?
The typhoons only came
to southern regions, where I was serving.
I was a second private,
and I went through hell.
I thought, "Yes, sure, go ahead and date."
"I'm going to fight against a typhoon."
The typhoon was named Na-ri.
Chan-hyuk.
You liked my sister.
You dummy. I liked Eun-joo.
See?
You liked my sister.
I didn't, you jerk.
Ji-woo, don't sleep there.
Ji-woo, lay this out…
Ji-woo, sleep here.
Sleep with me here, Ji-woo.
My eldest sister
has no father.
No, wait. How should I say this?
Dad…
isn't her father.
No.
She has a different father.
Now, why did I hear such a thing?
Come on, your father is her father,
and her father is your father.
What?
Ms. Jin-sook, I love you.
I really, truly love you.
I had forgotten.
There was a time when he declared
his love for me many times a day.
You declared your love for me
a lot as well.
You were too shy to actually say it,
so you wrote "I love you" on the note.
Whenever you made my lunch boxes,
I really loved looking for those notes.
Don't sneak out. Let's finish talking.
CLOSET: PETER YOON'S CHATROOM
What are you doing in there?
Charging.
Charging my phone.
Tae-hyung left his laptop.
Is that okay?
What's with the face?
Oh.
Hangover.
Eun-joo.
Don't look.
CLOSET: PETER YOON'S CHATROOM
We're family.
We are family.
but we don't know much
about each other.
Mom.
Mom. You spent a lot of money
to see your doctor son-in-law.
I really love these clothes.
You should've just given me
the money to buy clothes.
Ji-woo, what's with the face?
Just laugh. Don't hold it in.
Mom, do I have to wear this?
This is our first time seeing him.
First expressions are important.
Jong-pal is no match
for my future brother-in-law.
We should eat together.
Wow.
Dad, you look great.
That shirt looks perfect on you.
You need to shave.
It'll be done if you just shave once.
Dad, my newest shaver is now all charged.
You just need to move it a few times.
Jeez.
-Stop it.
-Why?
You don't need to shave,
so please wear that.
It's too uncomfortable to eat.
Welcoming a new family member
isn't a comfortable thing.
I'm glad you brought that up.
He's going to be our family anyway,
so what's the point of wearing this?
I didn't dress you up
to make you look good.
It's our first time meeting him,
so we need to be polite.
Don't be ridiculous.
You're intimidated by the doctor
son-in-law from a family of doctors.
Money is the best for you, isn't it?
Yes, money is the best!
Because my daughter
doesn't have to live like I did!
I love my doctor son-in-law to death!
So wear it for your daughter!
-Wear it!
-What's wrong with your life?
Did you have an extremely hard life?
-Did you work?
-All right!
I lived my life comfortably
with the money you made!
So wear it!
You just want me to sign up
for life insurance and die, right?
Enough talk about that insurance!
Stop it if you aren't
actually going to die!
Nice to meet you.
I'm Yoon Tae-hyung.
It was a bad dream.
It didn't really happen.
I'm sure it didn't.
Eun-joo.
Stop reading it.
What's the point?
Eun-joo.
Open the door.
Stop it.
CLOSET: PETER YOON'S CHATROOM
DAD
Eun-hee. This is your father.
Do you remember the day when my doctor
son-in-law first visited our house?
Was I there, too?
I read it because Dad texted.
Why did he ask
about Tae-hyung all of a sudden?
I guess he remembered something.
Are you okay?
I'm sure Dad's frustrated
about being unable to remember.
Reply to him now.
And you should go too.
I want to be alone.
We had dinner together.
You drank with Tae-hyung,
though you're a lightweight.
Do you remember something?
No.
I think I had a similar dream.
Dad said he was dozing off
and had a dream.
Looks like his memories
will come back soon.
This injection will be a bit painful.
First injection pregnancies are very rare.
It's almost impossible.
Eun-joo!
Answer the phone.
Answer me.
-Answer me, you cowardly bastard!
-What's the use of calling him now?
-He's at a seminar.
-Let go!
You go.
I'll just stay quiet in a corner.
Don't tell me to go.
I said I wanted to be alone.
How can I leave when you're like this?
You've been ignoring me for years,
and now you're worried about me?
Why are you crying?
That's a vulgar curiosity.
"What happened in this house?"
"You acted all smart and look at you."
That's what you're thinking.
I'm sorry.
I…
Why are you sorry?
It must be great for you
to say sorry that easily.
For a few years…
You cut me off
and came to see me all of a sudden.
And you simply said sorry meaninglessly!
You didn't mean it.
You don’t take anything seriously.
Eun-joo, I'm sorry. It's my fault.
I'm sorry, Eun-joo, I…
-Get out.
-No.
Leave me alone! Let go!
I'm sorry, Eun-joo!
Let go of me, damn it!
-Eun-joo, what are you doing?
-Let go!
-Eun-joo!
-Eun-joo, don't do this!
-Let go!
Let go of me!
-Don't do this.
Eun-joo.
My head.
Hey, Ji-woo.
Aren't you uncomfortable?
Hey.
Why are you sleeping here like this?
Gosh.
I guess I fell asleep
while listening to your gibberish.
It's cold.
What…
What kind of gibberish did I say?
That my sister is your first love.
Goodness.
My eldest sister
has no father.
Dad isn't her Dad.
She has a different father.
Chan-hyuk, can you give me the water?
Okay.
Ji-woo, I remember nothing
about what happened yesterday.
I can't remember anything from yesterday.
I didn't blackout.
But I can't seem to remember.
That's crazy.
Why did you leave me on the chair?
My neck hurts.
Hey, I told you to sleep on this
so many times,
but you just passed out.
You do remember everything.
You remember what I said
about Eun-joo, right?
The burden was too heavy
to keep to myself.
It feels like I shared it with you.
A private safe and a burden carrier.
Why is everything
being tangled up like this?
Our second daughter told me all about it.
She said I listened to music a lot
whenever I drove the truck.
Ms. Sook?
No, thanks.
Most of them are the music you like.
This is the movie we saw together
for the first time.
A farewell event for "Dr. Zhivago."
It was in theaters for only a week.
But before I saw it with you,
I saw it twice all by myself before that,
to be honest.
When you asked me to go see
a farewell event for Dr. Zhivago.
I didn't know what a farewell event
or Dr. Zhivago was,
so I saw it secretly beforehand.
It was a bit difficult to understand.
But the bigger problem was
that I cried so much.
I cried so much
everyone at the theater stared at me.
I'm sorry for crying so much
when I saw it with you, too.
You smiled just like that
when I cried back then.
Let's go now.
Where are we supposed to meet that guy?
The thing is…
he won't answer his phone.
You said you're supposed to meet him.
Yes, but he's not answering.
Call someone else.
Call who?
A friend who knows you well
or Young-sik's mother.
What did we need to confirm
that led us here again?
People might think
we pulled each other's hair and fought.
Even though I'm reckless,
I won't grab your hair.
Everything is so ridiculous.
You should go home now.
I can't.
Not after what I saw.
There are too many weapons at this house.
Don't get any crazy ideas. That's not it.
I wanted to cut my hair.
All of a sudden? How does that make sense?
It's true.
I was…
so heartbroken and frustrated,
so I wanted to cut my hair.
I thought I would feel better.
Do you think his family knows?
I think they don't.
They might not know.
Families are clueless.
Families may know
and pretend they don't know.
I hope he's not getting weird ideas.
He came to see me
and asked me to look after you.
Like he's never coming back.
If he had weird ideas,
he wouldn't leave his laptop here.
It means he doesn't want to
lie about it anymore.
He must not have the courage
to tell me in person.
So it wasn't my fault.
Tae-hyung
got colder and more depressed.
He didn't seem like a human
living on Earth.
I thought it was my fault,
but it's not my fault.
-About you working again.
-I've always thought of divorce.
That's very good.
I thought I was so smart.
-You are.
-I thought I could figure out everything
about anyone with a short conversation.
But I didn't know my husband.
Come to think of it,
he's been sending me indirect signals,
but I didn't recognize them.
I would've noticed
if he wasn't my husband.
I didn't know because he was family.
Because I was close to him.
Are you blaming yourself?
He's just a cowardly, irresponsible,
and shameless guy,
who's been tricking himself too.
I will solve the problem within my family.
Don't mind it, and just go.
If this happened to me,
what advice do you think
you would've given me?
"Be rational, not emotional."
"Think practically."
"Get compensated double
or triple the years you suffered."
"No one will point fingers at you."
"Get alimony,
shake it off, and come back."
This…
is what you would've told me.
Young-sik has been out of reach
for the past few days.
Did you go check his house?
Well…
His house was empty
like he ran away at night.
I heard you're going to start working.
What?
Well…
I heard there's a lot of work
around this time.
Ma'am, please excuse us.
Why did you bring your wife
when you're here to see Young-sik?
Is there a reason
why she shouldn't come?
I don't understand you.
Deal with your issues between yourselves.
Some people in Jeil Logistics team
lent Young-sik money.
They were all demanding to see you,
but I stopped them.
They didn't lend it to him
because they trust him.
But they trusted you.
Where's Young-sik's house?
Are you really ill or something?
You can't remember the place
where you were born and raised?
Near the Hungry Bridge?
If so,
please call me when Young-sik comes.
-Okay, I will do that.
-Yes, please.
Thank you.
Lots of people are trying
to get my position,
so I decided to start working right away.
I'll take you to the terminal,
so go back to Seoul.
I'll go after loading the truck
and unloading it in Incheon.
About Young-sik…
I'm going to keep calling him.
You were too shy to actually say it,
so you wrote "I love you" on the note.
Dad.
You came too, Eun-hee?
But you must be busy.
I just need to run some tests
because my son-in-law made an appointment.
I heard you started working.
It's not hard at all.
I'm not facing any troubles in working.
You didn't need to come.
I stopped by during my lunch break.
It's almost time.
Go say hi to your mother-in-law.
Let’s go.
All right.
Do you want me to go with you?
She's not here.
She has a class to teach today,
so she's at school.
If I do see her, I'll see her alone.
You're driving your truck
just as you used to.
Do the surroundings seem unfamiliar?
No.
Is there anything uncomfortable?
There aren't any aftereffects either.
It's all normal.
I was born healthy.
Did you manage…
to talk to Tae-hyung?
His phone is off.
And mind your own business.
Please show some respect to your sister.
Don't say it like I'm interested
in this for some ulterior motive.
Then…
don't ask me anything.
What's wrong with you two?
Don't worry.
They said I'm very healthy
and everything's normal.
Where's Mom?
They said his memories
will be back in one or two days.
Why is it taking so long?
We can't say it's taking long just yet.
Each person recovers differently.
Sometimes he remembers things
from 30 years ago so clearly,
but sometimes he says
something totally different.
You confessed your love
for me a lot as well.
You wrote "I love you" on the note.
It's like he's making things up
when he knows everything.
I don't know how much I should believe.
NEUROLOGIST'S OFFICE
Sometimes memories tell lies.
It may be a mixture of the dreams
he had often at the time,
or his long wishes and obsessions.
Dad, why don't we go outside first?
-How are you these days?
-I'm fine.
What did you talk about? Is he not well?
It's not like that.
They said he should have a thorough
checkup if his memories don't come back.
Ask Tae-hyung when he comes back.
We sent the document for this
marketing project to 530,000 offices.
We'll proceed only
with the offices that reply to us.
As you can see,
we marked the market research graph…
Yes?
Ms. Kim.
You have to rewrite the proposal
for the meditation book.
What?
Similar books have been published
by other publishing companies.
Yes, sir.
Come to my office to get the materials.
I'll find them on my own.
You can't find them
unless you speak English and Spanish.
Come and get them.
What the heck?
Is the vice CEO showing off
about speaking English and Spanish?
VICE CEO IM GEON-JOO
I can speak neither English nor Spanish,
so how can I use these as references?
I mostly picked photos
and translated the important parts.
If it's still hard,
want to do it at my house?
I have something simple to explain.
I'll check it first.
About being out of reach
-on the weekend…
-I know why, so you don't need to explain.
I'm sorry.
What would've happened
if I went up without calling you
at the parking lot?
That made me realize the reality.
Secret dating was exciting
only a few times,
but now it's tiring and frustrating,
and I feel cowardly.
Really?
Then am I the only one
who's still heart-fluttering?
Don't play dumb. It doesn't suit you.
I'm saying I don’t want to keep on doing
something tiring and frustrating.
If you're not tired or frustrated by me,
let's talk in the evening.
I have an evening appointment.
I really won't take them.
We have a lot left.
I don't need those.
I still have some left from last time.
It looks like Dad is resting,
so I'll just leave now.
Are you and Eun-hee getting along now?
It was good to see you two together.
Even if she lacks some things
and acts dumb, so be patient with her.
Mom.
Since we were young,
you said that too much
when Eun-hee is around.
That can hurt her.
She doesn't lack anything.
She's not dumb.
You asked me to have dinner.
What's with this serious vibe?
You want something to drink?
We can get food too.
Are you paying? Then I'd like some coffee.
COFFEE BEANS
Which coffee bean do you want?
Anything's fine.
One cup of Yirgacheffe coffee
and one egg toast, please.
I'll cherish it in my heart
What's with the blank look?
You're not dating Seo-young?
When was your last relationship?
Why can't you tell me?
I don't want to answer.
-Are you dating someone?
-Do you think I am?
I can date only when I have something.
I decided to have a business relationship
with Mr. Playboy.
I'll stop calling him Mr. Playboy.
According to the flow
of what you're saying,
are you asking me out?
-Are you a lunatic?
-Thank goodness you're not.
Then what are you trying to say?
Eun-joo was driving her husband's car.
That car is huge,
but she's good at driving it.
What is this now?
She married into a rich family.
She got a fancy car as a gift
when she got married.
But she was scared of driving,
so she said she'll never drive.
Then she gave me the car.
We sold that car to make two used cars,
so one car at my house, and one for me.
Why aren't you saying,
"Eun-joo is awesome?"
Bragging about your love family now?
Loving? As if.
Eun-joo was the breadwinner
of my family once.
But I hated it.
Talking like she was making
so many sacrifices for the family.
I hated it because she made me feel
like I'm indebted to her.
I didn't know I was this petty.
Come on, you're making me worried.
My sister,
Eun-joo,
resented me.
She said I'm acting to be a sister
after ignoring her for years.
I act like I'm so nice and cool
to other people
and try to please others,
but I guess I was nasty to her.
You…
Did something happen between you two?
I regret it so much.
I just
regret it like crazy.
On that day.
At that time.
I had to stop it
no matter what.
You're getting married next month?
Did I hear it correctly?
-Here's aged wine.
-Dad.
-Honey, go get a glass.
-Okay.
-Bring a ladle too.
I wasn't going to open this
until I get a son-in-law.
A couple getting married
after dating for three months
seemed too lukewarm.
My brother-in-law.
What do you like about her?
What an uncreative question.
Is your publishing company okay
with having you?
I don't think they're okay.
I'm honestly curious, that's why.
Are you
struggling to find
anything you like about her?
Oh, no.
She doesn't act girly.
At that time, my heart sank.
She isn't the type to let that go.
I thought they'd break up
even before setting a wedding date.
But…
Girly things?
What are those?
What you're doing.
Calling him your brother-in-law,
asking childish questions,
and talking gibberish
like a baby while drunk.
I was going to say,
"Isn't that a bit dangerous to say?"
But Eun-joo stood up for him.
"Eun-joo loves him."
Drink it.
That's what I thought.
"Yes, if so, I need to shut up."
Okay.
That's just how I am, right?
It means she doesn't act
like she's pretty,
distinguished, or smart.
Eun-joo is honest and straightforward.
"Acting like something."
So that's what girly things meant.
On that day,
I felt anxious.
That's been bothering me this whole time.
But why are you regretting that day…
right at this point?
Are Eun-joo
and her husband having trouble?
Why did you keep
Eun-joo's wedding photos until now?
They're black-and-white.
That means you developed
each and every one of them in a darkroom.
Do you really like my sister?
No, if you think of it like that,
I like you more.
How many black-and-white photos
have I given you until now?
I kept myself in the darkroom to develop
the photos I took of you one by one
and hung them up one by one,
so they could dry well.
-Shut up.
-So I'm saying,
why do you keep talking about Eun-joo?
Well…
You said
Ji-woo seems troubled these days.
I thought about it,
and recently, Ji-woo kept asking me
to go to Eun-joo's house.
Told me to be nice to her.
And he said that felt sorry for her.
Didn't he say anything to you?
If he has something to say,
he'd say that to you directly.
I realized this recently.
It seems like you know more
about Ji-woo than I do.
So if you find out what's troubling him,
tell me.
Okay.
But
you should be nice to Eun-joo too.
DIANA: A WIFE IS SOMEONE WHO HELPS HIDE
OUR IDENTITY YET IS SOMEONE TO DESPISE
VICE CEO IM
I saw you parking your car.
You shouldn't use the address
of the employees like this.
I heard you're taking a day off suddenly.
I was worried that it was because of me.
I'm too old to take a day off
to stay in my room and cry
because of a guy.
I walked around the area while waiting,
and I saw many lovely cafes
and lots of pubs too.
Let's go.
-It seems weird.
-No.
Let's insert this part here.
So it can show.
So this looks better.
Are wedding invitations nowadays in 4D?
It is covered in a super bad fragrance.
Did the sender spray it personally?
Leave it there.
It's from Park Yoon-ji.
Park Yoon-ji?
She told me via social media, texts,
and now an invitation?
Can I open it?
Hey, don't open someone else's mail.
A wedding invitation
is like advertisement flyers.
It's not personal mail.
Whatever. You're distracting me,
so go away.
No way.
It's personal mail.
She did spray bad perfume on it.
Well… An invitation and a personal letter.
How impressive.
It's either one of these.
"Screw you," or "This is my piece
of lingering regret."
I'm sure it's not, "Screw you."
Because Chan-hyuk totally got dumped.
Thanks for the harsh fact.
Whether you got dumped or you dumped her,
if your exes aren't avoiding you
and aren't afraid of you spreading rumors,
that means you're a fine man.
Did you know
how you were looking at me in the office?
"You coward, you're so disgusting."
"Don't talk to me ever again."
That was what I saw.
If that's what you saw,
then I guess that's what I meant.
I'm sure you want me
to be brave and honest,
and not do things
like thinking of breaking up slowly.
I read this in a book.
If a human being lives his or her life
in a such just and honest way
all the time,
the heart can't handle it and explodes.
So you need to make excuses
from time to time.
Use tricks when you can't help it.
And realize that you're cowardly
and repent.
This is the way to make your heart
handle things.
So you want to be
somewhat cowardly
and use some tricks
for the sake of your heart?
I'm saying I don't want to drift apart
from you.
And we broke up.
By the way, why did you take a day off?
It's a family matter.
It's complicated.
You know, about your friend,
from the hamburger place.
Mr. Park Chan-hyuk.
You memorized his name?
You have a good memory.
Do you tell Chan-hyuk,
"It's a family matter."
"It's complicated."
or tell him everything
without being vague?
So you do tell him everything.
Anyway,
if there's anything
I can help with, tell me.
Vice CEO.
I don't think you two
broke up because of me.
The relationship being estranged
without progress.
I know it very well too.
So…
I won’t feel burdened.
But…
I feel comfortable as it is now.
Nowadays, the best thing
for me is to feel comfortable.
Okay.
If you're comfortable as it is now,
we can hang out like this as friends.
I'll make you feel comfortable.
I can't understand anything.
Answer the phone.
Answer the phone, you cowardly bastard!
Leave me alone! Let go!
-What are you doing?
-Let go!
-Don't do this!
Are you going somewhere?
What brings you here at this hour?
Today's my day off.
Then why come here?
I'm busy. I have to go to
the KIPO for the deadline.
I'll take you.
You said you'll never drive
because you're scared
but you drove Tae-hyung's car.
Next time you want to give me something,
just give it to me.
I'm not like you, so I take
free things without hesitation.
All that becomes debt.
Not for me.
I don't ignore the sincerity of the giver.
It's late,
but thank you for the car.
And for that,
I'll be your driver today. Let's go.
No way.
Kim Eun-joo can make people laugh?
She can make them laugh that much?
Okay, goodbye.
Patent Attorney, you look exhausted.
I'll take you to eat right away.
Do you think Tae-hyung arrived?
FAMILY
DAD
FATHER
Hi.
Mom, are you awake?
Isn't it cold?
It's not cold. I slept well.
Drive safely.
Dad, that's an awesome photo!
Where is it at?
ELDEST DAUGHTER: DRIVE SAFELY
YOUNGER DAUGHTER:
THAT'S AN AWESOME PHOTO! WHERE IS THAT?
I wonder what thoughts Dad had
whenever he drove.
I think of all kinds of things
whenever I drive.
He drove long-distance almost every day.
I wonder what kinds of thoughts
came to his mind
when he drove on the same route
365 days a year.
The phone is turned off…
Do you know any doctors
who went to the seminar with him?
He should've arrived by now.
Call your in-laws, at least.
I'm really worried now.
If something happened,
I'm sure he would've called me.
He's just avoiding me.
Because that's the easiest.
Ji-woo.
Yes?
Stop shaking your leg.
Chan-hyuk, no matter
how much I think about it,
it was wrong for Mom and Dad
to keep it a secret.
Shouldn't they
at least tell her the truth?
Then say that to your parents.
I can't. Dad is 22 years old right now.
Then tell your mother.
I can’t.
Then tell Eun-hee.
I can't. I just can't.
Then should I tell Eun-hee?
Yes.
CHAN-PAL
The caller cannot be reached.
Please leave a message…
She's just declined.
She'll call you back.
Okay then, I must get going.
You can do it.
Sang-sik!
Hey!
Are you done, or are you taking off?
Come on, I'm not like you.
I don't work twice a day.
My daughter told me to just YOLO.
YOLO?
It means to live happily in the moment,
instead of working all the time
like you do.
So you need to reduce your workload
and YOLO.
That hurts.
Come on, did you just say it hurts?
When I gave you a massage before,
you said your fatigue was gone
and bought me a meal.
You don't remember that?
Did you know
who Young-sik is?
Young-sik, who worked at the Ulsan plant.
Young-sik?
Well, I did say hi a few times in passing,
but you never talk about that, so…
"That?"
What's "that?"
Well…
Your privacy.
You're so scared.
Yes. Just don’t try to remember it.
No. Just play dumb
even if you do remember.
Why?
When I saw you last time,
your wife was at least seeing you
with pitiful eyes, like a lost puppy.
If that memory comes back,
then it will all go to waste.
You'll graduate from marriage.
Graduate from marriage?
What's graduation from marriage?
Yes.
I'm coming now.
Who is it?
It's temporarily closed,
so the director isn't here.
Would you like me
to refer you to a different clinic today?
-Hi.
I'm so sorry. I'll get you connected
to a different clinic.
You can go there by…
crossing the street.
NOTICE
WE ARE TEMPORARILY CLOSED
YOON TAE-HYUNG FAMILY MEDICINE CLINIC
Hi.
You're the barista, right?
Yes.
Why are you here early in the morning?
I'm a patient here.
Okay. Do you live around here?
That cowardly bastard.
YOON TAE-HYUNG FAMILY MEDICINE CLINIC
What is this feeling?
We're leaving first.
-Bye.
-Goodbye.
Have a safe trip back.
That cowardly bastard.
I can't help but curse.
How dare you curse?
-Look what he's doing. He's killing us--
-You.
Don't even say a word.
That cowardly bastard.
Eun-joo.
Stop it.
Go to work.
Don't miss work because of this.
Yes, Ji-woo.
Hello, Dad. Where are you?
The Incheon plant.
I finished at dawn, so I got some sleep.
I will move for a short distance at lunch
and go home in the evening.
Mom is worried, so…
Tell her not to worry.
I'm moving around within Incheon.
Okay, I will.
Mom, Dad is working at the Incheon plant,
and he'll be home in the evening.
Okay, go to work.
Goodbye.
-I'm leaving.
-What?
This is what you call
going home right on time.
Your sister's been ignoring my calls
since yesterday.
Come on, no way.
Call her while I'm watching.
Goodness.
The caller cannot be reached.
Please leave a message…
Welcome.
I'm here to see someone
who works at this hour.
Isn't he here yet?
You mean Barista Ahn?
He said he has a family matter
going on today.
One hot Americano, please.
Okay.
Thank you.
By the way, how do you know him?
Well, it's hard to say.
He's in Goheung.
He called me in the morning
and said something urgent
happened to his family.
Do you know where Sorokdo is?
INTERNIST OH MI-SOOK
Yes.
I really missed you, my daughter-in-law.
It's so good to see you.
How have you been?
It's been the same.
Have a seat.
Right.
Wait…
Do you want to go eat
something delicious for dinner?
Have you eaten?
I'm back.
Go take a shower first.
Ms. Sook, thank you.
Thank you so much for staying
with someone like me
for such a long time.
I…
remember.
I remember everything now.
Let's
graduate from marriage now.
Do you know where he goes
whenever he disappears?
Don't use someone else as a shield.
She married you because she loved you.
You knew that and you used her.
Where are they?
Do you think Ms. Sook cried a lot too?
I'm sure she wanted to kill you.
There's something
I can finally help you with, right?
I know. I know everything.
-Is there something wrong?
-You want to end it here.
So why did you come here for?
And I haven't even gotten started.
Subtitle translation by: Hae-lim Lee
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/ah6xj
Help other users to choose the best subtitles