Hey! You!
I'm onto you.
I know all about you.
What's all this for?
We was done last week.
Why us again?
Quit moaning, Harry.
You. Out.
Move!
Sorry, Mr. Jackson.
Just saying hello.
Right, that's it.
Get this lot packed up.
Get sorted.
What have you got
with you, then?
Any money?
Phone cards?
Have you got stuff
you can trade, have you?
Bastards.
Right, Brinkley, shut it.
Come on.
Up you get.
Come on. Rise and shine.
The morning's fine.
Let's be having you.
Breakfast is waiting.
Come on, Brian.
Shake a leg.
It's your favorite time of day.
Hey, Dopey. See if you can get
some action out of Sleepy here.
Aw, shut up, Humpty-Dumpty.
Come on, Fisher.
Up you get.
We've got a problem.
Jimmy?
Keep them moving.
Come on.
Up you get.
Fisher.
Fisher, what have you done?
Dear.
One less for breakfast.
Prisoner number 214.
These are Alan Fisher's
documents.
Could you sign him out, please?
Thank you.
You'll be all right, you.
Rastaface.
Hey.
I'm talking to you.
You want to go back
to punishment, Braithwaite?
Any time you want, sooty.
Any time.
He's a pain
in the arse, is Braithwaite.
It's all these tip-offs.
I'm sure it's him.
- Anything for aggravation.
- Hey, Jackson.
You like working
with the blacks, do you?
- Get him in.
- Hey, Jackson.
Can't smell that.
Can you?
- I've got the gym.
- Shut up, Braithwaite!
Snoopy.
In you go, son.
Tell you what. Send the golliwog
down to the gym.
I'll leave the weights.
I'll work out on him.
Shut it!
Come on. Back inside.
Come on.
See this?
Found it under your table.
Hm.
Well, you could've fooled me.
I don't use that, you know.
I never see that thing before
in my life.
What wrong with you, brother?
I'm not your brother.
You want to bet?
All I am saying, Mr. Bunny,
is that somebody should have
given me prior warning.
Ms. Hewitt,
you will receive notification
as soon as I receive it myself.
I've had the testing trial
for weeks.
- Is that the official date?
- Yes.
Well, when it is confirmed,
please let me know.
Thank you.
"Statement of next stage
of Margate testing.
Prison Services today issued
to governors a preliminary list
of which...
For which one or two prisons
will be selected
for privatization.
Prisons listed for possible
privatization...
Aylesbury, Coldingley..."
We're not listed.
Next page, Gary.
It's been decided
that nine adult male prisons
be subjected to detailed
qualitative analysis.
Barfield is first on the list.
Already contracted out
are Wolds,
Blakenhurst, and Doncaster.
Any word on changing
the official category?
I mean, is this an A
or a B nick?
We'll be assessed on performance
to date.
Home Office have requested
details of escapes, assaults,
prisoner activities.
It's no wonder
we're top of the list.
And Fisher topping himself
wasn't good timing.
He had high alcohol content
in his blood.
I know.
And as if that weren't enough.
I just got these.
The date to open up to full
capacity is yet to be confirmed,
but we've been instructed
to stand by.
So it's any day as from now,
Gary.
Crazy.
Right.
Anything come up from
the strip search this morning?
Yeah. We found a condom
in Oswald Snooper's cell.
Norman Jones is back
on the wing.
There's nowhere else to put him.
He should be transferred
to a psychiatric hospital.
I'm pushing for a place
at Broadmoor.
- Anything else?
- That's it.
Well, with their rate
of suicides,
I'd say we might get lucky.
Mavis?
Last night, I went
into the maintenance department
and asked them to check
all the garbage
chucked from the cell windows.
Found five more condoms.
Oop.
- Morning, ma'am.
Morning, ma'am.
We are up for an in-depth
performance analysis.
I do not think that possession
of condoms is my main concern.
Anthony Kelly's on heroin.
I want to see him.
On you go, John.
You know anything about
these privately run prisons?
No.
Only what I've read about them.
Officer Harris.
A lot of teething problems.
Governor.
Gate 2 opening.
A bit slow off the mark,
aren't they?
Have you got to wait
at every gate this long?
Governor, Officer Udding,
Gate 1.
- What's the delay?
- Gate 1 opening.
That's right, Mr. Kelly.
You just keep on smiling.
But I'm warning you...
If you're found with drugs
in your possession...
I know the new regulations.
An extra 21 days.
You want a urine sample?
Why are you doing this
to yourself?
If I can lose Monday
and Tuesday, that's nice.
Thursday and Friday...
even better.
What have I got to lose?
Your life.
Who gives a shit if I lose that?
I do, Mr. Kelly.
Because while you're here,
you're my responsibility.
ENJOY ALL VOD IN HIGH QUALITY @ 4KVOD.TV
GET LIVE TV,MOVIES,SHOWS IN ONE PACKAGE
So, what do you think to our
little matchstick man, then?
- Harmless little bloke.
- Yeah.
You ought to tell that
to the mothers
of the little girls
that he raped and butchered.
Governor.
Gate 3 opening.
Gate 4 opening.
Ma'am?
Come on. Bloody hell.
We're losing bloody time here.
Gate 4 opening.
Mr. Jackson.
Stay with Mr. Malahide.
Ma'am.
You okay?
No.
Nor is that bastard.
He's been asking
for more gym time.
In future, Victor Braithwaite
must be accompanied
by two officers.
I-I was okay.
Maybe you were.
But I wasn't.
Stand by for return.
Governor.
Well, anyway we had
all these big, long sticks,
a-and we stripped them down
of all the bark.
Then we got some string,
a-and we bent safety pins...
You know, fishing rods.
Uh...
It's okay.
Go on.
Oh.
And there was this floating,
uh...
What do you call it?
Um...
Turd?
Turd. No.
Come on. Quieten down.
They're all in a queue system,
right?
So if a gate button is pressed
to be opened on E Corridor
and you have four more waiting
up in C, D, and F Wing...
Look, the thing is,
we are gonna have
500 prisoners here any day now.
We have to cut down
on these delays.
Um, can you punch up
the sound in chapel there?
Now, does anyone else
have anything to contribute?
What about you, Norman?
My first out-of-body experience.
Experimenting with
hallucinogenic drugs, LSD.
Most people don't understand
what LSD actually does.
It raises the level of vibration
and allows you to exist
on a different plane.
There are lots of
different planes of existence,
different realities.
We all vibrate
on a certain level.
If that level is raised,
everything is heightened.
The physical body
is only one plane of reality.
But we can leave that plane.
Then we have no need
for the physical body.
That's what happens after death.
I understand death.
Okay.
Thank you.
Eric.
What's your favorite memory?
The first time I flew solo.
On a plane, were you?
I was in the RAF.
Followed in me dad's footsteps.
Did you look up to your father?
He's short enough
to look up to anybody.
You done service, have you?
You scummy little git.
- Thank you, Walter.
- You bor...
Oh!
I'm all right.
I'm all right,
and my glasses are all right.
Norman...
if you touch another member
of this group,
you are out.
Is that understood?
Yes, Ms. Collins.
I'm sorry.
All right, lads!
Now, these joints are called
tongue-and-groove and dovetail.
You can see here where the
tongue fits into the section.
Now, we'll be fitting
the iron-edged glass
with a glass top.
You see, with this drawer here,
it's simply been
screwed together.
But with the methods
we've been using today,
it shows a genuine craft and a
love for the grain of the wood.
Right, then!
Pack your benches!
Come on!
Pack your benches
and get your overalls off!
Come on, you two.
Stop your nattering
and move along.
Come on.
You do it all day.
Oi!
Get you along.
Come on.
Chop-chop.
Move it, will you?
It's not a mothers' meeting.
Move it!
It finish?
Yours stuck up?
Yeah.
If these things spring a leak,
it'll look like
I've pissed myself.
You?
If mine split, I'm gonna look
like Niagara Falls.
Just back me up
for the airport, right?
Come on! Cut the chat!
What about Victor Braithwaite?
I am having that... done
for me.
You understand?
Now, everything is going down
at the same time.
All we have to do is sort out
the kitchen and we're hot.
All right?
Now touch me.
Ooh!
Fool you.
Come on, puppa.
- All right. All right.
- Through the gates.
Watch this now.
Get your watch off, Snoopy.
- He does it every time.
- Keep moving.
Don't overdo it, all right?
Tongue and groove, puppa.
Tongue and groove.
Wolton coming.
He's gone.
Have to be done
down the main kitchens.
We just wheel them
onto the wings.
We don't know which urn
goes onto which wing.
Do one,
got to do them all to make sure.
All right.
And you sort it out with
the others for tomorrow night,
right?
You hear me?
Take my tray.
I'm gonna see you.
Mr. Jackson, sir?
Mr. Jackson.
I want to get a transfer
off the wing, sir.
I'm getting a lot of aggravation
off of Braithwaite.
You know what I mean?
And that f...
Sorry, sir.
The man is a racist.
You know what I mean, sir?
I can't deal.
I'll put it in my report,
Snoopy.
Come on.
It's time for lockup.
Come on. Chop-chop, lads.
Time for lockup.
Thank you, sir.
Thank you very much.
It's time to lock up!
So that's Mr. Andrews,
Mr. Duncan, the area manager,
and Mr. Gordon Keller.
Good God.
Uh, yes, it is.
Thank you.
I was going to pop in
and get some if that's okay.
Yeah. Fine. Fine.
Not for long.
Mavis, would you arrange
security passes
for everyone listed for the day
after tomorrow, please?
Good heavens.
They could've given us
a bit more warning.
Well, the real bigwigs
are coming.
Do you know anyone
called Keller?
- Me?
- No, not you. Gary.
- Do you know?
- Sorry.
We've got 48 hours, Gary.
Barfield's being checked out
day after tomorrow at 3:00 p.m.
Every single cell
has been allocated.
House full.
Do you, uh,
need me to stay late?
No.
But, uh, I will need you
tomorrow.
Good night, Gary.
Keller, Gordon...
He's Governor 1 rank overseeing
the main dispersal prisons,
and he's a big union man.
He's publicly spoken out
against the Home Secretary's
privatization announcement.
He's after Barfield.
In the end, they did just use me
as a bloody caretaker.
You've done a damn good job
here.
Thank you, Mavis.
Go on. Go on home.
That husband of yours
will be waiting.
Could you shut the door, please?
I believed
that the loss of freedom
was the ultimate punishment.
I believed
that the loss of freedom
was the ultimate punishment.
Barfield Prison
is now fully operational.
All inmates please check
the bulletin board
for patterning changes.
We have to get that
digga to the kitchen by lunch
so it can be in the tea urns
for tea break.
If your name is not
on the board...
This is it.
Our last chance.
Word is we have a full house.
That means we have to go for it
tonight.
- So, you with me?
- What about Braithwaite?
Tonight.
Thank you, Officer Jackson, sir.
I really appreciate it.
You know what I mean?
Thank you.
Oh, yes.
We're sinking, Mr. Christian!
Mutiny!
You're making the raft...
He's gonna sink the raft.
- Brian.
- Mutiny!
Snoopy's been moved to C Wing.
Victor Braithwaite's
been getting at him.
It took two officers to move
all his stuff...
Tapes, stereos, Game Boys,
shaving cream, hair tonic.
- What?
- Yeah.
Not to mention
his Bob Marley memorabilia.
Uh, excuse me.
Your talking
is rather distracting.
But you are welcome to join
the group and participate.
I think I want to stop now.
This... This is stupid now.
This is...
This is bloody, bloody stupid!
Stop now.
It's all right, Walter.
Put the chair down.
- Put the chair down, Walter.
- Put the broom down, Brian.
- It's all right.
- Walter.
Give me the chair.
Go on.
It's all right, Walter.
Does it always hurt you
to remember the fishing trip?
That's okay.
I tried to save him.
I caught his hand.
I-I...
I had hold of him.
But I got scared.
He...
He was trying to pull me in.
And... And I let go.
And I let go!
And he was... he was shouting,
saying he...
He couldn't swim!
Could you swim, Walter?
No!
There... There wasn't...
There wasn't...
There... There wasn't
a swimming baths near us.
Okay, Walter.
I want you to reach out,
and you'll feel Brian's
and Eric's hands.
Hold on to them.
- Yeah.
- They understand.
You were just a little boy,
Walter.
Yeah.
Walter, don't cry, mate.
I hate to see you crying.
Come here, mate.
You hold on to me tight.
- Come on.
- Yeah.
Come on, mate.
You're all right.
You're all right, mate.
I like your perfume.
I'm not wearing any.
If any man on release after
serving a sentence for a crime
returns immediately to a life
of crime, we have failed.
I've always been
against these sessions.
Maybe you're reading
more into it.
No, I'm not.
She's out of her depth.
If anything went out,
she wouldn't be able
to control them.
And I'll put you any money on it
she's never worked in a nick
as tough as this one.
You have run me down
for 18 months.
Well, for your information,
when we have the big walkabout
tomorrow afternoon,
I am not quitting
without a fight.
Hang on a second, Ms. Hewitt.
No.
I wasn't talking about you.
It's Ms. Collins
and the drama group.
H-Honestly.
Oh.
The...
The lads seem to think
she's getting too friendly
with Norman Jones.
Ah.
Ms. Collins.
Have I interrupted something?
I wanted to see you.
I was just on my way
to the office.
More white slips still saying
there's alcohol coming in.
Yeah.
You want to do yourself
a favor, mate?
Take some time off.
No.
Oh, come on, Gary.
Listen, pal.
You may be think...
Oh, come on.
There, now.
Come on, pal.
There you go.
I don't think Norman Jones
works well in a group session.
So what do you suggest?
Intensive one-to-one therapy.
As his case interests me,
I'm prepared...
No.
- Mavis?
- I'm sorry.
Mavis?
All I was suggesting is that
I have closer access to him.
I think you're already
too close.
Has somebody said something?
I think you should tell me
if they have.
If anything's been inferred
regarding my interaction
with a prisoner, then...
Um, is Mr. Marshall still there?
Yep. I'll get him for you.
Fine.
I'll hold.
I don't know what your sexual
preferences are, Ms. Hewitt,
but mine are not men.
Perhaps I should've put that
on my CV.
I believe that somewhere
inside Norman Jones
is a decent human being.
You obviously don't.
Ms. Collins, you have
already complained to me
about being put at risk.
Your physical safety
is my main concern.
- Hello. Yes. It's Helen.
- Yes, Governor.
We've just had notification.
There's a place for prisoner
Norman Jones at Broadmoor.
We're to arrange transportation
at this end.
You pulled it off. Good move.
Was there anything else,
Ms. Collins?
Governor?
If you could just get
the necessary documents for me.
I'll get onto it right away.
Thank you.
♪ By the hand of the Almighty ♪
♪ We forward
in this generation ♪
♪ Triumphantly ♪
♪ Won't you help to sing ♪
Ras Tafari.
♪ These songs of freedom ♪
♪ 'Cause all I ever have ♪
♪ Redemption songs ♪
♪ Redemption... ♪
Come on. Association. Tea's up.
Go on, laddie.
How you doing, eh?
Oh. Sorry.
I see your mate Snoopy
went crying to C Wing, eh?
Chocolate lover.
I don't think I like chocolate.
♪ Don't worry ♪
♪ About a thing ♪
"I'm not your brother."
♪ Singing don't worry ♪
♪ About a thing ♪
♪ 'Cause every little thing ♪
♪ Is gonna be all right ♪
Come on. Association.
♪ Rise up this morning ♪
♪ Smile with the rising sun ♪
- ♪ Three little birds ♪
- Association.
♪ Sit by my doorstep ♪ ♪
♪ But remember ♪
♪ Don't push love over ♪
♪ Singing don't worry ♪
♪ About a thing ♪
♪ 'Cause every little thing ♪
♪ Is gonna be all right ♪
Victor getting it tonight, then,
is he?
Everyone on the wing
is gonna get some.
I'm gonna give them
the homemade hooch.
I don't drink.
Come on.
I haven't got a flask.
Get my share and yours
and we'll split it.
Get back on the tea urn, then.
Go on.
They're still dishing it out.
What have you got there, Brian?
A pen, Mr. Malahide, sir.
He's lying.
He's gonna ink up.
Is that all right, boss,
sir, your majesty?
You're not gonna put us
on report for that, are you?
♪ Melodies pure and true ♪
♪ Saying this is my message
to you... ♪
One by one.
Just be cool.
♪ You ♪
Let the stuff take hold.
Don't stress.
Are you sure this is gonna work?
Look at all those monitors
and stuff, you know?
Where you been, bro?
One black face look the same
as another.
Touch me.
Easy.
Ho! Jimmy!
I'm going off now.
These biscuits are amazing.
Oh, look what you made me do.
Dickhead.
♪ Is gonna be all right ♪
Oi!
Here we go.
- Yeah.
- Shut it!
Come on, Victor.
Shower time.
You two, move!
Come on, Victor.
We haven't got all day.
Chop-chop.
That dozy bastard
nicked the shampoo!
This isn't shampoo.
It's conditioner, right?
You.
I want you tonight.
Empty stall here, mate.
Man down!
We got a man down!
For Christ's sake!
Give me a hand!
It's not me.
Open the bloody gate,
you bastards!
Ready?
Oh, just what we bloody need.
Open up, son.
I'll tell you when.
Okay, boys. In we come.
Nice and steady.
Oh, marvelous.
Oh, bloody marvelous.
Hey!
Is that tomato ketchup,
Mr. Jackson?
Or have you busted
someone's snozzer?
Morgan's the last one.
Don't touch, all right?
No!
- What the bloody hell is...
- Leave it.
Leave it!
♪ Knock-knock-knocking
on heaven's door ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
Officer Udding.
Governor.
Open up.
Officer Udding.
Gate 2 opening.
It's Officer Udding.
Leave the gate open!
Get back to the wing!
It's out of control down there!
Ma'am?
It's not Udding.
Just keep going.
He's wearing track shoes.
Get security down here now.
Do not unlock
the interlocking gates.
That is not Officer Udding.
Open the gates!
Officer Udding with escort!
Open the bloody gates!
Come on!
You had no need
to hit Norman Jones, my lad.
I feel terrible!
- But you did.
- We all friggin' did.
That's what lets you
off the hook.
I didn't.
And if this is going down
on report,
I'll bloody well say I didn't!
You should put on report
that he's a liability.
- Oh, yeah?
- You get on with maintenance.
And you get on
with your bloody job!
I want someone here
and on D Wing.
Yes, ma'am.
- Is that yours?
- Aw, shit.
Mr. Morgan, if I find out
that this key belongs
to any one of the officers...
Are there any injuries
other than Victor Braithwaite?
No.
Well, I don't know about you,
but I needed a little snifter.
Where's Gary Marshall?
It was his duty night.
He was here, Ms. Hewitt,
but, uh...
he went to sort something out.
Go on. Go home.
Go on.
It's all under control.
Go home.
Okay.
I'll just finish up.
Cleaning's on the way down.
Move it, gentlemen.
We have till tomorrow afternoon
to get this place
completely bloody pristine.
Nice try, Snoopy.
Now you know how Samson felt.
Any complaints, Norman?
Norman.
You don't want to make
a complaint, do you?
All right, big man.
I was in the pub, and then...
Worse than some we've had
on the wing.
Yeah.
All right, are you, pal?
No.
But it's almost over.
Hey.
- Hey!
- Sorry.
It's me that should be crying,
not you, you big soft bugger.
I'm sorry, mate.
Come here.
Wing's clean and back in order.
Both escapees are in the block,
and I've arranged transportation
for Norman Jones.
We've got hangovers
and bellyaches.
Stuff was mainly puerile.
It didn't come from here,
did it?
No, it did not.
I'm afraid Colly is in
a catatonic state.
And how in God's name
did it get on every wing?
You'd better sort this, Gary,
and before 3:00.
Yeah.
Have you Norman Jones'
medical records ready?
Oh, Gary, Mavis has a list
of all officers on duty today.
I want all staff
not on the wings
in the officers' section
by 10 to 3:00.
Right.
Has the ambulance come
for Victor Braithwaite yet?
Coming for him any minute.
Don't worry.
We'll be neat and tidy
for the visit.
Not a stiff in sight.
You do realize how badly beaten
he was... or is?
The entire wing was drunk
and disorderly, Dr. Thomas.
Would you like to see the
bruises on some of the officers?
We're ready
for prisoner Norman Jones.
The van's waiting outside,
ma'am.
Yep.
Thank you, ma'am.
Hello, Norman.
What's looking up, then, eh?
You've always talked about
Broadmoor, haven't you?
Wait a minute.
No.
Let him go.
Do you want to have a word
in private?
This will only take a minute.
What I have to say
may be unethical, but...
Look, I have the Home Office
and HQ coming.
Yes, I know.
But do you know Gary Marshall's
wife has terminal cancer?
She might even be dead.
Now, if he hasn't chosen to tell
you, that's his business.
But at the same time,
you should have been
the first person he told.
Do you understand
what I'm saying?
If your officers
can't talk to you,
then you're the wrong person
for this job.
- You are so obsessed with...
- Why didn't you tell me?
Just let me finish.
You may have a vocation,
but don't for one second think
that you're the only one here
that has.
You have officers that care,
Helen.
And you also have some
that get away with beating up
a mentally sick man
like Norman Jones.
As a doctor, I am responsible
for the inmates' well-being.
Excuse me.
- Helen, listen.
- No. You listen to me.
Don't you dare talk down to me.
For 18 months,
I have had no private life.
Just Barfield.
Suddenly you feel
more than medically responsible
for the inmates.
I was responsible for you,
for every prisoner...
and for every member of staff.
I needed you to confide in me.
And I apologize.
But... I doubt
if you would've listened.
You never even tried.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
And having a schoolgirl crush
on you at times
wasn't a great help.
I can't eat a thing either.
I have got a stonking headache.
I know.
I did me tat last night.
- What?
- Me tat.
- I inked up.
- Oh.
Do you want to see?
Yeah.
I have it for this.
Nairb?
Well, what does Nairb mean?
Nerd?
No, you dickhead.
It says Brian.
Can't you read?
No, it doesn't.
Oh, you pillock.
You done it in the mirror,
didn't you?
Hey!
Hey, he done his own ink.
Got his name back to front...
Nairb.
I apologize for the way
that I spoke to you.
Could the governor
come over to the control room?
Thank you.
Yep. She's here.
I'll be there in a second.
I'll make sure
that you get this.
On the way, Mr. Marshall.
Officer Keith here.
Gate number 3 with a prisoner.
Gate 3 open.
Gary.
I'm very sorry about your wife.
If you need any time off
or anything at all,
please... just ask.
There's nothing.
Officers Frisk
and Aspen on Gate number 6.
You've make me feel
very inadequate.
Gate 6 open.
I should have got to know you
better.
I apologize.
Thanks.
Um, what's this?
Belonged to Norman Jones.
Look at the flyleaf.
"For Maureen Collins,
whose laugh was like music."
Norman wrote all those notes.
- It's the same handwriting.
- Mm-hmm.
He said it was coming in
from the outside.
He comes in on a regular basis
for the workshop.
You'd need more
than one of my hacksaws
to get through these bars, eh?
Body-search Mr. Walbrook,
please.
So, uh, this is, uh, this is all
part of the new security.
Is that it?
Oh. Listen.
Uh, we should...
Should be finishing that, uh,
dressing table today.
Norman was wrong.
They've not found anything.
Not so much as a condom.
Take his trousers down.
Oh, shit.
Like... Okay.
It's, um...
See, I...
I was just short of the cash.
Uh...
- Oh.
- What you got here?
My God.
Hm.
He's a walking
bloody distillery.
I didn't mean any harm.
No harm at all.
I was just broke, you know?
I feel stupid.
- I want him charged.
- They're here.
I'm not ready.
Yes, you are.
- Gordon Keller.
- Nice to meet you, sir.
Is she not available?
Uh, yes.
Here she comes now, sir.
You all set?
- Everyone standing by?
- Mm-hmm.
I'll get them in the
lecture hall as quick as I can.
Uh, Mr. Keller, Ms. Hewitt.
Ah.
Helen, isn't it?
Yes.
Mr. Keller, nice to meet you.
I hear you've been recruiting
new officers.
What about the ones that have
been on detached duty?
Some will return, but a number
have decided against it.
If I am to remain here,
then I'll obviously have
a large ratio of locals...
Unless, of course,
you're taking over.
Not really made up my mind.
And if it's to be privatized,
then I wouldn't be interested.
Can't get the decent officers.
Big problems already
in Doncaster.
That's why I hand-picked
officers with experience
to back up the trainees.
Not to back you up?
I don't think
any young recruit's
been thrown into the lion's den
straightaway.
Not like in the old days.
You wouldn't even remember
those days, would you?
No. I'm not ready for my pension
yet, Mr. Keller.
Gentlemen, shall we go inside?
Barfield Prison has cost the
British taxpayer £69 million.
It has facilities
that any school,
college, or university
would get down on their knees
and beg for.
She's going for a knockout
in the first round.
I'd say it was shit or bust.
I believed that the loss
of freedom...
was the ultimate punishment,
that it was every inmate's right
once inside prison
to be given the opportunities
we provided.
I now know
that is not his right.
He must be taught to earn
every single privilege
that in our modern prisons today
are taken for granted.
If any prisoner on release after
serving a custodial sentence
returns immediately to a life
of crime, we have failed.
If that man has gained
criminal experience
from inside the prison
that held him, we have failed.
If any man raping a woman
rapes again on his release,
we have failed.
If a man kills and murders again
on his release, we have failed.
If any man on home leave,
any man on parole
commits a crime or does not
return to his prison,
we have failed.
Yet at the same time, we must
never lose sight of the fact
that no matter how hard it is
to find,
there is inside every criminal
a decent,
sometimes helpless,
frightened human being.
We must not fail him either.
Just as we must not fail
his victim.
The punishment must fit
the crime.
Only by implementing a tougher,
harsher regime,
can we hope to decriminalize
the criminal.
Rehabilitation is still
our priority.
It must become our prisoners'.
Bring all your personal
belongings with you,
'cause you're not getting
back on the bus!
Come along!
Get in line and move along!
Two orderly lines! Come on!
Move it! Move it!
Will you get a bloody move on?!
Pick your feet up,
you disgusting little man!
When I say move, I mean move!
What do you think you are,
the bloody circus?!
Governor?
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/agzyc
Help other users to choose the best subtitles