Use the free code JOINNOW at
www.playships.eu
Get into that car.
Not you.
Go to that car.
Where did you find this notation?
We found it in...
- It was in Master Kedar's music notebook.
- Yes.
We got it from there.
Kedar's music notebook?
But he's not supposed to know it.
This is an ancient system of notation.
Don't expect any help from me
if you're lying.
No...
Why would we lie to you?
I found it in Master Kedar's notebook...
But I don't know
how he knew about it.
Hmm.
It'll be a big help
if you could explain this notation.
The maestros of the Anandagarh School
have received national awards
for the last three years.
Couldn't they crack it?
Do you sing classical music
in these torn pants?
All the melody will escape
from these holes!
No, sir.
Well, I sing with my heart and soul.
No holes there, sir.
Oh!
You're good with words.
But are you equally good with the ragas?
You can put it to test.
That I will.
Sing with me.
CURSE OF THE RUDRABINA
PART 2
(vocalising)
Rapture rapts Krishna and Sudama
A love-starved woman looks on
But comes not near
(vocalising)
Rapture rapts Krishna and Sudama
The forest is swaying
With the wind
There's an eternal charm
Of the flowers around
Radha sits in agony
In a land faraway
Her Shyam is away in Mathura
Separated from her
(vocalising)
Rapture rapts Krishna and Sudama
A love-starved woman looks on
But comes not near
(vocalising)
Rapture rapts Krishna and Sudama
Bravo! Bravo!
Sir.
Can you give me
the notebook please?
What are you looking at?
Sir...
my mother had taught me something.
The seven notes of music...
symbolise the seven gods
and goddesses.
Does that mean that they define
the seven moods as well?
Correct.
It's mentioned in ancient texts
on music.
That's why they demonstrated it
through dance postures.
"Sa" symbolises limitless, infinity.
"Re" symbolises sadness and sorrow.
"Ga" symbolises peace and calm.
"Ma" symbolises the sexual and erotic.
"Pa" symbolises happiness and joy.
"Dha" symbolises irritation and disgust.
"Ni" symbolises the serene and tranquil.
That means...
each note symbolises
a specific mood pattern.
Exactly!
These really are like social media emojis.
Come on!
Sir...
I have one last question.
What?
Did I pass the test?
May you achieve success.
SASIKANTA BHARADWAJ
MUSIC INSTITUTE
We finally did it, huh?
Hey, stop worrying.
We have some idea
about Raga Sanjivani now.
No.
This looks like...
Raga Jog.
What?
(humming)
Mom taught you this.
Hmm.
The "bandish" of Raga Jog,
taught by Ma'am.
And she said that...
it was composed by Amanat Khan.
(indistinct chatter)
Your grandpa learned it from him
and taught the others.
After all this effort we get to know
that it's Raga Jog?
Where is Raga Sanjivani?
In his riddle, Amanat Khan wrote...
"In the heart of Rudrapur
lies a Shiva lake.
When the discs are aligned
And the notes are played
at twice the pace of time
Raga Sanjivani you shall find."
Each disc has an instrument painted on it
along with the notations.
So if each instrument is played
according to its notation
we'll get to know the "bandish"
of Raga Sanjivani?
I don't think so.
(indistinct chatter)
Finding the Raga Sanjivani
won't help crack the entire mystery.
The game isn't over yet.
But Naad ran away with the discs.
What if they decode the notation?
They'll find Raga Sanjivani!
It won't be that easy.
(indistinct chatter)
Rudrabhairav.
Rudrabhairav!
Our best musicians have played
this notation at the Shiva Lake.
But nothing's worked.
Now?
It won't help
if some random person plays the notation.
What do you mean?
Amanat Khan popularised
a particular style of music.
It later became the specialty
of the Anandagarh School of Music.
Master learned it and taught it to us.
You mean it has to be played
in the Anandagarh style?
Hmm.
- Seems that way.
- Hmm.
With a combination
of "shruti", "meer" and "gamak"
we can play a special style of music.
No other musicians can play it.
Then go on.
You're the best person for it.
Sitar, sarod, flute...
Santoor, shehnai, sarangi...
Rudrabina.
I play the sitar.
What about the others?
We need them too.
Mom learned the santoor
from Salamat Uncle.
And Noor Aunty taught Saaz
the shehnai.
But do they know the specific style
of the Anandagarh School of Music?
Look...
Both Salamat Uncle and Noor Aunty
are disciples of Mustafa Hussain.
And Mustafa Hussain and Kedar Mishra
are disciples of Amanat Khan.
Hence...
They all belong
to Anandagarh School of Music.
- Hmm.
- Right.
Hey, it's ringing.
Hello!
Can you hear me, Mom?
Listen carefully.
Alap has cracked the notation.
Yes.
You, Dad, Lolit Uncle, Ramnidhi Uncle,
Bahadur Uncle and Saaz
come to the Rudrapur Shiva Temple
immediately.
Yes, all of you need to come.
Call up Lolit Uncle
and Saaz immediately.
Alap and I will go directly
from here.
What?
What are you saying?
O... Okay.
- What happened?
- Hey...
Naad has kidnapped Saaz.
What!
What do we do now?
Come along.
Fast!
Hurry up, Shruti.
Get in the car.
- Alap!
- Shruti, come!
Shut up and get into the car.
Hey!
Get in.
Fast!
Into the car.
Get in!
Naad.
You can't harm them.
Can't you hear me?
Get in.
Do it!
Naad!
Come with me.
Call the ambulance.
Fast!
They... won't get here in time.
Before I die...
let me tell you something.
I...
I was a fan of Raunak Bai.
Naad was after her.
I waned to save her and her son.
I had tried my best.
I wanted to do one good deed in life.
From whom did you want
to save me and Mom?
Mobile...
On my mobile phone...
there are some DNA test reports.
I've not shown one particular report
to anyone.
Not even to Rudrabhairav.
Instead...
I'd shown him a fake report.
If you see it...
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today