"The secret bandish if you sing
from the heart
You shall pacify Shiva's "tandav".
The beats of 'dadra'
Shall nullify the poison.
Then Raga Sanjivani you shall find".
Lord Shiva took the poison in his throat
during the "Churning of the Oceans".
His throat turned blue from the poison
and he was named "Neelkantha".
Hey, know-it-all, stop your lectures.
Where's Raga Sanjivani?
Have patience, Maestro Sasikanta.
Shruti, give me your phone.
I think the "bandish" which appeared
on the ceiling...
were composed by Amanat Khan.
And if it is sung flawlessly
in the six-beat rhythm...
the bluish glow on the throat of the idol
will wipe off and a magic will happen.
And you have to sing it
in a particular raga.
Which raga?
"This secret bandish if you sing
From your heart
You shall pacify Shiva's 'tandava' ".
According to myth, Shiva started
the 'tandav' dance when "sati" died.
Goddess Saraswati created a particular raga
in order to pacify him.
Raga Malkauns!
Malkauns.
I've understood everything.
It only needs to be sung.
So... Naad alone is enough for it.
Naad, sing the bandish
in Raga Malkauns.
After we get the Raga Sanjivani
we'll kill them...
and bury them on the banks
of River Domor.
Start singing.
api.OpenSubtitles.org is deprecated, please
implement REST API from OpenSubtitles.com
Hail, Mahadeva, the almighty
Dancing with with all his rage
Who will stop this furious rhythm?
Hail, Mahadeva, the almighty
Dancing with all his rage
Who will stop this furious rhythm?
Hail, Mahadeva, the almighty
You're clad in ash
Who burns in the roaring fire?
Along with it burns a thousand flames
smeared in agony
Falling at your feet
Will your eyes shower mercy on them
Instead of staying inflamed?
Hail, Mahadeva, the almighty.
"If you sing the secret bandish
with your heart and soul
Pacifying the angry 'tandava'.
Where's the soul in it?
Naad...
You think you can pacify Mahadeva's anger
with your lifeless singing?
Leave it.
Listen to how Alap sings instead.
Where's Raga Sanjivani?
Come on, Mr. Sashikanta...
What's wrong with you?
Play "dadra".
(vocalising)
Hail, Mahadeva, the almighty.
Dancing with with all his rage
Who will stop this furious rhythm?
Hail, Mahadeva, the almighty.
The trees burn
The earth trembles with your anger
I see fire showering down
When I look at you
You hold the River Ganga in your locks
And your forehead
ornamented with the moon
Hail, Mahadeva, the almighty.
(singing)
"The beats of 'dadra'
will wipe away the poison.
Then Raga Sanjivani
you shall find".
- "Raga Sanjivani"...
- Give it me.
I'm the master of Rudrapur.
It's mine.
Wait.
Alap's music led him to the raga.
You don't have any right over it.
Hey.
What are you staring at?
Finish him!
What happened?
- Did anyone come?
- What?
Nobody will come.
Everybody has realised...
that you've misled us for ages.
You did not let us live or love.
You confined us here
because you didn't want us to go out.
You've denied the natural phenomenon
and called it the curse of the rudrabina
You've manipulated them
for all these years.
What nonsense!
Why would I do it?
I'm telling the reason.
Because you...
never wanted us to surpass your music.
That's the reason!
- It's a lie.
- Yes.
You're lying.
The curse of the rudrabina is true.
We can't escape the curse if we disobey it.
If that's the case, Mr. Shashikanta...
then why does the mystery
of Raga Sanjivani...
have its solution in the music
of the Domors?
You...
who were the Rudrabhairavs, failed.
Why so?
The truth is that they have used god
to create a caste division.
But it has no value to God.
And you...
You know everything.
Don't you have another reason
to kill us, Mr. Shashikanta?
You're using the curse of the rudrabina
as an excuse for it.
- Isn't it?
- It's a lie.
He's lying.
Fine.
Your esteemed Rudrapur School of Music...
lost time and again to your former slave
Kedar Mishra's Anandagarh School of Music.
How can you accept this humiliation?
So you used the curse of the rudrabina...
to kill the musicians of Anandagarh School
instigating the Domors.
Isn't it?
What are you waiting for?
- Burry them alive!
- Yes!
Skin them alive.
Hail.
What's this?
Nobody will come.
They've understood your trick, Master.
You consider this laddie to be your god?
Ask him...
if he can bring water in the River Domor
by singing Raga Sanjivani.
Then we'll see if he's really a god.
Can he do it?
Then ask him to prove himself.
Always remember one thing...
Music is not magic.
It's a practice.
It can awaken the different parts
of your body.
The great masters used music...
to connect with the divine...
Strange incidents took place
during such times.
Not everyone can do it.
But...
Dad could do it.
You can also do it, Mom.
I know it.
Can I...
do it, Mom?
Yes, you can.
You have it in you.
If you practice honestly...
you can do it.
(vocalising)
(singing)
(all singing)
Watch any video online with Open-SUBTITLES
Free Browser extension: osdb.link/ext