api.OpenSubtitles.org is deprecated, please
implement REST API from OpenSubtitles.com
FAMILY MOTTO
A HARMONIOUS FAMILY WITH LOVE
When sad hunches come true,
there are signs that come beforehand.
NOTICE
That cowardly bastard.
The small anxieties
that I've been trying hard to ignore
keep knocking on my door,
telling me not to ignore them.
Why are you staring at me like that?
Do you want to go out for dinner?
Or do you have something to say?
I have a favor to ask you.
Hello?
You've been ignoring my calls
for two days in a row.
Are you busy?
Sorry.
What are you doing tomorrow?
Today.
Where are you right now?
How about a drink today?
Now?
Oh, you're busy?
Then we can meet tomorrow.
Chan-hyuk.
Why are you lowering your voice like that?
Spend the day with me tomorrow.
Dr. Yoon…
didn't come back
from the seminar in New Zealand.
What do you mean?
He was supposed to be back yesterday,
but he still hasn't called me.
And of course,
the clinic couldn't open today.
Mother.
He often used to disappear and come back.
I thought he got rid of that habit
when he got married
but looks like it came back.
I should find a doctor
who can work briefly at the clinic.
Do you and Father know why…
Dr. Yoon disappears and comes back?
He's emotionally sensitive
and likes to be alone.
And he has a bit of
chronic depression too.
You and Father
knew about his orientation--
I told him to take antidepressants,
but he doesn't listen.
Doctors are indifferent
to their own diseases.
He has no reason to take medication.
Because it's not a disease.
I looked it up.
Famous people graduate from marriage too.
They hold a graduation ceremony,
go on a graduation trip,
and have a graduation party too.
I'm not going to drink it.
I don't know what you looked up,
but I'm too tacky to have parties
and go on a trip
for graduating from marriage.
Are you sure your memories are back?
Sang-sik.
Do you know how manly you were?
Yes, those eyes.
It doesn't suit you at all.
Do you think I want to do this?
You can't even drink.
Wine isn't even strong.
Let's talk when the house
is taken care of.
Ms. Sook, I'm not finished.
What I'm saying is…
No need to sell this house.
Put it under your name.
We decided to divide it.
That would make me feel comfortable.
Let's stop talking about it today.
I'm here to drink
some strong coffee you brew.
Is something going on?
I'm a bit far away,
in Sorokdo.
If you wanted to hide perfectly,
you shouldn't have come here.
You can't even look in the mirror, right?
You only know how to blabber
in the chat room.
You are always scared
if something feels a little off.
I'm not scared of it. I hate it.
I don't know
why you came all the way here.
I don't want to deal with you here.
Get out.
If you wanted to avoid this,
you should've minded your own business.
Someone else stole from me.
Why are you paying it back?
Weren't you hanging around me
because of money?
I was curious about
what kind of person you were.
But,
I stuck around because I pitied Eun-joo,
who is being tricked.
How do you know if she's being tricked
or pretending to be tricked?
Regardless of which one it is,
I know what it feels like to be unloved.
If you're never going to say the truth,
don't use someone else as a shield.
You're quite sentimental.
That's why you guys get hurt, break up,
get ripped off, waste your youth,
and live the lowest life possible.
Want me to buy you one more?
No, thanks.
Didn't have dinner yet, right?
I saw you leave work right away,
and I got worried.
Is the family matter still complicated?
Yes.
Very complicated.
There's something
I can finally help you with, right?
How are you so sharp-witted?
I've been living my life
needing to be sharp-witted.
No reaction? That was a sad confession.
Tell me.
I'll listen.
It's a bit cunning
since this favor uses authority.
According to you, Vice CEO,
humans sometimes need to be a coward
so their hearts won't explode.
It's philosophical,
but you interpreted it in a simple way.
I…
I can't go to work tomorrow, either.
But I was off at work too much these days.
It's a mess.
It was a mess.
Okay.
I may report it as you working away
for me tomorrow--
-Thank you.
-I said I "may."
Can you tell me
why you can't come to work?
I have to find someone.
Still ambiguous without any information.
All right.
Thank you so much.
Remember when I told you I broke up?
I told you that
this is comfortable for me.
You're so stern.
But…
I will try and wait
until the season changes once.
"Once?"
Come on, you weren't serious about me.
Yes. Until the season changes once.
This is non-negotiable.
Wait.
It's nice to be older.
No one nags at me even when I play games.
Did I nag at you a lot?
No, when I think about it,
my sisters nagged a lot more.
I can hear them even now.
My son, you look great
when you show your forehead.
No.
If I show my forehead,
it makes me look old.
Do you hate looking old, even at your age?
Yes. I totally hate it.
You're a baby.
I am a baby.
That's why I can't move out.
Look at you.
You came to tell me to move out, right?
You have to go to work,
so go to bed early.
Mom, I really can't go off on my own.
My sisters were older but stayed.
Why are you doing this to me?
I'm going to use Operation Youngest.
The youngest spends
the least amount of time with his parents.
I get it. Go to bed.
Always picking on me.
Dad's memories came back.
I liked it when he was romantic.
Sorokdo?
In Goheung, Jeollanam-do?
-That's almost the southern tip.
-It's an island, right?
Is it a place where we must
stay for the night
when the ferries are cut off?
I don't know what you're imagining,
but places like that hardly exist anymore.
They built bridges.
Look at the time, will you?
Sleep in the car. You can't even drive.
Exactly. Why are you taking me so far
when I even have no driver's license?
It's the matter about my sister,
whom you like.
Eun-joo?
What happened to her?
What are you doing?
Are you trying to go hiking?
Good morning.
Not hiking is allowed for a while
even on your day off.
It's not my day off.
I'm going from Incheon
to Ulsan after lunch.
Then why are you looking for
hiking gear at this early hour?
So you can go hiking again?
No, I'm not.
What is he looking for?
What are you looking for
at this early hour?
I will find it for you.
Don't make the house messy and tell me.
I can't find the letter you wrote to me.
I put it somewhere, and I can't find it.
Are you sure your memories are back?
Good morning.
Dad, I heard your memories came back.
Dad? Don’t call me Dad! You're not a kid!
Oh, my Dad…
I mean, your memories did come back.
Why aren't you saying anything?
What should I even say?
How's your sister doing?
She's getting through it.
I can never fully understand
how she feels.
So, you're going to trust your hunch
and go to Sorokdo now?
I wish I would fail too.
But when I ran into him
at the clinic yesterday,
his facial expression seemed like
he saw this coming.
What are you going to do
if those two are there together?
What else can I do?
I'm going to tell them to wrap things up
so Eun-joo would never know.
It's okay with the new patients,
but make sure to check the charts
of re-visiting patients.
-Yes, ma'am.
YOON TAE-HYUNG FAMILY MEDICINE CLINIC
You look tired.
I couldn't sleep.
Looks like you couldn't either.
You don't need to worry about the clinic.
The local residents know me
more than Dr. Yoon.
Act naturally in front of the nurses.
Okay.
I'm not worried about the clinic.
They said Dr. Yoon
left the seminar a day early.
Do you know where he goes
whenever he disappears?
I'm sure he's at Sorokdo.
Sorokdo.
Whenever I went to find him,
he was always alone.
He never made mistakes.
GOHEUNG SPACESHIP OBSERVATORY
Are you here on a trip?
Why are you going in circles
when the peak is right there?
Then why are you also going in circles,
without rushing me?
I'm waiting thinking that
there must be a reason you're doing this.
People see my brother-in-law
as a son of a successful
family of doctors,
a doctor himself,
and a man who married a fine woman.
But…
would he really be here?
If he's here,
it means he's going to
give up all of that.
And it also means
none of that made him happy
and he doesn't want to
deceive himself anymore.
If the world had no discrimination,
isn't barbaric, and is nice,
would my brother-in-law
have come out of the closet?
We don't know about that.
There are lots of people who hide it
and reveal it right before death.
It's mom.
I have a bad feeling about this.
Ms. Lee Jin-sook.
Can you talk on the phone right now?
I'm talking on the phone now.
Your brother-in-law
is back in Korea, right?
Right…
Is he?
He said he'll be back
in two to three days.
You know it so well.
Then I'm sure he is.
Call your sister and tell her
to come visit us with him.
Why did you call me about that?
It's because your
brother-in-law might be tired
after coming back from overseas.
Who was the middle man
when I cut ties with Eun-joo?
Why can't you call them directly?
Who is it that you find difficult?
All right.
I'll call them.
No, don't.
You're right, Mom.
Tae-hyung might be tired
and Eun-joo is grumpy and difficult.
It's right for me to call.
I, the messenger, will call them.
You're going through a lot,
getting stuck in the middle.
What am I supposed to do?
Why is the CEO at Goheung
Space Launch Observatory?
How did he go to a place
380 km away from here?
When he can’t even drive?
I guess we're filming a space launch soon.
Yes, awesome.
And he went all the way alone
for field research?
I know, right? He wouldn't do that, huh?
He needs to learn how to drive.
It's so troublesome.
Are you sure you don't know
why he went there?
I don’t.
-What?
-Ji-woo.
Is it difficult to talk on the phone
when you're working?
Really difficult.
I'll finish in 30 seconds. How's Dad?
Dad's memories came back.
Really?
Then why is Mom looking for Tae-hyung?
Why? Why is that so?
Eun-hee, you need to come home
this evening.
There's still
the graduation from marriage.
I don't think Mom's going to be
stern about it like before.
Come talk to them.
Not today.
Are you busy?
I'm a bit far away.
I'll talk to Eun-joo, so don’t call, okay?
Okay.
My dad's days in his twenties have ended.
I asked him to tell me first
when that happens, but…
Hey, stop calling!
Do you want to take care of
everything yourself?
I'm sure there's a reason
why he's not saying anything.
Right.
If his memories came back,
I'm sure he's in pain.
He should've stayed young a bit longer.
My dad also had
a shining and bright twenties.
But weren't our days
in our twenties totally awful?
We were broke so we collected cybercash
and had terrible sense of style.
Isn't that just you?
I'm still shining brightly.
That's the funniest thing
I've heard recently.
If you were so bright,
why would Yoon-ji marry some other jerk--
Did she send you an invitation, too?
Yoon-ji sent you her wedding invitation?
I really hate girls like that.
She sent me via message
and said she ran out of invitations.
And she sent you an invitation?
That backstabbing witch who broke up
with you all of a sudden.
That was a long time ago.
You drank like crazy at the time.
You almost died
in the valley from drinking.
That brat is shaking up my friend again.
Stop overacting and let's eat. I'm hungry.
Right.
Forget about wedding invitations,
memories and stuff.
Human beings need to eat to survive.
My friend, don't be heartbroken.
I will pay for the meal.
You should pay for the meal
after dragging me all the way here,
don't you think?
Should I?
Yes, you should.
-Dismissed.
-Well done.
Ms. Kim said she may have to
work away until the evening,
so she'll go home right after.
Yes, writer Choi Dong-ha lives far away.
Vice CEO?
I have something to say.
I…
I know Ha-ra.
People in our neighborhood
tend to take similar routes.
Kindergarten, elementary,
middle school, high school,
language studies, and studying abroad.
Ms. Seo, you live in that neighborhood?
Yes, the families roughly
know each other too.
-I guess so.
-But,
Ha-ra suddenly contacted me
and said we should meet up.
Actually, we weren't even that close.
But she acted like we were best friends.
If you know her, you might know
my relationship with her.
But you must be good at keeping secrets.
Can I tell you my secrets openly later?
See you later.
Was there a letter in
the wedding invitation?
What did the letter sound like?
"Chan-hyuk…
I'm…
getting married…"
Was it like this?
Or… was it like,
"Chan-hyuk, I'm getting married."
What's the difference?
Well…
If she wrote an ellipsis
with sentimentality,
she wants to keep the memory
and remain a woman.
If she wrote it short and tough,
it means she has no regrets,
and just wants your cash gift.
I think it's neither of those.
So she did write it.
-Wow, what did she write?
-I don't want to tell you.
If you don't tell me,
I'll go to the wedding and ask her myself.
You know I'll do it.
Don't hold back.
Hey.
She wrote I don't have to come
and told me to be happy.
She sent you an invitation,
but told you to not come?
Do you think this makes
sense in terms of context?
I went to Jong-min's wedding to see you.
But you didn't come.
Lots of rumors spread.
I was glad I broke up with you.
Congratulate me on my wedding.
P.S. I absolutely reject a wedding
invitation with your name
and Eun-hee's name on it.
What are you going to do now?
SOROKDO CATHEDRAL
He's at Sorokdo Cathedral now.
He's showing his location
way too accurately,
which is even more strange.
Why spend all your energy
on your father, your mother,
and even Eun-joo?
Even if they're your family,
there's nothing you can do now.
Just…
I feel bad, that's all.
I almost cut ties with them
for a long time and lived
my life recklessly.
If I stayed by their sides at the time,
would Dad, Mom, and Eun-joo
have become different from
how they are now?
Hey, what makes you think
your family will change because of you?
Right?
And you lived recklessly? No, you didn't.
Do you actually know if I lived
recklessly or not?
I lived recklessly.
Let's say you did.
Let's go.
Was it that weird that
I didn't go to Jong-min's wedding?
All of a sudden?
That was like 50,000 years ago.
Yes, it's all in the past.
I'm wondering if there was a reason
for you not to go to his wedding.
Jong-min didn't even
send me an invitation.
So I thought, "This means
he doesn't want me to come."
He's small-minded and timid.
By the way, how did you know
that I didn't go to the wedding?
They live streamed it
as if it were a royal wedding.
The chatroom blew up about you not coming.
"How loyal." "Awesome." It's going crazy.
Super loyal.
But the end of
that live stream was so bitter.
Everyone was suspecting
that we were dating.
Thinking that we had an affair
before Jong-pal did.
Some say he's the victim.
Wow, I've never imagined
such a rumor would spread.
What are you doing?
Sorry. I neglected the rumor.
No, I think I watered the rumor
so it can grow fast.
How did you water it?
"Chan-hyuk is actually quite okay."
"Chan-hyuk is thoughtful."
"I knew Chan-hyuk
before I knew that bastard Jong-pal."
Are you nuts?
I couldn't help it. I lost my temper.
What's the point of saying it's not true
and that I cut ties with you?
Everyone believed it anyway.
Yes, well done.
That's never going to happen
between us, anyway.
So you gave them a nice big blow.
Right.
I came all the way here,
wishing that it wouldn't be true,
but bad hunches always come true.
Just play your part.
Okay.
How did you find out where I was?
Someone scattered breadcrumbs,
so I could follow them and find you.
It wasn't scattered on purpose.
I'm going to go back anyway,
so you guys go ahead and talk.
Don't you have
the courage to talk with us?
You're good at running away.
You're cowardly, irresponsible,
inconsiderate, and rude.
What a connection you have.
I know this looks weird.
But he disgusts me too,
so don't get any weird ideas.
I didn't know you would come.
I didn't think Eun-joo would tell you.
Eun-joo isn't the type to tell me
things like this.
Even if you hate your wife,
you spent a long time with her.
I saw
your laptop first.
Why would I hate Eun-joo?
That's what happens when I chat.
I get smug, boast,
get angry, curse, brag, and giggle.
Why would you do that?
I'm just not good enough, that's all.
Do you know what Eun-joo did?
She totally broke down.
I've never seen her like that.
I was so scared something
might happen to her.
Why did it have to be Eun-joo?
At that time…
we wanted to cut ties with our families.
Both of us were sick and tired
of our families.
"I'm sick and tired of my family."
This is what I hated the most
among all the things my sister said.
What's the name of the bottom side?
A square.
I'm sick and tired of them.
Whether she meant it or not,
that sentence was harsh and hurtful.
Young-sik, that brat.
He's been working at the plant
his entire life.
He has no other skills,
so he can't go anywhere else.
There's no need to go looking for him.
Just have your walkie-talkie on
when you have time.
The sky is beautiful.
What's wrong? I can't get used to this.
It's frustrating.
You're frustrated by me?
Look at your face.
Well, you were very manly,
but this also suited you back in time.
You probably made many women cry.
I don't make women cry.
I didn't, right?
Well…
You were a CMDT.
CMDT?
Cold Man Driving a Truck.
I'm sure even if you didn't
make them cry directly,
I'm sure many women
in the hiking club cried.
Do you think Ms. Sook cried a lot too?
No, I'm sure she didn't cry at all.
You think so?
I'm sure she wanted to kill you.
Even if you look so soft,
you're super picky.
Me?
How was I picky?
We gave our paycheck to our wives
because we're scared of them,
but you kept it for yourself.
And you've been giving your wife
a petty amount of
pocket money your entire life.
I still find it amazing
how she raised three kids
with such a small amount of money.
Because you gave her
a petty amount of pocket money,
she hid the fruit.
Fruit?
Those wretched Korean melons?
I'm not sure if it were Korean melons,
but you said you went home
and saw your wife hiding fruit.
Because you didn't give her much,
I'm sure she wanted to give
expensive fruits to the kids.
They say you get angry
at others for your own mistakes.
You said you turned the house
upside down because of the fruit.
And injured your hand too.
Stop it.
You should never judge
a book by its cover.
I take caution with everything
I do in front of my wife.
But you…
I said stop it!
Damn it!
On-su.
Mom.
I did everything I could.
I was always there to greet him
when he came home.
When we were newlyweds,
he used to run around
looking for me like a kid
throwing a tantrum when I wasn't home.
Mom.
I said it was
when we were newlyweds, right?
Goodness, am I becoming like him?
Why do I keep recalling
the old days recently?
I was so excited about
the thought of leaving everything
and living alone, I couldn't even sleep.
What should I do?
Jin-sook.
You're early today.
I had some time.
Are you sure you don't need money?
Everyone needs money.
So why do you only do
community service every day?
You need to start working.
You've learned everything.
I'm going to start working soon.
Right, today's the day
Mom takes a bath, right?
Stop calling them "Mom."
The families hate it
when they come to visit.
"Why do you call my Mom 'Mom'?"
"Even if I can't clean her feces,
she's my Mom!"
I see no scar…
That must've been a big injury.
Why…
Why did she meet a loser like me, and…
HANSUNG NEUROPSYCHIATRY
YOUR REGULAR CHECK-UP
IS ON JULY 8, 1 P.M.
Neuropsychiatry?
WRITE HOW YOU FEEL
I WANT TO KILL MYSELF
The medical note…
There's a coffee farm nearby.
Want to stop by?
I don't have the car key with me.
I can't drive.
Oh.
I didn't know.
Has anyone asked if you can drive?
Not really.
If they just think I can drive
on their own, and I tell them I can't,
they look at me like, "You useless loser."
Same for me.
"Are you a homosexual?"
No one asks me this.
Can you drive?
We need to talk later alone.
Yes, let's talk later.
Where are they?
Your sister's car is over there.
Whether she was sick and tired of us
or had more serious reasons,
she married you because she loved you.
You knew that and you used her.
I always felt indebted to Eun-joo.
If it were money, I could've paid it back.
But I didn't know
how to do so with feelings.
But…
as I kept feeling indebted,
I started hating it more.
You hated it? You made her
read all that harsh chats
because you hated it?
Too afraid to face her?
If I told her myself…
I thought she might try to understand me,
and not know what trash I am.
Eun-joo…
Did you drive all the way
here by yourself?
I really can't understand you.
You should've told me if you found him.
Why come?
To take Tae-hyung back to Seoul.
Why did you bring Chan-hyuk?
Do you not use your brain?
Just in case something happens.
What would happen?
What did you think would happen?
Do you need someone to whine to
whenever something happens?
Can't do anything alone, can you?
-Are you on a trip with your friend?
-A trip?
What if he knows?
Does it hurt your dignity?
Can't you just say
that you're having a hard time?
How can I tell you
when you're not trustworthy?
You can't even take care of yourself.
I don't want to see you here anymore. Go.
She has already ended it.
There's no reason to get angry
at someone who's over,
so she's shouting at me,
like how I did to her.
Eun-hee, I think you should go.
I heard you said you wouldn't come.
Why did you?
Let's talk in the room.
-Just talk here.
-Are you hiding something else?
Let's go.
Now?
She said she doesn't want to
see me here anymore.
Did you
tell my sister about this place?
Yes.
How did you find this place?
I heard it from Eun-joo.
You call her Eun-joo?
Yes.
She doesn't care about titles.
Yes, she does.
She totally cares about them.
How did you get here?
He got here on a bus, and he can drive.
I'll give you a ride.
Let's take time to talk
while driving back.
You're really going to leave?
I can leave if I have to.
Why did you bring me here?
Well, this was my first time
coming here, and if I failed…
I wanted to see the ocean and chat…
Enough with excuses. Be honest.
I wanted you to be the first
to know about my sister's situation.
Why?
If she gets worse,
someone has to be by her side,
but I can't be with her all the time,
so I thought it would be good
to share it with you.
Ji-woo shouldn't know about it.
No one knows my family
and my sister as much as you.
It's a relief that he can drive.
You two go ahead first.
Not going to work tomorrow?
I might get fired.
I'm sharing the burden.
I'll stay here, so you go on.
Don't you have work?
I'm a CEO. You're an employee.
Mr. Playboy can defend you
since he's your boss,
but others would say something.
I'll stay here and go back with Eun-joo.
You go first.
Let's go together.
I'm sure they'll take care of it.
I'm worried about Eun-joo, that's why.
It's okay. Just go.
The clinic is open today.
Your mother is there.
I'm closing the clinic.
You're not going to
do it yourself, either.
I'm sure your mother will.
Don't be sarcastic.
My mother thinks I'm a patient.
I hated it. But she dragged me this far.
You shouldn't have done it then.
Don't blame others for it.
I'm not blaming her.
I am going to try changing it now.
You?
You can't change it.
You only know
how to solve things with money.
Did you think Hyo-seok
would take the money?
Is that the price for stealing his lover?
I never got in between them.
Were you…
trying to live here
with my brother-in-law?
I'm not the one.
I did date someone who wants to live here.
He…
He hated coming out
of the closet and fighting
like I did.
And then he got to know someone
who has similar tendencies as him.
He said that he felt like
he met his soulmate.
My brother-in-law?
Yes.
He totally fell for Dr. Yoon,
so he stole my money
and ran away to New Zealand.
Then did you work at that cafe
to have revenge on my brother-in-law?
Rather than revenge…
I just wanted to scare him.
But I became friends
with Eun-joo, and, well…
I failed.
What is considered
getting in between them?
Is chatting not enough?
Your mother said this.
"My son
never makes mistakes."
Are you saying you didn't make a mistake?
You…
-Stop being sarcastic.
-Does this sound like sarcasm to you?
Are you offended?
It feels like everyone
is laughing and talking
behind your back, right?
If you're that scared,
why did you chat online?
You couldn't control yourself?
Let go!
Yes.
I knew you would read all the chats.
I'm horrible, aren't I?
Is there anything left to discuss?
You want to end it here.
You always end things clearly.
So why did you come here for?
Don't act like you know everything
like you're wise and not greedy.
Your face and the way
you talk make me sick.
Let go!
I said, let go!
Let go…
You…
What did you think
when I was trying so hard to get pregnant?
You know how painful it is
because you're a doctor.
What did you think?
I asked, what did you think!
I detested you.
It was detesting to see
you try so hard to have a family
when you were so sick of them.
You hate your family,
but you're okay with ours?
Did you need
an elevation of social status?
You're a snob.
Detestable and sickening?
That's good.
I have no feelings for you.
And I haven't even gotten started.
EUN-HEE
I'm still in Goheung.
If you still want to go with us,
we'll go pick you up.
Bye.
Today is such a long day.
Here.
Did I sleep like a monster?
I wasn't looking.
So you weren't interested.
I'll drive from here.
It's okay.
What's your relationship with Chan-hyuk?
We're university friends.
Does Chan-hyuk like Eun-joo?
Do you always show
your thoughts on your face?
He liked her before.
You know, what all guys do.
Having a crush on a friend's sister.
I'm a guy, but I didn't do that.
Is see.
DId you crush on a friend's brother?
You slept well in the car.
You're not feeling good
right now, are you?
I feel bad for Eun-joo…
but I feel relieved.
To be honest…
I never liked my brother-in-law.
I always thought
he was cold, authoritative,
and selfish.
But…
when I think that he's been
deceiving himself all his life,
I can understand.
Hating someone is also a waste of energy
and since I'm not anymore…
So I feel much relieved.
I sent Eun-hee back.
You have to give me a ride. I can't drive.
Is that so?
Then why didn't you go with her?
I told her I'll stay.
I didn't think…
Eun-hee would find this place.
She said it was a pure hunch.
I didn't think she had a hunch.
Eun-hee actually has quite good hunches.
Although dense.
I'm sure she brought you here
because she's dense.
Perhaps she brought me here
because she has a good hunch.
But us two going back to Seoul
together may seem weird.
That's Eun-hee's true talent.
The talent for making things weird.
The talent for making things weird
and escaping on her own.
Do you know who Eun-hee
went back to Seoul with?
The barista.
I'm actually laughing, surprisingly.
So this is how it feels to be comforted.
I'm going back with Eun-joo.
She's fine, so don't worry.
Just you and her?
What about my brother-in-law?
Thanks.
You've done so much.
I have something for you.
I'll wait at the cafe around your house.
ACTUALLY, I…
I'm almost there, so don't run away.
OKAY
It's because I have nothing.
How could I do something
even a barbarian wouldn't do?
Throwing fists at home…
Bleeding…
How can I be forgiven for such a sin?
YOUNGER DAUGHTER
-Dad.
-Hello.
My Eun-hee.
Yes, this is your Eun-hee.
Don't you have something to say to me?
What?
Did you forget the promise
you made with me?
What was it?
I heard your memories came back.
Right.
Dad, what happened to your voice?
Did you catch a cold?
No.
Tell me your driving schedule.
I'll go see you.
-Okay.
-Yes.
Ah, I'm tired.
I'm getting old.
We're family, but we don't know.
We don't know if we don't tell.
It's so good to be with you, Ms. Sook.
Ms. Jin-sook, I love you.
I really, truly love you.
Everything shone brightly since you came.
Thank you, Ms. Sook.
I'm so thankful for being with
a lacking jerk like me.
After all this time…
how can he try to stop me?
Ms. Lee Jin-sook, this is your messenger.
Yes, did you talk to your sister
on the phone?
Your expectation was right.
Did something happen?
Tae-hyung was on the plane
for so long going back and forth.
He's not feeling well.
I'll tell them to call tomorrow
or the day after.
Is Tae-hyung badly ill?
It's not that bad. Don’t worry.
They'll call you soon.
Okay.
Mom.
What happened to your voice?
Did you catch a cold?
Dad sounded like he caught a cold, too.
A cold?
He was fine in the morning.
Mom, I have to go. Bye.
If you always answer the phone
with a calm voice,
although you're sometimes heartbroken,
then they will never know
until you tell them.
You look tired.
I'm fine.
Come to work tomorrow with this.
It's the project plan
for writer Choi Dong-ha.
This is enough to say you worked away.
I can read "Thank you,
thank you so much!" on your face.
Do you want pizza and beer?
If you do a bottoms-up
with the first glass of beer
when you're tired,
your arms and legs feel relaxed,
your brain gets dizzy,
and you get confident.
That's some amazing flirting skills.
Look here. This is not a flirting skill.
This is just a drink with a coworker.
Or with a boss.
Are you drunk after drinking one bottle?
I…
I couldn't sleep last night,
and I got up in the morning
and drove to Goheung.
Plus, I hardly ate anything the whole day.
I had some lunch.
Wow, you drove all the way there?
Did you go with that friend?
Well, it's a bit…
complicated.
I realize that what I just said
can cause misunderstandings.
I didn’t ask you for your help
to go and have fun with my friend.
I don't get any wrong ideas.
I just want to know
what this complicated matter is,
and I want to comfort you.
Because you're the one I love.
Although I didn't want it,
thank you for today.
It seems like you're okay now,
but when you're home alone…
The emotions will come back.
You should stay at
Eun-hee's house for a while.
I don't know where she lives.
I realized that just now.
I can take care of myself. Go home now.
Do you have something to say?
Haven't you thought that all of my actions
are the actions of a man in love?
I think…
I tried not to think so.
Why?
Because we slept together
the first day we met?
And…
you don’t know me that well.
I know you very well, Eun-hee.
When the meeting is boring,
you write the Chinese character
"Taoist Immortal."
Because you like the meaning
of a person leaning on a mountain.
You don't like taking sides either,
so you don't take anyone's side
in a meeting.
You're the second daughter, stuck
in between the eldest and the youngest.
The name of your email
is the main character
from Pride and Prejudice,
Liz.
The email address?
You always translated my username
and referred to me as that.
Thistle…
You mean…
Yes.
I'm Thistle.
I had a great time too and thank you.
Thistle,
Be happy.
I'm the one you've been emailing
for more than a year.
No way.
Thistle is a cute
and capable female student
in her early twenties who lives overseas!
Yes.
Because she's cute and capable,
she got a better-paying job
in less than a week.
So I got to use her email.
I tried to tell you…
but it was so much fun,
so I decided to pretend to be her.
Then I became interested in you.
I came here because I wanted to see you
and fell in love.
It was an honest conversation
between women.
I thought you wouldn't have opened up
if I revealed my identity.
I think I said inappropriate things, too.
I'm telling you.
We mostly talked about books, authors,
and work.
We related to each other so well.
You still should've
revealed your identity.
You see…
At first, I missed the timing.
Then, I just didn't want to reveal it.
Why not?
Because I liked your writings.
They made me laugh
and they comforted me.
And it was heartwarming.
Then you shouldn't have told me.
It's embarrassing because it feels like
my shameful secret has been revealed.
I'll get going.
All right.
Right when I thought I fell in love,
I heard another sound
that knocked on my heart.
And I badly wished that sound
wasn't you.
I want to know why
you're ignoring my calls and texts.
They say you should give up
if your heart doesn't flutter.
I don't want to be a man
who's jealous of your friend.
You were…
particularly cold to me and Dad.
October 13. That was the day
I proposed to your mother.
-They said I tried to kill myself.
-Try reading the diary!
I've been holding back
because of the kids.
I was…
done a long time ago.
Subtitle translation by: Hae-lim Lee
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/ah6xg
Help other users to choose the best subtitles