THE NAMES OF PEOPLE, INCIDENTS, AND
BACKGROUNDS OF THIS DRAMA ARE FICTIONAL
GU JINGI, CANDIDATE
FOR MINISTER OF HEALTH AND WELFARE
My knight…
finally got the king.
Don't you know what I did for you?
How dare you do this to me?
Sir!
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Candidate, what is this video?
Who are you stabbing?
NO TAEHYUN, CHOI SEUNGJUN, JEON DONGSEOK
CHAIRMAN OF THE HEARING
It's Lee Dohyung, the assistant director
of Banseok University Medical Center.
The man who got stabbed in the neck
by Gu Jingi
was a witness to this hearing.
He is Lee Dohyung, the assistant director
of Banseok University Medical Center.
HEARING FOR GU JINGI,
MINISTER OF HEALTH AND WELFARE CANDIDATE
ONE DAY BEFORE
GU JINGI'S CONFIRMATION HEARING
NEW-HOPE LAW OFFICE
NEW-HOPE MEDICINE CLINIC
Was it Gu Jingi's order?
Did he make you find out
about Kwon Yoonseok's condition?
You don't have to answer me.
I can ask Gu Jingi myself.
Don't do that. Fine.
You're right.
Chairman Gu told me
to find out if Kwon Yoonseok
can recover in any way.
Go tell Gu Jingi
that Kwon Yoonseok is brain dead.
Don't tell him that you were caught.
Tell him he's brain dead?
That way, he'll trust you even more.
And meet him tomorrow
before he attends his hearing
to ask about that night five years ago.
And? Then what?
Just ask him. That's all.
Let me know where you two will meet.
As you already know, Gu Jingi is a man
who always betrays before he's betrayed.
Dr. Lee Dohyung.
Don't get framed
for other people's crimes.
Just be punished for what you did.
It's a piece of advice
as an attorney and your junior.
NEW-HOPE LAW OFFICE
NEW-HOPE MEDICINE CLINIC
What he said isn't wrong.
Assistant Director Lee Dohyung.
Hello.
Have you thought about my offer?
I didn't get a minute of sleep last night.
I mean, ten billion won?
My offer still stands.
Aren't you with Dr. Han Yihan?
Why did you tell me to ignore you?
At times, I have to fool my own team
to carry out a perfect plan.
It's simple.
We will ruin Gu Jingi to get our freedom,
and you will get ten billion won as well.
EPISODE 14
I will get my freedom
and ten billion won too.
CHAIRMAN GU JINGI
My gosh, he surprised me.
It's such odd timing.
Yes, sir. This is Lee Dohyung.
Are you ready to appear as a witness?
Yes, I'm ready.
But--
Before you go there,
I need you to help me one more time.
Tell Ms. Cho and Ms. Jung to come
to the assistant director's office now.
Tell them you need to discuss something
as my witness.
Yes, and then what?
Contact the head of the Security Team
and come to my spot
in the underground parking lot.
I'll be waiting there.
Why? Is that too hard to do?
No.
I'll do as you say.
I'll see you soon.
Well. Things worked out by themselves.
I'm to meet Chairman Gu Jingi.
I'll see him
at his parking spot in Banseokwon.
I'll bring it up then.
Don't overdo it.
You might get yourself in trouble.
It feels uncanny
to have you worried about me.
I'll call you later.
THREE HOURS BEFORE
GU JINGI'S CONFIRMATION HEARING
Hi.
I kept them in the room as you instructed,
Chairman Gu. I mean, Minister Gu.
-Good work.
-It was my pleasure.
You promised to make me the director
of Banseok University Medical Center.
Mr. Cheon, get in the car.
Yes, sir.
Yes.
Yes. You will be the director of Banseok
University Medical Center from now on.
I will protect
your medical license as well.
Thank you. Thank you so much, Minister Gu.
Thank you.
Sir.
What is it?
I mean,
I thought I should know this
before I attend the hearing as a witness.
What is it?
Well…
That incident in Banseokwon
five years ago.
-Sure.
-Who was the VIP
that received
the heart transplant surgery?
I mean,
I couldn't dare to ask until now,
but I've always had a question.
I mean, who could it have been
for you to take such a drastic measure
to find the person a heart?
You suddenly wanted to know that?
Come to think about it,
we've known each other for a long time.
We've worked together
ever since you became an anesthesiologist.
About 20 years now.
I see, 20 years.
What a long time.
I left you by my side
for such a long time,
but you can never tell
what's on someone's mind.
Sorry?
No, wait.
It looks like
you got an irresistible offer.
-I didn't think--
-This is nothing.
-Let go!
-Chairman Gu, it's not--
Please spare me.
Don't you know what I did for you?
-How dare you do this to me?
-Sir!
Why…
Keep it safe
until the confirmation hearing is over.
What should I do?
We're at the hospital,
so he'll survive once we move him up.
Do you know what I regret the most?
Five years ago in the detention center,
letting Han Yihan go alive.
If I took care of him as you suggested,
I wouldn't have been annoyed like this.
Deal with him.
-And keep this place off-limits.
-Yes, sir.
I am…
sick and tired of this.
Why does everyone…
annoy me like this?
CANDIDATE FOR OFFICE
CHAIRMAN OF THE HEARING
WITNESS, CANDIDATE FOR OFFICE
Ms. Cho.
What's going on?
Did he really kill him?
Why won't he pick up?
Move aside.
No, I'm told to keep you two safe--
Do you still not get it?
Chairman Gu Jingi is finished.
If you don't want to end with him,
give me my phone back and move aside.
If I short sold that at the maximum price
just as you said,
I would have made over 50%
in today's trade.
It's not just 50%.
It'll plummet for the next few days.
We would have made
over 80% of the shorted price.
Thanks a lot.
Thanks to your useless meddling,
we lost our chance to make
tens of millions of dollars.
I'll make an official request
to have you disciplined over this matter.
All of our conversations
are already recorded.
You!
Why did you kill him?
CANDIDATE FOR OFFICE
All he did was ask you about Seokju.
Gu Jingi.
You're under arrest
for the murder of Lee Dohyung.
You may choose to remain silent,
and you have the right to an attorney.
Although it'll be useless.
We must take the suspect away.
Please move aside.
-Move aside!
-Please move.
CANDIDATE FOR OFFICE
-He's coming!
-Say something!
-Did Mr. Lee Dohyung die?
-Do you admit?
-Any words on the video?
-Please say something!
-A word, please.
-What happened in the video?
-Did Mr. Lee die?
-Say something!
Can you explain how you got a heart
for a VIP patient
at Banseokwon five years ago?
-Say something!
-Do you admit?
-Do you admit to your charges?
-Did he die?
Say something!
We're both on our own from now on.
-Did he die?
-Anything to say?
-Do you admit to your charge?
-What happened?
How…
How can he kill a man?
It makes no sense.
Ms. Pyo, you know, don't you?
Why did my husband hurt
Assistant Director Lee Dohyung?
And what's this
about taking out a patient's heart?
I don't know.
You can't just say you don't know
in this situation.
I need to know what's going on
before I can take a measure!
I heard about his plan
to stop other witnesses
from attending his confirmation hearing
by using Assistant Director Lee Dohyung.
But he didn't tell me anything else.
I think he gave a separate order
to Mr. Cheon Hyungu.
Mr. Cheon?
Where is he? Bring him in right now.
Well, I haven't been able to reach him
after Chairman Gu was arrested.
The police are looking for him too.
Hyunseong, is there anything you know?
He didn't say anything to me either.
What on earth have you all done
while I was gone?
I'm sorry, Boss. Forgive me.
"Boss?"
Do you still call me that
after deciding not to follow my order?
I was going to, but at that moment,
Susie Yoon called.
Yes, I'm sure you were torn.
That's why I gave you another chance.
Yet you chose to betray me to the end.
You're right. Everything was my mistake.
I'll own up to everything,
so please give me just one more chance.
You know that I've done
everything you told me until this day.
I'll give you one last chance.
Bring me 50 billion won.
-What?
-You lost me a chance
to make at least tens of billions.
Do you think your apology was
worth that much?
I forgive you for your betrayal.
But you must make up
for my loss with money.
Bring me 50 billion in three days.
If you can't,
don't ever let me see you again.
GU JINGI ARRESTED FOR SUSPICION OF MURDER
Thanks.
Congratulations.
You're the presidential candidate.
You won't have to worry
about the primaries.
Do end your relationship with Chairman Gu.
All of us at Honours Hand will provide you
with even more active support.
Okay.
Let's talk again later.
I thought I should know this
before I attend the hearing as a witness.
That incident in Banseokwon
five years ago.
Who was the VIP that received
the heart transplant surgery?
What a long time.
Come to think about it--
I think I found it. Come here.
Look at Gu Jingi's eyes.
He's looking at Lee Do-hyung's chest
instead of his face.
His chest?
Is he looking at his fountain pen?
I think so.
He continues to look at the fountain pen,
-then he takes it.
-Yes.
After that,
when Lee Dohyung tries to take it back,
he stabs him in the neck.
The fountain pen.
Wait, maybe it's that thing.
A fountain pen camera.
Some reporters use it in secret
while covering a case,
although they shouldn't.
He found the fountain pen camera
and stabbed him abruptly.
He must've been stressed out
right before his hearing.
But still, how can he kill a man?
He was once a respected doctor,
but he has hit the rock bottom.
Chairman Gu, from now on,
you must share everything with me
without hiding anything.
That's the only way I can keep you safe.
Did Nam Hyukchul kill Park Kitae
because of your order?
You're right. It was my order.
What's the reason?
I told him to bear false witness
in Geum Seokju's case
five years ago,
and he tried to share that in court.
That's the only reason why you killed him?
By any chance, does this have
anything to do with taking out
someone's heart five years ago,
just as Assistant Director Lee said?
That's nonsense.
I wouldn't do something that ridiculous.
I'll spend the rest of my life in prison
because of my charges of murder
and murder instigation.
So you don't need to know anything else.
You didn't prepare a weapon beforehand.
You can find a way
to reduce your sentence
to involuntary manslaughter.
If Mr. Cheon cooperates
with the murder instigation,
you'll find a way out of that too.
No.
Your job isn't to protect me.
It's to save Banseok.
-But--
-Ms. Pyo.
I'll take all flaws of Banseok
with me and go down.
So you must not focus on protecting me.
Focus on protecting my family and Banseok.
Protect them from Jayden and Honours Hand.
Give me an answer.
This is my final request.
Yes, sir.
How could he hide the body
in the morgue of his hospital?
He probably hid him here to buy time
before he actually
takes care of him later.
Did you find the fountain pen
he used as a weapon?
No, I think Cheon Hyungu took it.
The police are looking for him,
so he'll be caught soon.
Where's his guardian? Nobody is here yet?
I don't think anyone will come.
He's separated from his wife,
and their children are still teenagers,
so she can't show him to them.
Let's move him to the NFS for an autopsy.
What?
There was a hidden camera
on the fountain pen he used as a weapon?
Yes.
I think Lee Dohyung got caught
trying to record their conversation.
That's why Gu Jingi…
Why did Lee Dohyung do that?
Why did he take such a big risk
to film their conversation?
What if someone put him up for it?
Someone might have told him
to film their conversation
for something irresistible
so that Lee Dohyung will risk himself.
I'll get going.
I only have less than a day
to hold Yoon Miseon under custody.
Right. If she got a heart transplant,
she'll need a daily dose
of immunodepressants and antibiotics.
So find out the drugs she took
between yesterday and today.
Okay, I'll check.
What if someone put him up for it?
Someone might have told him
to film their conversation
for something irresistible
so that Lee Dohyung will risk himself.
YOON MISEON
It's my resignation letter.
Please process it anytime.
Sure.
A prosecutor confessed to using
coercive measures before the public.
Of course, you should resign.
I am sorry.
You punk, why did you do that?
I have known you for years.
I know you aren't like that.
You don't receive bribes
or special treatments.
What was the reason?
I don't know.
I must have been insane back then.
For goodness' sake. Give me a break.
I will wrap things up
as a proper prosecutor.
It took a long time.
We should have met like this
five years ago.
Unbelievable.
How dare you arrest me,
a presidential primary candidate
over a fabricated ledger?
Listen carefully.
Once I get out of here,
I will cut off your pretty neck first.
Go right ahead
if you manage to get out of here.
I warned you to lay low for a while.
I couldn't do that.
It wasn't a meager amount.
Hundreds of billions were at stake.
What's the use of money?
If you're jailed for attempted murder,
you'll be there until you're 60.
That's why
you should help me, prosecutor.
Did you forget about
the Oath of the Peach Garden?
The Oath of the Peach Garden? It's over.
I just turned in my resignation letter.
Resignation letter? Why so suddenly?
You don't need to know.
And the person you trust as much as me,
Assemblywoman Yoon Miseon,
got arrested and detained yesterday
for abetting murder.
If you don't trust me,
call your lawyer and check.
But I am not sure if she will pick up.
What's the password?
Daejun Construction, 500 million won.
Samhong Distribution, 400 million.
Jinhang Transportation, 600 million, and…
Banseok Foundation, 700 million.
300 million, 200 million,
1.3 billion, 21 billion.
The total is 4.6 billion won.
My aide had no fear, didn't he?
He collected slush funds for himself
by using my name.
Sure. Let's leave it at that.
You got this drug administered
twice a week without fail.
Don't you remember what it is?
What's that?
I have no idea.
I knew you would react that way,
so I prepared evidence.
I am a bit tired these days.
I shouldn't appear exhausted on TV.
Don't worry, Assemblywoman Yoon.
I will make your skin glow.
I am in your care.
Let me get some sleep
during the treatment.
Yes, ma'am.
Who recorded this?
A third party's recording
can't be used as evidence.
It wasn't a third party.
It was a Banseokwon employee
who was there with her.
If needed, she will testify in court too.
Give me a break.
Do you think something so small like this
will bring me down?
Every politician
who has worked as long as I did
has such faults, okay?
You are right.
That's the thing with wrongdoings.
They begin as tiny specks of dirt.
I am the one who collects them.
But when I began collecting them,
I realized that your wrongdoings are
as big as a mountain.
Assemblywoman Yoon?
What are you doing here?
Do you believe me now?
No one has your back.
Assemblywoman Yoon,
tell me that he is wrong.
You are a presidential primary candidate,
so you can handle this.
Stop talking nonsense.
I don't even know who you are.
Are you kidding me?
I came this far
because I trusted you!
Investigate him thoroughly and find out
what Kwon Yoonseok did with my name.
I can't believe this woman.
You have a knack
for making people go insane.
"Woman?"
How dare a thug like you call me that?
That's right. I am a thug,
so I will be comfortable in prison.
But would you be okay with that,
Assemblywoman Yoon?
The harsh wind in prison
won't be good for your skin.
Your skin will shrivel up
like dried radish.
Calm down.
I will find out
which one of you is telling the truth
so that no one feels victimized.
You helped me in the end.
Why were you like that before the hearing?
Did you want me to hate you?
Five years ago, I truly believed
that Han Yihan killed Seokju.
But when you began to investigate
Park Kitae and Nam Hyukchul
and Gu Jingi asked
for my cooperation again,
I realized it then.
I had helped Gu Jingi entrap Han Yihan.
If you knew, why--
I just…
couldn't admit it.
What I had done for you five years ago
made you struggle more.
Han Yihan told me
that you trusted me until the end
and that the hearing was my last chance
to live up to your trust.
That was why I testified.
Thanks to Han Yihan, I got to wrap up
as a proper prosecutor.
An arrest warrant for Assemblywoman Yoon
has been issued.
I checked if she is taking any medication,
YOON MISEON
but there was nothing
other than supplements.
Immunodepressants weren't
among the items she requested either.
So it wasn't Yoon Miseon.
If you received an organ transplant,
failing to take immunodepressants
can put you in danger.
YOON MISEON
Then we are back to the beginning.
I will investigate Gu Jingi now.
No matter what it takes,
I will find out
who took Seokju's heart.
I will also meet
the person who has the highest chance
of requesting Lee Dohyung to take
a video of Gu Jingi.
LEE DOHYUNG
DECEASED
Five years ago.
Who was the VIP that received
the heart transplant surgery?
PRESIDENTIAL PRIMARY CANDIDATES OF A PARTY
I mean, I couldn't dare to ask until now,
but I've always had a question.
BANSEOK R AND D CENTER
CURRENT STATE OF STOCK
The price has been falling for two days.
What a surprise.
I didn't know
the price would fall so much.
This is the beginning.
When you release an article
about withdrawing the application
for the new drug for Alzheimer's disease,
Banseok R and D Center's stocks
will be trash.
Where are you, Doctor Lawyer?
We should celebrate our victory.
I don't think
it's a cause for celebration.
Lee Dohyung's body
has been found in Banseok's morgue.
Is that so?
That's unfortunate.
Let's meet tonight at New-Hope Law Office.
I have something to discuss.
Okay. See you later.
Han Yihan?
Yes.
He has something to discuss.
Something to discuss?
You still need him?
What do you mean?
Gu Jingi got destroyed
and Bankseok R and D Center
fell into our hands.
That means you no longer need him, right?
CLOSED TEMPORARILY
DUE TO A PERSONAL MATTER
What a surprise.
I didn't know such a place was hidden
inside the law office.
What is it that you want
to discuss with me?
Is that the video from the hearing?
What about it?
The fountain pen
Gu Jingi used to stab Lee Dohyung
had a hidden camera.
Did you give him
that fountain pen?
I can't believe she is investigating
the man who killed her brother.
Even watching it
from the sidelines is hard.
Seriously.
But she needs to put an end to it herself
to make up for the past.
It angers me. It does.
That's right. I gave it to him.
I offered him ten billion won for a video
of his conversation with Gu Jingi.
Ten billion.
Why did you do that?
You knew I would secure
a video separately.
If I hadn't offered him money,
I highly doubt
he would have moved as we wanted.
I am a bit offended.
I thought you would be thankful.
Thanks to my work on Lee Dohyung,
you took down someone as big as Gu Jingi
in one go.
I would have taken him down without it.
Then Lee Dohyung wouldn't have died.
I am sure you knew
that Gu Jingi would hurt Lee Dohyung
if he caught something like that.
At Banseok University Medical Center's
morgue,
Assistant Director Lee Dohyung's body
was found.
You aren't surprised.
It happened that way.
I gave an order.
Mr. Cheon Hyungu simply followed my order.
Through the medical director
of the detention center,
I ordered Nam Hyukchul to kill Park Kitae.
I also ordered perjury
at your brother's trial five years ago.
And Assemblywoman Yoon's political funds--
What are you playing at?
Will you take the fall for everything
now that you are caught?
What's the matter?
I am admitting all allegations.
Those aren't all.
Geum Seokju.
You killed my brother.
I drove him
to his death.
Is that what you want to say?
I don't understand.
Why are you so hung up
on Lee Dohyung's death?
Could it be trauma?
For revenge, you drove the man
who used to be your friend,
Park Kitae, to his death.
Lee Dohyung was a bad man
who needed to be punished anyway.
He helped Gu Jingi
open Geum Seokju's chest
and take out his heart.
Don't tell me you believed his clumsy lie
about how Gu Jingi did everything.
Even if it was a lie,
the truth needs to be revealed in court.
No. Had we taken it to court,
he would have received
a slap on the wrist.
Did you want to end your revenge
in such a lackluster way
after five years of preparation?
Whom did you give it to?
Answer me.
Who received
Seokju's heart?
Prosecutor Geum.
Mr. Geum Seokju died
due to medical malpractice.
The talk about taking out the heart
and giving it to someone else
is Han Yihan's delusion.
Why? You admitted all other allegations.
Why are you keeping quiet
about my brother's heart?
I have nothing else to say.
I will plead the Fifth from now on.
Please call Ms. Pyo Eunsil, my lawyer.
Fine. Do what you want to do.
So that the world knows about
what you and Banseok did to my brother,
I will unveil the truth until the end and…
Prosecutor Geum.
-What?
-Hey.
-Prosecutor Geum. Are you okay?
-Ma'am.
I am okay.
Stay outside.
How pitiful.
You have the same hereditary disease
as your brother.
Your condition will worsen
if you overexert yourself.
Get hospitalized for treatments.
It's a doctor's advice.
I don't know.
It seems
like you want revenge more than me.
What's the reason?
It can't be about money.
Why are you obsessed
with Banseok and Gu Jingi?
If you are curious, you should find out.
I intend to do so.
About what happened
between you and Gu Jingi,
I'm dying to know.
I guess this is
where we stop working together.
I had a lot of fun thanks to you,
Doctor Lawyer.
You are a brilliant man
with good judgment,
but there is one thing you lack.
You are overly clean.
Even when you are seeking revenge
on someone stronger,
you hold fast to your beliefs and values.
It's a type of arrogance, you know.
That's not how revenge works.
With resolution to push your opponent down
to the deepest gutter,
you need to tear him apart.
My revenge is different from yours.
I don't aim to destroy people,
but make them pay for their crimes.
I became a lawyer to do that.
Watch how I slaughter Banseok and Gu Jingi
and enjoy.
It's my last gift for you.
I heard that you almost collapsed again.
That's not true.
I simply ran out of breath for a second.
I heard everything,
so don't think about covering it up.
Apply for a leave tomorrow
so that you can receive treatments.
I'll take responsibility
and see the investigation through.
No.
Not yet.
Hey, Geum Seokyeong.
I finally have Gu Jingi behind the bars.
I will investigate him myself
and identify the VIP
who received Seokju's heart.
No.
If you don't take a leave,
I will notify the chief prosecutor
so he will get you off the case.
Give me a week.
Just one week.
I will finish it in that time period.
Even if someone else attends the trials,
I want to finish the investigation
with my own hands.
Just one week.
As soon as it ends,
I will drag you to the hospital.
I promise.
And…
don't tell Han Yihan.
I will tell him myself
when everything gets wrapped up.
The leaders of Daehan Party
released an official statement
about discharging Candidate Yoon.
Okay. I will need to hasten the surgery.
Now, the period after the primaries
will be more important.
Yes, but do you still intend
to make Director Gu Hyunseong
the official operating surgeon?
Ms. Pyo?
It's me, Gu Jingi.
I apologize
for causing trouble.
What do you plan to do from now on?
Don't worry.
I won't make an unreasonable demand,
such as helping me walk free.
But if you are going to be
the president of Korea,
you should protect a Korean company
from a foreigner who hunts for companies.
I admitted all allegations today
to Prosecutor Geum Seokyeong.
So please protect Banseok
in my stead,
as the next president.
Okay.
I will think of a way.
Thank you.
Do you plan to help Banseok?
Father, you need to cut ties
with Banseok and Gu Jingi.
Han Yihan.
I wanted to spend
more time with him.
YOON MISEON
Jayden.
JAYDEN LEE
What are you hiding?
YOON MISEON, JADEN LEE, LIM TAEMOON
GU HYUNSEONG, GU JINGI, PYO EUNSIL
BANSEOK FOUNDATION'S GENERAL MEETING
OF STOCKHOLDERS
You can't enter.
What are you talking about?
Why can't I enter Banseok Foundation's
General Meeting of Stockholders?
I am sorry. Mr. Jayden Lee ordered us
to keep you from entering.
He did?
Listen. It was just an altercation.
Even so. This isn't right!
I'm overseeing the Strategy Team for Asia.
Do you think it makes any sense
that I can't attend
an important meeting like this?
-Move.
-I'm sorry.
We're just following orders.
Thank you all for coming.
The stock price of Banseok R and D Center
plummeted three days in a row.
If the price hits the floor one more time,
it won't be possible
to return the investment,
even with all of your stocks combined.
To make up for the insufficient fund,
I would like to take Banseokwon
and Banseok University Medical Center.
What nonsense?
Who said you could take the hospital?
Are you all just going to
listen to his ridiculous demands?
Ms. Jang Jungok,
you should sit this one out.
In a couple of days, you won't be
the largest stockholder of Banseok.
Honours Hand will be.
But according to the law in Korea,
a foreigner cannot own
a university medical center.
You don't have to worry about that.
Once Honours Hand takes over
Banseok University Medical Center,
we plan to get the permit renewed
as a for-profit hospital.
What nonsense is he talking about?
-Seriously?
-Director Lim.
-That's not right.
-Of course not.
Take a look here.
We will combine Banseokwon
and Banseok University Medical Center
into a for-profit hospital.
As Emergency Medicine suffers
from the largest deficit,
we'll minimize its operation.
As for OB-GYN, just like Banseokwon,
we'll provide tailored services
to a small number of expecting mothers.
Restructuring will be done there.
As for Cardiothoracic Surgery,
it will no longer be operated.
-He'll get rid of it?
-That's nonsense.
Cardiothoracic Surgery
is the symbol of Banseok.
How could you get rid of it?
It may have been a good symbol
in the past.
But now, it suffers from
the worst social stigma due to scandals.
That's not an essential department.
I wonder if operating the department
is worth all the risks.
You, the Head of Cardiothoracic Surgery,
could lose your medical license
at any minute.
I don't think there's any other option.
Once Banseok University Medical Center
becomes a for-profit hospital,
the board members here
will receive a part of the profits
as dividends.
You can decide.
Will you hold onto the stocks
that don't hold any value in the market?
Or will you receive
billions of won every year
as your dividends?
Is he serious?
Gu Jingi admitted to all the charges.
But he won't even talk
about the heart transplant
from five years ago.
I'm sure there's a reason for it.
A reason why
he must keep it a secret to the end.
How did it go with Jayden?
I asked him why he gave
Lee Dohyung the fountain pen.
But he kept mentioning revenge.
Revenge?
He told me I was doing it the wrong way.
He told me to watch
how he would destroy Banseok
and Gu Jingi.
That doesn't add up.
Why would Jayden want revenge on Gu Jingi?
It makes sense if it were vice versa.
I don't get that either.
That's why I need to meet up with Michael.
Michael?
He knows about Jayden the best
at least in Korea.
JAYDEN LEE
HEAD OF HONOURS HAND'S ASIAN BRANCH
Michael.
But do you think he will cooperate?
He's Jayden's right-hand man.
I should at least try.
JAYDEN LEE
HEAD OF HONOURS HAND'S ASIAN BRANCH
He made me do all sorts of menial tasks.
You're abandoning me like this?
I'll kill you.
I'll kill you!
One more bottle.
Are you sure? You already drank a lot.
MR. HAN
Han Yihan?
Why is he calling me at this hour?
Do you think I work for you?
The person you reached is not available.
You'll be directed to voicemail.
After the beep--
He's not answering?
No.
He must've found out
we're not working with Jayden anymore.
The phone has been turned off.
You'll be directed to voicemail.
It has been plummeting
for four days in a row.
I don't know
if I should be happy or sad about this.
Don't worry.
Once Honours Hand becomes
a new owner of Banseok,
the stock price will recover.
Anyway, congratulations.
With this, you have taken control
of Banseok for sure now.
We should congratulate your father.
He's registering as a candidate today.
Shouldn't you be there with him?
No.
Watching it from here will be enough.
The candidate is coming in.
LIM TAEMOON OF DAEHAN PARTY,
SPECIAL PRESS CONFERENCE
My fellow citizens.
Before I register myself
as the presidential candidate today,
I'm standing here
to share the direction
our country ought to take
in the future.
But how come your father
still can't give up on Banseok?
Gu Jingi is done for,
and he no longer needs
Gu Hyunseong to operate on him.
Is there another reason…
I'm not aware of?
Another reason?
The low birth rate and aging society…
Yes, there is.
…will certainly become
more serious problems.
I…
Even if Gu Jingi is completely ruined,
he can't betray Gu Jingi for this reason.
LIM TAEMOON OF DAEHAN PARTY,
SPECIAL PRESS CONFERENCE
Candidate Lim, are you all right?
Candidate?
I'm the ambassador to the US, Lim Taemoon.
Who are you?
What are you doing?
Stop taking photos of me!
Please calm down.
We're in the middle of a press conference.
A press conference?
Why am I holding a press conference?
Stop taking photos of me.
-Stop taking photos.
-Move out of the way!
I think it's time
to tell you the truth now.
What if my father
should never be the president?
What will you do?
-Stop taking photos of him.
-Move out of the way!
-Stop taking photos! Don't!
-Move! Move over!
Move!
Don't tell me
he has Alzheimer's.
That's right.
He's been taking the new drug
the R and D Center developed
for a very long time.
So his illness recurred
even after he had a heart transplant.
My father is actually the victim
of the new drug.
But the new drug
is significantly effective
in treating Alzheimer's.
He's been taking it for a long time.
Why is he suddenly showing symptoms?
Because I swapped it.
He's been taking health supplements,
not the new drug for over a month.
I thought
the symptoms would show up sooner,
but it took longer than I thought.
-Why would you do something like that?
-Like you said, only then
will I be able to stay as Lim Yuna,
not the daughter of a president
or Gu Hyunseong's wife.
I told you my secret.
So there's something
I need to check with you.
I need to see
if you are my true partner I can spend
the rest of my life with.
Ambassador Lim
decided not to run for president.
He suddenly showed symptoms of
Alzheimer's during the press conference.
And Prosecutor Geum Seokyeong
requested your arrest warrant,
and the warrant was issued.
You'll be transferred
to a detention center tomorrow.
I must meet with Jayden.
-Jayden?
-Yes.
Once I get transferred, call Jayden.
And tell him to come see me.
Yes, sir.
The very first moment I met you,
I was reminded of someone.
Salome.
She danced before the King of Judea,
Herod, on his birthday.
And as a reward,
she asked the king to behead
the great prophet, John.
Salome.
Are you saying I'm evil?
It means you're loyal to your desires
more than anyone.
If chasing desires is evil,
I will gladly become a villain.
Are you stalking me?
Do you know how many times
you called me yesterday?
I'm sorry.
There was something
I had to ask you in person.
Ask me? Why?
You should talk to the almighty Jayden.
I thought you guys were best friends.
Jayden didn't talk to you?
Are you mocking me?
Don't you know he fired me?
I didn't know.
And there's something
you didn't know as well.
That Jayden and I
aren't working together anymore.
What? You're not?
Take a seat.
I get the feeling
we might see eye to eye on things.
This footage was recorded by the camera
in the elevator to the penthouse.
And the security guards saw
Director Lim Yuna enter through
the penthouse entrance this morning.
Bring me the master key.
Pardon? But--
Are you deaf?
Bring the master key now!
Yes, sir.
The fountain pen
Lee Dohyung was stabbed with.
No. Jayden gave him the fountain pen?
You really had no idea?
No.
I didn't even know it had a camera.
He must have kept everything
under wraps even from you.
You were his right-hand man.
Right-hand man, my foot.
He fired me over one mistake.
We want to know
why Jayden cornered Lee Dohyung to death
and why he is so hostile against Gu Jingi.
Do you know anything?
Actually,
Susie Yoon and I found that odd too.
Jayden seemed
to get unnecessarily worked up
when it had to do with Banseok Foundation.
Susie Yoon? Who's that?
She's an executive
at Honours Hand headquarters.
She was up for the position of the head
of the Asian branch against Jayden.
It can be anything.
Anything that can tell me
about the relationship
between Jayden and Gu Jingi.
I'm not sure if this will count
as a reason to hate Gu Jingi.
Five years ago, he came to Korea
to invest in Banseok Foundation.
And Jayden was in a car accident.
A car accident?
It happened late at night,
so I wasn't at the scene.
He was transferred to Banseokwon
and had emergency surgery.
Afterward, he was in a coma
for two to three weeks.
Who is that person?
You don't need to know.
He came in three hours ago
from a car accident.
He won't last long.
He needs a transplant right now.
There really was a car accident.
What is it? Did you remember something?
If you're curious, you should find out.
Yes. I finally get it.
Salome. I quite like it.
She sounds like a woman
who will get anything she wants.
-This is…
-Yes.
This is the freedom you gave me.
If I didn't take this that day,
I would still be the daughter
of the presidential candidate,
not Lim Yuna.
So I got this for us
because today is the day
when we both got freedom.
What? You can't take it
because it's not yours?
I kept wondering
if I passed out from the pill
because you made an honest mistake
or because it was a part of your plan.
You can't come in here.
I'm Prosecutor Geum Seokyeong
of the Medical Crime Department.
Who is it?
Hyunseong. Why…
"Why?"
I should be asking you. Why are you here?
Why?
I should have done this that night.
I was stupid to hesitate.
Look who's here.
Did you get your daddy's permission?
Right.
You couldn't have gotten his permission.
You scumbag.
You…
-Open up.
-But I was told to guard--
Die!
Die, you punk!
Honey, it's dangerous.
You should go upstairs.
Okay. Be careful.
Yuna.
I didn't know a papa's boy
like you could be this bold.
What a surprise.
You lunatic.
I'll kill you!
Open the door now!
Gu Hyunseong!
-Han Yihan.
-Come to your senses, and put that down.
Unless you want to join your father.
You should have let him do it.
It was your only chance
to get revenge on me.
No.
That won't be enough.
You were the VIP patient at Banseokwon.
You have Seokju's heart,
don't you?
You have a wild imagination.
But do you have evidence to back that up?
It's a chance for us
to turn the table around in one go.
Chairman Gu, Mr. Cheon brought this.
I guess he still has
some tricks left up his sleeve.
What about Cheon Hyungu? Any progress?
This rat is determined not to get caught.
We must find him before Gu Jingi's trial.
I'm sure he has evidence with him.
I'm here to save you
from Jayden and Honours Hand.
Don't make me use
the last card I have left.
You are despicable to the end.
Do you really think I don't know
what you did to me that night?
Translated by Eunsook Youn
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/agzuv
Help other users to choose the best subtitles