ENJOY ALL VOD IN HIGH QUALITY @ 4KVOD.TV
GET LIVE TV,MOVIES,SHOWS IN ONE PACKAGE
are you idiot
you are hiding in pakistan
come in writing
what
in your office
Ready to tell, I told him that some electrical work comes in handy after fixing it.
so it will come later
Ok
Newspaper market will have to be cleaned son
No problem
thank you swear
thank you so much sorry
Because the radiator is late in my office, you can check it
kiss me
i have to finish the job
It is not necessary to lower
I have my own work
i will do it in a week
Perhaps
now go to sleep
Wonderful
i need you some training
you are going
about ram
You do not understand anything, especially have you understood the things related to the network, have you not?
just a little training army training or sir bhagalpur
All the work to find a way to do those things again
protocol school
Classified principal has not even told, he told
If told, I do not want you to take him with you by mixing him with a little trouble.
that i can understand ok so let me show you something
We meet in such a quiet place, graveyard is a good place, across the city
This Communication Laser Printer
IT department company
Communication device is always ok to center using sim card
start over
It is easiest and most reliable to get the hiding place as soon as the game is over and where is it
Shows this is our classifieds document room
To open it, I will take the government, you can take the mariadhas, I have taken it
Don't be left lying around for the whole day, we don't need to remember to keep the document safe.
You put the film in the box, and you will put the box under the lantern, the glory of hiding it until you are told in another place.
Yogi under London and somewhere else ya
If Jharkhand is burning, then understand that there is a problem, then get out of here, if it is not burning, then come and keep your patio and burn it.
ok if you want to meet then make a cross out of hobby
How to register goat
way of talking and this is to seal them up and make classifieds
Hey understand this and get them covered if you need anything
And don't understand if you need anything else
which will be found near your house at 98 if you look a little right means we can't find you to get out
keeping a dog but my wife is allergic to it
then how do you get out
never question me so i need to ask her
If you are stuck in some trouble, hope that you are not able to explain
so straight to me
we will tell together
help others now
remember you work for me
it could be ketaki trouble
keep your eyes and ears open at all times
if anything goes wrong you have to rectify it
don't say what you're working for
Ok
Don't let it fall on the ground before
must have been dirty
Yes it is OK
Where was Holi that a safety is lying in her basement, Holi can be
good things headache reduced
well said
Is it a carnivore?
Yes
don't be worried
hey man i was so busy with work that you got out of my mind i call them now
It's night now, I'll call you tomorrow morning
Tomorrow bring Dipasso powder too
Ok
powder diapers will take all
Sleep
Means we have nothing, we have nothing and never was
what happened late mean
They say that Sonia has no friends or relatives to take in heaven, there is no personal work or connection.
Ok
We have to check everything that's always happening
looking for something
ok i'll go i have to do diapers
Haryana
what are you doing ashram
Work
ok then we are the people
tomorrow still
i will be at work
how will tomorrow be
Ok
what are you doing call
otherwise your home
lets go
if i do something i have to save
We talked about that you are the only one to come.
you do something do something
We had decided whether you should come or not let us go to Kaal Bhairav ​​Chalisa.
Look it's all over, understand it's all over
by understanding
in bengali dance
June 1
of the water
you have a lot
It will be good if you come to school and talk about your profession.
Would love to hear about Sunil Sonakshi's friend
when to come
if you're free
next tuesday
Blue is very excited
will enjoy
say yes alfred
hello young
yes i am telling you that
can you come to my house
number plate
yes man was following me so i want to find out who it was
And you can find out without any bureaucracy under control, right?
comrade
You don't become mentally ill by going to the Ministry of Defense
ok send me that number please
Dialect
you month
Manish
your favor mantra
Those who have to demand the documentary Krutika level answer with English hands, it is necessary that they are facing problems due to this.
Yes brother, pressure on Nana Intelligence and we will not be able to do anything
He's there to keep you apart from all this I'm just like the one above you got your new
I feel like saree classic from all subdivision
Only we should get peepad information, it is necessary because
As a district, how will I know that in the Department of Defense Intelligence?
If all the rules are being followed or not, if the secret of the country with all the employees
If it is shared, it will be very difficult for us to save it, I think
so what about you
Our department should have the authority to decide which coins with the skin and price of the Ministry of Defense
And it is also necessary to get the result of the instruction only and only us.
And yes, we also got the personal security files of all the intelligence of the Defense Force.
He should also see the details of his operations in all the functions and all his other activities.
People who have violated a lot of rules recently because it is illegal
Everything I can do under my control
what we have to do
Photo Background check of all employees of all Military Units of Military of Difference
Pilate who will catch them
Ask Lithuanian for help
We have to send all our personal and operator files to the Ministry of Defense
on 65 minutes
The hotel of the classified external information belongs to the ICC World Cup India Order Minister
we will keep an eye on them
Good luck
Things have completely changed because of very nice Naths
we have to be more careful than ever
And keep everything going well, take care of the farm
i have to keep
the city will be done by telling me ok
ok to tell you
Just by telling me and I will not go to you too and only they will need a phone call in China about this
what happened now
let's go
Everything is fine
did you talk to my wife
how are you in the block now
Ok
We are preparing for the operation and you will be able to talk to him in a few days
I am going to Mussoorie
yes don't worry about it
akira
My wife
did he tell you anything about this
To be honest, he doesn't know anything about it
from you
can you tell when you meet
Something sensible was happening, everything will understand itself
Wouldn't be the same for couples
his friends his parents
my parents
And what is being written about me in the newspaper is not writing anything is not writing anything
We will cross the border very easily and the pet specialist will take care of everything.
daily
Say you will not welcome him like a hero and then the worm will also be happy
don't you understand
good it
Where is the file of wind Girlfriend who asked for our file
the one who first
220 Roskil is handling Russia's security check internal security
It was written at the behest of man
Means say they can follow us and we can't do anything about them
good for us
don't know good or not
Hi!
you talked
oh man you talk about baby
yes i do i talk in school right now
oh
you are not angry
i'm talking now
Nayapura Fort About Laden Police
I don't want to go out no thank you
I know about bin papers
ok as you
you will go brother today there is some work
Maharaja Maharaja Maharaja
Hi!
All set classified channel information department
Banka has a camera in the documents room
i want to see his recording
of our department
It's my responsibility to do security checks
which camera
I got some action camera on the table in the documents room
Nothing must have been recorded in the camera to see that recording to take decisions.
no connectivity
what do you mean your camera is not connected
According to Russia, it was imposed but
Not yet decided whether to connect or not
Whether to connect or not what it means can be a security risk
If someone hacked him then he's talking about it
well understood
because do yours in everything
Yes
us fashion pathani
And yes I don't think you should sit and eat in this room friend
Khanpura is hungry, eat mother's food
love use me
But whenever we want you we have to enter in the log book
i know son
I didn't completely inside means I haven't taken any document
I just went to check
Did you go to check?
I went to check the condition of the room
Apart from this, there was no other work, so people entered the group.
Well why aren't you fearless
otherwise i said i will
Follow us milk completely
neither
remember patidar
I felt like time
I left the police department of my own free will
I felt that I should contribute to the state security, present the work of man to you.
The video was taken as Pintu Lokesh Milan, at that time you accumulated a lot.
What is the reason why I got a job to get Kajal caught no one about it
They needed them at the time of the sun.
Some other young girls were also taken with me, they said that it is ok in this way and some other way
We got the reward too, since that time it was light like this.
ok u will be told about that for state secret ok
what heater
stat me
was called to get the ticket and
very stupid
what a fool
I forgot to tell about my grandfather and that was necessary
Don't think it's so important to tell
Defense Force Intelligent Just Extended My Clearance For 3 Months And That's All
It's not good if they don't move on to Clarence what will I do
what's up in the morning
what didn't tell me about grandpa
Grandpa used to work in NCVT when I was 2 years old he died
Do not worry
i will handle
you should handle this by calling ring in defense force intelligence sir
She is very small but she is getting very upset about it, gets upset by small things you know that she is very nice and
And being capable was not hiding this thing, just forgot to tell
i'll handle i'll call them
we'll do our work here
I want to know when are you walking with me caught on the bus
Troubleshooting going on in the woods
and i don't wanna go alone
yes i am speaking
wanted to be his
garima good evening
So we thought that your new job is more than that
We are joining NATO
responsibility and work
both rain
Frustration to the roof police
will be happening
photo old things
Now you are handling international affair
is a big deal
new chance
everything is new
hello good evening
i called about that number plate
That village is in the name of Tutna
Call to my contractor and his wife's name is his 5 year old baby in British milk
do you know about them no you must have made a mistake
your so
ok i leave
someone at the door
Who is there?
your husband following me in his car me you and your his
means to be away forever
explained that when i talk to him never think of my photo i work
no kidding me and i have to fight him over here
Tell us to explain that nothing has happened between us and will not happen, then you will not hear much about it.
how give me
Give me somewhere and we end this fight right here
Navya Sapna Sattar Live CP Thakur
I don't even want her sister
by dna test
all will be clear
yes ok but it will take time
Mine too
It's a long time ago first and I'm fine now
know who you are talking to
I've had four divorces
you will be in favor
tell me she's beautiful
you leave all that
i want to rain man
work is too much
and this is distracting me
don't worry friend i am
Hi!
The embassy is now being closely monitored
We'll have to wait a while before we go there
over there inside
NATO people can have brains
but let them run
Even then
You don't even have lights, which at this time
There is too much risk in crossing the border
we can eat
And for a big operation we don't have that much vantage
He said that's what I'm saying
blue picture of sunny leone
say your agent
Jain
there is a security risk
In no case should not be caught, interrogation will not be able to play even 1 minute
Go
Asonance will tell him that his wife
Was rested on the same day in Riga
and her child
sent to her grandparents
How are you
So what
it will be finished have to wait a bit longer
nothing will happen when she turns 20 then we will get a place in preschool
Laxmi
can you take the help of office in this no train
Why I talked to the manager of the preschool
she said maybe she can make the class to see
Yes
i come too
Look, don't be angry, my bread will not last for a few days
soon everything will be normal please understand
Go
Thank you
Varun Dhawan
why have you come
Baba's Temple
What are you saying
Know brother is Suresh or Scooty 2 days ago
And it's been like this ever since
he's gonna laugh at us
you rinku
Do not tell anything about this, if a lot comes to know about it, then he will always tell about it, whether it is a selective or
his leg will keep going
Ear
talking softly
Have an affair with your wife, this has to be talked about, tell me what to talk about
Bhojpuri has to be abolished, there is too much in this, I know the matter.
how can you make such a big mistake
Why do you need to have me today you have to finish it all
I'm not here to fix your love life
Youtube channel has to handle this then comment
I have confirmation from friends on this matter only yesterday, have you not allowed me to drink, have you increased your bank?
When a 5 month old baby falls, it grows rapidly that we want to appreciate our people.
don't worry sumit
I got stuck in a problem
Good good
i.e
lets go
we Late
leave him
put down
everything will be fine let's get dressed
But
My wife
did you talk to him
you will see him soon
it's totally cool
wanted to say thank you before doing the waterfall thank you very much for your help very scared
everything will be fine you were just doing your work thank you friend it was ok
Mahabharata Our people are waiting for you there they are visible
You will not be seen from here, you will have to go a little further, those people will take you from there
Applications
i open
Let me tell you one thing, I told you the president
You don't need to think so much, I will hit you by train, right?
I am thinking more sitting at the computer then tell me when will you tell my hand in household chores
So I'm doing it or I can't do it if you understand
What do you do
calm down train calm down i'm trying a few days everything
train please
train train
Train
My nose got long watching the dance
I am Neelu Mamta Soni
hello yes
Yes
what
no i am listening
what did you say i don't understand
Do you know that time is broken?
arches
Hindu Kush
Mehndi
Dhand Hospital
what happened nothing
Wanted internal security job, if their investigation was completed, then all the benefits would have been sent.
we have come back and put in
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/ah2fy
Help other users to choose the best subtitles